Alexandra first in color with huge fan I love your work
We're couple dudes go to sit around drink novelty Beverages and have a little chitchat about Alex Jones
However a twister that correct it's like it's like our Blues Traveler
If you want
This would be the thing in the middle
Apps
We are celebrating a little bit I'm about to go to Iceland
See the glaciers
Is right before they disappear forever
Jordan's to fill in here and there but I don't know we'll see what happens but for now we're celebrating
Safe travels to you sir wonderful is my best to the people of Helsinki white Bronco
Reykjavik
Because we're celebrating and I was going to get to the factory
I've had a couple of steps and I'm drunk
And that as you have
Is built around
What color is that box
Pabst Blue Ribbon
There's a red stripe
There's it's got a white background
Blue Ribbon blue goddamn American American
Chicago
Thank you for joining up with the show
You should recommend
Exposition in these here parts
Before you go on vacation I wanted to
You know sit-down with you record this episode cuz I needed you I couldn't allow the idea without being up to
Speed
On what's been going on in 2017 with Alex Jones Show
Nothing will happen
In the next week
That will be very
Our political system
So we're going to be going over
Mostly August 4th
Okay Friday August 4th
But in order to
I'm going to be just
Discussing
The narratives that Alex Jones is
Open pitching on
You're stuck in Dempster
Note 4
You're recording this on Friday holyshit
It's Friday August 4th
You and your girlfriend both have the same database delusion
Alex Jones on the last episode
On the 1st
He was
Coming in
With some new Seth rich
You coming in with
Another Wrinkle in the Seth Rich case
On the 2nd
He goes even harder
He goes even further
And that is because
Some audio was released
Seymour Hersh
Award-winning journalist Seymour Hersh
Giving about how
The Russian
Stuff is all nonsense
Panino's
5 who has like pink
And that he has been told by high-level sources
That Seth Rich was the
He's the guy
He was the guy who gave stuff to WikiLeaks
But he also says
I don't know if that murder was related to it
Could have just been a murder what a crazy
In the Seymour Hurst tape you talkin about how
You're coming to possession of
These emails and what have you
He was trying to get money
From WikiLeaks
In exchange
WikiLeaks
And get indicated two people that he had given
A lock
Dropbox
Write to some friends
Even killing him
The stop the dissemination of this information
That stuff would be very trackable under apart
In Central Park
Safest place
Absolutely like in the movies
His narrative
First of all Seymour Hersh
The last statement that he gave was that
He talked to
The gentleman
Who
God is good
Twisted web
So there was a republican fundraiser that donors
The big donor
Who had hired Rod Weaver the private detective
I am
Got the family too
To sign off on its efforts family.
And Wheeler is suing Fox News
For taking his words out of context and attributing quotes
Court
Big Joe
Is also the one
Apparently recorded Seymour
I'm sure he doesn't have a vested interest
Austin either direction
Coronavirus
About
Getting the truth out
Yes and then beyond that Seymour Hersh
Has said
The only comment that he's made
About the entire situation
Is that all he's heard as rumors
The donor guy whose name
Always slips my mind
I feel
But I actually
Just
I think the quote was either too into and put them together
I made his own
Okay
Seymour
Confirm that that was his voice and those were his recording he has not made a comment about the actual
Okay for him to make that comment
Deep caught what I mean if you do a voice comparison apparently it's pretty similar I don't know if I can scientifically say that
Yeah it's believable
Him
But it is a real problem that he's
Piano
Making
The statements with Oliver's burgers
And then on this tape you saying
Something
Yeah absolutely
I mean the idea that Seymour Hersh somebody's
Who does have a
A real track record in journalism
Am I supposed to
You know all the people that we deal
The idea of him
Given credence
To this
Is it you know the Seth rich
Conspiracy
Huge deal
So if he isn't
Commenting on whether or not
It's his voice
And the audio comparison says it
It's him
I think he's probably the guy did it
Yeah yeah
Well
I mean kill Seth Rich that's what he
Yeah
What are you talkin about
Killed Seth rich
That's
A couple of Pulitzer prizes historically respected journalist
He's also a guy
Believe
Nonsense stories
From Anonymous sources
Repeatedly throughout his career
Okay there is a lot of criticism
You can find a people were like
This is absurd this is absolutely absurd
He is believing
Just telling him shed
Laika
He's even said
Journalistic
He keeps himself to feed his writing and I don't like that
So if he gives a speech
He doesn't have to hold himself to the standards that he has to hold to write it
So he said quote
Sometimes I change events dates and places
I can't fudge what I write but I can
Certainly fudge what I say
Traveling
Yeah when I publish things but I will lie all the time if I'm talking
Another was also a really high-profile things
Forget
You know maybe I
Mistranslated them he said fudge
Lie
Is there is a pretty high-profile in
Incident of him
Claiming
The
Abu ghraib prison
Soldiers were raping little boys
To terrorize
Terrorized
Detainees
The soundtrack of the screams would play
Americans are raping little boys
Wow it turns out that when he was pressed on that
He
Pretty much
Back down to saying
Look
Contractor
Might have
Rape the young boy
If someone might have taken a picture
Is there a difference between these two stories I don't know what like
Are they've done all the
You can do I'm not talking about what's true and what's not I'm talking about
Is mate what claims are made and then what explanations are given when asked
About those claims
Does have a good track record with like the My Lai massacre
Other things
He does also have a problematic history of embellishing
Admitting he embellishes
And believing Anonymous sources that are probably lying to him or unreliable
That has happened a bun
So I don't I can't take
Seymour horses were totally at face value
From this anonymous
Source clip is published on Cassandra Fairbanks as website
So it also has like a Providence problem
Ascending upcoming
Yasso Alex Jones is screaming about this for most of the day
But I don't want to listen to that
Cuz it's not
So I have this clip instead for you
He's still a little mad about John Oliver he's in the middle of a plug
Here's what
With just water
Okay
With milk
Tell me it doesn't
Filling
Ashley
Whipping
Yogurt ice cream or something
I think I'm going to
Absolutely
From
Wendy's if you're getting a frosty you're going to get it from someplace like Wendy from Wendy's
Big Mac replaced with like
McDonald's from a place that's like Wendy's
Dairy Queen
I used to work there when I was 15
That's him skirting the line of safe as a weight loss product
It tastes so bad you never want to eat
Translating ho
You still it
Still just in his craw
The John Oliver insinuated that one of his products taste bad
Used his own reaction as
Furious about
I buy that would be shocked if you just moved on for
To him this is an affront
To his business
And this is a reason that people might not buy
Which is the only thing he cannot abide
So that's most of the substance
Of the second
Is taken up with the the Seth rich
Narrative
I want to be fully f****** clear about this
Infowars as an institution
Credibility
But they should have lost their credibility
Visa Visa
What they tried to pull that stunt where Jerome corsi might get murdered this week
That's right how quickly forget
Did they pretended the Jerome corsi was going to get murdered
Is Jerome corsi still alive
Just on the other day
Jerome corsi alive
This is Friday
If by Monday we don't know whether or not he's alive I think we know what happened another weekend
Bulshit
I got got a lot of gotta keep eyes on that hearse for the ghost of Seth rich
I will buy absolutely August 3rd
Is Seth riches bones
Weight loss
So
Surprisingly much to my surprise
He actually dropped the second
Because on the 3rd it came out to that infowarrior got fired
So that was the story where
Oh yeah that's right brother got fired from the National Security
Good Department
A paper that had to do with how the globalists were trying
To team up
With the islamist
So that overrun the country
You get out cuz you are crazy
Of course
Alex
HR McMaster
Is a f****** globulus
To keep our people out
And of course good as we all should
Party everyday I don't want to get a peanut buster parfait
Place like it
The thing that I think of
Super fascinating
When is
If Alex
Himself believe
Was murdered by the DNC
His narrative
Lychee
He wouldn't
Talkin about
He makes a big deal out of days we can come back to it a week down the road two weeks down the road or whatever
Bored
Going down that road
The push too far you start to realize oh my God
Is other Russian alive propaganda store putting out this
Information
Is really fascinating I think you're going to love this
Is that
Alex's Menken
Complained
Is that
Circle Trump
They're trying to cut off all communication
With him
From people who aren't approved by HR McMaster
General Kelly and the third one I don't know
Bad dog
Matter
Is triangle of generals and hey
I'm with you
I don't want generals all over the place
That they're used
I don't want a military coup
Alex doesn't either
But we have very different views on it
Cuz he think
The globalist
Are using these generals
How to get Trump out in a military coup
Rational Minds
He don't like he appointed all those generals this on purpose
Or maybe they will just maybe he's or Fraser Trump is a moron
Tell him what they want him to do and he'll do it have an effective too
The cabinet is all people
It's f****** dr. Strangelove
To some extent
So Alex believes
That
The Trump is becoming
Incredibly isolated from outside information
Sources
To say that I think is
Fascinating cuz it
It belies that something
He's based his entire
Position on Trump
Complete lie
And he knows it
Social Security
There's nobody in the state
Globalist
Al Gore
And of course George Soros
We're getting rid of using Muslims to do it
He is taking everything out of context
These people are not saying
But that's what they're doing
It's not Beyond I want you to
Keep track of
Soros
Has been a globalist
Forever
And everything that has been doing is a been on record
It's not like
Last week he did something real globalist
Or something like that
Send the past that's important to remember his arrest
What goes on in Alex's lying about
Admitting the plan
And I don't want that thing giving out the government
But they've already admitted it
Pumpkin pops the president recently
Frozen Tupac tournament
I mean our long conversations
He's basically winking
A lot of this
Other isolated more and more
So beyond it being kind of alarming pinhole into the world is Sean Hannity
The only way he gets a window into the outside world
Is through Sean
Goddamn
Beyond doubt is that
He's talking about what this guy was writing in these reports about all this
Yeah I was just stuff
The president
That's Tuff
Which flies in the face of this clip
From January 19th this year
He was on the whole communist
By the Congressional
Information
Show me want to stand exactly why Trump has been
A patriot Sleeper Cell
People
Went along with the system like the left
Festive.
And it turns out
But he doesn't know who Peter Sutherland is or what his plan dating back to that always known about all of this
Since the 60s
What the f*** is wrong with you
What the f*** where is that what are you making
Of course
F****** course
Do you know them know about this cuz he needs this guy in the National Security committee to write papers for
Keep him abreast
He's a play Prince Ali but doing it's as easy but it's all this
We've got a patriot
That's what he doing
Cuz Trump
May have early onset dementia
I think that's what's going on
Exactly
Deep Cover guy doesn't
The digital drop
So
As it relates
To Trump being a secret
Anti globalist
Who's at the door
Lovelace
I forgot how to do it
You're busted Alex
We go on a little bit on August 3rd do you want to talk more specifically about
McMaster
Matt
So you he's going to eat he says this
Look you can be a fighter pilot
You can be Maverick
The Iceman
You shouldn't be running
Country is much more competent and
Sensible
But a lot of
But anyway Alex has a different complaint about them
And that you make
Bigger than you guys were Saudi deal or some five million dollar your defense contract
Go play golfing with your big fancy house
With a billion and a half Muslims and really sell us out to him what's going on
Is your problem
Manifestation of the Awakening
The bottle you must join with us
You must join with the Republic
You must join with prosperity you must join with Christianity you must join with common sense
And be honorable
Which ones
Confederate 100 traditional military
Honorable
Call Papa
The genetic family bloodline
Image big multi-dimensional complex system
Wants to destroy the West
It wants wants to enslave everything you do not.
Prevents
Do you think he knows what he saying
Basically
Liberty of keeping black people away from Eddie right
It's like that's what he's unbelievable
He's a f******
Absolutely no other explanation beyond the dog whistle
Harsh oh yeah
Coward families or something like that
You your family fought for the Confederacy dickweed
You f****** prick
Call
It means only one
Explicitly
I'm used to amuse
Obviously
But this is f****** this is a Step Beyond this is unbelievable whenever you get into like
This is profoundly eugenics
Even
Want to go back to the
The beginning of the clip
Were you saying like
You have to come
With us
You could join with us
You're the join with prosperity
Get the join with Christianity
So it's like
Rhetoric
A hundred percent
Yeah
CNN
And Alex Jones
We'll just piggyback
What's your start throwing it will have a listen to start
Crossing things out as what is ice
Ascend at this point
This isn't even as bad as ice
Smell of Alex
Believe
I want to play you the end of that clip again
And then what happened to mediately after
Tell you this
Going to get boring a little bit towards
Middle of this clip
But it's worth it just to hang with it
Fans
I've not edited this
At all this is exactly what happened
At the end of that clip we just listened to where he screamed about good families
And you have to come with God
Yep here's what happened to me Delia
Not join with cancer
There's a fax
Front
You have increase your funding and support of our operations and your prayers
Nothing can stop you you are are
Social media team
By Michael Chicago
So now.
In its entirety because I think it's fun every now and again
Take a nice
Look at his literal like how he does
Who's John Oliver did a good job of covering a lot of the sale stuff actually play like a full commercial
And I want to point out a couple things
This is the beginning of our
Celebrities with the June sales
Standard Auto Sales
Just ended
They might as well
Dora Halloween that I want to make everything is always
And you'll see it demonstrated in this clip
Free shipping specials
Followed products for Monticello
Show me
But we're launching in the month of August
Very popular
Percent off
That 1776
B12 synthetic garbage under the tongue highest-quality
Secret 12% off
Everything normally cost 35
First of all these are not that different than the sales they had
Before
Except he's made all the prices 1776
If you want to turn yourself into the
Patriotic Brandon Dollar Store
I like that I like the idea 50.
Level
76 Dollar Tree
Dollar Tree of Liberty
The tree of patriot blood
I think I
I think this really should
Highlight
Desperation
Because I don't know what kind of markup they actually
Play do
Can't be much more than like
200%
Or something
You think it's much higher than I do
Anytime you're talking about business
MSRP is usually 3.5
Okay
React
Like it's 22
Would still be a 200%
Prophet
It's
I have nothing
To anybody at retail
Crazy
Amore getting at is the idea that like
His
Consistently on these big
Everything is pretty much
Consistently 50
2% off
60% off
85%
Remember
Free shipping ended at the end of July
Yeah keep that in my
Introducing
It's 11% off at 7
The John Oliver challenge chocolate or strawberry caveman give the freeway protein
15% off
Infowarsstore.com
Are AAA 2533
AAA 2539
And
We have ended
Hell yeah
It says free shipping
We'll see how long that goes
I wonder if it'll continue beyond
Will keep you posted
For like a week straight
Oh maybe we
Baby we charge
Search for everything you're imagining there's a marketing
And f****** Alex Jones snorting
Super male Vitality crystals
Football and ideas Buckley's got the good stuff
Call U-Haul
Pulled out a little sack over a little baggie of Superman
Got to love it
It's supposed to be sublingual but I like to snort it like poppers
Now George
Yes we have to move on
To August
Fourth
Narrative
There's no real need to dive too deep into it
Reminder
Perspective I think General Kelly is largely
Just trying to do damage
Control
For now
Narrative is nonsense
It is just a real desperate attempt
The triumph
Cover up
And really reinforces
This idea that it wasn't Russia
All that game is
And they're doing it
And
But everybody knows that it was like the family the the private investigator all were like
This is unrelated
This is just a murder
Oh yeah I'm at the Russian
Call Alex h-2b the leaker because if not
It exposes that
The the Russian tank
His complaints about it not being the Russian
Fall Apart
And the
Leader in the clubhouse is far as explanation
Is what everyone else is saying
I bet it is
Beyond the fact that Julian Bond
Has been playing into
The idea that it was Seth rich
Who was he
Assange is gone
If this
To fall like I said
Episode
Julian Assange
Is ink
Incredibly
Vulnerable
He's very
Exposed
But I mean he's exposed in terms of like
The geopolitical game
Corollary, gyro is Chelsea
And he'd be nothing without her and
All the triangles
No I mean the graders
Spear of the import of Liquors
Snowden did and the ensuing conversation
Turn led to a lot of
Pro Julian Assange Center
Not necessarily that they had anything to do with each other
Not Snowden
Stonehenge
Episode
You may remember that I made some
Claims
Or some assertions
Speculation
Things about Alex Jones
Having a
Pro-russia stamp
That might be more important to him
The new Pro Trump
Yeah responded with a lot of skepticism
Your arguments are
Hard to argue
Guy who gets really nervous
Whenever I make a claim that might sound stupid
I'm sofa
For the better part of the day
I was feeling like s***
That didn't help know everything
Amaya f****** dumb dumb am I an idiot
Listening to Friday's show
I Came Upon something
That made me think
That maybe I was more right than I did
Then even you had
Yes
For the rest of the episode
First hour of the shows boring
I discussed it all I don't even think I took
Notes on it I was just
He's just yelling about stuff
I think it's more just McMaster is trying to isolate Trump
They're going to kill him I think there's some of that
You've got to get him
They're isolating him in order to prepare the public
Emily's also
Assassination bus probably not
Whatever second-guessing himself to positive
Bro
He wouldn't if he had
Actual sources
I'm sure Donald Trump jr.
It's going like
Pictures of very smart
McMaster is a genius not troubling approved
Well I mean unfortunate for us cuz if Donald Trump
Junior size Dad we would get
More Wackadoo bulshit from every angle
Block me
The second hour starts up
Tower of
August
Fourth start
This is what I hear
And
Perked up
Ears ears raise hackles up heart rate starts
Glutton
A little bit
And I start to realize
We've got a name
Alexander Dugan advisor is coming up
Not good
No not going to Subway
Wait we're doing Duggan's coming on info
Dugan
He does
Jewelry a myth
Chances are Russian collusion situation of Alex has the balls to have him on
Wow
I want to say that Alexander Dugan
Is
Tea as an advisor
We're getting into a lot of the details
Of why it's really problematic
Yeah that he is on
Infowars
.
Alex Jones
Is platforming
To speak his
Bulshit
Over American Airways
Encourages Alex Jones doesn't have the fear of sponsors or anything like that
He can do whatever he wants
Good on you it's free speech
But him
Choosing to is very
Very seriously a problem
The last time he was on.
Free shipping
The last time Dugan was on I swept it under the rug
Because there was that whole after Trump got elected
Dugan came out in
NSAID
Alex Jones is the greatest
Example of an American
He is a great human because of him we don't hate America anymore
All this b*******
Blowing smoke up his ass
But he said he wasn't
Alex
Alex had him on his show
Made sense
Is just sort of like
You suck my dick
Again is
Led me to think
Especially
Now
Wouldn't you want
From that is possible
If your argument
Is there's no possibility of Russia
Conclusion
Why would you have one of
Advisors come on your
Show
It's it's incredibly weird I don't know
I don't know
Stitches effect
Is there suggest that you are involved with the
Totally
Yeah
Big time
What did you get in
Email like hey
Somebody got it that the records
It is not true
And then we'll leave it
Look
It's baffling to me
Are over the course of the rest of us episode
I hope to layout
How much of
A problem this
And in order to do so I don't know if I should just get into Dugan up top or if we should let him
Talk and then get into it
What what do you think
What is the best gyros
We got to let him say his piece
Okay we got to let him say his piece
Here's the first clip
Globalist
State Russia
Geopolitical. Argue
Do you got the for my friend.
What their names are
Why they hate the United States and Russia so much
PlayStation will detect
Willow
That is not as realize
Is Russian accent
I want to broadcast in the United States
Is because on the 11th of March in 2015
The United States Department of the treasury as well as his organization
Just called the Eurasian Union
Do it the list of Russian citizens were section
As a result
Involvement in the Ukraine
Exactly what his involvement was
A little bit later
Yeah
No cancel
He's not paying him to be there
It's the Department of Treasury I don't think you can be safe I don't I don't
That's true no other like media organization with
Never going to
I'm not entirely sure but they certainly wouldn't allow him cloth
Just to say whatever you want
There would be like an interview
Cuz I know that he's done
Johnson interviews like the BBC
And stuff like that
Where are they
Push back again
Empties ideas
Has its own unique truth
Because
Because every truth is really relative and subjective
Capital T truth
And then they started to get into while like
Between Russia
But I was just in the United States
Seems that way
Seems well
You Are My People
F***** up stuff
Cuz that would work there we go
Great Cheese's
Part of his big philosophy is the destruction of the world
Exactly
The same thing as Jesus
There's a shocking amount of overlap
So let's not let him get into it after his kissing ass of Alex for ignoring
Here we go
Your station
Right
Michelin
Usher
So
Dugan dentist
Yeah you can absolutely smart guy
With satanic
He's going there dealing with The Wrong Enemy Russia
As a
F****** phone is also gilding on to add
Doesn't talk about any of the other much more problem
Because he is
Tricking Alex
He's incredibly smart
Alexander Dugan is a philosopher
Social science
And Alex being played like a
F****** Jeep
Violin
This is so easy
It's like
He's reading off
Script
Is pathetic
Is Alice Vale four-door is Alex just
Alex gets flattered
I'm hard-pressed
To say that Alex is falling for it as much as he is on board
A hundred percent
Absolutely insanely hateful
He's been cutting back the corruption
Wow powering programmes for the family has been promoting Christianity
He's been exposing through National shows
Technology being used enslaved people
The wicked
Human
But this isn't something he got from Putin
At what we face
I wanted to stop at there cuz he's a really horrible about women
I wanted to give us a chance
2:30 compress on that part of it before we get to the
Part that's just ugly
So what
Of Putin
Magical
It's magical nonsense
Analysis
The Putin
2 Russian TVs exactly like propaganda Outlets
Yeah
Glorious leader
Absolutely
A little bit of tyranny is a good thing
Especially with dictators
You know how they're always
Proceed with restraint
You know how they're always like
Let's not go too far
We're going to do we're going to get it we're going to get out we're going to save the world
Are you living in a dictatorship
Are they restrained in their action that's a dictator right there
At least
Is just lionizing
Like anything he's done a ton of research
Persian
That's not
That's absolute nonsense
He's getting on his show and
Being a Russian propaganda
Yeah that's true he's putting on the Hat
So we can hang out with Alexandra Dugan
They are fun
Comforters
Tezos earflaps
In August
Nice massage
They're also obsessed with him I mean
Weather in Westlake
I want
What the f***
Megyn Kelly
But make it clear
Alexander Dugan for all of his problems
And being an awful person
Out-and-out
Russian
Probably doesn't think that Megyn Kelly wants to f***
He is still asleep
Substantial individual
What is Megyn Kelly
Like that's disgraceful
I would like
Listen you're talking one to one of the true monsters in this world
Dial it back
He's at least give him the respect that a true monster desert he's created like philosophies that have created a lot
Water damage in the world
Don't don't do that
At least have it like it's clear that Alex is not read his book it clear he doesn't know what he's saying
Because if you did
Is very big into the destruction of the United
Not a good guy to have on your
Patriot base
Yes
One of the most
Explicit things he's argued for in the course of his career
Has been
The destruction of the United
The destruction of
Hegemony
Well yes and really is just
The freedom
Individuality deeply against the idea of individuality
Yeah because individuality
Takes you outside of the
The collective
I takes you outside of normality
And it makes you
I accept things like homosexuality
He's right up in that like culture wash it
That a lot of the conservatives are now
It's deeply troubling
2cv overlap
Nobody is more ideologically aligned
People in France
And hateful heart rate brackets in
Britain like all of these people
Don't realize that they're on the same side
Like the only thing that's protecting us
Is all of these idiots thinking that they're fighting against
Cuz if they actually United
Like like brexit like
Cambridge analytica
They really did push all of these
These people together on the Nash
And that is
A very bad
Like
It's like the f******
It's like the old Batman and Superman
But these people are insane
But also if you'll recall that last clip
Ended with a question
Why does Megyn Kelly get to
Hard yeah
Dugan a bit of credit
What's this
He does not
Engage with that partial pressure spiritual
Porter
Defender Defender exactly
Obstacle
Dream to be installed on the planetary level
Technocracy
American Russian collusion is
It's the same spirit
Alex
Does Alex
Realized
Is the last defense against
Christian tiger
Yep
I think he doesn't know that
I think
Cuz that's what he's
I've been saying for years
He's the lad but he's the only defense against the f******
Antichrist in 2015 he was saying
That was the only person who is standing
Against the New World Order
Against the globalist
On the world
Before he supported Donald Trump at all believe globalist
Transitional to bringing in a one world government lead
By the Antichrist
Of course he agree
Putin is what's going to save us
From
Hell on Earth
Ran the ascent of the evil one
I'm just that we were talking
More about
We were talking more metaphorically about you would have believed he would help
He goes directly into Christian orthodox
Greek Orthodox beliefs
That he is the defender
I did not expect Alex to be like
Throw out all the Christian should I be
Pretend to believe
F****** is the only one keeping the 7th
Steal from being open
Yeah
F****** unbelievably might be getting a glimpse into what Alex Jones is actual version of Christianity
Because words
Understand Christian
It may not be the key
It may be that there are some similarities.
Greek Orthodox people in my day
My dad's a religious studies professor at newsom's orthodox
When I was a kid
I don't think
I believe all this
Wacky nonsense
But be that as it may
You're seeing like this
Between the two of them
Alexander gifted manipulator
She knows what
Sort of things to say
To make Alex Jones be like I'm on board
But then at the same time
Documented this over and over again with Leo zagami
Lord monckton
And now Alexandra Dugan
Anybody with an accent Alex
This is like yours
Alexander Dugan
Incredibly smart
Therefore far more dangerous
The entire internet should be banned
I think that the internet as
As a phenomenon is worth prohibiting because it gives nobody anything good
Beyond
In June 2012
An orthodox Russian around the president of Russian Federation
In the last battle between good and evil
Following the example of Iran and North Korea
He added quote if we want to liberate ourselves from the
It is that we liberate ourselves from textbooks on physics and chemistry
Totaltrack
In Zaire
If we want to liberate ourselves from the West
Alex has a boner for the West
He's saying that we should follow in the example of Iran and North Korea
A12
REI
I will give it to Alex
Never ever
It's life red.
I don't
Not even one
It takes a Google search
Which is
Never read it
It takes more than once.
So now I want Google search to remember what it is he's looking for
Which is his next guest with
Click on
One of many results which is just too many
Yeah so I want to I want to say
That
Earlier that Alexander
By the department of
The treasury
Because of his eyes
Activities
In the Ukraine
Crisis
I want to touch on that for a second
Cuz I feel like weed
Should be specific
People know what he's been up to
1500 norgan ization called the Eurasian youth
Union
I love it I love it when people add in you do your raisin used
Hitler use like all these programs are really good programs
Organization that has a youth component
Children do not understand politics
They should not be indoctrinated
But be that as it may
On March 31st
March 31st 2014
Bahia
A member of the Eurasian youth Union of Russia founded by Alexander was arrested
Did the group of about 200 people to
Cease Parliament another government building
According to the Secret Service of Ukraine
He was basically training paramilitary groups
To go College
Trouble in Ukraine
It is on
Clear how many of the
Attack
And
Bombings
Result of that impossible to tell
There were going to seize the Ukrainian
So it is not low scale stuff
But you know
24 more than 200
Parliament I don't know
Situation there's there's ongoing Strife all around 200 people are well-armed
You could do
You can do some damage
EXO
You see
Benign
He's training
And I'm not around personally training time
Reggie created this organization
He's responsible for that troopers from Star Wars
Showed up
McLaren
Belief
The right side of history on that one
I got
So
Like that was just sort of a flip
Here is Alexander
That
Stop antique
Sharks score
Superficial interest
Because wow
Yes exactly
Spotify
So this is also the probably based on the uranium
Bulshit
Did Hillary
Beyond
You can't really find a whole lot of
Concrete
Examples of people being
Pacific about
Supporting Hillary
Alex
On the episode
He plays an interview with Julian Assange
Where Julian Assange
And for my end
All like
Can tell is that Hillary had contact with Russia
Ed Financial
The uranium one deal
Which was not with the Russian
That was with a canadian-based company
Russian
Those words are uranium right
She didn't make the decision it was the
Gibbous
Organization
Had no involvement
Always been over this
A whole bunch
Evangeline song
The only other piece of evidence
Is
Podesta
It's crazy
Russian uranium deal
Yeah that doesn't mean nothing and the Alexander
About how you heard
They were supporting Hillary
You got to kind of believe it's something like that
He's good he's throwing in that camp that idea of getting rid of physics and chemistry
Rid of the internet
He doesn't mean that what you means is getting rid of it
Yeah
Mickey and his cabal
Keep it
But that's what he's doing
Can lie straight
Hey dumb dumb you're on the internet now
You couldn't you couldn't get your propaganda to the United States without the internet
Effectively
Not in this day and age no one read smartphone
Umbrella
Shoots and they made it all the way.
What
American soil hold on
Did they launch them from the ground
Like they just tossed
With an umbrella cuz that's crazy
Okay
Join another fun fact about Alexander
In an interview with the Anna newsagents
The Alexander Dugan describing the alleged atrocities
They were perpetrated against the Ukrainian
Cold for them to be killed
In the 18th minute of the interview he said referring to the Ukrainian
The following
Kill kill kill
There should be no more talk
As a professor I think so
He's not a good for
No entiendo came fire force
Usually advocated
Especially would you like
Yeah yeah
Tarnish his credibility or his position in Russians
It would only
We have in place already we have
He started a Youth Organization
Turn based on Eurasian is
In a little bit
As an offshoot
Situation
Ukraine started
They were
For it and went around cause trouble
When interviewed
He advocated for the state
Going in and killing granny
Which is a war crime
The advocates for war crimes
F*** frog
Livin On borrowed time
What's going on
This is unfair
King real
Holyshit
Beside myself
Yeah this is great I don't like how this is
America at least Alex and Alexander
Finished
Another show
Where they're going to talk about how great
But I know that you are kind of a spiritual advisor to Trump
I just want to try to get an idea
Also lives in Russia about the real mindset of poop
Ethan Farmer or whatever
Oligarch South
Getting shot
He was a child
Birth rate backup
Abortion
The family
Who is killing all the journalists
Please call the Starbucks
A specifically a spiritual advisor and can you give us a view into
Vladimir Putin
I hope not but also I lied
They're not nearly done talked about our great food and
That's that's crazy
The eve
He's just doing
Freddie Gray
I love a bumper
What we should do is put together a
Long clip of all the X Alec
What's makes a mistake
Mock him the same way he tries to
To do Pelosi
He was an advisor to Trump I mean
Like either he's an idiot the same way he thinks she is
Which means
You can shut the f****** about that clip
Or that's the most Freudian slip there could ever be
Absolutely
Do you have absolutely.
He just wants
What happens after that
Maybe goes on
To talk about how
Putin is
Indicative of the soul of the Russian people
As much as
It is a representation of
People any pragmatic
I don't want to become a dictator
That's
Just Alex Jones allowing this dude to spit
F****** straight up
Putin propaganda on his show
He's turned his show over
Russia
For an hour
But there's no other way to put it
Bucked up
What
I don't know what to say
Of all the things
I could have imagined
Uncovering the
Alex is
Russian
Again.
Is not what I was expecting
Like if we if it like all the stuff you know it like I talk about
RNR opening
It's like I don't know anything about Alex G
At the all I knew about Alex was he was a lunatic
Then as we gone through this the whole time it's like
Detroit
Is bigger
Spencer's
So I didn't know that that's what we were dealing with
He's a Russian on the way learning videos this weird
The religious thing going on
Make slime
I meant getting to the Russians
And I'll tell you this I listen to Alex Jones a B in my
Younger years
To do another investigation of
When did
Alex become a Putin shell
I think we already are
You think so yeah I could I think we've already gotten because
When we started the
June in June of 2015
Over the summer of 2015
Yeah they came in
Trickling a little bit
And then where we are now in September
End of September beginning of October 22
15 he's going Whole Hog
If we were called
Justice
Call me
In the summer of
15 the Russians really ramp
Information
Influence
Campaign and stuff
Holyshit
Yeah yeah
Funnily coincides with
His campaign
It starts to become a picture where
It dumbass
Chicago we don't know anything
Look a lot like there's something going on here
I'm supposed to believe someone's investor
I don't know
But I have to believe that we aren't the only people who put
Two two and two together
It doesn't
You put that together with
With Trump
When did the Russian start support
Is maybe the best question
For when Alex
Supported him
Before even started running for president as much as made
Yeah money-laundering and what-have-you instances that have been
Pointed out of
Tears
For example
Russian people with weird connection
Buying some of his property for inflated prices
Never moving into the house and then selling it for Less
Seems to happen a bit
And it appears that they bailed him out of being
Beyond that
There are indications
Is going back at least
The 90s
Possibly even earlier
Of him having
Fro
Russian
Or at least
Pro-russian businesses
Yeah we have we have
He took out an apple
Right
The Central Park five should be hung
No that was a very different one
Another quote from Alexander
There are no more opponents of Putin
Of course
And if they are there mentally ill I need to be sent off for
For clinical examination
Putin is everywhere Putin is everything
Putin is absolute
And Putin is
Play I do not like
That language
I don't at all
That's really bad
Priority of History
Where is that was a
Interstate about anybody know
U-Save right before genocide
Yeah here's another quote
Here's another quote from
All Is Dead with modernity
So what should I do
We are going to end
Unabomber sketch
He hates the idea that the world is becoming modern
Yeah if you are the boring guy at a party
So Jordan I told you that
Where that clip was going to go Dugan
Was going to explain that Putin is
Pragmatic
Through I mean
If he's the only single person
Who knows what's
Going on and if you
Agree with him
Killed
Then
It's the only way you're allowed to
Absolutely
Start
Alex Jones
I'm coming too
Conclusion
Doesn't stop this feeling this emotion and Country
Nationalist with a y
Yes
Amanda
That's fun because
Then making it abundantly clear that they are comparing the two men as being very similar
And whenever they looked like his reveal
He is rational
What, you trying to say that I do that's fun there
But what he's trying to say is he's rational but at the same time is
His priority is the fact that he's Russian
For Trump the priority is Betty's America
I don't
Yeah
It works great works great
To kill us
Well now they're trying to kill a lot of people that is fairly URI
Not yet will probably be
You know collateral damage
Cuz I want to
So bad
That you may have your chance
I want to be perfect without a little bit
Down the line
As this episode goes on but
Dugan is Angela
For a war
Between the United
Russia
I don't know why
Alex Jones would have him on his show
Because
That is part of his worldview
I don't know how else to put it
Like
Alex Jones
The Supreme
America
Can Patriot he comes
From America
Connor
Royalty
Bloodline
Confederate in his version Americana royalty
He's having a guy on the shows
Expressed opinion is
Destruction of the United States
Destruction of the West
You're staying United
States
This is how we
Alex just wants Texas
If you don't want go to work and even play that game because Alexander Dugan is very specifically said
So is his branding or like
Semantics games with that
He said that the West
And liberalism which doesn't mean liberal
In this case
Okay
I'll just give you umbrella version
Of Alexander Dugan
A big book
His biggest book is called the fourth political ideology
I believe Harry Potter in
I apologize it's a very moderate political Theory
The argument that he lays out in that book is
Is that liberalism communism
That have been the warring ideologies
Of
The world
And liberalism is one
That's very rude.
Did way of putting it
But over the course of recent history you have those three they're coming up against each other
Liberalism destroyed fascism
In World War II
Liberalism communism with the breaking up of the liberalism
Has become bored I guess he's fighting with itself
And that's why you end up with these positions
Like political correctness
Well
Because
A Within
In his in his freedom within his term
Liberal
Generally it's eating away by fascist
ISM with it
That is
That is a fairly good
Assessment
Right so he proposes a fourth
Political Theory
Elements
Traditionalism
He takes element
Some some Elementary believe liberal
Look I haven't read the book
In its entirety I don't know how to break it all down
But from
All the reviews I could get
Most of it seems like there is just a lot of Proto fascism
In his world
And incessant
Do that
Ideology
Yeah I can't be
I wrote a book about a fascism is one of those right
He says that fascism is bad even though he says a little bit of
Is good
Fascism is bad
3 reviews of like his worldview that all looks
Express
Against fascism but is a fascist
Into that that idea
Who's going to stand against the
Can rust be killed
No too big of a dick
Too big of a dick
Guess what happens
Alex loves big dick
Showbox
That's actually why he loves to BBC interview because
Dugan
It's possible he's got a beard problem-solve
Because
The restaurant
He's called that because of his sort of Mystic elements that he has
His worldview and then the fact that he has a beard
So
The Antichrist
You're going to get some you're going to get some
Send his
Is larger philosophy
Which will get you in the moment but here let's get you another clip
The Spear of Destiny
Go look up
The movie
Our greatest living
Keanu Reeves
I like the movie
I thought leaders
No I haven't seen it
Since the 2005
But I liked it then I might have been highest
To the nation to the culture they're not soulless
Globalist who noticed have never have children
Are totally about destroying anything
Arnot
Satanic
Wow.
So now Trump America
A good thing the Alex Jones Show
No
You doing this now
Cuz cuz he doesn't think it's weird
He thinks that the globalist
The did all this shooting Ukraine not realizing the guy he has on his show
Legitimately was training a paramilitary organization
Attacked
He doesn't realize that it's very clear
Russia did
He thinks it is a globalist
So all of his
All of his premonitions all of his ideas are like
All this Russia stuff is b*******
Because he believed the stories that come to him from official
Russian state
That's a big leap.
Like
I'm sure that the
GOP
Who are all on that
There's there's no Russian collusion
They're different
If you are dealing with them
Even those guys
Possibly be okay with you saying
Trump is an American
Nothing that's okay Alex hates the Republican establishment as much as
He doesn't give a s*** they don't they can disapprove of him
Me too like I said if that's what you're saying no cuz he's radicalized
People are still bulshit the Russians story is nothing
Thing is very different from saying
Trump
Is the American
Journalist murdering
Country invading
Billionaire
Tucker
To use Alex
But here's one thing that you're missing
He's been prepping his audience
For this for at least a year and a half
That's true not like this is the big reveal or anything like this I think this is him showing his cards way too much
To someone like me who's listening critically
But I think that
He's been
By talking about how the globalist
Organic snacks
Your kids out of the backyard want to drink their blood
Call Vista
Defending
Talk too much about that for a while now
With the same
Gold
The same goal being that this is
What's Co-op Alexander Dugan language
You know the the he is the guy who standing between the Antichrist and you
Idea on and applied at the Trump
And now the audience is ready
Ford
Between
That man the Antichrist
It's incredibly f*****-up
That's
It's deeply and profoundly f***** up
I think it comes
Entirely down
To the fact that Alex Jones has been
F****** he's lost his mind
And you just believe
Outnet propaganda
He's been in a propaganda whole for so long
Yelling about the globalist
Believing nonsense stories
Again it's because he has brain damage
Mitch from these things that we've
Ring uncovered from his own story
The heat doesn't understand where truth and
Reality
Mixes into fantasy and lies
And he's been lied to
He believes that lie narrative
Because he has too many people around him
Who are aggressive
Look it comes down to I think also
The fact that we talked about
What's going on this show
Who the f*** is actually going to
Spend time talking
This dick hole
He's a racist f***
The oldest of it's been demonstrated over and over again how
Much of a
White
Identity bias
He has yeah
So who's going on
Credited alienated show
That maybe has a million listeners baby
That's entirely possible
But
Do you want a million bigots on your side
The people who are going on to that
Are people
Good question
I don't I'm so alone
They've got way more than a million I'm certainly happy with the about butts
You know less than that policy walks that we have
I'm thrilled with it
About Alex Jones
Discover the craziness
And let's be clear let's be clear let's be clear we
If not necessarily uncovered it believes we've seen very strong indication
Alex Jones
Not that he's a Russian agent again I'm not saying that he's on board with this stuff
And is beholding to because he
He does not understand the differences
You tripping reality
Propagate
Yeah
Spreading
And here's the thing
I get
I know if you know this or not but
During the run-up
There were a lot of APA American newspapers
Supporting Hitler
Yeah in a bunch of stuff about how Hitler will calm down once the elections over until
There a lot of people normalizing and being like to blow over
I want to say this but Media Matters I don't think they're necessarily dumb or evil or anything like
But they are an organization that relies on
Clicks in traffic
And we aren't
Because we are just
Doing this we don't expect to make a living office
Who be great
Expect to do that we're dumb asses you're a comedian I quit doing comedy
Did like once a comedian always
In my bones
But we're doing this because
The reason you couldn't cuz I drink your adrenaline in my blood
We're doing this because we
Stumbled into something and we believe in
Bullied you into it
And I'm just right here
Palatable I need someone to Bounce It Off
The back to Media Matters
Radar
They're really
Getting attached
Whenever this
This came out
This interview is on the 4th
On the 3rd
Milo yiannopoulos
Gay Bash
Glenn Beck
What you talked about last night
Article about and
People were complaining about
Milo and him talking about Glenn Beck
Text gay sweaters
And stuff like that
This is so much more important
No I don't know I don't go to Media Matters all the time so I don't know what all their articles are
But in the past I have gone and looked
Like what are they cover
And I know
That in the past they have covered
Not stories like this miserly
But more substantial stories
Robert Glenn Beck
About Alex Jones
Look at the shares on it not as high
Isolo
So it's just that most people don't
Engaged
Yeah
That's because
I would say
Before before this
For me
There was a lot more complications
It was a lot more new
Right Alex Jones
Situation
If you are really trying to
Parks that
There are a lot of different elements that could come in
You don't just like you and I have talked about
I've I've consistently been
Skeptical of your
Of your kind of
Gestalt
So did I
More for me than for you cuz I want people to realize
I'm not lying
When I say
I didn't come into this with an agenda
Other than laughing at Alex Jones dumbass
So you were saying
So I would say that it is
Much easier to be sky
Because there are so many
Coming into
If he's just saying you know
Putin the strongman
You can say well he's
Who likes
As you might imagine
This is kind of unequivocally
He supports Russian
Russian
Would like
So but
Let's be clear for about a year-and-a-half
Screaming about how Donald Trump is our only hope
Anna Baba
Art Van on this the Oggy
August 4th 2017 episode
Kilauea
An associate of poop
Who is
Propaganda
To come onto his show and say that Trump
Is the American food
And Putin is the Russian Trump
And Alex Jones
Agrees
Down on it
So that means that everything
Did he believes about Trump
And has been saying in the past
In some fashion he believes
About Putin
Trump is the
That's genuinely what Alex
So now I want to bring
I'm sorry cuz I want to I want to okay
What it is he's going for is or is he supposed is he just going on here to kind of spread Pro
You want to talk about it
Is Buck a little bit but then also the other thing was on
Because Alex Jones is selling his
His book on Infowars
SoBe
Call Silly primate
B12
The only outlet that would still sell
Well that was secondary he went to the the f****** Mercer's
Oh that's
And he plays this whole game in the interview where it's like
You know what I just had to rely on
Supportive
The people
Looking for Q
Right now we got Lake
We haven't
Easter sale on my bucket
It's 55% off it's 1776
You can get it at Infowars
Question about most of it is you want to talk about his book a little bit
He brings up his idea about the
The fourth political Theory
It's boring out
Cut the rest of it is all just
Just pro-putin
Which is
Cause of the nature of the enemy
I think he actually does
You think
I can tell from his writing
But
I also think that it's a
Convenient excuse
His eurasianism
Siri which we'll get to in a minute
But before we do
IO games
With the destruction of the Republic does interrupted by state
This is the first time he's ever happened I have prepared a segment
So at the end of that clip Alex Jones
I know it's like 15 minutes
Alex Jones globalist
And you know this
Because they don't have any children
Now
I pulled up a list
Of some of his big globalist
Okay and I'd like you to try and guess how many children they have
Bill Gates
How many children does Bill and Melinda Gates have children
Jordan with 1.0
Two children children
That's correct
Toppers
Champion globalist zbigniew Brzezinski
Mika
Son who was a child
Family business
Does the baron of Rothschild whatever the 4th Baron
His four children
David Rockefeller who just recently died
Hitstick
Six children
That's not 0 Alex billionaires
George Soros
PS5
5 kids
Five kids Soros
You got to stop
Has five kids David Rockefeller
Those are big numbers
Book Little House On
You have a f******
Global operation in banking
Concern yourself with
What are you doing
Soros does have
Do you remember that one
It's another example out of nowhere
Alex wants to play this game
That wasn't actually bills kid
I will say I don't care about your b******* narrative it's still Hillary's kids
I don't give a s***
Let's go f*** yourself
Is the father of Meg
Kelly's kid
Got her all wet
Does Kelly have a child I didn't look into that
Old-school globalist
I mean you could make an argument that Brock Obama and the Clinton
Things are just tools of the globalist
But the rest of them likes the Alex Jones talks about how he is
The agenda
George Soros runs the whole f****** thing
David Rockefeller was the heart and soul of globalism the Rothschilds family is what's all behind
It's
F****** nuts
So stupid
This should just be a small indication that everything he said is
It says made up yours comes up with stuffy nose no one's going to look into it wasn't even something that he
Like that was
Just a thrill
Yeah but it was a throw off reinforcing his idea that does low globulin
Satanist to don't give a s*** about anything
Like throwing out a bunch of s*** and then he's like
We probably don't have kids
I don't know hours on are complaining about George
Cirrhosis
Clinton over and over and over again
I never
A bunch
Segments complaining about how Barack Obama's kids behave
He was in that s*** man what they were talking about
Maliah dancing it's a Lollapalooza
He was onboard
They're terrible
Look the problem is that we're not normal
Regardless
You were weird
Alexander and Alex
Normal
Represent
Specialized or special world
So I hey
Putin and Trump are normal
Yeah there's a normal people
Aldi's
All all these people are just to evolution
Normality
Freak
Him having love the the most average amount of children
That's about
All of our world leaders are not Norm
Do you want to be a world leader some overlap between
At least I got powerful personality powerful ideology
You have backing
Your principles that's not
Not normal
This guy
Alexander
Sing
Who sang with the two of them are normal
It's a good time as I need to
To talk about what is normal to him
So I looked into this a little bit options and I have to
Pick out which one is normal to have
No I'm just going to read some paragraphs
From this
Pink.com
There's a bunch of sources I've looked into them they
So I trust this
Some Russian sources
On this too
Because Google translate stuff
I've gone in
My everything that you saying
Mattress
But he writes it up very well so I'm just going
How to read hazard
I can try
I need to give a little bit
He talks about a lot Alexander Dugan that is
Couple
Decade
We've had a unipolar world where the United States is the
Only massive
Power in the world
Right
What would like
She is a multipolar
Which
Make some sense
Bon-Ton on some level
I don't disagree
Bree I suppose I don't think the United States needs to be
The only supreme power in the world I think that's
Egotistical
Little tunnel vision
I think I would probably argue that there should be a
Called as opposed to a
Unipolar tri-polar whatever it is I like the sound of that
I like
Yeah
Civilization
Dubin likes talk about a multipolar world where in
Russia become
A superpower that is able to check
The United States
That's why he's really big
Into what's going on
Syria
Because
It is a situation where
Well it's a situation where a sod and the United States
Is there a soup
Superpower
But no Russia comes in
Hold on
You don't get to just say that
Through the way Alexander Dugan wood
Present that is
AB massage
The way you present that is
Because we have nukes
And because we aren't
To be trifled with
We can step in and say no you aren't the big
Supreme leader of the world it's just on principle
Like
Nearest croc from the ark
Dugan contrast
Theory of a multipolar world with what he and conspiracy theorists worldwide
Is the movement towards creating a global government
Light by disingenuous globalist Elites
Route to deprive people of a sense of identity and to subjugate them into their corporate need
In this world have a number of regional superpowers what role would Russia play
Dugan's tease Russia
To be the leading nation in the Eurasian Union
And is founded the international Eurasia movement to make that happen
What is Eurasia
Basically it's the territory of the former
Soviet Union
Really that's
The berries
Yeah
Dugan
Dugan fix the Soviet Union just took over the boundaries of a historical Union of people
And ethnicities that were there for the Russian Empire
Is Russia is a country of a unique culture and death
It is admission
Create a center of power that has elements of both Europe
Asia the two continents
Straddled by the expansive
So
Part of his philosophy is this thing called Eurasian ism
The reason Union
Alex Jones is really against those sorts of things
Relieving
Globalist organization
He use that
IJustine
Alex know this
I would say possibly
Possibly
Dumb that's not
It's not the
Evil or or some kind of
Linkage
Idiot
Idiocy
Like how no it's not no it's not
It's a fine it's a fine layer of varnish
Over
Expansion is
Yeah
It is
Good that's what I'm saying
But it's good PR to put it in this sort of life
In the same way
But what are you saying is
We want
The Soviet Union back
What kind of what kind of boron
Would think that they would
Stop
At the f****** Soviet Union
F****** believable
There's no way that the
Say they get the Soviet Union
What else was part of the Soviet Union world
Do you remember that
Made up bulshit
0 pictures of sorbet that at some point
Nobody
Buy it Publix
You're having such a difficult time
Stroke it is you're trying to accept
Face value from propaganda
I'm not I'm just trying to say that
I just
I find it so fast
That these people
Sociopath
Twist reality version of this world
And they can pull it off
Like
Really it on the show
And this is old card
Alex
That's very fair he's well he's no fill heart
I'm not sure which one
Come on
Like the thing about
What do you want
Do you watch True Crime at all
I've seen some stuff
And you think
How can a human being
How can a human being do something
But these guys
I know I've watched a lot of like cops in those sorts of shows
Everyone
Whenever you're caught red-handed come up with an excuse
And those are jumpy
Dugan's a really smart person who knows he will be caught red-handed eventually
And it's created an entire worldview based around
Preemptively not having to make that excuse at the last second
Between a human being and a cycle
Like if you're if you're on Cops
If you're on top
Well I don't know if I would go person normal person and a psychopath
To some extent
A layer of intelligence
Well I mean
You're not wrong
Serial killer usually gets away with
So you have to be pretty smart to get away with that many
Yeah so
Alex Jones likes to talk about America being the new Atlanta
Recall the number of times that are
Investigation
And episodes where he's talked about that
He's also talked a lot about Atlantis in terms
Don't match up with Play-Doh
On that
About Dugan from Alex
This is from that article for Big Thing
Dugan digs even deeper into his very controversial historical analysis
Does claiming Eurasia
Opponent is not just the United States
But Atlanta
Cooperation
Between Europe us
Canada the crosses the Atlantic Ocean
These Maritime liberal Nations value individuality and Market
Forces
Eurasia on the other hand
Representative
Conservative philosophy
Continental
Which according to Eurasian
Has among its values a hierarchical structure Law and Order
Traditionalism and religion
The we have Atlantis versus Eurasia
In fact claims all history can be viewed as a battle between maritime
And land-based Nation
Very true
He's written a bunch of
To stuff about that a lot of words can't be traced back to
Wild
I mean the water vendors in the Earth
That's what's good
Freewheeling people I base alot of My Philosophy
This is very important
Yeah
Water people versus lamp
Was
Fighting against the law
Stetson standard
Pretty dumb
I'm trying to
Complete sentences
A little bit earlier he wants to end the world
It's a quote from my his book that
Political Theory
The end times
Eschatological meaning of politics
Will not realize themselves on their own
We will wait for the end in vain
The end will never come if we wait for it
And it will never come
We do not
It is the fourth planet
Unless we do it
If the fourth political practice
Is not able to realize the end of time
Then it would be invalid
The end of days should come
But it will not come by itself
That's not good
But whatever
That's that's
Patton Oswalt
George W bush
Amazon
Yeah but this isn't a joke no it's not this is a real guy this is a Russian philosopher
Putin
Who's on Alex Jones
Who now has
B e r of Alex Jones's
Yeah who have been primed for at least a year to be sympathetic
His views
Because the globalist and the globalist controlled media are just lying about all this s***
Bringing about
The end-times exactly what the
The Antichrist
And what band kind of wants to do in terms of its nickel view of History
Is
Godby
Crazy
To a macro scale
We talked about all the
All the time we bring up how Alex Jones accuses people of doing what he's going to do
So
If we take it to the nth degree
I'm talking about the New World Order
And all that stuff
Maybe that is
Maybe that's our goal because clearly that's Dugan's
Dugan wants the New World Order
He's peddling this
Yeah
City of destroying the world
Wouldn't reality what he's talkin about is creating that very new world order
That he is claim
Aiming to fight again
But he wants to do it
Through like a
A massive war
Do you want to do it through and then I'll have more
Yeah so here is the last bit
I'm going to read in this have to do with the idea that
It is kind of confusing to think
Beyond
Trying to hurt Hillary Clinton
Why the Russians
Wood metal in
The election
Exactly their goal is
Enter this article this gentleman
Lays out the
Is Paul Ratner lays out
Influence probably has some
Role to play
The actual
Campaign
To see what Dugan might advocate
Specifically we can look in his best-selling book the foundation of geopolitics
Pixar 1997
Which had particular success among
Russian military
And according to foreign policy
Is assigned as a tech
Text book at Russian military University
The book outlines a vision for Russia in the 21st century they would lead to eurasia's formation
Is that you
But also
But also include specific strategies for defeating or neutralizing the United States
These include destabilizing
And disinformation
Two campaigns using
Special force
And asymmetrical Warfare
Splitting alliances between us and countries like Germany and France
As well as fermenting division within the country itself
Specifically singling out race relay
On page 306
57 of the first edition of the book
Dugan explained
Quote
It is essentially important to introduce geopolitical disorder into internal American activity
Encourage
Encouraging all kinds
Separatism
Mix social and racial
Actively supporting all dissident movement
Extremist racist
In sectarian groups
Dusty stabilizing internal political processes
In the United
It would also support isolationist ended
In American politics
Got to give it to
They're good
They did it
Yeah yeah
Like they did a great job and Alex's f****** help
So even though it was like even if it's not out no collusion
These people are
For the Russians
Running on a purely races
This campaign
And isolation
Perfectly for the Russians
And that's for 1997 he had these ideas
Possible for us
How to figure out exactly when Alex
Became beholden to
Russian propaganda I know I said that it's
The summer of 2050
But it's entirely possible he died in balances
Beyond that
It's just possible that
When Russian
Act like they became much more active
In terms of their their behaviors
They realized
Do these goals
That
Alexander Dugan clearly set out in this book that is now a textbook for Russian military operation
Have universities
Alex is already onboard
He's really into creating race racial Strife he's really into all this stuff
Yeah like legitimately reading that my heart flutter
Because I'm just like
So clear exactly what Alex
Exactly what he
Yep
Nuts
Yeah
Do Dan
We're going to die
About that
I believe that this is going to go
It's not going to go well
It's better that's definitely
So I mean look
Look at all the details
Look at look at the stuff about
In 1997
Alexander
Creation
Of Eurasia
Wedding vows
Ortigia splitting of strong alliances
Like with Germany
Like with France
Coronavirus
Bye and her candidacy
Absolutely.
Pacifically in their butt
That's part of the alliance or whatever
People elections coming up
Insulted
Germany and
I've been very degrading about their willingness to accept Refuge
Ugis and stuff
Like
Relatively
The fact that most of the EU is really you tonight
People think that we're saying or something like that
So far it seems that a lot of
Things have proved fairly resilient
In this
Sure
Enter International
Assertive
Institutions theme much
Stronger than our own
Let's say internally I think we have much more to worry about
In terms of our norms and values a rodent
Was written.
Turns out
Lego
The Assumption on so many of these things
Before they were written
People will like
Comerica
Yeah
We were the founding they were way off
So
Attitudinal Congress should have
Plan for America
Yeah I want it I want to go back to this part of the quote to
The direct quote from Dugan
How about encouraging all kinds of separatism
An ethnic social and racial conflict
Actively supporting all dissident movement
Extremists braces
Sectarian group
Dust destabilizing in
Internal political processes
I want to go back to that because
I think it's really important for us to look at
In the wake of the election
There was a guy named who was in
Toledo
Secessionist
In California
Telex
He was working on that and then he moved
To Russia
That's not true and then gave up on the collection campaign it is tell me that's not true
I wish I could get one more time
How not
True that was absolutely true
The collection
Play Jingle but it's weird
Weird
But that was a
Massive failure
You were talking about
Propaganda
To try and fund that
That had
No
Fertile soil
No but
You cast a wide net you're going to not catch a ton of fish
You're going to catch the rest
Exactly
I think what
If we're if we're talking about that
In terms of
Maybe that's
Plan
Yeah
What they've discovered is that are racist
Are bigots
Religious
All of those people are far more easy
U2
Hoodwitch
Then our secretary
If you will
So what who are sectarian
The collective
Secretary
Alex
But he has more of a a nonsense bialigy
As opposed to an ideology
J or h
Traditional
Fair enough
Dimensional being
You're not really
Slick
Unfair
You're right that was my fault
I kind of agree but at the same time I want to be clear that like
This is a book
The hero
Became widely adopted
And became a tech
Textbook for Russian military University
I am supporting disruptive entities Within
Our internal body politic
You would if you go back
Petula pain
And those she was
You know why Alex Jones
49045 / 2
It's a loss leader
So sometimes
You know you're Russia new support some movement but doesn't end up working out
Yeah the Lost leader
You got it you got a
You got a
Spread it out and then eventually something will sprout
I think there's something
The longest line
It does
It does seem like
It does seem like they've thrown
Whatever it is they cannot
The wall
Without racists
It's stuck
Good news
What's your name
No
My good news is that
We like to think
You know Trump
Putin
Sky Zone
Spell really
We like to think that they're sort of
Nabi
And you know
Think of them as
You and Alexander Dugan Alex Jones have something in common
God system and play God
They are
Swadesh artificial synthetic
World Government transhumanist movement
Has openly declared war on
Men and women in America and schools don't have men and women it's hurtful to others open
Do you guys have her
That's exactly why I kept
Because it's like it's degrading
It's degrading for you to be
Speaking to someone
Propaganda
Right field a little bit murky giving him like
Any sort of respect
At all
Time
He is way smarter than Alex and that that isn't
Example
The way Alex
Does the things in interviews where he says he's lying narratives and when the other person doesn't push back against who knows
Worrying good
Yeah just let it slide
Lebron James playing against
College ball play
I like this is
The same in the same stratosphere
Just a couple more clips
To get through
Next one
Sister pretty Tarot
Which has meaning their normalizing its
Sky's the limit
Russia
Psychotic
Alex
Your guest for
20 years
Has been angling for a war with us
Yeah
Why are you talking about the Deep State trying to
To create a war with Russia
You have a Russian on your show who has the hero of Putin
Or at least has for years I don't know what the current
Situation is
But he's been trying to
The off on the week
He's been trying to start a war with us
Great
Great it's
Crazy
When they actually do assassinated
Yeah witches
A witches
Normalize would reunite the Soviet Union like and further Alex is trying to Norm
Normalize also
The idea of it
They do
And by the way I put agave in quote
If Trump does get impeached or assassinated
He's normalizing the idea that is all-out Civil War at that point
Idea that we are
Currently
Hot Civil War
Savior
Is taken down
I'm looking for
To tear down the Mexico
Can border wall
If you're if you're writing the history book
Therapy
Terrifying
Able to legitimately take some nights High Ground
Not pleasant
It's weird to listen to this episode in
Because
You don't like
A lot of the terror that we deal with
I can I can
Can go home
Processes
Yeah this is
Legitimately terrifying to the
The point where
It's deeply troubling
I won't feel comfortable for days
Yeah
No you'll be fine
Georgia Norway
Whatever who cares
Global us speaking like a globalist
And this one is just
Just a little bit of
It's it's interesting cuz we're done
Dugan now
So a couple days ago
Couple days ago back on the 3rd
Mike cernovich
Came out he released a video where he said
That he is pivoting away from
No longer on the truck
So I'm glad I've been doing more gorilla mindset stuff
The journalism
I pivoted from a pro Trump unquote Journal
I pivoted from
Pro Trump guy to Amor journalistic guy and I'm going to keep making that pivot
So whenever people think of me is like
The pro Trump guy
I don't want anymore guy
A journalist commentator social media personality of filmmaker and author
But it's so far away from anything pro-trump
I just got to keep going that way
But lately
I wish I told you
And now the pivot is going to be even bigger
Because what do you get from being a pro Trump guy right you sure
He got in a fight with Alex
That's what he said on the 3rd
Yeah
As you recall you recalled tell me
Before this he was hosting the 4th once a week he was a very frequent
Alex Jones
He came up with the CNN is Isis
Which Alex
Blumaan
Right
Just got down on his knees
I'd like to further.
Pivoting
I've been giving a little bit which I told you right
Now the pivot is going to be even bigger
What do you get from being a pro Trump guy got a shill for Trump all day
I'm pivoting away from anything pro-trump
No damn don't play the clip of him being on the show this is from August
Forsook me
Picture of Ash's house in the forest hours in a pop in without horses
Of course than Trump
Continue
The first identified
Don Jr
The division between the two of them
I don't want anyone to think of me as a pro Trump guy I'm going to
Specifically reject any kind of brand pro-trump or whatever I'm going this way
Big big pivot big big pivot
I've already made a bit of a little bit more now all the way over here that's where I am
When the GOP Elite in the Deep State goes after Trump hard
Who's going to have his back
Do you gain anything by risking your reputation your career your business supporting Trump what's the upside
So everything in life has an upside and downside
So you go risky for Trump you might lose it all you a big downside
Huge downside of trump what's the upside
First of all
Everything
Mike cernovich
I really just care about money I was just doing this for money the whole time
I legitimately have no principles
Secondly next
4th power
Queer propaganda outlet for Donald Trump
And he's doing it to talk about how right he was about the McMasters lie
And that's what brings me to my main
It's not about
The trouble thing was a way to make
For Mike cernovich
He just laid it out
On his
F****** Periscope video that he put out where he pivots away
From Trump
Alex Jones made it clear in 25
15 when we had that clip
That episode
We're f****** Joe Biggs
Went to a trump rally
And Alex Jones realize he could make a lot of money on
The reason that Mike cernovich
Is still doing the 4th hour
To talk about is McMasters
Because this globalist narrative
Is more important to them
Then
Any of the little pieces
Any of the
Any of the details
Doesn't matter about Trump doesn't matter about it
Chatters about books
No
The book sales
But the anti-semitism
That wise be
Behind the globalist Merida
Is inescapable
It's metastasized into
Too full on white
Like
We walk hand-in-hand
They do but anti-Semitism is much more
Picture of McMaster as a marionette
And the person who had the strings of the marionette was Soros
And then there was another marionette above bat
That's all just
Sucking this same nonsense narrative
You really dig in
Do not have nearly as much money as everybody for 10
And the whole story of their Ascension to
Our global banking
Cartel that controls everything
East
Complete nonsense
Historical
And I am the same way that everyone
It's right up there with everyone's anti
Central Bank
Is problematic as an idea but it didn't come around
Just a way to be evil
Same thing with Rothschild
They were very successful for a bit
And now their money has been diffused quite a bit they aren't nearly as rich as ever
The greatest
It comes
To anti-semitism
The greatest lesson
Nobody ever learn
The death of G
Weather
Don't
Comes back to bite you
Yeah 3 days later
Well I mean
The Jews for
No good reason
I am firm in my
Based on all the research
What's that I've done about Alex Jones
Does individual sources
But he claims
Approved globalism
Just don't say what
He says they say
The things that
Do you match up with the things
He says
Come from sources like
The protocols of the elders
Deeply auntie
Systematic fraud
Throughout history
So I am over to mine
Exactly
I'm totally I'm of the mind that Alex Jones
Is
Going it or not
Behold into a deeply anti
Do somatic worlds
And
A lot of these
Johnny-come-lately
The crnkovich is
The jackdaw
Episode
Cassandra Fairbanks
Is Lauren Southern
These people
Are falling right in the
Gavin McInnes
They're all just going along.
The exact same ride
There
Doing it
Maybe more effectively maybe smarter
Then Alex because there's the group
Is just admitting it
Out now
But it wasn't good for Book Sales
They are
Much less
You specifically says in that rent that
The Trump mindset book didn't sell as well as a bog
Trucking
Have any
Still fighting it
Toxic masculinity identity sells far better than
Then fighting Fortress
Well because that's too much
That's putting a hat on a hat
Yeah you're
Masculinity on top of toxic masculinity
You don't need to do that
That's a comedy error
I don't know if I'm making my point fully
Like
This thing with cernovich
Incredibly revealing
But it exposes
So much
It exposes a ton about Mike cernovich
Like really meaningful
For him
The fact that he does this
Big big pivot away from Trump
I reject all branding of me being pro Trump
And then it rain later
Doing the Infowars fourth hour
Which is an out-and-out Trump propaganda
Operation
Like Alex had him stay
Amway anti-trump
I'm free if I reject the Brandon
Yeah but
Then I was 2 years back
The long hangover
Rejecting that out of course or we still going
I just I think that
We never should have elected
That's where it all began
How we feeling
We doing okay
You know where I'm at
Here's where I'm at
Where you at
I got too much going on
Inside my head
In terms of a lot of these angles
Very worried that I'm not laying it out
In a way that makes
I'm deeply worried that
It sounds like
Rampant
Conjecture
And none
There's no shortage
On the internet
Right and I'm not trying to be Louise Mensch know I'm deeply critical of myself
His much
Even as I'm saying
These things I like
What are you doing
And as soon as I post
Post
Course
Used to get on everything
Podcast
Exactly what am I why am I hurting people
Insecurities that is just
From bad parenting
Who knows and that's how we got food
Who knows
Let's not psychoanalyze everything
Deeply
Deeply concerned about tooth
What is the big picture that we were talking about
About the Dugan and Alex
Clear
Pro-putin
Possession
That is incredibly troubling
Because
Does matcha
With what we saw in our last episode from 2
Years in the past
And there's a
Chance that all of this has been
Alex's
Position the whole time
And no one
Realized
Is not a Russian agent
What is a Russian
Mouthpiece
More
Maybe by flattery
Because farison
You know what
He lived
In America
Top 2020
Dean what would that be
20 years 19
Teen years doing radio and everyone thinking
He's crazy
Some Russian p
People come around to be like your f****** awesome
You got it
You're so great
Thanks
Steve Russian propaganda that sounds a lot like him
How is that not
That's true that's super villain backstory
Yeah so there's that
Yeah there's that image that's in my head
The honey pot
Being told you're a good boy
And then beyond that
I mean the start of it s***
I'm stoked
I mean who cares really
I'm torn between
That whole pivot is fake
That's all it's just absolutely
Does a media stunt
The other
Maybe
Yeah maybe
But it's possible that he's being since
Sear
But then he still will be on Infowars because
He still believes in the globalist
Anything
But he can exist on Infowars
And not be branded as pro-trump
Which I'm here to tell you you can't
You cannot do
But
Heimlich
If that is
Case
That's even more trouble
Because
How many globalist
Are real
And
Don't give me that way
You know damn well
It's an audio podcast
I just
Razor
A raised Brown people's Brown
I just I just don't know what to do with it
That I don't know what
To do it
I'm not ready
Need to deal with the idea of their
Being jumped
Out-and-out
Anti globalist
Propaganda Network
Where is Alex Jones allows someone who's not pro Trump
To be on it
Like
For me is
It's scary
But it's fast
It'll be it'll be
Be interesting to see how
Influences
Who here
So imagine cernovich
Just pivot
Real not because he doesn't
But just because
Why would I align myself with Trump
Clearly disintegrating
Right right
So
If that is true
Then his argument to Alex
Is one again of Craven
Opportunistic
So he and Alex have a conversation
Alexei
My audience
Show pro-trump
I can't pee
It's a smart move money-wise
In the long-term
But I can't not
You know like for me to sell books I have
Tubi
Divorced
YouTube
You have to be on board with
You know what though
This pivot didn't
Come six months
From cernovich
Do you know what I bet
I bet his book sales work great
Initially
And they're terrible now
So they dropped off because everybody hate
Right
The argument that Alex could make about long-term
Farm stuff
Holds no water
And I would argue
Long-term
Yeah but Alex saying
If I pay bills
Everything is over
To take months
Stop it
Cernovich
Came up with
He is a Wonder
In terms of like
This guy is an idea.
Alex Jones
Mike cernovich
Buckley with a little sack of male vitality
Annabelle
Like they getting a room
Together they snort two lines that super male Vitality they can come up with
Let's get out of this thing
Real quick
Because Alex Jones for the last couple years
Has been beholden
To Russian
As early as Friday
Has had
Representative of that
I don't want this to be the truth
Propagate likes about him
That cookies the hold into stuff in the same way that Alex is but
He's also just a s*** head
Gamergate
Which Eve
You can go f***
I hope
Bucking chutes
He's that kind of guy
Contrarian
Mail
Identity
Kind of dude
Online
Scope studied him enough to know if he has
I don't know if his narrative
Matchup
5 with Russia
F******
Is himself to this
Idea of masculinity dead
God help us
Go away
Agree that's all he
Axesspointe I'm going to wish you a happy vacation
I will I will I think I think at this point
There's a lot more information that we want that we don't
Yeah I will find out eventually
But at this point
It's deeply troubling
But I will see we'll see what the
Other
Call man
And if you want to know more
Wait until we find out
Knowledge underscore
Go to our website knowledge.com
And you know you can
Find archived episodes that Ally.
To this point
Wild heroin eight-month Journey
Send
Like what's going on
Yeah I've been also filled with more Revelations of
Did he just just like the Thin Man I want I want some kind of drawing room team where every all of the
Players are put together around a table and we go like
Now it's
Could be Alex Jones
Now I thought you were talking about the Slender
I only know about the Enderman
Great movies
The punching wives back in
It's a very
Movie
You can go to Facebook
You can check us out there
Just Let It Go but
Big shout out to all our peeps
Keep sending us match
Messages on there
Yep and we're getting buttons made and other merch
Stuff will be flowing in the near future
You know summer weather
All the girl out of business
Orchard
Probably not
No one wants to be associated with
This denture mouth
You know what that's fine
That's a good car would love to know the truth about that
Dia dentist
Comes in
Hold on
Call Don new narrative
Never going to work
At one point
Was normal
Yes
This is Baxter
Okay talk about Frankie
1 years ago
John Rappaport with a normal investigative
He was just hanging out trying to get to the bottom of scoop
Right
What am I going to do
Well I haven't been as well
He's a great guy
No time for Love Jennifer Jones
Just got to get in there with the Pete
He goes and gets his teeth worked on
Turns out
Chimeras in Disney
Talk to him
About
Dr. Jones
Puts in
Animal Human
Chimera
Inside the feelings inside
Audits are telling about things like
Okay start Whispering Springs
Which I mean
Tavern
Side of mouth and you speak towards the throat
It's going to get today
Tiny cameras inside
Start giving out
I'd love it if you're running out of steam but I've loved it
The moment we get into plug
Makes me laugh so much more now
Competent manner
What's the point
That you're trying to make
This guy named John Rappaport
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work