I have great respect for knowledge but now it's like I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
MoneyGram
Facebook.com
Everybody welcome back to another episode of knowledge fight I'm Dan
The Elder of Selene from afar while we're in this hotel room Alex Jones
Question for you
My bright spot Jordan is going to steal yours
Robert Barnes on Twitter
I thought there was going to be for sure
Yeah and Infowars character accidentally stepped into your Twitter mentioned it down it and got blown up with all people
Getting ratioed
Nickname that is that belittling and then step into that Arena that would be me I would avoid that
It was it was fun to see of all the Twitter nonsense that you're getting into that it was definitely a peek
What about you
Bio bright spots or my
Dark spots I don't know
Whatever it is we found out today
That's
The man
The myth the legend
Will be testifying in open court
Tomorrow Alex Jones is supposed to take the stand in the trial
Episodes coming out
And you would think
Cuz here's why it's my birthday
Because if you were a wise man
Who is going to testify in your own behalf
You would absolutely stick to what you said in your deposition
Dust
Proving that you are not a liar
But seems like it's going to be tough
Oh yeah
A lot of things I'm at deposition
Yeah I think that'll be wild to see and expect
I think I'm going to shave my beard so I can achieve super Incognito we should definitely be doing that
I will be there in the other side
Do Jordan today about what's going on on Alex's show
But it'll be fun to have
I guess come in and talk about the goings-on here in the trial
Experiences at the coverage
Yes but not in the room with us.
Are welcoming back to the podcast
Hey guys
Now let me ask you this what is your bright spot
Oh my gosh
Okay
So completely
Was that
For the first time
Since I've been here which is
Almost a week
I did get out for a run
Morning
And it was
Only 90 is opposed
201/2 you must have gone to that run at like 3 a.m. or something
6:30
I would have 110 by then
And I have to say by the end it was getting
Spell
Temperature
Totally well congratulations on mustering the the drive to do that I've been telling myself I'm going to go
Go to the gym in our hotel for a week
I've been saying it for a week instead
I have s'mores snack mix I'm glad you enjoyed me about
The shameful moment where I went out
To go for running
And I told you there is no shade away from being elf
Did you really
Would you get
At the Voodoo Doughnut
So they have a limited edition banana cream
Thai Donuts
Is a lot of trucks
A little bit better about myself so it's
Voodoo Donuts version of a salad
Cinnamon cake Donuts
Oh yeah I got this i got this peanut butter banana thing that's blood
Elvis situation no idea but it was the size of a horse's flank
Like it was absurd
To try and fit that anywhere near my
I'm ashamed to say that over
Two days I ate a third of it
That I couldn't really finish it and then I didn't know what to do with it because
I didn't want to throw it into the hotel
Smile like a donut
Toilet
I thought this was going to be a I threw it off that's helping my situation
Allusion to the problem
Cutting out the middleman right
Bat is cracked alligators got a little bit bigger yesterday
Camaro smell like
I personally can't get away from the O Captain my Captain the Captain Crunch donut and
I hate myself every single time
It's good I eat it
When you're standing in that line
You don't really know unless you
You did a QR code which I'm not very good at
Your choices are so I'm looking at the sort of revolving you know that old school Bakery
Diner revolving display
To the checkout
All right what do I choose what do I choose
Stressful moment so
I did
Tell you something in a non misogynist way I'm going to do my best to do this okay they deliver baby
Yeah
A door
Yeah I had to do that myself cuz I I couldn't
Handle
Well basically the moment they're describing was the kid in the candy store but
I'm not a kid I'm not going to let you bring it to my home
It was kind of fun though to go there early in the morning
Really want to get there
Before the line forms
People who
Waiting for you
To buy them one and give it
The monster
Beat when I was in town for the depositions I went there at night
I went there at like
After we'd all got done with everything I think it was probably like 11
Sun or something
And there were just drunk people hanging out really weird
Party time place
I'm not sure that's what I want after a big night stays open past 11
You are giving drunk people don't
That's your business model I want I want
Nachos
Oh my God
I think just created a situation as Dan a heart attack and two years chili mac chili
There's a million-dollar idea Lanes killed if you've killed my best friend how dare you
So good so good
Mac and cheese
Alright lose we are here not just for donuts although
They are more positive in many ways than a lot of the other stuff that's that's happening in town
Subject you got a greener pastures flushing Donuts
But don't do that
Episode
Hey listen you didn't tell us everybody I know I'm human
Cool monster waltzes a cluster donut
Destroy the environment around the plumbing
Good good
That is how much we don't want to get to the trial is that we almost got there and then immediately were like
So
I wanted to ask you a little bit because we're all in town
Experience
This mistrial
Far more professional capacity than us
You also have had more experience on
This story in particular you're following the Sandy Hook story
Came out recently
Cliche you literally wrote the book on this case
Yeah how you've experienced it
So far
So
You know I'm worried about
Definitely
The plight of the families
And got to know them
Pretty well
And today you know
Listening to
Mr. Crouch
Therapist
Who has worked with
Neil heslin and Scarlett Lewis
I did have a couple moments where I was
Really got a little bit emotional about
How to say about their struggle
Describe the sort of
Two bucket
One you lose your son in a mass shooting
Second bucket
People call you a liar and
Say that
Not only
Boise not killed in that way that he never existed
And at one point
Mr. Crouch the therapist was being
Prompted to say
Well what does that actually mean
The parent your kind of dealing with
And he said you know is just in
So important
To kneel and Scarlett
Jesse's parents that
He matter
You know that
That this was
And and Jessie in particular
Has a very particular narrative
And that's that
You know she
When the gunman entered his classroom
Started shooting there was a pause
In the shooting where
Either the magazine
Or he was
Reloading
Jesse yelled run
And 9 children ran
Survived
Yeah
And so you know one thing that I'm sure that Neil and Scarlett will speak about is that
He was actually given
Fallen heroes
Funeral
Because
Please
You do recognize that as of
Heroism
The children who survived
Said what had happened and that's how they knew
So
That part of his life
Is
Tremendous
Important
To kneel and Scarlett as you can
Imagine
Yeah I miss idea that that would be taken from
The first thing that
Both told me them separately
The first thing they told me
Was
That story
And so it's so important
From them
You know in their their therapist obviously
Described
Well it is
It's like saying
You know it's
It's taking that last bit
Did that someone would kill
These were his final moments he was
Spine
Child and end
Saved his class
It's in his final moments
And to think that
Someone
In order to
So
Or
You know
Would take that
Shred from you is right
You know the the thing that got me about that is
The the therapist
As much and as powerful as that story was
When he was asked
What's the most important
Sing to the parents what's the most important thing
To them
He didn't say that
His he was remembered as a hero or he was remembered as somebody who saved anybody
He choked up
And he said the most important thing to me
Are the most important thing to the parents
Is just to let people know to let the world know
That he lived
That he matters
Yep
Was when I actually
Did have to
Look down and compose myself
I cried like a baby I was in my hotel room I didn't have to worry about people like judging me in the courtroom
Weeping uncontrollably
Because
Those words
Were veronique De la Rosa
Who is the mother of Noah Pozner who's the youngest Sandy Hook
Victim
The shooting she said
The same thing
To Anderson
Thank you for an interview
People to know that he
You know and that
I don't know something about
To take these here
But take your time
Formulation
Is
You know
It just
How much is
From you
When you lose
A loved one in this way
Particularly your child
You're then
Yourself saying
Really
That just speaks
To the utter desolation
These parents must
Yeah I found it almost everything
That went on today
Quite heavy
Yeah of course
For a lot of those boots
Same reasons we're touching on
And there's one reason that
I think I want to I want to ask you about a couple of questions about the
The trial just because
After we heard that testimony
We also saw the way that the defense behave
In their cross-examination and how the the judge
Was not happy with their behavior
Did you did you experience that in in that kind of way
Yeah
And so here's an interesting so
As you can well imagine there are a lot of lawyers in these parts who are watching this trial
As we know it
I don't want of them was fighting with Jordan on Twitter earlier
Hell yeah yeah
Also a lot of regular lawyers
Are watching this and are just riveted by this
Because
It's such a challenging case
The family's lawyers obviously
Certainly Sir Alex Jones this lawyers
But they were saying you know
One of the things that you know the unenviable position that Alex Jones is lawyer is in
Is that
She of course
Cannot attack
Niall and Scarlett when they testified
Tomorrow
So the alternative that he has is
2 attack
Drlupo
6 psychiatrist who had
You Know spoken with them
And to attack Mr Crouch their act
Sexual therapist
So it's
You know lower steak
Try and impeach them
To go head-to-head
Course
With
Jesse's
So so that was sort of interesting
Because
The therapist
Mr. Crouch was
So
Kind of a sympathetic character himself I mean he actually filled up with
When he said that about
He mattered
You know she was filling up
Yourself and
Ghetto he obviously
Feels very deeply
Yo for Neyland
Scarlett and for Jesse Evans and JC his older brother
And so
I think it was a lot more difficult than they had anticipated this wasn't
Somebody who is
Very much
Infested
In the plight of this
And I think that made it
Supertop
Uncrossed
Come back and say
Manual
DSM-5
Was just
My favorite thing that I think is ever happened
I've ever seen an acorn look like you just Googled something
He tried to he tried to catch so what happened was
He was trying to catch the defense lawyer
The serapis
In like a
You don't know the exact definition of PTSD do you
So the first thing you did was he tried to bring up the definition to the
Therapist didn't realize that he had brought the wrong version of the DSM
Which was an issue
So then he went to the APA website
To try and find the definition
In the DSM-5
However
He found vapa
Summary definition
Of the DSM-5
I didn't so doing revealed that he had no idea what he was talking about
The therapist away
I don't think I know what you're
I don't think I know what you're showing me
And then he just
Changed
I need the lawyer turned around 5
Two guys walking by holding a glass pane I was watching
I found it to be really uncomfortable because
That's going to play
Traffic
It was really grim
Funny like
No matter who you're watching it
The public performance
Enso
Your kind of
Cringing
No matter
Just taking out you know
Where's
Lawyers for
Plaintiff
You're just taking all that out
The public performance
So whenever anyone
Azure there's
Weird awkward thing that happens
You're just sore
Seriously
Binging
For them
The case at hand
Oh my
Do you know how did that happen
It's pretty daring
Do the start of ad hoc
Open court
But but you were serious
I found my
Thinking well
Here's the therapist
And the DSM is something that therapist
Consult routinely
So if you thought that you were going to
You know these definitions and
The question
Maybe just
Go out
Sudoku
Bookstore
Darren is a fun word that using that
It seems like desperate
Tragically stupid
Foolhardy
Y'all
Use my Texas
You know I just
My little choirs
Kaiser tell you I have Googled a thesaurus
Exact letter words though
I know I just
Did not understand
Possibly understood that
I don't know understand that
Do you think anyone has ever even seen that before right like in real Court
Yeah
Dome9 cases
You do you have
People
I'm really young
I'm really trying to
Understand
The night moments for that lawyer I just
You'd hope
But I mean like
Also I get the sense from
I don't know maybe just a Vibe I'm getting off of him
I don't think he beats himself up too much
Pittsburgh
Coming off poorly
That's just my sense
Texas monthly is apparently doing
A profile of
Alex Jones
What's the square
Federico NG Marino
What happened
Huge interest his name is
Federico Andino rental
Oh what's his name again
Hi I'm sorry I'm just kidding
You know I think she's kind of
Play
From what foods
As monthly reporter was telling me
Grnn
For the families
That he's kind of
Family name around here
Emma sister
Us attorney was
Disappointed by Eric Holder I think
Jordan
The pain that when I was
Tweeting that about his
Mystery
A matter of
You know okay
Sometimes it's
Yo
This person will pay you
New or
What have you
There's some idea here that
You know that.
You know everybody deserves
More that than the payday
Oh yeah
Yeah I'm sure I've seen his mentor sitting in court right next to him the entire
I'm sure is not about money
Actuation
Yeah it's all about
All about everybody deserve their day in court right
Dakota wire
The career fuc
In case that's true this is the kind of thing that can really
But you know what I got to say like
Recognizing that aspect of his history that makes
Some of the stuff that's going on look way worse yeah
Because they're there have been repeated instances where he's shown Witnesses things that he hasn't
Taken by
To the plaintiffs attorneys for football
Which they pointed out a couple times is like Year One
Yeah
Those aren't mistakes that someone of a caliber would make
Yeah at least not a mistake number for
Then I expect it's on purpose getting into a fight with Mark Banks
Giving him the bird in court like these are things that like
Free that
Observing that
Camille
Suddenly
He realized
This
Is
Place I want to be
I don't want to be within a thousand miles
Where I am
China
Getting beaten up
Pure in this case
I'm really trying to
Keep it there
Salt Lake that moment in a wrestling match when someone's losing and they go for a chair
Disqualified
Putting it then anything I can
Map with right now
I have to go with my favorite adjectives for him at this current time which is eviscerate
He's literally had his guts ripped from his body
What day does this Soros
After you know the judge had
Admonished him and he was losing that exhibits
And he was feeling frustrated because
Who is maybe in his mind he genuinely
I don't know but it felt like a kind of like volcanic
Frustration that have
Right there
You know
It if he's like this kind of well-bred guy that you know we're hearing
You would be a childish bully a well-read guy being a childish bully giving
People that finger whenever they embarrass him
That's crazy
What's the equivalent of picking up a chair in Smash
You know what I mean you know you can't do
It's wild
That was sad that
Whole confrontation happened
The parents of a murdered child
Standing 10
10 ft away
Damn
I think strategically when the judge wasn't in the room
Yes
Judge Campbell was in there she said today that if she were available she would have held him in contempt of court
Yeah
Yeah she said had ice
Christine had I been in the room
When that happened
Yeah so she was definitely so I kind of love is a defense for not doing anything is like
Well because I only saw accurate live video of it occurring I can't do anything
Didn't see the chair
Real wrestling
Turn this back and then they hit him with a chair
If I
Turn around while I'm driving
This car and I see what you're doing to your brother
There will be problem
I know it's happening
But the minute I see it with my own eyes you kids are in trouble
Yeah it's your responsibility to do something once
You observed
Not yet not to ask you a question that might be uncomfortable
But exactly how many times have you felt
Like you and the judge are both moms
Really trying to handle unruly children
Same here
Yeah
Yeah I mean I think about that
Alex Jones I mean just his behavior and their you do relatively rare occasions he
He turns up for
Receding
It's like this
Kid who has stalled out
In Middle School
I mean
Even
The whole idea that.
Traveling around surrounded by bodyguards I'm sort of thinking like a high school hallway
Bought lunch for the whole football team so that there's 10 other people
There's exactly 11 people with Alex it is literally the Star Quarterback being surrounded by the red
What's the team
Sublime
I'll pay for your lunch if you just
Follow me down the hall to my lock or so no one beats me hop
I need any big big muscle guys with guns to
Talk about one thing that did happen I've made reference to this on a previous episode but
Are you experienced that's why I want to get your take on it was from today
Last week when Alex was there
And was giving his a little 8 years doing at the press conference out in front of the
The courthouse so yeah
Bissell
This was a situation where there was no one but security guards
You
Sebastian Murdoch
I believe
And it
What was going on there
From Hurst
Okay
Is one other person baudin
Inaccurate
Yeah out of context
Anyways sorry I was I was observing this from
Safe distance
I have binoculars I was on the roof or the building across the street
No I was maybe
No
Right
I was maybe twenty feet away
Serta just standing and
Vaping
And giggling
A little bit because
The spectacle of it was was truly bizarre
My assessment was
He didn't know
He didn't know that you were you and that Sebastian was Sebastian
He just thought this was media
Which is
Happy
Give me an idea of how many times you have met and spoken to Alex Jones via any different
Luke was backed up
True true
Yes
Well I've never recognize anybody who is wearing a mask before so I do understand now that it makes perfect
Blind
So yeah I mean I spent a lot of time with him
But it was in 2018
So I think it also I think in the heat
Publicity moment
I think she just
She's as you say
No I think you just
People
Recording him as generic media
An audience
Faceless audience
He was talking to
He did ask
John from hers
You know where are you from and
To talk to
Oxygen because
He did ask
So what is it
Condition
Here
Hip Hop
John Cena really good journalist was like
This says that it's a
Important
He was like
Really you know what is it
No really what is it
What is a hernia
Okay
Here's an untreated hernia and that
That is
Medical condition
Prevented him
From sitting through the
The trial
I don't even believe that
Yeah I was going to say that doesn't even sound reasonable to me
Say something like you know I got the
How to get removed
Feel like my response to that is do you even lift bro like I feel like that's my
Okay I'm done
Yelling probably
Are you sure if you're happy
If it was his like fifth or sixth about of covid that he's dealing with
Keep getting that
He was coughing
Keep
Smart
How long did it take for him to realize that this was not unknown
Media to him
So
Sub
From from HuffPost
Sub murdoc asked him
Cryptocurrency that you got is an anonymous donation because
We sold it was only worth
Directions by criticism
That is fair
Exactly so
People that does not equal bankrupt
And so he
Persist
He said
I said something like
Didn't you just
$1000000
Anyways like
And I said
So you're not exactly
Broke
When I pee it means
That is a man
Who's got the goods
If you really wanted to insult me like
Why wouldn't you pick like a smaller
You know item
Brazil nut brain I was going to say it like why aren't you just followed me on Twitter and grabbing a couple from there
They're Universal I'm not like that personal
So you are pretty comes out
Recognition
Oh this is Batwoman
This is that woman from the New York Times
Is that he said
Oh no heat he did look over while he was talk
270 said
This is a trial of media these are these are fraught like that New York Times person right there
And then I asked about the million dollars and he
He said Walnut brain and then he went into
Percentage of monster and
Stir-fried
Here's the good news the only people he's saying these terrible things about you two is who's secure
There's no one else
And you know at least
If it's
Bodyguardz
Good to be
You know armed
It really it really did take awhile for me to remember whenever the bodyguards were sitting next to me it took me awhile
While Furby to remember like
They can't bring guns into the court
You realize that Jordan
That's not okay
And they're not going to like
Pushy
And of course they've a license to push for money yes okay
Alright I was I was watching all of this I thought it was really fun because I could see a shift
All happening in the conversation
And then after the shift
Once became a little bit hostile
Alex put on the bumper sticker on his face
I took a picture with his lawyer and I've actually been really offended that some
Outlets
Have a run with that picture on their story
It's such a it's a it's a Well framed picture I will give I will give the photographer that but it's
Like I was there when it was taken
This is Alex with a dumb bumper sticker on his mouth and he put on for show shaking hands with his lawyer
Wild no one watched yeah like it was
It's
I don't know it it kind of
Even before opening arguments began on the first day
He put it over his
Federico
Indeed
Can even laugh now
Dan's even laughing now when you say is real babe but it's longer
I just feel like it's important
The accurate
So yeah so he was sort of mugging for for him
And then he put
Didn't put it away I mean
Reynald gave him the side eye
Don't do that the parents are
Sitting right there you know
The only person
That you're entertaining with this you're definitely
View of the parents
But this isn't that question can I ask you
Who is real quick
Real quick
Do you are you surprised like
I really never thought I would be surprised
At what happened but for some reason I really thought when it actually came to being in the courtroom
There's no way they would behave like the like
They had to prepare they've had
So much time right now
Are you surprised
You do yes
So
One thing is that
First of all I get
From rain all his lawyer that
She feels like oh
I'm not sure what I got mice
I think that that
You know explosion with the you know
In the bird and all that
What is a sort of expression of that
Today what happened to him
Boys another
I think he feels like
Oh my God I don't know what I got my
The idea that
Trying to kind of waffle about actually weather Jones
Fire not
Torres
Yeah I just show like I'm so
Testify
And then he had to go check with them I think these are all sort of
Indications that
You know he should have known what he was getting him
Myself into but I don't
Incubus Philippe
Prepared for that
If I did
Not exactly a knock on him
Because
Is anyone ever fully prepared for things that else
I'm going to have a disagreement with you there real quick I feel like
Any kind of preparation any kind of preparation even the slightest amount does not wind up with you
You having 10 minutes left to call your main witness as
Whether or not they will take
Fair fair
Yeah that was today
Wake me up
The previous lawyers what should I do
Yeah oh yeah Oh you mean like
The 12 previous lawyers
You could have had her Focus
His previous players
Call Dave a Baker's Dozen basically
Yes it would have been like him
A crowd
Zoom
Previous lawyers where are you
Could say
What advice
Do you have for me
Can't do that with one of Alex's lawyers you're going to get it too but that's just going to happen
So he said
So he's I said will
Is out
Going to testify and he said
It's all up to Alex
And I said
Do you mean
All of it
The nearest like yep
It's all up to Alex
Bro
You know how that goes it seems like a lot of stuff in his life is that
Yeah but there's not a lot of great Council in many areas are
Anybody really telling him he cut it out
Just be so curious
No
Is really like to see go home and say well that went about how I expected or
Oh my God I can't believe I got myself into this
You know I
Ladder
If you talk about Alex he goes home and says hello whiskey my old friend
Yeah
You know I don't know but yeah no I agree I
There've been a lot of moments I think he's
Actually you can tell that
She is
Criminal process
Cuter by the way
He cross-examines the witnesses
He is pretty aggressive
He's he also just
Kind of rolls with it when the judge kind of slaps him down on the various things like we talked about
Quick on his feet
Coming back
Back from that kind of thing
But that's not to say
This is
Going well because
It's just
Even if no one said
Edward just the idea of
Alex Jones
Anna Sandy Hook family
Europe
How to say a word
To know that this
This is probably going to be a tough
You know did ironic thing is it hadn't occurred to me until I was watching him and then put it together
Said that he was a criminal defense lawyer and then started thinking about what
Erno a criminal prosecutor
Answer to thinking about what they do and then I started thinking
96% of cases go to a plea bargain
In in that kind of
So this is probably guy
Who's really good at doing paperwork and like negotiating with other lawyers as to what's an acceptable
Sentence doesn't end up with a lot of trial going to an actual trial because he does
Does not have experience
I just can't believe that he does
Yeah I think some of the Warriors who have been
Have been watching this
Kind of weighing in
Completely descent
Interested except for
For the fact that their lawyers and this is
Fascinating
Would disagree
Agree with you there
A lot of prostitute
Tutorial courtroom
Experience
On the other side you know
Some of these
Injury
Chase's or
You know lawyers
Who are tort lawyers
Impact
The father of Josh koskov who represents
The Sandy Hook families in Connecticut
His dad has
Passed away but I interviewed him for the book
And he said
One of the funniest things that has
People settle so
Frequently
We get less
Some less time in the courtroom
What are the reason
Catnip for the legal community
Is that you have
Tucson
You actually have
Amount of courtroom
And so it's
It is kind of fast
Fascinating to
Reynald
S*** the bed like a f****** idiot
Different ways of describing the same thing
But yeah I mean it is
The whole thing is
If it weren't so tragic I think it would be in a text
Kind of way really
Rarely
Rarely anybody drag their feet this long
Dishes at this far
Yes exact
Exactly and then that's
Determination to kind of roll back the clock
And say
This is a defamation trial no it's not you lost
You know because you
Because you had
Complete contempt for the judicial
Are you lost
Your opportunity
To make the surf
Chase
Because you didn't wind up at trial be
Because you would not come
Comply with
You know not any but most
Of the court orders
And most
You know what your
To prepare for that trial
Sailed
And now here you are and it damages
And you're trying to
Turn it into a
Signal test
Which I think
Most people would have been
That didn't happen because
He stonewalled his way into a damages
And so
He is where he is
And I think both he and his lawyer
Wish they were in a different
They're not
Yeah
That's the thing that I find so frustrating
A lot of the responses that I see from people who are not like
Necessarily paying
That close of attention
But the dealer
Not recognizing that Alex absolutely would have gotten a trial on the merits
If he just
Cooperated in anyway
Yeah like here that point be made and then people just not hear it
Not listen not understand that like
The only reason
That this is happening is because of
These choices
I really almost want like every article written about it to begin with a
Timeline of the number of times that Alex could have
Just apologized and stopped
With no lawsuit whatsoever
Could have just made a public apology and stop
With no lawsuits for whatsoever and then the number of times that once the lawsuit was brought they could
Could have done any
Billion number things to keep it from getting to where we are now and instead everybody keeps writing
Sing like the families are seeking damages
12 template of how trials are expressed her or
I have labored with that Justin writing my stories you notes
Trying to say all the time that
What they really want
Is
You know they want that they are a mean this is the altruist
Fixing here they really are trying to shine a light on the fact that
The lies around Sandy Hook
Yeah and here I'm like
You're talkin about
What I talk about it
My book
And that's that
It really was
Foundational story of how
Formation has
Taken hold
In art
Discourse
You do because
It just went from
And Alex was at the
The center of a lot of this you know it went from
Pizzagate
Qanon
Coronavirus myths
To the stop the Steal
Campaign 2
January
Directions
And you know
His fingerprints are on
Pretty much all of those at all
Throw Charlottesville into the mix too
Absolutely
So
His fingerprints are all over those
Development
And so in that
This is
It really is a kind of
Fake news on trial
Pipes
Really is
Yeah
You know and I think that's one reason why people are so invested in it and
Defense that that
He's trying to put forward
Really does
Concern first
First Amendment lawyers this idea that
There's so much
Garbage
In the atmosphere there are so many lies
And Miss Truth
International
Discourse right now
That who's to know
True or false
This seems like
Such a specious cynical argument
Actually
The more of this stuff that is
Floating out there the more lies are you are spread to millions of
People the more
People will advance
First offense and you will see
See it in these Dominion voting
You'll see it in the January
Insurrectionist
Cases
You'll have p
People who will say
Like Alex Jones said in his deposition
Kind of psychosis
Because I was lied to so many times
In an interview with Glenn Greenwald he just said he was drunk
It's a kind of insanity defense
It's the Jamiroquai defense
I woke up the next morning and work 1/2
I didn't put the pieces together I thought you were trying to polish
Wasn't me because I got high
One other thing I was just thinking about was
If Alex does take the stand
Tomorrow
That is going to be wild for a number of reasons first of all because he will be in Ohio state of cross-examination
But then the other aspect of it
Is
These questions that the jury has been giving
Oh s*** it's been pretty good
Yeah
It's because I do think that it's there's a lot of things that probably need clarification from the jury's point of view
That maybe the lawyers aren't aware of
That's really helpful but I think it would like based on the trend of the questions we've been seeing
They could ask some really messed up things Alex
Not messed up like
Bizarre anything but like
Pointed questions that he does not want to answer
And then he appears to be evasive to the jury's on question
Like he puts himself in a really really dangerous position there
The best
He would do that he would have made them I mean
Bedford
The worstest the contempt I mean like getting thrown out of court
Exploding
Which is what
Did in his car
Anthony trial remember
That was where you know it was like
His ex-wife had attorneys who
Really knew how to get under his skin
And he finally just
Bloated I I talked with Charlie warzel about that cuz he was in the courtroom
And he was saying
If it would have been a regular thing of bailiff would have
Escorted him out
Wow he's just he just
Exploded and ballast for him because I'm sure Mark has no idea how to get under his skin
Doesn't seem like a guy who knows how to get an Ender anybody skip from sitting in that deposition
His numbers
But good news is if a bailiff to get Alex out of the courtroom
Standoff
I don't know I mean
I don't know it just
Wouldn't rule out
The facts
Or the
Not the fact
The possibility
That rain all his lawyer is
Working on him
Right now just to say
Alex
Unless you're going to like
Prostrate yourself
Before
The court and end at abject
Apologize
There's probably not a lot
You can say that's good
Can I help you
Yeah you you being you
You know
Begging him to know how many I mean you remember better than I do but
How many times did Alex in a softball t-ball interview where his aunt is
Questions were answered
For him
How many times do they say
I never lied on purpose
8 and 40 minutes
Yeah yeah
And then he said he was drunk when he was saying these things about Sandy Hook families twice
About the Greenwald say I thought you were talking about something
Decided in advance that the election was going to be stolen
Really messed up things just like
No one asked him to do one like it wasn't doing being pushed on everything
Becca Becca
Of all people
Do you know what confirmation by his his
That was really
Next episode Alex Jones like
I decided before the election happens that it was stolen
Confirmation bias is like the most
Elementary
Term for her I just I can't even imagine
I'm sure that came off to her as late
Of what I do
You know what my area of study is or
Or are you just purposely trying to belittle me
You know
It probably was
Was legitimately the ladder
I mean
I don't know I mean
That was a wild red man with a lot of connections in a in a city General
Really treat women really well
That's what I've noticed
Yeah
He has to attack p
People like that
Because he cannot attack
So
You notice
You know
Impeach her or belittle her or make her seem
Like she does
Have the gravitas
She has
I think is just
At some level
Because
He really cannot lay a finger on
Niall and Scarlett
It just
Too awful
They are
It's weird because I think on some level the the attempted impeaching the
Psychiatrist and therapist
I don't
Thank a tits
Really easy to see that
If you're the jury and not see that as
Being an attack on the
The airlift experience.com Scarlett tell you their therapy
Best bet they are lying to you the things that they have told
The therapist right
You know that because they were not I think what he was relying on is that they were beat that they would be much
Older and more clinicals and they actually were
Yeah I think that's right
Especially the therapist
I mean that was you know I mean he was
Mr. Crouch was
Literally
Starting to cry and he you know he was
Obviously very much feeling their pain
And soda
Come after him as if he would have been this sort of like
Great clinician
That's just not who I have seen in my patients many different desires they have
If you would have been someone like that
A great strategy
Because
The man himself was so sympathetic
And because he had
You know you was just sort of integral
What part of
The community
Around Newtown
And he had worked
With First Responders and he was
He had very much
The tragedy and the aftermath
He was not
The kind of basic you know
Hired Gun
Start at all
That was one of the big things that backfired on the defense lawyer was when he was trying to Almost Say
Hey like
Because you're part of the community
You are so biased in their favor you could never be an impartial Witness
And instead of like
Saying instead of successfully getting the jury to be like this guy's biased
The jury was like
Yeah fukin right man
God
Yeah no yeah I mean
It would be impossible I think to be
Well not impossible
But I was going to say
Nearly
Impossible
To be in that Community when
Those events happened
And not
Heal an abscess
For everyone
I mean it just
That's kind of party
Being Human
Being right
So
Again that was
I don't know I
I'm sort of
Shaking my head cuz I don't
Really
I mean I can
First and I think he prepared
Four different person
I think I think you're right
But also I would suggest that if some tragedy befell Austin
Alex would not
Feel
Does Superbad agree with Dad on this part of a community
Sentara Leigh make one
Doesn't
Empathy
I don't think Alex would be in the position he's in
Yeah it's probably true
Well we should probably
Before too long
But I wanted to just say I guess and I'm sure you're on the same
Same page
With this tree has some thoughts on the matter of
Making sure that this all stays squarely focused
On what this is actually about as opposed to
You know special 100% specially as we go into tomorrow where in theory Alex is going to be there in
Who knows what could happen circus if the clown show we're all in there that there is no danger of that
I I know that you're someone who deeply appreciates what
Niall and Scarlett have gone through as well as
We know many other parents and
Community and family members
What are your thoughts about that new if you have any
Anything you want to say on that
I mean that is there was
Sort of like you know
In the courtroom when
Became apparent that
You know
Quite likely
Jones will testify although I
I still
But I think the whole thing of
It is super unfortunate when it comes to the families because
It's going to be super traumatic for them to
Sort of share that day and share that
You know
The the sort of
The same space
Space with him
I'm sure they'll do everything they can to to insulate them from
Bob in the same
In place while he's
Testifying or what have you
But I couldn't agree with you
Seymour
The sort of
Proceeding that is
Udo has lots of aspects
Stericycle the legal part
Intellectual part of it the
A sort of you no competition of it
And all of that and I think in in covering that and in
And thinking about it and being part of it and being immersed in it
It's
Easy to forget
That this
About
The parents
Of a child who is murdered in Cold Blood
After saving the lives
Nine of his classmates
End
Then his parents
You know as we sat at the top you know what having
Dot-dot
Story to cling to and having
Just this
You know
Thousands of people
Share that narrative
For them by
Saying it didn't happen
You can intellectually know how
Nuts
But at the same time and and how and how ridiculous
And how it how it should be a non-factor
Right
But it is as though
Psychologist
Testified today it is
You know no-one like
Steel
Miss apprehended even on a minor
And to have somebody
Take that
That
Precious
You know narrative ends and you know everything
That you're
Child was away from you
I mean that's
That's really what this is
Is about
And it's also about the broader thing and that's that the families are doing this
Not because they even expect
Any kind of
Yeah monetary recompense from this
Really as and I know this
Talking with them
4 years
For my book
They're trying to send a message they really are trying to
Say
Is this
Can happen to us
This could happen to your
Community shooting although God knows that
But this idea that Miss
Information and disinformation and the scrambling of
You know everything that we hold
It comes to
Establishing truth
And relying on facts
Could come for you in your community it could happen to your family
And that's really the
Like
Blaring
Red
Signal that they are trying to send
People
This is
A problem
If you didn't notice it around us maybe you noticed it around January 6th
Maybe you saw it around Coronavirus
These are all the
Same phenomena is and they're really trying
To raise awareness
And we should be thanking
Because
Of all the people who should be
Be spared having to
You know habit
An additional burden of
Standing Force
Thing in America it should be discreet
Families
And here they are
Dinos
This is
You know pay attention
Thank them for that
Definitely mbb just your mentioning
Like the
Re-traumatizing of being in the room when Alex
May or may not testify absolute I couldn't even believe the Poise of them being there when Alex
It was just sitting
Yeah
Yeah yeah
You know
Be in the presence
Someone who has
Abused
You or
You do or that you
Thought within the past or that
Yo a person who
Stromedy
Right
It kind of shaky and nervous
And you know
It's really
Scary and I I actually do think you know I hearing
The two
The psychiatrist in the end there
Their therapist say that today
They're scared
I believe that
Yeah absolutely
It's it's
It's
Because it's
Heaped on top of what happened to them everything that they
You everything was
Torn out from under them they lost all sense
Control and now
Their child they lost
You know
Your whole world is thrown off
Access
And now you know
Control even over
Story of how he died and
And his heroism in his last moments
I mean that's
Understandable
Yeah and to even add on to that you have the added
Sort of
I don't know the unfortunate thing on top of it that it is it Alex's now
Trying to control The Narrative of their involvement in this suit
Yep you know lexulous
There's even almost a metaphysics going on him
What
Turn out ironically whatever Mark was like
Okay
If you say that they're adding to their own pain
Guess who's at fault for that
It's you you just added that we are now included in the charge
What is funny Park
Mark there's no more Mark moment than being like
Find man
See if I'm pulling out of steel chair
Billion middle fingers after that one
Well it's it's amazing cuz
You would think like okay
The Lost
That's additionally traumatizing actually not it would have
This happened is this
4 years
Stonewalling and
Infighting and
Tooth & Nail
On the park
Alex
So
That's the
The traumatic thing is
The four years of
Trying to drag this out
Trying to use
In the book you know
All of that
Does he have a right to
Venom cell
Siri does
That's not exactly
You do that
It wasn't
A fair fight
From the beginning so that
Turn around app
After four years of
Extending this
And then
Well you know I'll be healed if you didn't sue me
Is sort of the Hide
Cynicism
Yep and we would be
Foolish to expect anything better I don't know if there's a better way to end it
That's perfect
Well live thank you so much for joining us again it was great it was great to see you and I'm sure I'll see you again at the core
Courthouse but also great to chat
And thank you very much for for doing your best to represent
The families instead of just
The trial will stay in the
You get to do it for professional people who actually can matter so
Thank you
I'm so happy
To talk with you but also just
You know your knowledge that you have Alex will be nice to us we don't handle it well
Sound is naked in my security blanket Sports Mix
How many others
You as well
That's very sweet
Alright well we will talk again soon
But until then
Emilio at later on PCH Clark and Dale run
I forgot I did not run this exactly I'm out of nickname
Holding
Alex