I have great respect for its knowledge by knowledge I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
MoneyGram
Facebook.com
Saline from afar and talk a little bit about
Alex Jones
Zen hotel room
When did we are Dan Jordan
What's up
Vibrate Spotify
Is to fold the first is that we are heading back to Chicago
Without without giving too much away in terms of dachshund our location
Do not tell all that much the
Service not good
Is a lot of noise from
The building next to us
I've been multiple false alarm fire alarm
Yeah I miss my cat and I want to go home I want to see how my potato plants are coming along
Half the plugs in my room when I got there and I bet $5,000 they're going to try and
Charge me for it yeah so we've been here and we've experienced a lot of the trial and we've seen
Things being in the room
And what have you
And we figured that
Tomorrow being a travel day
Would be the most economical thing for us to do in terms of being able to
I'll be back and respond to some of the results of the trial
Supposed to staying like
Another
Week
Yeah I was out of control
Yeah God knows if we start thinking hey we're going to be just stick it out the trial of infowar
Like
Maybe
The NFL just deliberate 45 minutes and then we'll be fine
You don't really know and so I am
Excited to go home be able to sleep
Vodka.
But just with a cat on me and that'll be great
But it's been nice and I appreciate the
The kindness of
Evokes
You're outside of the hotel on this bright spot is
DJ Marky
I was working on a Cantina Theme remix
And I'm like and where it's going man that whenever two theme remix of her theme song
I need it now dad
I'm going to lose my mind
I'm here let alone
Going forward
That's true if you like it
Much like the Caravan of the project had a theme of its theme song but it's like
Vibe of its own this trip has really been Cantina thieves
Is it is the medically appropriate
The house serious
Alex is taking the
Through every talk about that a little bit today but
My bright spot is today
My bright spot was
Also the dark spot and just maybe the most powerful
Miss Lewis
Looked Alex in the f****** I and Alex
Blanched
You know
True
Yeah I wish I could use better words but really
Really
That was that was powerful
Recording this on Tuesday and today was
I think fair to described as the
Jonathan Moore a heavy day of
Testimony that we heard
You had Neil Hansel and and Scarlett Lewis take
The stand
And Alex was not there during meals testimony
And I think that that was
I mean first of all just
The passive active disrespect
Maybe someone
But he did show up
For the middle
Of scarlet
Testimony
Thank ya yeah and
Her poise
In being able to
Say things like
Sort of blood Lee and correctly
Text was
I don't know I don't know I don't know how you do that
I really don't I really don't
I really really really really really really don't and I
Could not admire her more enough
Well I think that I mean I've looked at Alex in the face before
I think that you see the eyes of a of a fish when you look at him
Like I don't think that like
I feel like if you're expecting to have some sort of an emotional impact when you're saying emotionally impactful words yeah
It's
Kind of a
If it's a chore that will not be completed
At some
Points in time
The way he looks out and his eyes kind of going opposite directions I halfway think his tongue is going to
Shootout in like get a bug off of one of them
And then and then you're like I caught that
Your lizard
Swear
But yeah I am so just be able to like
Power through that
Is
Admirable
It's all talk a little bit about that and then be going over Alex's show from today as well
August 2nd
2022 he was doing while the trial was
Testify
I feel like
There's not a whole lot more
To say then
The two of them
Gave
Quite powerful testimony moving
There was some tears in the courtroom and what have you
Are you did
I tried not to look at you
You were fine but gavi
I don't I don't have a whole lot to analyze
Of that other than to say was
Quite a thing to behold
The mood in the courtroom was quite
Serious true
And then Alex showed up and things are a little bit less serious
It is kind of crazy
To let me know and I told you if you know when we were walking
To the court I was like
Today is going to be the weirdest juxtaposition that may Everett
Yeah
And God damn it if it didn't live up to
Yeah yeah just emotionally difficult and
Sort of optimistic even within the darkness
Kind of conversation about
But people who've gone through hell and
Then
You know we're coming back from lunch
Standing outside
The the courthouse
7 maybe now reporters
Larry 7
Do lakeover Infowars fans except for Rob dues mom I think
It might have been his mom's old lady who said that she was filming for Rob to and then you told her not to use
Is the iPhone cuz it has too many chemtrails
Which is a mistake you should have said 5G
Like all I've got is Chemtrails that was my only polci that's has you marked you as a prankster and she did not take your warning screen
No I know but yeah it's
It was it was bizarre cuz you know Alex shows up and he's like the Democrats are jamming me up
It was the
Great
Alex got2b stand
Did a little bit of
Direct
Questioning who you love so much
And I don't know I think
By the end of the day
The judge was saying that Alex had lied under oath twice
Right numbers low for I think you missed a few things
Some things you could be understood to have me
Better like to pick up on this like Alex saying that he left
Rockwall because there's just too much prime
Yeah or the cops were going to kill him because he uncovered a drug ring that's within the police department
Euro boy
So they do their stuff like that but it was just kind of like
Directed story about why you're so great
And your your various accomplishments in the field of
Roguish journalism
It was it was as if like
Imagine you had never learned
And in fact never learned language at all
You were born in a cave
You lived in a cave
You are 45 years old when you walked into this trial
The moment you saw Alex start talking you would immediately understand the definition of the word bloviate
And it would just pop into your head and that would be the only word you can speak
You be like
Baby
That's what it is that's what it was
Yeah it was covid-19
Is the epitome
By the end of the day the day
With
The judge
Dismissing the jury
Ban Mark raising some important questions about things that Alex had said
Alex
Said that you was bankrupt
On the sand can't do that which is directly against the orders of the judge
Concerns was that his lawyer led him to that
That that statement more or less he did one hundred percent absolutely on purpose
Exactly also
And then also Alex brought up
Lawyer had brought up in in
In terms of the line of questioning
The notion that he is not
Guilty of the things that you
How many times
I am going to observe
In a trial about damages
And attempt to prove
Wild it is wild
So we ended on a bit I mean do you know if this were a
The TV show there's a bit of a cliffhanger
Aspect to it that is like serious problems are brought up with how things are going
Direct examination isn't done so that'll still pick up tomorrow or a sauce
And so
I think I speak for you as well and that like
There was an exhausting
Today I think
Obviously for other people more than us
But it would be very difficult to be in that room
Experience
All that happened to not just be like
I mean
I don't even know if I can
Can do it again like straight-up like when he when he said the reason that he left Rockwell was because
There was too much crime
Like I mean I got to work I got to work again from the from the bailiff for making too many faces or whatever it is
You warned me to I know cuz you I think it I think Alex said
No I didn't wear you I said this is the first time you're going to have to try not to laugh you said you have to leave
Oh no that was what you will because Alex said that the goal of talk show host
Is to make the most right prediction the moment he said
He was trying to here's what he described
He described it as talk show host
You become
More popular it becomes a game between all of the pop talk show host like a power rankings
Skip the most
Predictions right
Everyday that is measured and then
You're like in the lead or not Nielsen ratings
I almost lost my s*** laughing 100
Want to do the news much anymore I do more of a philosophy show I'll God more of a self-help.
I almost wanted to yell reset War
It's just we can't be in there
From being in a position where like
All right this very serious Alex's understand
I respect the process
I respect what's going on I respect plaintiff soon
You know to
Not be able to laugh at him is very hard
And I'm not immune to that
Much as people think
I have ice water in my veins in human icewater boys I apparently crypto
Holding in ice water in your veins can't not laugh at Alex talking about the prediction hierarchy
Irene
Listen
It took
A lot
It took a lot then it took a shity hotel
It took a week
Being in a terrible state
It took us going to a courtroom
4 hours
It took us
Experiencing some of the most devastating
Personal stories let alone like testimony in a court but just
If somebody was
Telling me the story
It would be devastating for you to eventually come all the way over to my side and say I
Have to laugh I survived myself
Nation that I think a lot of people would have reached
Much sooner that is like I just want to be around this guy in the same room as him
Easier to discuss this with a slight amount of distance
And I'm going to reclaim my space
My proximity to a very beloved one eyed cat
Yes
Indeed did on a bit of a sour note
You can see the video on the Law & crime
Website of us
Leaving the courtroom three seconds of the video that everyone is sharing shows you and I walk
Walking out of the courtroom pretty like meaningfully 15 seconds before it happened and we were like
Like we're out of I was I was on a like
I want to pass out I want to take a nap totally killing me
Also Justina can't Vape in the courtroom right and we
Mingle let's say
And to think
Thank lucky stars
Because there's a little bit of another fight
Oh my God
You just
Yeah you know in your heart of hearts
It's going to happen
You know it's going to happen
We've studied this man for how long
What world would we believe that this wouldn't happen right it's some kind of b*******
Same time I was sitting in there today going like
Well you know
We're in a quart
I don't know why I think there's a did I don't know why I would think that Alex
What's the difference
Between
Sitting on a
Witness stand and
Sitting behind
Yeah not be a difference which is scary
It's happening was the judge that left the room and
Miss Lewis Scarlet had handed Alex a water
I'm not sure exactly what predicated that he'd been coughing the entire testimony
Quite aggressively
Complaining about having a torn larynx that sometimes flares up and that he will be
Better in a moment.
Definitely did not come off.
No it was important
For him to listen and not talk
Throat was so find it made a remarkable job before he went outside
Nightingale did people's cameras listen
Let me give you his bottle of water I you need
Yeah it go well Alex
Started saying
They have been manipulated and chilling
Fake videos and edited videos and
Bunny went for a handshake with her and then Mister hats
And that was when the lawyers are like we're not doing this
And
Alex started to get mad about edited videos
Again and it was
Disgraceful
Yep and shity
So that was kind of weird things left off
Tell Alex
Went outside the courtroom
And there were some cameras
And here I'm going
To play a bit of video
You came from video
Alex's comments
About what happened
At the end of the day
Outside the courtroom pologize is he admits that he was wrong he says that he shouldn't have said about
The Fitbit right
Just off
Politely all closed
That have been caught
Claiming
Did I attack Scarlett Lewis
Today on here when I did not I said I think he's
A good person
The real person
Nope
Depart off where I
I said I believe
Real
I believe
Charlotte Lewis
He's a little bit
Flow
I said they're giving on Edith
What
Why are you guys
What is it
Why are you talkin to me during trial
I can't talk to you
I know but the point is is that
It doesn't matter of the judges
We're going to talk about it
From the court of appeal
This
Being developed
I know you won't cover
And his ex-wife
Wonderful lady
Weider book all of it
Don't
And that's why people
Corporate media
You will be
Ipledge
You only spent we're doing
Episode
Is
It's an interesting question cuz that's not
True at all not even a little bit
Interesting to wonder if that is legitimately how Alex
Experience The Exchange
Or if it's
It's just
Like if it like is a delusion or is it malice
And why I watch the video cord
Because I had that very same question of like
There's no way
You know
And what are you
What I think
And and you know I mean
Obviously we're we're speculating so I would not be called as an expert in
But it's so
Watching it I truly believe that Alex
When he went up to the
At first
To apologize
Believe
That what he was going to do
Was it
Expressed genuine remorse to them
And then
Because
He couldn't do it the way
He wanted
Wrightwood that included the also I'm right
Exactly
When Mark and and Company
Got in the way
He did what he did he did what he does
You know and then it becomes
They were trying to hug me or love me they're my fans now
Thanks but the lawyers won't let him say it
Manipulated like you wow
So
This brings us to our central question
And to do with
If the tape
But Alex is referring
Yes
During Mr hasland testimony
Alex was on air
Can you say it too
Batshit
Everything but also master has one in particular
Yes and
So during the break
The clip of this was
Cured by the plaintiffs team
And
It was played
In court
Oh yeah and Alex then
Use that is kind of a hint
For him to make a they're playing edited videos because it doesn't show the part Ray
Said I'm sorry
Elvis
Doing what we do as a show
I thought
Let's look at the totality of this
There's no reason to
Alex didn't say anything in his testimony today that is worth
Discussing really doesn't have time to listen to the full video but do you know who does
Court of public opinion
So where is start here where Alex starts on the 2nd
Boy he's whiny
On this line Tuesday worldwide transmission I have a torn Larry I have a
Washington Post headlines
Where they say
Of the four
Sandy Hook trials they have lined up there now started
To shut us down
MSNBC
The goal is to set this pattern with Alex Jones
And then go after every
Body
Play Fox News
Will get Fox News
They're going to come for everybody
I'm sure that Alex doesn't have tons of articles that say this antiques
Pads and not some revelation of a grand conspiracy to shut up the media
Also is anyone at Fox rcnn or those you did what Alex did I think they should be punished just the same
It's so weird that Alex has so many strong feelings about this but he doesn't seem to remember that like
Seth Rich's parents sued Fox News and settled for an undisclosed amount
Warehouse CNN settles lawsuit with Nick Sandman the
Covington Catholic kid back in 2020
He doesn't bring up any of this stuff because
He doesn't give a s*** about the actual principal of people suing media entities
And how that happens
From time to time but it doesn't lead to a complete end of the first amendment AT&T ready
And the devil walking Among Us
Snow it leads to CNN's lawyers talking to other lawyers and being like listen we know we f***** up here
Let's figure out a reasonable amount of money we're we're fine and you guys are taking care of we all get to go home
Call Alex cares about is comically exaggerating his own persecution because that intern inflates his
Sense of heroism
Everyone so against him and he's up against such great odds and yet he fights on and it's just a breathtaking active him a
Imaginary bravery
You know that's
That's all gay
Imaginary is the
The perfect word
Yep
It doesn't get more cowardly than literally everything he's done today
No doubt No Doubt
Maybe rightfully they give Don Quixote a tough time
For the windmills
Fighting all those windmill nights
Sure
Alex does a similar thing
But with strawberries
Right that's how you protect his own cowardice and makes it seem like heroism
And here's a here's a big one
Probably sit there and show
The jury's there
How guilty I am
Not if I'm guilty or innocent
Juries all these emails and all these videos
While the judge tells him everyday twice a day
Remember this man's guilty
Riverside how guilty he is
Third-world dictatorship
This person is guilty
I think they do
You're also the judge
Instruct the jury not to bother with the question of Alex's guilt or innocence because there's a damaged
Just trial
Get every right to participate the initial trial where he could have mounted
The defense of the judge absolutely could not have said that kind of thing
But he chose not to participate
He did he would
Just lose faster
No one's claiming that Alex didn't turn over any
Turn over a bunch of stuff like a hundred plus page professional background check on Lenny Posner that no-one it in
Infowars can explain
Where did this come from no one knows
Alex is creating the strawman but he's being accused of not turning over anything because it's super easy to defeat
All you have to do is show that he turned over something and just like that Alex has proven that the cord is lying about him
He needs the audience to accept his drama and framing devices of the situation because
If his audience sought out any other source of information is entire argument about what's happened with looked
Aesthetically silly
The last thing he wants is for them to understand how much of an active participant he's been in getting himself defaulted
Because it raises so many questions about why would you do that
And the only real conclusion is because you're guilty as s*** right
For someone who talks so much s*** about the Amendments that he doesn't
Understand and cannot read
You know that I was thinking about that idea of like
You should have the right to face your accuser
You know
You should
Sure and sometimes and maybe only maybe this is the only time it's ever happened
But the accuser should have the right to face the Accuser
Do you know what I'm saying
Especially when they're already f*****
So he should have been in there whenever nail is there nail should have been able to look him in the eye and tell him the truth
The same way that
It's active
Claim your space
And be there and run your mouth and say about the b*******
While meals got to listen to you and I'm not pay the same courtesy
Stand respectfully if not
Actual but implied violation of the Bill of Rights
Look I'm no scholar
Mediator I do think another thing
You do want to do I mean I think you should be there to pay respect or at least give the appearance of respect for that
I think you shouldn't do is Maybe
Talk rampant s*** about the judge
Junior case
Tell the jury
This person is guilty
But she says up there
Universal
Demonic
Monica Lee possessed
The judge
Lawyers
It's surreal to be around
And it makes you feel sorry for them because these people are committed to a cult ideology of the new
Never going to stop
They're getting rid of all the
Freedom border
Everywhere
They're just annihilate the social contract
They are destroying our country by Design they have been turned
Day I mean
The general crazed Mob of the left
I thought you were talking about the
Judge he specifically was talking about the judge so now it's the Mob of the left
Okay alright alright correctly what we're trying to say is that
Bet if I said
Dan you're a giant piece of s*** that I hope gets light lit on fire and the damn that I'm talking about
Is everybody and you wouldn't at all think that perhaps I was talking about you
You would know that I was talking about everybody
Also
I have not checked up with my man gygax
Is a dork Goblin
Vet in the Monster Magnet I don't believe so
I do not wish it
Believe you can be
I don't even know if you can be a mixed-race torklaw but I think there's two or
Orcs
Interesting interesting evolutionary thing like if you're too far away on the genetic change you can
If that's the case then I would say that Alex needs to get right with this and start calling people like
Does George's up there like a beholder
There's charges like a half elf dwarf meaning
Monster the plaintiff attorney is a gelatinous cube
What's the what's the name of the ones that are devils in the monster manual guide
So Alex has decided he's going to do the first hour
Event he's heading to court baby smart
Are the judges
Achoo
Testified today in the show trial
What the judge again this morning said cuz I've got the
Twitter alerts
To the jury it's a decided issue he is guilty remember that
He's guilty
You just decide when you give him 150 million
Because he questioned the shooting or 59
A b a damages
Hearing
I still do not understand what you are trying to explain to me Dan I've been in court
7 days
Or at least I haven't been in court but I've watched
Trial for 7 full days
A damages trial
And I have not
Scene
Full
Acknowledgements from tomorrow since I have lost the trial already
I mean it's a it's a it's an active mass gaslighting of his body
There is just an attempt
To pretend you don't understand
The situation because
If the audience did understand the situation
Better say it raises questions
And they are questions that Alex can only answer by
Well I'm stupid
Or I torpedoed my own ability to defend myself knowing
That I would be in
Incompetent and unable to defend myself right given the opportunity and that would be
More humiliating than situation we're in now where I can just gas like the s*** out of you all
Ariel still give me money
So I think that
I understand why you taking this approach
Basically Aldi
Please God
I mean
What's so ironic about it
Is that essentially what he's done is he's hired a
I mean in his
World
A high-power
Democrat lawyer appointed by Eric Holder
Stonewall a trial and a
I guess foursome mistrial in order to delay even longer
So we can just keep up
Well it's fun that you know you have a
Setting Court
You have a high-powered Democratic lawyer who was hired by Eric Holder who we should also say is a man of
Trees of the highest order exactly.
And being involved with Obama and all this stuff that probably
Alex should examine that also you got this high-powered Democratic lawyer hired by Eric Holder who's fight
Leaving the globalist for Alex what what's going on here can you imagine if Mark
Tomorrow just looks at him and he's like okay you say it's the Democratic party to set out to get you
You know your lawyer was appointed by Eric Holder right
I would ease into that just make you think about Eric Holder
Blindsided
That would be amazing
So Alex
Sees himself in a particular way
In this trial
In the circumstances that he find some
Themself in
And
Naturally there
From a movie
This is beyond the movie Gladiator where they tie up
Gladiator in Elkhart
Coliseum Florida
Good explanation of that movie
Where is Debbie
15 *
Lion on top your head biting you
And then they come out
Find HBO camera with their Almighty
Sandy Hook
This man made hundreds of millions of this man tortured
10 years
And then finally
They testify
And their psychologist testified
Add
Has one and his ex-wife
Bill and Scarlett didn't need to be aware of Alex himself to experience the effects
His actions
Even if Alex were portraying the situation honestly what he saying doesn't in any way invalidate their position
This is another strong man because Alex can't really address the case on its merits
If he did he would have to reveal that he isn't the gladiator who was stabbed to soften them up for the big Showdown
But he would win easily otherwise
It's more similar to a gladiator who is politely asked to show up for their their Showdown for
Years
Decided to not show up to
H & H ranting publicly about how he was going to win
Not fight
He never shows up for the fight but he's legally obligated to be in it so
He's made to appear in front of a tribunal little decide what he's going to be fined for not doing this fight
And the whole time he's just whining about how he was never given a fair shot it is Big Show dad to begin with
It's a prosthetic kind of gladiator that I don't think would make a good movie
I mean
Argument directly
Which is absurd
Is essentially like okay
Say I'm the strongest man in the world and I can throw a javelin from Texas to Connecticut
If I hit somebody
In the leg
And they don't know it's me
How is it my fault
There's a million ways you could formulate a rebuttal to that stupid logic that he's using
The javelin
I mean it's it's evocative
Is an image of ABC
So here we go Alex getting getting shity
The media Brockton the clip of Owen
Talking about
Has one on
Megyn Kelly
To make him mad and assuming
Bouncing on quartz
It's all these lawyers all these Democrats always offered as going out to the families
Another name for that
Investigated right now
But
It's just insane
Yes
Alex is attempting to deprive mr. heslin of having any agents
See here
The goal is to make sure the audience accepts the idea that the lawsuit isn't something that's inorganic decision has Lynnwood
I eat
It's something that was pink
He's being put up to buy the media these lawyers
Alex is doing this in order to appear like less of a monster because it's easy to play like you're the good guy Wendy
You yell at a nefarious lawyer plot than it is when you take a guy whose son was murdered and you already lied about him a bun
You may notice
That Alex is going a little bit harder towards
Discrediting needle and there's a reason for that Alex knows that is far as the
Ariel he's produced
He's not said Scarlett's name on air
His other legal complaints are diff
Do you have a defamation case from Neil but and intentional infliction of emotional distress case
From Scarlet
Alex knows
That the one where you said the guys name is more of a clear-cut case where
F***** up
So being able to assassinate this character and insist that he wouldn't even sued if it wasn't under the sway of some
Globalist lawyer conspiracy against Alex
Is him a tempting
To cover up the more serious of his f******
While giving lip service
Do the other one that he feels as less
And that he's not saying Scarlett's name
And is saying meals
Or at least is attacking Neil and not Scarlett
Kind of Morris
Suggest that this is a man who knows that
I've already defame this m*********** haha it's probably a good idea to leave it at intentional damage
Judges on the other person
So I don't add defamation to her name
Maybe it may be that this is the easiest
What's this person I can punch them
Activating him more now I will say that the strategy
A bad strategy
At least Alex doesn't continue to call the judge of God
Judge Goblin here in Austin
Wow I would have really not.
Ashley finally got to see a real goblin
Oh my God
I have some fun
Goblin
Wow that's why I'm so sweet on her but the point is
Last Friday
Go forward
Went back on Monday morning
No matter what you doing
Because this is all
A giant
Exercise
Our freedom
Go after conservatives and populist and Patriots and the judge said
I also is bankruptcy has no bearing on this case
So you know I've been trying to Aunt my brazenness up about his
Hi as I can possibly put it
Yeah
I got nothing on that
It's hard but you got nothing on that I just don't I mean that's that's
What is that you also don't have people enabling you
You have people like me who are like 8 maybe should come down with this ship and I'm grateful for that
Because I'm not calling the judge of goblet right now years of people just not telling you to shut up I'm a zombie
Like that
Crazy
So yeah it's all just about getting these conservative the Nationalist
Alex's whole thing is just part of a larger pattern
And somebody who's in that pattern
Is Alex's new friend
Former mortal enemy
Steve Bannon
How tall are you
And now they're coming with fully weaponize courts
Amanda DC criminal trial
Smart
Dog crazy they're going for breakfast
Yeah those Bandits choice
Yeah I think I mean
After watching
Defenses lawyer today
Question
I mean
Again
Brazenness on a scale that I can't comprehend
Choose not to defend himself
Or do any of that
Rodger
Pictures of Mount no defense
Ensign his case
Sprite
They're not being deprived of their right they're choosing to wave it
So they can pretend to be victims later and so they cannot
Hurt their own case further by victimizing the victims that they are victims
We will see that's right that's right it could come back to to really help him out in that
So Alex does talk about some news
Sure
I'm sure everybody's interested in
Monkeypox
Well
So here we go
Bounce mask
Listeria
Either way
And beating the drum
Lee behavioral psychology
Incrementally say okay
Tell masks indoors again
Okay now only certain businesses are essential
Okay now
New California governor Gavin Newsom declares
Monkeypox a state of emergency
Illinois
Monkeypox
Back on the balcony
And the dog
And he's announcing
All the same stuff
Right before
Lockdowns you've already witnessed
Alex has interpreted this headline
Biden's covid sequel about being like monkeypox is the sequel to covid
But it's actually getting a rebound case of covid-19 to go back into isolation
The way Alex is reporting this headline the way he's using it
Is this made up
He's taking this headline and then just
Is making up and lying about what the article is about because
He's a lazy liar just makes things up all the time
The word monkeypox doesn't even appear in that article I mean also really I think having a double case of covid like
Like it's the
Best thing for him to riff off of right
Like vitamin has a rebound case of covid
Maybe it's out of
Control even the Democrat establishment doesn't have control over the like you could
Spin-off of that for a long time if you weren't distracted by some
Some other kind of thing those taking up all of your attention even if you have his full attention there you still wouldn't notice of his about monkey
U-Box a lazy liar
I would like him to say
Who is this the Charles Barkley of covid
The round mound of covid
Anyway Alex talking about monkeypox
Trunk
Of course he's bought in quite heavily into the right wing
And the very dangerous talking point
Of
Associating the lgbtq folk with monkeypox
India Venza it being something that is
Unique
To the homosexual Community which we all knew was just a matter of time
Yeah and man
He is going weird with it
Keep
Your piehole shut
You're getting a bunch of monkeypox spray in your mouth
Real quick I'm going to pause it for a second
It was pretty gross
Just be warned
Yes
Will be able to legally change their gender
Once a year all my goodness
Sticker on your car handicap
Visor
Red Yuma Manger
Homosexual
Image search
This makes sense
Basil plant
Put a lightbulb on your head
I mean do people have those like
Stickers on their car windows that have like
Dad
Mom
Chill child child child
May I mean maybe I don't know I like Mom I don't think a lot of attention to bumper stickers
The window you know those ones would like that they do what you're talking about
They do not there
Purple
I wouldn't do that
Lightbulb
Surprise getting rid of
Global social credit score
Carmen taxes
Bring in the yellow nothing you'll have nothing
You're about the only perfect
Greener purple
And you can go eat poop in the street
What
I mean just you can don't you believe that's your American Rights
Well
Hold on now
I think there's a
Slight bit of a discussion difference
Between painting your hair a certain color and
Eating poop in the street you know there are a lot of people who bite notice a few distance
I think the way you would discuss those things would be slightly different
MyHealth
Standpoint exist in purple hair colors
You people to wash their hands when they work in a restaurant Freddy Cole I ordered
Hair color
Yeah so I was pretty surprised by this because
Essentially what you have here
Is Alex is taking a
Very
Old
Old homophobic
Kind of
Smeared
Guston characterization
And that is all you eat poop
Combining it with the
Old Testament Passover concept of how we should move through life
Yeah and this is like it is
To the spread of
Monkeypox absolutely these people out in the street with our light bulbs in their head
Poop all I'm saying is that we should go from door-to-door find out who's inside put a mark outside their door
And maybe they have a son tomorrow maybe they don't it's not me
Well whatever you do
Just be aware people are eating poop
I'm not kidding
Now
I'm eating poop and peeing on each other
This is so liberal so trendy
And then the monkey box explodes and it's all our fault
Will have to be lockdown now
The pedo parade in the poop eating will continue and I'm sorry to have to describe
Get me to talkin
Gobbling
Oh really show buddy what are you doing oh my god do you remember the critic
This is the song of my home country why is everybody laughing
Fantastic
Got a joke
What are the greatest
Good show the critic
It stinks
My review of Alex's show
So yeah apparently Alex is taking up the mantle of
Some of the more
Gross
Dangerous
Types of rhetoric
Descending into
Obviously he's been on this like equating lgbtq
Uq folk with pedophilia for quite a while right that's kind of not new ground for him now but somehow
Call the
All of these Pride parades are people eating poop and peeing on each other and they're spreading
Monkeypox
All right I just don't see how this
I mean easy
I use it
Truly possible
I think Alex is trying to find out
Is it too is it possible to go
Too ridiculous
The even
An Ardent infowarrior would go
Listen man
Nobody's eating poop
The pride parade
I did I just
No I just got to say that no
It really isn't I do think that
There are people in his audience that
Would be like yeah that's
What I kind of always thought I can't believe they're eating it always looks so fun with all the candy cuz you know what
It's cuz of the Liberals and let it get out of control
Forget it's cuz of liberal
So we get to the point of this episode where the issue with talking s*** about the plaintiff
Just comes up
Not a good idea
I think that there is an argument to be made that the clip
That they played in court was shorter
I think it was
Now do I think it matters
No
Yeah I think it's worse
When it's longer
So here's the beginning of that
Segmented it into century
3-part
Because otherwise it would be about
6 minutes or so
Ouch but you'll see that each clip ends with where the next one begins
So this is all tore to make sure that we're not getting
Doctored video
Did the people go straight through the thought goes
Bill Haslam
Those people are real
Is the government lie so much
Question
Anomalies I was the first to bring up the anomalies
Literally
And
I thought it was
When I saw some of the stuff on TV just because
Became office show
What you say
He's he's he's a he's a he's a nice man
And
He is
Being manipulated
He slow
Okay
And
Got to be honest
Stupid
Ottoman
Subway
Inflow and others and he's
Makes me feel like an even bigger jerk
And now that I've been around for over a week I'm like okay
So the Clippers they played in court
Did not include the part of the beginning where he says that they're real people
I think it's irrelevant to the larger point
Like how the clip was it was playing
And then the clip ends with just include those last like 5 Seconds
Which I'm really only using there is a hinge to get to
The next segment obviously is
Is that
If I was allowed
To play for the jewelry
That I
Magnanimously admit the people I'm sitting across from nearly
Less than 10 feet away
Are in fact real
Very proud of myself sure and if the jury had seen that
They would have been like
Not only should we award him $1
He's innocent
And
We've hired a second line band we're having a parade
Phillips because you did that I couldn't get it occupants in the feet
So I was wondering
And somebody who was in the courtroom as I didn't see this show live
I didn't see all of it
Probably did
You know express some kind of
Sorry
At some
I mean I mean
Really do you know
Cuz that's the argument that he's making Universe things that are cut off
And so I was like all right I'm going to listen to this
Let's see where it goes
Here's what happens now
I said I get to news
The office
Talk to me
And
Basically
Without even
Watching
The trial
This is what happened
And all the stuff
A fly on the wall
Fascinating
It's just fascinating
How the scammers work
Government who work for the Rothschilds and Rockefellers
The argument that he's laying out is essentially that
Leo and Scarlett but mostly Neil who's writing a mad right they are on for
We've been fooled by these ambulance Chasers
Into doing this lawsuit
Mlr I mean I think that there is there is
An element is this that
Gets dangerously close to the things he's being sued about
Yes there is
Because
In essence you do at the
At the core of the claims about crisis actors it is these are people who are feeling a roll
That is deceitful about what is at the core of
You know there isn't somebody who died according to these theory that they are acting as if they are in order to it
The Second Amendment
In this case
The argument that Alex is putting forward is they don't actually
We care about what I said
They don't actually filled defame
The mental anguish that they're describing isn't anything to it's either not real or does nothing to do with me
Any of this stuff
They are people who have been willfully
Or tricked into acting as if they were rendered to be used by these ambulance Chase
This to me
Seems maybe acronym
Let's talk about
Movie
He's real quick down
Now I want to call.
As as we all know
Every time you have an actor in a movie
All of their dialogue is required to be direct quotes from real life
Otherwise
Every movie would be defamation
So we know that actors
Only tell the truth despite
Being real people
This actor can only tell the truth in this workout lie lie
I understand what Alex is doing
I get
I also think that it's
Maybe the worst idea ever normally in a
Defamation
In trial where you're trying to determine Ennis
Centor guilt
Then at the time
You can
Then say
These people are only out for money
Because if they're only out for money
Then maybe I'm innocent of the charge
Now here's the twist what's the twist
0 landforms
These people are Patxi's that are being used
As Pawn
In Alex's the game against Alex can I hear the original conspiracy theory again
It was that these people
We're being used as Pawns
Any attack on the second
Alright I balance
Until they were being so they're suing him for saying that they're what very least
Did this attempt
Depriving
Neelix Scarlet of the agency that with which they're using to sue him
Trying to deter
Define
The criticism is pretty
And I think
At bottom
At minimum
Yeah what you are doing is calling in
The question the experiences of a testimony that they have given in the trial
Painting them as
People who is with Scarlett is he saying that she's really smart
And nice you painting
Neil is a dupe
Yeah who's been suckered into going along with this which raises the question
What are you actually saying about star that this Tuesday willing
Person who knows what she's doing and going along with them
This
Sucks and doesn't
It's not better longer
Nope but
The appearance that Alex can get out of insisting that it's better if it's longer
It's basically the exact same game that he plays with all of his clips
You need to watch the whole show
Second of stop it it's it's
It's really not better well if that's your only excuse to just about anytime anybody ever plays a clip
Then it's
Glaring that because we play the entire clips
He does not talk
That is suspicious
Yeah you were suspicious that Alex wasn't actually going to
Forgive an apology
In these in this
When you bring up what I was suspicious about
I'm interested to see where this goes
What
The world
There's a
The sabotage our nation
And I'll bring it down
And so I can really see how the sauce
Getting made
Give my asking questions about public events hurt these people's feelings I'm sorry
And the most important point is this
Knowingly promote Sandy Hook questions
And they love
Single
Second
This stuff
They are just living off Sandy Hook
Look alive
Bring it to me
Until the point of
And there's some other lawyers there
Adam Lanza
They think I did it
And one of these lawyers that's a well-known lawyer
Who's Adam Lanza
This is y'all on Friday
I'm sorry that your lawyer friend is dumb
But that doesn't mean anything
Does your lawyer think you did it does your lawyer friend take you did it I mean
Alex Jones must have been the shooter I've if I understand correctly it walks free
Out in the world having killed all of these school children and teachers
What could his lawyer friend possibly think
If his lawyer friend being a lawyer
Would have to know that he's already been
Found guilty
What is the lawyer think if he's like
Never heard of this and Adam Lanza cash but I know you're guilty of this trial I figured this person doesn't
So that is the apology that Alex was so insistent that the plaintiffs attorneys didn't include in the clip and therefore we
We're trying to mislead the jury with an edited video
This was the basis of the fight that Alex in the plaintiff's team got into at the end of the day and what Alex was talking
Think about outside it's a lotus
This isn't an apology
This is a statement disguised as an apology
In order to accept this apology you need to accept Alex's framing of what he's apologizing for and that
It's not based in reality
He's not apologizing for what he actually did
He's apologizing
Questioning he did of anomalies around Sandy Hook hurt them
That's not a real apology in anyway and I'm entirely certain that the jury would be able to
I understand that could easily put that in its proper context
You wouldn't want to play this whole clip though because it's a long it's stupid and it really
Mostly is just Alex whining to his listeners but everyone so mean to him
This falls back on the fundamental defense Alex seems to have to offer which boils down to
I did the thing you want
Me too. Just a little bit after that clip ended
He's essentially appealing to the unknown
The part of the knowledgebase that isn't available in order to undermine the premise of the plaintiffs
It's pretty dumb
But it's kind of how information Works in his world and it's kind of like
I mean I hate to
They'll fall back on this event but
Basically what killed
I mean
Sometimes
When I listen to the
The consist
Threads
If there was a pole you know
You know that whole thing
Like if we got rid of all politics
Text Em we're just like asking
People straight up
Do you think
If I hurt you
Then I'm sorry
Is an apology
I think we will be able to see 100% exactly where the far-right
Haha cuz that's the one thing that I hear from that nobody says
I'm sorry I'm sorry I hurt you
I realize the damage that I've done
I'm going to seek to correct it and then no longer continue the behavior
How many gigs is the most
Generous perspective on the if I hurt you
I'm sorry thing
Sure that is fine
If it's a first step
Like if it's a I don't understand if I hurt you
Now let's engage in a process where I understand better
How I hurt you
No. Once I what is what that apology wants to appear.
People want to look at and they want to see
They want to hear you say the words sorry and then forget all the rest
Yeah it's disgraceful and
It's only made worse
By where we all know where this is going
Here's the end of the stereo
Who is Adam Lanza we all just looked at him
Who's Adam Lanza
You don't think
Put on me and made me a
Money off of it
This is the beta test
And this is what they're doing
Imma stop ranting
I need to hit the energy news
Stop going on with loveseat
I'll give you my take on that
Got so much more and we're going to have
Studio
Also help blisters understand that
Infowars really is fighting for his life
But will be able to stay on the air
Indefinitely
If you will just continue to support but we need folks
Want to know what the globalist
Infowarsstore.com right now
Appeal a plug
Give me money
Yep
I guess all of that
Italics w
All of that to be played in court I don't think it helps
I think I make some Oak way worse
Yeah it's the
Uncertainty of what else is there at Alex can play with that unformed space
That he can mold into being whatever he wants it to be
And it's an abusive tactic it's really it's cuz he knows what he said
He knows
Babe
There isn't things that we're completely Miss
By the end of the video that was played in court
It's a
Antabuse
You know it is it is one of those things where I keep thinking about this
During the trial specially while listening to
To the full clip
Casino
If we were in the jury
You and I
Catch
All of the Liza
Right really wanted you know what it why we shouldn't be absolutely
Play but my point is
If I were in the jury and I was the lawyer for me in the jury
Then I would play that whole clip and I would be like
Here's where he goes into that sales sales pitch
Do you remember on the stand
Whenever he's suddenly started telling you about
Ales for some reason
Play let it happen earlier today
That's the kind of thing that you could pull in there but
If you were to play an entire 6-minute clip of Alice
To a regular human people jury
How is
Is it possible for you to get them to like your eyes are glazed over that you be like I genuinely don't know what he just said I don't
No
Good skipping around there's so many things he's saying I said like
The only thing I think of is that
The juror who put his Pad down
You know like it's bad
It's 102 make sense
That's a moment that a live forever you know
Yep
Why you promised talk about Pelosi
True
Well it's
It's kind of hard for Alex to talk about right
Cuz
Well you'll see
Pelosi in Taiwan
Call Melo
And a woman is a total joke
And roll
What
Explain that
Obviously
She's doing
Probably
More money
He directly aligned
Alright Alright you're just lazy somebody
Nancy Pelosi is a decades-long communist agent working for China but also she's going to Taiwan
Yes and this is not something the China likes
So we have to make sense of this until it is is it.
Stunt because Biden's going to step down and something's going to happen to Kamala Harris
And then Pelosi zombie president be able to help China Crush Taiwan I guess
I I mean
It's all the
Stunts in order to rationalize her Ascent to power
So she could be an even better
Agent for communist China
It makes sense
You know
When you put it that way
I really can't argue
You don't want to know point
Between video
It is about 2
To Dismount and it makes a bad prediction and that is that he's going to do is.
Oh that's true the talk show right now his prediction is that he's going to do his whole show tomorrow
He is not know he's going to be in court
For the full show tomorrow
I'm sorry
4 months in Connecticut
That's why we do the bankruptcy
Because work
Don't have the money
To do three trials at once
Because I've got to be on here we don't bring the funds in
I'm almost resigned all of this because
Stop
Credibility is exploding
But just as an instinctive level
Enjoyed talking to you everyday I enjoyed being here I love the crew
Give up I won't give up
It's probably going to be a nuclear war
Okay
Call Josh
Trouble
Chills right now
Just real quick
When Alex is receiving $8000000 in Bitcoin
Are we about to have a nuclear war
When Alex is about to lose all of it everything
And he's getting chills talking about
Yep yep
So
I mean I don't know go f****** prepare your family newsletter
You dick
Subset that works old people hard copy that's a good point he's got to get a printing press
Back to the early days
Guinea pigs edible type eating out to be sitting out their hands taking a zine
Or something like that today was like Hey listen
You need to tell us about your
Time
Coming up
About how you turned yourself from us
Nobody into a man with
Almost 50 employees
Is gold
Bought me a show right all of this is not help with a myth
Doesn't how I think that if Alex is going to start busy
But I'm imagine
Global is proof
He also going to need to make his own paper
So yeah some Lumber he's going to need some land where he can grow trees
Some trees isn't Papyrus a lot easier on terms of like what kind
Dovetree like you don't want to waste too many tree
Look man
I don't believe the dump
He's the one who needs to start his being out in the woods so the Goldbergs can stop at that does make sense
Alex versus the hour comes back for a little bit and starts rambling about how
Bill Maher w
Depopulate the planet and I was like
I heard that in court today
You said that he was a secret Patriot ago
Come on man
Different types of bankruptcy
Is a reorganization
To keep Infowars going
There is a point
Easy projection
Do that and not laying people off
With this headline
Lawsuit
And that's what this is
Usher
If you hadn't messed with me
6 years ago to be phased out at all fair by now
Maybe doing a podcast and writing a book and maybe
Film
Enjoy certain levels but it's time for a change
Never now
If we don't get the funds we need so help
Amazing
Tony infowarsstore.com right now
How about you go f******
That is
A
And almost
Like
It is
Gone through to the other side
To become a heroic
Belief
In that if I get this money
It will not go directly
To the family everything will be fine
Lake Daddy's that is the most delusional like
I would I would honestly if I was in his situation be actively telling people
If you don't want to give money to my dad
Shmoney
Give it to anybody else
Yeah give me a other newly founded company in Hood probably exists somewhere
So I think
Another thing I'd like to highlight In that clip is
And Circumstance that I'm in right now
Hotel
But I would say if you hadn't messed with me I would have quit long ago
In this
Hour of his show where he is
Preoccupied right with
Melding
Scarlet and kneel with
The Democrat conspiracy ambulance Chaser nonsense
Teddy's going often because
I think it's pretty easy to hear that say
Niall and Scarlett if you hadn't messed with me I would have quit long ago I don't think there's any way to hear that
Fine I mean with the part where he says it
Yeah that would make me hear it
Sure
Yeah but what if I
What if you told me you didn't
Then I wouldn't have any idea
You're out of control
So Jordan yes Dan
Bedtime
But
What is until advised is the way Alex is playing at
Yeah you know the Booty like
Yeah if only people that seed all of it they'd see that expires it creates a distraction from the actual topic
Totally
I do appreciate that I don't feel like the judge
And the court had much patience for that I don't think that it played
And
I think you know the clip that we played of him talking to people outside
I don't think they were putting up with it very much
Alex maybe in the past was more able to steamroll Media I don't think I'd
I didn't get the sense
Of much
Of that
Tolerance
Positive thinking
You know I mean to that point
To that point
Especially
Like when we were at the end of the trial
I didn't have any problem rushing out of there
Immediately after the judge
I didn't
I intersect I still kind of Beyond how horrific a treatment it is of
Neon Scarlet
His behavior after the trial
To me is less important
Then what the judge said right before the end of
The day
Which is
That she basically agreed to marks
Instruct
Hints for the jury
So tomorrow morning
The judge
Without Alex on the stand
Will say directly to the jury
Alex is guilty
Yeah Alex
Alex has plenty of money
To the extent
That
The defense is trying to
Push things in that direction or apply those things out your to disregard any of that
It is going to be you know like in a in a law show and all that stuff because this is what it
It's become
That's what Alex is trying to turn this into is a TV show
I'm going to have it you know
But
This is the moment
In a movie trial
Where's the judge
Outside of like
This lawyers a character and that lawyers character in these lawyers are representing people
And the people have a vested interest in all this stuff
When the judge says
To the jury
This guy
It's f****** guilty
And you have to know that
There's no lawyers arguing there's no ambulance Chaser at all
Yeah Alexandria
Alex's fishing for a let you go see where you're going with this and he got a
Shut up
And that's a positive sign is a good times
So I will
I don't know
We will it'll be a day
It'll be a day and a half
It's already past midnight
So let's
Please see what
The fuk goes on the ohmigod tomorrow
Anyway
Will be back
From Chicago
So on Twitter in Chicago
Dzx Clark
Hope you all have a wonderful dream creamy summer updates coming on ice creams that I've been eating sorry
Been busy here in the evening
Yaks
Nicecream don't you worry
Alexandra Thurston color