Dot-com
Pray
Quick question for you
My bright spot is that sweet Cantina theme remix of our theme song that just played by
Celebrate
Crushing the game
With ease
Remixes
There's definitely the theme song of our trip to Austin and being able to I have that incorporated into
The podcast for us
Special
We're two lucky
Talented photo
Or willing to create
Thanks I appreciate it
I would say my brights
Spots well might as well we were on the televisual box
Television debut
The demon stelter
Was here we weren't in the same studio so we can smell them through the camera but so far already there
You know we can't confirm sulfur or not
Yeah I agree we also
Yeah we were in a studio we were staring at like
A black wall
We didn't see him
Even at school
Which was a little unnerving
Is this
Concerta
It's faces that he made
Producer Michael
Just making mocking faces
Jordan I mean we were on with stelter
It's all right there's a couple of things I want to point out
Question was whether or not we got to ask him about his hatred
Or Alex hatred of him
And
We didn't on-air although he did say we could ask him that
Alexace
So that part week
Can confirm
I meant the second thing I wanted to bring up Visa V that interview is
Are star parents have different response
I got a text from my dad that was about how proud he was and how I was the first family member to
To make it on the national news
I would imagine there had to have been some kind of coverage of my brothers ice cream shop
In the day you know
But I know that there was a ton of
Serve local and Regional stuff
Like a national Spotlight but there was
But certainly no Seltzer baby
Ya-ya-ya people's my my cousin
Who consumes a lot of right-wing news
Was the first person to text
And then you go on the Clinton News Network know he was like you did a great job
Some preaching today so they couldn't get to see it
You know and then
I sent him a picture and they were like congratulations
So the conversation went
And I won't fall asleep
Avalanche of appreciation
It's
No
With smooth as they say
It's it's been it's been a really interesting couple of weeks with the trial and stuff and
Just adding the surreality of
That is
It's almost hard to process
I don't know how I feel about having makeup
Put on me
Thanks
I ate yeah it's it was all is all a lot but I appreciate them having this
I appreciate that they allowed us
Not play into like some of the
You know like
Hey why don't you do a talk talk about Alex's
Able to
Speak on the issue as we
I wanted to and I appreciate that that's something that's
You know
Maybe some people wouldn't
Media outlet with the offer
Yeah yeah yeah I think we're both actually very lucky that we're not in like
Like this is the Behind the Music moment where it all starts to fall apart
100% in agreement like
We're going to say exactly what needs saying ghetto
I think I saw a little bit of feedback that it was a little bit of a shallow interview
You know like she is really dive too deep
You got to
Question
Move along and end so
Unfortunately it does
May not satisfy people
Sarah deconstruction of some of the
The podcast is for
Yeah it was it's a treat
And speaking of treats Jordan
We had Ferrari episode today we are thrilled
To be joined once again by Mark Bank
Paxton Bill Ogden
I think I think marks in our little
Everybody on on this but
We always really
I feel like it's kind of condescending to say an otter but it was
Meaningful
I'll be always be very
Thrilled to have been able to be whatever small part of
They said it wasn't I I appreciate them so much for allowing us
Do you have
Inside track on some stuff
Send their generosity with
The Listener is
And it's just so wonderful
I'm glad that we are able to
Have this sort of button
A little bit
Although maybe it's a button the last
All of sneaky
Wrapping up some of this this sort of
Chapter
Is very nice and being able to
I have have a conversation with them to do that
I think everyone will enjoy
I think it's great
So we can belabor this longer it just
Chat about nothing but
I'll be honest
It's late
I got to get this episode
Don't
No
Never
Don't care
Who knows we might be sneaky as hell this week
It's Nico
Anyway enjoy the interview
Hey ladies and gentlemen we are back and here in
In in Chicago
As is
Is this the norm
A bit of a chat
Decompression session
But you can press that if you like
Was it good
Listeners will know we were in Austin recently
Trial and a couple of people out there
Just two dudes
We would they were wandering the streets
They were wearing nice suits and we were like I can't believe that these these two people are not being take
Taken care of
I can't believe
Share wisdom
Security detail 10-strong
0.
Disguise security
Lewisberry we're actually running
No I did
We figured this week
Is snake week
We have honorary call
Squeak
And what better way to begin
Sneak week
I went to have a little bit of a trial
I guess you better join us then
Mark Bankston
Plaintiffs attorneys for Scarlett Lewis
Thank you for doing
What's up
How are you going for the walks
Certainly become favorites
Of the community absolutely
So
Doors at the
This is the office of the only interview I'm doing
No other press
I said I'll do this one and that's it
No joke though this is
Since I walked off
The courthouse grounds
Playing first time I've spoken to any sort of public media
Why don't you drop the butler public media now
Glitches
I mentioned this morning
This morning as recording is I we were on
Reliable sources with Brian stelter
And I was just
Cuss swear
It was so hard for me to like
I didn't scream one time
What time does
The reason I'm here actually is because I knew if I went on CNN the mood I'm in
What's my email
What's bringing that swearing to mind what to wear where y'all heads at
We just got
I don't know
I was
I don't know why but this
Trial
Took more out of me
Like emotionally and just exhausted I guess why because everyday was something
Holyshit
Oh good now
I think that
We wanted a little bit of
Difference when it comes
The numbers breakdown but
We're extremely happy with where it's at and
And I think the message
That
The client wanted to send
Weston
Pretty damn clear and loud so
I'm super happy now
But definitely
Exhaling
And taking a deep breath and just kind of relaxing a little bit
This point I'm not wasn't jumping on a private jet to go to Waco to New York City to do interviews
Good point that you bring up
The numbers and
I think a lot of times the
The reporting on this misses you know there's a lot of
Flashy numbers and millions and stuff
And the context of it as the message
CMP
The actual intent
Of the plaintiff
It's kind of lost in the shuffle a little
I mean two in the in the complications of
How does a
Actually plays out
It's it's
Not exactly sure
Caps are they
Then what people have to remember
Yeah
You know
50 Burke Lane
And then you got to to finish per claim
So-so is the capital
Pink Floyd Pulse the 1.5
A million in interest on the 4th
Right right
Birthing appointment
Bitcoin
But here's the thing about that is that
Because they put themselves in bankruptcy
And that means that the potential appeal
What you going to be doing
How Beckett
Potential to have that
Not applicable
Is Gibbs enough value
That's really interesting
Judgment
If you know jokes
Constitutionality Thompson
The Sacketts the day
The sad part is that's not going to happen
Value
You got Maddie coming in with his
What is a 9 plan if you got two more dead with Osmond Delarosa
Griffith
Serfontein
Misidentification
Right2know
I mean that's what it like
You for somebody who claims to not want to court
Attention and media is dropping these bombs that just
I'm going to throw pipe bombs from
Top of this roof
Kill
Yourself
Story
Probably
5 years ago
Maybe six years ago Mark try to case
Call
Harold Adams
And he tried it
And with his dad
And they got screwed
And
He got done with that case in Hebrew
She's like I don't
I've never tried another
This isn't for me
This is my
And I think this is the first time he was in a courtroom since then Llamar
Oh no I got a couple cents
Yeah that you want to meet
But yeah there's been a couple of been like okay.
And then you start participating in some of these
Before you guys get out
If you got a little good feedback and then you're ready
You spend your life second sharing trials by giving your young plants while you're in
This this
Yeah
That's interesting.
Wiethop
Is it Direction like
I thought I was good at this was going to be good
Cuz now I
The most famous lawyer moment of the last
Decade
Absolutely
On television
Saw that it was just
Rock everywhere
The new if
The glub glub.
It really is
And I for you like
Such a question
Because because Mark
Slapped
Retinol and the Jet bus marking the judges type right now so many times
I really feel like at the end he was like
I just don't even want to stand up
I'm not going to feel good about what
Concierge
What's 1
We shouldn't have absolutely understand the Plainfield he thought he was going to come in here and figure
Address is good press
Guys named right now
Lawyer and
Was Not only was it
Pitch Perfect like
In America
Sputtering cost
But the fact the moment itself
Focus so intently on opposing counsel
But even though
A person
Play does the dramatic painter pants down the rain all are sitting there just soaking
Right now
I tell you I saw I saw
Open Cloud on The Daily Show tonight after I did it and I was I was obviously on the list I was like
For a second I almost done cuz I know all of his friends
I mean
He inherited
Indicates that was s*** already
There's nothing to do about it and I
She probably took
That case without
Appreciating where the case was
And in chess
After Bob
Dropped on him in
I do I kind of feel bad
Because I think in 5 years
And I'd like a
With the
Is that what you're
I I just I
It's rare that
Something like that happens especially on such
Such a big stage
Rare Plus
I came home and I have a kind of rough around the edges cousin who I would not expect
And he came right up to me and he was like what
Man
Is it me in the Pepsi challenge
And I did I'll tell you I felt bad for a moment but I need
A story that that
School
But
The first time I met renewal back in March when he was coming into December
Outside on the steps out from Courthouse
And he even tried to do some sort of psycho psyop stuff you know mess
Tell me something along the lines of
But you never get mad I'm off this case of your clients are Never Getting It.
And then that s*** just collapses on itself
Everything goes south hands up Owens have any kind of a million-dollar zensation Petit pays in the middle of truck
They actually had me. Checking and get that'll never
And now he is up
It's just dessert
If you were coming to send it like with
That's one thing
But if you come in and just meet bagman for Alex Jones proto-fascist
Whatever
Right now
Oh my God
Do the show cause hearing for discipline all of that
Complaints against them
Rodger stone is begging him to sue him
Staying
Is Eric Holder
And somehow weasels live in the jungle
Defamation claim against Rodger Stone
But it's all this is going until you
Kman
We had this verdict and then I know what's about to happen
Is he is going down the tubes
What is
Is this
Doubt
Exit of Jones
Is going to take a considerable amount of time and
You're going to have fun today
For the next year that is
Finally.
Yeah yeah
Think I think one of the things that's really important
About that is that
It happens
Probably because it'll be a little bit
Protracted there will be
So many opportunities for the
Inside of the saucer
To be understood
Ray middle bit more by the public
Like what could be
Incredibly helpful in
Teaching people about
These sorts of actors
And how they operate
So you can
Understand other
People like
And avoid
Falling for the same trick
Another
Western cottonmouth
Want to come talk to you when they can do some educating and if you think I'm on your podcast
Lake-Link
I was like absolutely not
Was something about his Tennessee draw
Something about
Foster the tenor of the whole damn case
About Jonah
What does a sup on the witness stand
Yeah she say that
And that is when West did that
She
Just landed
That was everything that he had the most
He had practice
Tom's with this night before
And it was it was
That was
Weird because
Grass was like
Kyle cross
What I came here for
Mark
Introduces the term Perry Mason
Listen to the world
Dairy Queen
Scarlet
Christian Dennis
In my opinion demos
Powerful moment
Machine
Doug Henning
What's right Alex
Chew him
It wasn't
Ejection
But there was
So no questions being asked she was just talkin
What's Raynaud's
Monologue
Because your attorney didn't look Jatt
Choice
So we get that and then
Here Comes
He was the only one of us that
Without crying
Dad
Me and Kyle
I can't do it Mark was going to do it and that's a
Like mid-trial marks
So Westside that's we didn't get
Huestis
You know
Everybody's got their own style
Definitely the most
Kind of cavalier
Style and
It's just a different type
Uptown
Until
He didn't get to show that and then all the sudden he
The closing and chest
I mean
Laid it all out there and it was it was
Dallas
Buy For Less close
A little bit unfortunate that it's
Denotes overshadowed by the Perry Mason
You know that like
Almost
Shadow using say because
We're not talking about the fact that for the first time ever we played
Clip
Of the defendant calling the judge a pedophile
I forgot about that
Play we played a video of the defendant
Calling the jury bunch
Blue-collar simpletons
In the middle of trial
Astros
Things are insane and they're not
Yes
Call Linda Neel on the Spectrum
Show me show me
Huge moments
Happening in this trial
But most
I mean obviously the Perry Mason one because
Nice try on the Perry Mason
Oh you have
No idea what I'm saying
I was going to ask you guys how do you feel cuz I feel like
Ultimately the jury did an amazing job
Because of the amount of
Bulshit that is barrage that that
In such a short.
Give time
That their ability to kind of like
At least
Processes
Into where when
I feel like it's kind of almost amazing anyway did you guys feel that similarly what are there really UFOs
Right in that jury was a broad mix of different backgrounds
None of this b******* stuck a second they were on it from Square
And there was basically a conjurer who was who was a little
Dino hesitant about certain of the ideas of
I don't know free Express you're not necessarily
Compensate
Stop so adorable
Once we're able to talk to him they gave us
Feedback
And if we didn't really didn't know like you say
You know my brother actually told me about the see what you sent
This trial it's like
It's like trying to get your mom to start watching the Marvel Cinematic Universe
Why is Harry Style showing up
Steve pieczenik
Hell don't want to miss the post-credits
Time everyday when she left
Yeah he was
Stepped in
The song I believe I was
One publication
Describe me as
Like one of those large
Or you know Kimmy something that larger
You sound like a
I don't think you saved his life but I do think you might have saved his license
Because there's no really did go after I have no doubt markers and going to be like
Can I get the cops
Nearby like I don't think that.
Around is because as the
They both started
Mark's wheel will you talk
Talk to me in
The cameras
So funny
You were in jury selection you didn't know where that
Bratz
Seminal moment
Is that
Immediately preceding that I'd basic
We managed to have a large walk 2016
Doesn't know his way around to the wall
Poster board
Videos
Like seriously up in my face
School.
And am I grabbing like
Kind of diffusion
So what I say is
It looks on the camera like I'm being super super reasonable
Hey Federico will you talk to me
We know is that this dude started
General admission
Miss Miss Rodriguez whoever was right
We talk to me
Thing's weird
Journal 3
Jurors in the goddamn awkward
Third row
Who's out there by said that ostensibly like I'm being a peacemaker
It will
North Carolina little
I have stopped paying attention
No and I
I'm watching it
And then I see just
Camera starting to Folk
We got to get this
See you like 10
Different journalist
Yeah exactly
I'll just boring myself
The camera
Dubai
Yeah whatever
Who's going to end in so I was like
Yeah there's a great picture that I saw of like
The two of you I buy mark
Did reynal and Billiard looking on like
Buff out here we go
Please know the cameras are on please don't say anything bad.
Not least of which because that
Wasn't like
The middle of the trial
That was Dave
A f****** 101
Right on
GetGo
Everyday and you have to understand
And I see you also
You also had to wait a couple more days before we leave
As it were
The clock to run out
I said this on
On Twitter but it mean it is
It is something that kind of it is hard to wrap my mind around
If the defense had made
No defense
Those text messages wouldn't have been allowed.
In a week
Doing this and not
That would be even after
If after the trial you wouldn't have been able to use them
Overwrite but you would have had that loaded
Exactly and I could have never trap Jones into
CC
Is lie on what
Text messages
Made that choice
That day I was I was free and clear I have
And I had Jones under subpoena
And I could have put them on the stand
Didn't I read
I knew they were going to call Joseph.
Devastated
Basically
Yeah
Boy
You were sitting there in.
You are a lawyer with all that rain down on
I noticed
Even during
The closing arguments
When Kyle was presenting his closing argument
Rain always on his laptop
And I can see just enough
Screen to see the Giant
Logo on the bottom of an email
Communicate with
Call Scott lawyer Medical
I think it was circumstance like that it's time to tear lyrics
You know Snickers isn't going to cut it
You need something you could just all
Stop.
Call Fred
This is what everybody seeing on Mike Scioscia right now I guess
But the
Rumbling
Eggs that were half
Throughout the development of the questioning like
No remember you had
The depo and I asked
You said you pulled it down into
The search bar
His mouth is still talking
Amanda
Off drops
He has multiple cell phones with that number I
Oh my God
Pasta on the spot
Is it there's a picture of a doting on Marcus
Is exact
What I thought it was this is so much better than what I thought
Nobody even with this outcome the clients like
Nothing could have happened in the trial of fighting the outcome happened
Broccoli
A right to talk a little bit more about that we're supposed to get
Yeah it was an absolute
Everything I've ever wanted
It does come down to such a dramatic
Jumps in the courtroom
Where things are going they know the other case
Just makes them feel like they just put a battering ram to
Fortress and it's all crumbling down MI
Now
When I say in some ways
It was like they were
In the sunshine
Constantly thinking about
He likes
About
What's Scarlet
Is that
Check your child
And she was like
I couldn't be there
When he died it became my job.
That was my job now
And that's what I've made my whole life
And that's what I'm trying to do with the movement to counteract this stuff
Can't you feel like every time you see this jumped-up everytime you have these people contact you every time
You feel like you're failing your child again and again and again
And she's like it's over now
Did the only the absolute most crazy people
Everything has become toxic and not induced gun
And then see them
So happy
Oh my God
There is a small part of me that
But maybe I'm just such a pessimist that I worry a little bit about people
Being readable
Spy
The consequence
They come to Alex you know like
It'd be a being a galvanizing thing
Folks
Harassing more
I hope that's not the case
I don't think that will be based on
You reacted
Intuit all which was I you know I do believe the parents and Aiden
You know he he
Is is
Half-assed
Apologies is he's made
He did
To some extent at least on the stand
Hundred percent counter repudiate
Dumb stuff
She's been saying
He was saying that he wanted to have Scarlet on and that he supports
Beautiful woman
Windows before the trinity
I wish more people that talk
Talked about it's like
That idea of Alex
Inviting them on their show on
His show is so disgust
The idea of having them on
Staying
I guess borderline
Things and then I'm almost going to
Assumed that he would be like
And also you know I'm
I'm right to
Question this whole thing
Things sooner or later
Like that
Disgust me on a level I can't even
Comprehend what I say
Think about
I will say this though
Scarlett's reaction to that
Was
It will get to just one
Person to support
The movement
Further
I meant
Lake tschida
Strong person Neil as well
And they do it in different ways but
But
You know involved
In the
The Choose Love movement is
Impressive when you look at what her story
Job everything about her is impressive might be in a better position to make this
Council but I would advise her not
To go
Jonesville Jones is a Madman so whenever
Expect
What I did not expect this
I work at your trauma
We are supposed to do that Miss Louis
Oh no he didn't
Maybe I like you just did the whole thing and it's free
You say that we looked at each other like
Easter
Is that like its first they came for the Socialists
Alex hate communist
He would come get with it
Alameda
I'll try
Appleminte
Cast
Neon scarlet and their lawyers
The first extermination of the jurors
Probably it's probably more
Poorly thought-through then
Like intentionally
Getting that across
That was the
That cuz you could
That poem
Miss much more applicable to a
A criminal trial
Sure sure
Computers are
He's coming forward people for this that and the other
HughesNet
A few other times
And interest
But yeah that was interesting
Quote specially with Joneses
Especially for me to play more Jacobs
6 Depo
Albany
The one that
Greeley by Mae
Caught my breath cuz I was in the court that day
But when he decided
To cross-examine
Both meal and Scarlett
I was like there's no way
You can possibly think
This is a good legal
Strategy
Think about you defaming like that
Interesting strategy
We can't say everything you did was
Who's bad
Because
He did hold
The compensatory
We do we work at
Try you you want to set
Yohai bar in
And work down
4.1
Significant less than what we would want
There
Made up for it on the
But walking out of of that I had to say like
As much as I hate the 808
How many mistakes
Prevented
He told me he
Anything he did
Metro Pizza
Conscious what the situation is or what
To send a message
To give these people to billion dollars
Sprite number
Another
That is another kind of point about that is that
What are the hard things that you guys one of the hard jobs I'm assuming you guys
His head was trying to impress
These people
That 150 million dollars
Is not
A huge amount of money
Do you know what I mean like
Twice that in a few makes calls to a million dollars everyday
He made twice that in a year
You don't
You put on a certain case
The trial based on the evidence that's really out there in front of you based on what
Businessman
Anything above that is just mess
Who's once you were starting to talk 10 million
You start that average those out
There's no
Superbook
Hidden somewhere that it's not that that's not
A Rippling
Effects of those wrecked
Judgment
Impact
His business in ways that are
You do not judge
Just directly you have to pay this there other things
That will have those bows like
The ball rolling down the hill
Listen to music library.
Billions
Going on an island in Barbados
Yes we got to go pick it up
If you have two little sisters
If you haven't left out there
The evidence is out there that can be used
Moron
Economist
Evidences is real
Is that real
Ajayll
Like I need you to understand that
Brighten our opinion
Just for
Does bankruptcy
Yes
If you
It should be on
That
We Believe based on our Accord
I don't understand under ocean said $2000000 will wipe us out
Astro
What's the other thing
Why I'm saying that that thing is also untrue
And there's a metal ware in there
Orbi
Eleni
These - 4
I can understand the Temptation by somebody like
The first part of the trial
What I can't believe is that they allowed it to happen. Jones
Testimony under oath about his financial condition
For a baker
Yeah that's reason why
Yeah it is definitely
That is if any of this if he was lying then he's in a lot of
Bestie
Prison
Wilson
The amount of help
Report that we had throughout this trial
Do y'all have to have the most loyal
Fan listening base
Of all time
I mean
Dover Mall
People
Sending us
Clips
When they were being put out by Infowars
We had
Connecticut lawyers were helping us out as much as they could they were watching
Your lawyer
Where's that were friends with from
That did the
Alfred
Posner
They came down and help with
The last few days we have friend lawyers that came in
Bankruptcy lawyers were there they were healthy
My girlfriend
Help me play
French the the Medical
Expert that I put on Doctor Who
It really helped us
Him getting Crossing
It just the amount
People that
We're willing an offer
Bring all this stuff
During the trial
Insane
Letsjerk
Suppose that
With Alex
And
Hit some of lawyer friend apparently who came to the courthouse
And I didn't know who Adam Lanza
So
He Had a Brain Trust
You know he had a lot of help
Right
Realtor
Was the old dude to the psychological Adventure
Say this
He
He didn't talk
Did the
Times that he spoke with
Where to
When you got off the
Just and I waited in the hallway with him
Jurors had their questions with submitting the question
And he was coming from the bathroom right before we got started
And he looked at me
Can I shake your client and I said yes
I'm so sorry for all of this
Mirai
Hey Liam, hat
Don't forget
Open Waze
Mark
Imrane all had
Just got
Done with some sort of battle in front of the judge
And it didn't go their way
And I went to the back
Would you expect to me
And I just looked over
Alex back
Made it safe
Gladiators go out just like
You're not gladiators
There was nearby
Neal's ant
Couple of Gladiators going at it
There is not a gladiator
Directions to Prost
Yeah that's what this was
Nissan directions
Original compression out of the room
About that
You know Joe is still in the courtroom for a minute after.
They're just running
Text Tiffany
But Joseph
Any kind of standing there the day is looking at me so I take the opportunities turned over to him
Hey by the way I should also let you know that was in those Direct
Which contain the entire confidential psyche
Medical record
Call Central.
Either you or me
Mr an hour allowed to have sex
Immediately
Is cholera
Absolutely
Just Don Knotts I guess I mean he is just
Nice nice
Tired of it in
Actually have an interaction
I maintain eye contact
And just step
Backwards out of the courthouse.
A little.
Bobby Barnes
He had some Choice words but
Marquis
Demon demon leprechaun
Yes but also
Appositive
He was so confused
By the moment where you
You
Bobby Barnes
Lyrics
We're just had a really good bet and I come back in there and there he was
And it was because I had just been back just as like maybe
30-45 minutes
Before watching a video with our judge
Simulator
I wanted to ask Drano
Ian book nobody wants a gag order
A judge to hold of your client
Is slapstick version of a lawyer
Something about
End-of-course exams
Listen to No Man
Please with a couple days later I'm literally playing to the jury
Like video of Barnes talkingshit
Videos of
Siri is Bobby
Sitting in the gallery
Lawyer
I think I heard that on Infowars but that doesn't mean it's true
He was insisting that you're obsessed with him
And B
No one has called him Bobby
In in
Since he was a child
I think I've pretty routinely called him Bobby pretty I think we're right on top of the bottle
Call service
Trolls get back in the day
Yeah
Do loves playing around people's names and so when we know his name was Robert Barnes
Hey
And like and then it turns out
23 months after Barnes got out of the case
Another lawyer there
Bill referred to
Bob Barnes
Barnes & Noble
Or something like that
Personality
I would say that I am obsessed with him
In exactly the same way I am obsessed with
Laughing
Basically the same
Lawyers right exactly
He's literally falling out of this coffin
Every time
So apparently the John Oliver
Skip
Just aired and Kyle said it was hilarious so we'll have to go back to the club
I don't think things are done between me and
Stokke talking on the show
Shadow s*** he is
I love it
I think he is going to be obsessed and come up with a fun
Nickname for me
Marquis Bank
Is that
Is that she is the
Guy
The Alexander write an affidavit about
He is messed up everything and please don't punish me because we are getting rid of them and you will never have to hear from him again
Representative
Practice
Now
Write like there's no
There's a sinking ship
Call me smart
Infowars
Janoski
Marco's a little bit of an
Megabus
How do you put a little bit of a Kind word towards Brad Brown
I don't know
You are fairly nice tan
That was my twin.
Might be what I was picking up on Les
I'm a lawyer I'm every participant on season 1 of Survivor almost like I'm not here to make friends
Like that's like I'm getaway
Point of order
I am a survivor historian and they were not doing that on to zandalar
Taking his dick out Rudy
I don't know what happened
You're taking me back
What are we doing
We don't want to make friends with anybody else
That was BP like
Rock of Love
Yeah
How do I make friends
The Flavor Flav show San Diego
Peperomia Rosso
Okay
Tila Tequila
God of love
Charlotte Web
Michigan
Jeep dealers
Earlier
Really
West Richland
Brad's
Forthrightness and honesty attorney
We likely would not have
Discovered some of the other
And and
When did when the ship was hitting the fan on
Brad
His license
Earlier to listen to me
He couldn't get out it's about to get bad. One more paycheck
150-gal want to be a part of this and if he didn't
But not but I was a brat
Was the only one
Teach
The s*** that
Everybody inherited
That was already made
And he tried
But there was just
With us
Pressing the way that we work was asking
With Mark pressing the way that he was
You know there was
He couldn't keep up with that
Let's go back and try to
Figure out the messages made
Which what
Appeared to me
Tubino
Client in her 80s helping him
Control
He was just like
Sorry
Biscuits to another thing about the assertive
Elena same way that Reeves inherited a lot of this
Renault it is well
Probably with the least lucky of all of them
Because he
Lawyers
But the lawyers progressed
Behavior kept happening
You guys
We're out of the Mind
The lawyer is maybe something
It also should be as opposed to just sanctioning Alex Wright
Is my understanding was
Isn't really the case with some of the earlier lawyers
Who behave poorly
Kind of got a little bit of the shaft
There is
And that's because
We truly an hour
Our firm weed that we do
Press sanctions against lawyers
We just
Unless we can
The decline
I had nothing to do
It was purely the lawyer
There has been very few inches
Just that
But
But yeah
At that point
Yes that is
That isn't there weren't that many instances of
Purely lawyer like
Without cuz I mean even some of it
Even some of Reno's
Cross-examination
I really could
Here
The voice of Alex and Infowars behind it like
Hey we need to ask
Please question
Absolutely
Whispering and right now the ear in the middle of his
In an emergency hearing
Records
Claire
Lingering question
But I feel like we can
Address a little bit more now that case is over
And one of them surrounded the
My involvement
In the deposition
When I came down
One of the questions that we have not really been able to answer was
The question of whether or not they wrecked
I'm part of the reason for this
Because they
Didn't
Until they read the Tramp
Exactly
This was something that I knew that we couldn't talk about but do you want to say or do you want to explain that a little bit
This was a little bit of drama
I saw it and look we were sneaky because we always are
We we had
Mini Mart
We have the ability to bring
Experts weather test finder
Depositions
They have to sign a protective order
I'm sorry
With other documents
Start of deposition
Understand
So he's got the documents
Okay now I'ma start Google
Are you not plugged into this
Is that a walk
Mulatto
Good advice
Dial
Alex's yes
Yes or no
So
I'll be at you know a little bit
Heavily bearded I cleaned up
Music rap
Brewery of experts
As a law firm
Yes so I think he just kind of fit in a weird way
On the first page of the transcript of the list of everybody's president
Google junior what the hell
They actually tried to insinuate
Protective order in Subway
Because
I don't know I guess
WhatsApp
Very like whatever
Find article
The entire thing that they were arguing along with Mother stuff just
Sooner face during that
And I think that directive I mean
But you don't know if that was a larger strategy moved to try to do that at that
Yeah
What is a piece of information
We are
It's something that went
And so you know according to the law
Fix it something you want to watch YouTube
Describe beer
Business cards and letterhead
Consulting expert
I'm a consultant
Playing
Firstenburg
Things I wanted to
Get to use the
Like the
Protracted
It's of the case
Dislike
Is all frustration
Constant roadblock
And everything
And then
Get to the caves
I don't know your experience was like
Even in the
Process
The trial
There was
A sense of pretending that it was
The damages cure
I meant it was
Actually
Innocence or guilt
I kind of
Trial
Was that
Extension of olives
The b*******
Coming into the trial at
Siamese cat
Here's the thing is is
Is
I don't know if you're saying that that
That sort of issue on liability
That was
That was she lying
Passing away because
Lot of heavy focus on just
Zircon.
The amount
Appeared
Right
Shown to show that they were liable
With the exceptions of Something's reading
True
In the same
And so because we obviously
You want to
Got to be the thing you want to drink
Thinking about so that whenever you can
Even more importantly to
Consider
5 years they have
This back
Push this back
Any point in time if they just said
Fuk it we quit
You win will pay what we need to pay
Text messages come out
Themselves in the foot
Is there going to
This judgment we have it is
With an amount of money
Madonna sincere apology
What number to say Sandy Hook
I agree
Like later on these kind of
4sho kind of offers of
Of yeah
Saddlemen
Do you know Lake Forest
Whatever became official in terms of settlement offer
They wanted to give him 500
Attorney fees cutoff
After they made the settlement just out of thanks
I'm going to take that way more
Don't even think that you're hiding
More than that
Weather in Portsmouth
Pressure now they barely know
Now.
We look at our briefing about the about the bad faces bankruptcy why was she can take some to get some of those
Schedule
Oh no they they they on the intellectual property
100% And I'm not joking
If you were to shutdown Infowars as Amityville
Jokes
You can watch a new website
Call Infowars
That is legit Independent Media critic
That doesn't really well and really right
Agreed launching Infowars
Well
Record
The absolute most movie ass dumpling
That we could
Popcorn devoting a suddenly just walk into the Infowars Studio the movie
Because we have
Some friends on the
Podcast
And we
We need Alex
Called dibs
1 people to walk
In the Bible
In my office and see that waving flag and talking win
Call Dad
Dallas
Scan the document camera
I will challenge you to a game of poker
When we were thinking we're going to start seizing assets as like
Make the desk is mine
Every psychology
Very specific
But bread in reality I don't know if
So we wouldn't it would be
Victory for me to get
That's Bud
I want the skull
But you put on the desk every hour
Me
I want all of his guns
What else
Charity that we're thinking about doing
Second Amendment savior
Homeless people exercising
Their second amendment downtown Houston and start handing out a ours to home
Story about
Suddenly like you
You get all these like
Business been conservative
Alarm at 1
Is that what you're telling me
Tank if you don't have
A place to live
Stably
You might not need a Barrett
40 cal
Can get a place to stay pretty quick have squatter's rights
Interject
Hello neighbor
Robbie Barnes yelling about
Leprechaun Bethany's trying to start a revolution
That kind of went over including our heads
Is Daria on the stand brought up fast and furious
The movie however
Fast and Furious.
In I was
Friday and I'll driving
Back to Houston cuz I went home to see my son for the weekend
And I called Mark Nelson
Eric Holder
Ran Fast and Furious he also app
Pointed right now
Truth
Department of Justice I think it Laredo is like
Was that the same time
Oh my God
That is around here
Reno
What time did you work for Eric Holder
Run around
Yeah
Kapiti article law
For her
Stickman
I think that they made a bit of
Miscalculation
Allowing
Testify
Because I think
Two more of
The world image
No
Yeah that's the way and then
We wouldn't have had her on the radar or the deposition
I subpoena do
Rosewell
And they said
Verde Alex
Was trying to get the
Clip from Idiocracy
And he said
Do has it on his
Computer that means he still works there already
You still doing some contract
He's been dead for like a month
Easel
Process server instead of up to music
I was waiting for you to say cuz I I can see bills got gamer I was waiting
For you to be like he's playing a few games
Call of Duty with Bill the other night
It's weird they said they do
Control
Find az100
Equity Holdings LLC bankruptcy documents
That had the theme of like
Define rhetoric of a CIA black site
Interrogation
The theme
Boba father
John Wick
Dumb Frat Boys son s*** and just has taught him for the last time on everything
And in the jumps thing was just on another
Planet
Phoenix Wright Ace Attorney
Tamia still go back
Shiver down my spine
Her reaction to some of these questions
Moment that moment at the end of her
Whenever she's trap
Fully
Enabler in either a yes or no
I'm a psycho or not question
Doesn't even it even the question doesn't really matter because it really boils down to
Are you willing to say that
Do you have it in you
And then she tried
Not too I swear
She tried to fumble and then finally she was like
Yes
And you're like I can't believe you
I really can't believe you're a
Yeah
Beyond Scarlett's testimony
This whole experience
Being in the room
For the Super Bowl
Picture questioning
Yeah in the composition
Itself
Will live on in my memories one of the most visceral
Things that I
It felt like it was
Hokkaido
Together in the room
Like of just like the gas
That I almost let out
That's just how
You're sitting by the side so you're having a process it emotionally
Me in the moment
Tempered and put to the backseat
By the fact that I
Compass MPG
Yeah yeah yeah
In front of her face
Who is the disgusting all that but also just
The surprise of like
That's where your mind was
Like
Teams
Like that's something you might say if you're trying to come up with Anna
That's nuts
And I just think about all the people worldwide who saw that Super Bowl picks
For the first time in Toronto
Yeah
That was the goal with Daria to get you
This was something much more.
That's okay
Is that like
The notion that it's like he got something wrong and he said if
A few things is so full
Yeah
Based on the information that's presented
Care to take
Take the time to look at it
Is a
Conscious negligence
There is a willingness to platform and
Fundraise
4 people who were
Acting maliciously and
These people
There's so much more than just
We went on this story
You know like that something
More people need to recognize
We were at we were ask kind of an inch
Interesting question today
Ultimately a boil down to like
710 episodes
Can we like learn anything about this
And it's like
We're on here for 6 minutes
If we were able to explain
Anything
To you then
Why would we do 710 f****** episodes
He has that that will have anything to say of any value to you in this
That's almost a repudiation of everything we've ever done
Also did a little dirty for seltzer
Business
700 UPS
Somebody's Daughter come on
Y'all have before we
Before we wrap this up your perspective
Unjustly
Babe do you want to make sure people know
You going
We
The
The one thing I will say is that when you when you go through trying to get
You don't have a choice
You're with him everyday
And
You talked with him and that's where you get
Really appreciate them as people
And the more and more that I met
Niall and Scarlett
You know at times I would
What year at times you get frustrated for certain things
But I'm not going to
Nothing bad
Show me that some of the surrounding circumstances
Never going on
Outside of Austin
That we're going on during the trial
But I will say that
It was
There's a
Is surrealness
Feeling whenever they both took
The stand and they told their stories
Completely separate ways
And I think when that
You know
And
Everybody had heard
Ridiculousness
Craziness and there was all these moments
Witnesses
Is getting bloodied over and over again
The stand
And the mood shifted a little bit
Even for me
And I know 4B I think all of us
We we talked about it more
When that moment
Hit
A kind of
Got me back on track of like
This is
But let's go
Like this thing up for real cuz
This
As fun as those moments can be proved
Professionally
When when you hear from the person that you represent
How it how it actually affects them Empower sheet of really
You know
Put your foot down on
Throttle and I mean
You can see that that's kind of what
Because after
After that it was
A bunch of surgeons in
Operating room
Cutting things down
And then I'll come
I got put back together
There's something that's so
Kind of bizarre to me I have a perception of
Lawyers
In general
Baby
It's not entirely favor
There is something about
I hate lawyers
You guys I've met you I spent time with you and it seems like you have such a
Ability or willingness
With your client
Scarlett Marcel
Hear that you have
About your clients
The context of
Being your client
McKay's
You know that
Disorder cut-and-dry nature
McKay's
It's one of
Offends me I guess
Maybe it's me taking so
Something personally that I don't need to
What about when Alex describes you guys as like
Ambulance chaser
And this that you know
How much you all do actually care
It it it adds an extra layer to to that bed
I think is is
That's so undeserved in
Obviously
Yeah not all about you guys but
There is an angle of that the
It sucks yeah you went to confession does
You were talking about how nice our fans have been to you and all that stuff
And I will tell you this
They are not nice
Because
You're good
If you weren't
Boris be nice to our fans are
Very very good at
Discerning whether or not
Who gives a s*** about
But yeah Mark and I don't like other attorneys
We hate we we hate others
Personality
Your you're
Your view on us isn't a
I would say that
But it's not as
Big of a minor
There are a lot
Plaintiffs attorneys
That do personal injury work out there that
Truly do do it for the right reasons and then the right ways
But I can set a time to get overshadowed by
It's overshadowed by
That you know some
Push certain limits that they shouldn't have
That they shouldn't have
And that's always going to happen any profession but yeah
I mean
When you guys
Don't tell you I mean they have
A decade's worth
Stories before
Thick client
Years & years later that are
Pelagic settle steeltech
Text them and they still let you know they they check
It's hard not to when
We don't do
So it's rare that you're going to go do a case where somebody got rear-ended in the
School zone
It has enough
$30
Chiropractic
So if we're trying a case
Significant
And because of that it's
We try hard not to get
Get too emotionally invested
Because it'll mess with our performance
But at the end of the day
Possum
Care about
These people because
There's been very
Few people as any
Can't think of any off the top my head
It deserved
Happened
So right
I'll say that
I hope that what we did you know your Drano attack
Employment lawyers
For the people who do well we have
I don't write that a lot of people
Adversarial
Never
I've never been clients of never paid me up front
Always taking money from some bad person or Evil 4
Corporation
And i e no ice
Growing up I wanted to eat be either Robinhood or Blackbeard
And I act
That's really what I dance
It's been really rewarding to have all of the
It's been really nice
And I was getting a lot of that
I got home
And I walked in the door
My son Ben comes up
That mean he's he's getting
What date now
When I first
Cypis cases USA
When they die
And he was born on the same day as Noah Kostner
It's his first birthday is Noah's first birthday that you wasn't around
Was in 2013 the first round
Ben has a little.
Charlotte gave him that's as the Jesse Lewis to his T-shirt
And that's his Jessie.
Call Jesse.
And he knows a little bit about what happened to understand what I'm up there
This horrible thing happened
Disparan a little boy
And there's a man who
He understand
Door
Came bounding up to me and
Pleasure in his eyes of daddy
Truck route me around
Every damn thing to me Busta week's melted off
Like snow
Just came all off
Am I everything
I broke Mia. I got a bad a night where I just
Just stop for a minute
And thought about where all this lad
That was more important to me than any of the things
Proud of myself to him
If I had to come home head and changes that could help you people
Man
To the world
We're John got to Steve kicked in the middle courtroom I love it I'm so happy
The people will have that for you
Come to make
Trial by jury was still on the episode where they have you
One of the riders for Law and Order
If I would have
Written script based on what
What's going on
Immediately
From that conference room
F****** play that was ever going to happen in real life
That's the type of stuff that only happens in real life
Alex
Bell
Dude said he got
B b
Ministere
That story
Because we know that
Power that has to counteract
And I'll just tell you we got we got sequels coming up
Show me good
Clear your
Using this like
Theatricality
A narrative
Stuffing any dishonest way and I honestly think that
It's one of
The reason
Confetti
Against al
He's using things that are dishonest
Manipulative
In a theatrical narrative-based and it's so powerful against
Text him to use things that are real
And truthful in the same
Starbucks
No magical realism
Where we're coming from
This is about the
True American story
A Hundred Years of Solitude
Obscure
But yeah with that said I am check
Working out from
Social media
The news media everything for
A few days leaving now by sugar mom is taking me on a trip
Birthday
A little bit more get away from all the noise
Now gets to do all of that while I'm
Because he's the one that everybody wants to talk to you this morning
Your audience in into maybe old by this time in this area surrounding over to go put this out or whatever tomorrow
I got
Some of them
But tomorrow night Monday night
Check out Turks
Batman
I'm sure that you know our walks are very enterprising
People and I'm sure every single appearance
But thank you so much for taking time
Like in this immediate aftermath
Ulta
Means a lot
Right
Is my gosh
It's going to be a problem for them what some of the stuff that happened on that show
I would
Anything imaginable problems
Future
I guess I don't know
Anything to plug
Jessie Lewis Choose Love foundation in the choose choose love movement
Two things are
They're both doing
Really good stuff for
A moving forward one on misinformation and one on just
Teaching kids how to stop
Dating app
It's amazing what Bill enjoy your trip
I hope you get all the the Sun and relaxation you deserve
Mark
Enjoy
The Young Turks
Whoever else knocks down your door
It's over there
Well we'll talk soon
And I'm sure in the lead-up
To the depositor trial
If the bankruptcy doesn't tall derail everything
Completely will have
Some debriefing to do there
Absolutely
You have a great night
Take care
Alex
In color