Knowledge party.com
I have great respect for knowledge
Sick of them posing as if they're the good guy
MoneyGram
Knowledge fight
Everybody welcome back
Like to knowledge
Let's fight I'm down where couple dudes
Blexit around worship at the altar of Celine back
And it's company very close to the altar
And talk a little bit about Alex
What is ghetto
We're back
From our trip to Austin
And there's something to eat
Text to be really exciting.
Being in my own
Space
Of course saline being around
But then there's other things that are kind of acid
Surprise
One of the biggest
Is my back scratcher
Oh yeah yeah
On the trip
Realize how much I use
Was itching almost
If I was rubbing on doorway like a bear
Coming back I was like yeah
Travel back scratcher
Like three or four of them
Back scratchers
You just need some back lotion
I get some
Yeah
Really
Maybe you just
Baby
I don't know can you have backs
Dry skin
Okay Paradise
My bright spot very similarly is a small thing
From home that I didn't
You be such a delight
Sebastian and I had my bath
Add salt in there I've turned into that guy
First shift
Absolutely
Years to get there but eventually your bath
At salts
My brain about
It was so good tubs in our hotel room
There were
How good was our hotel rooftop
Deep tub
Slender
Mine was not deep okay
That's weird
Was just super
I think that's
Jacuzzi bathtub in your ear off
Yeah
That's it
Jordan
Episode
Is very exciting
Over the course of the time in Austin
When we were there for the trial
Figure a merge
The trial
So take him to a very serious way
I have paid
Attention to
Admired
Of her work over the years and
Call Becca Lewis thank you for joining us
That is that is very kind
Awesome
That's great
We can finally sit down and have
Have a chat
I have to ask you what is your bright spot
My boyfriend is really similar to both of yours actually I am also back home
But the Comforts of Home are
Are really nice
Includes my own altar
19 year old delightful grumpy old lady
Love it I love it I love it grumpy pet
You need to be
Am I right
Yeah but I love I love I love an old
2 likes
Just so you know Mike doesn't have
Viber
Just sort of
I know what's up
We were at.
A friend of the
Deep clothes
Friend of the show who helped our audio issues
Making it
My hero when we were at his place
He had a very old black lab
Schreiber
Yeah Golden Retriever and then break
Huge
It was the biggest dog
It was so old and then whenever you came over I gave her the right ear scratches boom right on the floor give me some
Belly time
That's a big old old animals die only adopted
They're just chill
And God bless her for it
Becky you were a part of the trial
Be at the plaintiff
Expert witness
Jordan
Like what
The subject matter you were brought in
To talk about was
Yeah from good so I research
Communication
Retraining for race social
Ulta
Disinformation efforts across the
And how they kind of disseminate throughout the internet
That was really the role they brought me on to talk about so
Like other other Witnesses
Talked about
You're like Fred's at the journalism expert talked about kind of actual protocols
Journalism
Following any of those
Of course the forensic psychologist talked about
Experience
To talk about
Alex Jones
Spread this conspiracy theory has become
Atopic
It's a guy got to be found a lot of your your testimony
Pretty interesting Illuminating
A section of
Understanding his reach a particular is
In the past
It is something that we haven't delved too deeply into
Understand our own
I swear I think there's just 50
People listening honestly cuz I feel like
Really know what we're both on your team
We can talk ideas about our kids coverage of things but
The stuff
Around
That picture is something that I don't know
I mean I I certainly have a sense of it just sort of
Like being around conspiracy circles at
Ioi
I need a new way we know where bulshit is and you know where
Goats
When you work in the space you quickly
One very very small piece of the puzzle
So
Massive there's so much to do and so you really do have to rely on the work of other people
And it's incredibly important
Now you're just
Yeah definitely I think
I think that's something that's really important is that
People
Niche
Specialized a bit and then
Networking
Can be important
Sink tap
The failings of our show I think really is
There was none of that really early on never
Because
I think I was scared
Because I reached
But I'm guessing they were so resistant
Yeah
Like we are not
Academic sweet we don't have any real background
Study Alex Jones
It's obviously like
Concerned it like all these
Crazy people
I got go
Gun-shy about that
Didn't didn't really Network
Nearly as much a
Cuz I could have
No I was just going to take the cool thing for me is that during the trial
Your podcast have been the Forum where you've been able to bring a ton of
People together right
From the lawyer
Elizabeth Williamson who's incredible like a
The case initially and certainly as the case now that you're bringing like
Bringing everyone together in a really cool way I think
Except for those people who I shan't
And all of the people that I have spoke
I'll tell you that right now to block you
Exactly
Getting back to this this idea
The Alex really was
Galvanizing force behind a lot of the
The Sandy Hook
Conspiracy
Theorizer
That was something that I took away from
What you were saying
Yeah that's exactly right I'm in love
That's what's so fascinating to me as you can see like
Network studies
Got done about these things you see the giant forum
The the big institutional home throughout
Fox News online
Breitbart
When you look at individuals
There's no one that you do really the only person
Comfortable reach to him in this basin
Joe Rogan and like obviously Jarvis a bit more of a complicated person
Then they probably have
Much less of a
Exactly yeah yeah yeah so when you go back and you look at what
Alison Brie husband
Huge for the time it was like
He had
In 2011 he already had half a million
Subscribers and like
No one at that point there was no one with millions of subscribe
YouTube
Right, Sandy Hook you already have 100 million views on his page it was
Really really substantial
Like other people who
You know wood
Tubi
Given that conversation I'd like Bill Cooper was dead
She could really be
The widespread ended
Visual Voice
Kind of
But not really it's not the same thing
There are a lot of angels
Information if I recall correctly Hangout
Alex Jones is really does hinge point where it's like you're saying
She was there in the 90s he was doing the
Does television
Was incredibly
Yeah pretty early on
Depressed about weight
Yeah
You know I haven't I have a quick question to ask you one of the funniest parts about your
Testimony which of course is the only thing I pay 10
Ancient Oaks
That was a good one. Hahaha
Is the the
Position of how Alex
Describes all of his guests as
The most qualified.
Top of their field
The single grader
This person everybody knows this person
Could not have tried to twist the knife more at the beginning
When he was like
Where did you graduate from
Oh that's
Cool let me ask you a question did you graduate from
Genuinely the most
Early Autumn
At Mark and he knows what he's doing and so I
Good hands but it was really
How many degrees do you have
Just suggest her
That would be embarrassing
Badham
Yeah I got into there then I was like they're so cute
Institution
Harvard
Turned out its share of people
I dropped out of high school
And after that
Applying for colleges
Is and
I was
Guaranteed basically that I
I could get into the University of Missouri
I lived in Columbia and it was easy
The only other college I applied to was Harvard
Missouri
Makeup for me dropping app could not work out
Evocative
Submissive
I regret nothing
Another
As fun as I believe it was
Or did that question not make it through
Yeah there was a juror that aisle 32 swear under oath that I was not a lizard person
The question did not make
Get through so I didn't get the
Gallagher time to really reveal yourself to the world I guess
Christmas Eve that I am not allow
The podcast
Yeah that's a good point we tried to clean doesn't hold you accountable for what you
I can't lie.
Attempted love Claus it's terrible
30 greater than that of the
The law
I'm thinking about this
This this
Picture of the media landscape back then in like 20
12 realize
Lycoming Coast AM
Is probably one of the biggest
Things
Other than Alex
The touches on some of these issues
But even seem silly to say because Alex was
Constantly
Even like
A couple times I hit Steve pieczenik
Coast to Coast
It's not say if you need a big
Can you call Stevi B's
That that wasn't done
Peter Griffin
Cookout
We got to get the guy who murdered all those Muro in here
It's about the internet at that point and I feel like
Episode about like
Facebook being an entirely different place back then too
B11 you find when you go back and start rooting around in like archive.org
Bless
Verified account
So you had Alex
I thought you also had like
Do the dozens of every looking with the other recommended
Reposting and reposting is like
Something better
Hard for us to even conceptualize now and this
Is there a difference
Yeah that's right I bet I could have buried that memory but there were no a
Couple of times
The friend of mine was like
Became friends with a celebrity on Facebook
It was like that's not a real account
It is it is like thinking of it as the Wild West
When you think of the Wild West you think
The distance
Pass not like
A few years ago
We still think of social media
Obviously it is but
BMO
That has changed
I meant your point about the kind of
You know Alex Jones
Something bad
I didn't really have time to
Different creators
Amplify each other and each other's ideas and create
Like self-reinforcing
Reference Alex Jones as like the authority and be like
This idea
Networks of people
We're all going on each other
Shows were all-time amplifying each other
And seem like they're kind of sightings
Yeah
It's like almost circular credibility but it's a completely different shape
It's a million sided shape of
Self-feeding credibility
That's kind of what I was going to ask
Could you give us kind of like a visualization of how that
Disseminates like what I kind of see in my head is almost
These these Giant Circles that eventually
Well actually I can
Actually
Brought you into biosphere
The alternative influence Network
Reported
I believe
2017 and 2018 Buick LeSabre
Yeah yeah
If there is a visualization in there with a bunch
Sublime
Between
Surprised I haven't read the answer to my question alright
This is a visualization of things in 2018
And so I would imagine
That would be
You know the way we
What's so fascinating is
Different
But Landscaping
Couple years later
Frances that you've noticed
Specifically
100% yes
Yeah 100%
I feel like well first of all
Think about that
Got Network
Made was
It was specifically looking at kind of like
Dave Rubin
Person
Influenza
I'm interested people from Alex Jones
World on that Network
Start
Ended up having to wait him out because she was at the center of his own alternative
Is that like if you
Brawl like
A completely
Even though
There's a ton of overlap
Well I guess at the time probably not
Nick Fuentes
Radar
Joe Rogan Candace Owens
Gavin
Cernovich
But yeah
That's better than
Interesting that he would he would be his own
A visualization of a yarn pattern
It's like Circles of influence and where they are and I'll
Alex Gibson Amorphis
Blob cancer cell Somewhere over the distance pack some stuff
Everywhere
If I include Alex Jones I need to do an entire other report
Hasn't happened but
But yeah
They're not in the algorithm
Exactly so credit
I think
Wild
100 people that aren't
Literally said I am a white nationalist based on empiricism
You know
Right
Because people didn't yell at him and told him
Adult bar
Keep them but I would have so many receipts
And then
Also it's just someone who is able to
Is such
He was such a powerful radicalization point right
Because he was someone that
Maintain
Credibility for a while that he would get invited and so
Right
Mainstream
Again quote on Co credibility
More openly extremist shows
Speak his mind
He was
Just like no one to be
What about this
Told you know
I believe that he was one of those mentioned by name
But
Yes
Kick-off I think was a huge deal
The fact that like red ice and some of these other kind of openly
The big deal
Change
Actually
I wanted I wanted to touch on Red Ice really
Quick because
They've come up a couple times on our show in the past
I owe you looking at this
Bears 2018 report
Henry
Weigh-off
In the side of this
Visualization of the network
But
I was thinking about this as I was looking at it
That's right real quick I just want to interrupt
So because we can't see you on the screen Becca you just need to know that man instantly brought up your article on
Computer that I brought up how stupid I am
Refresh myself on a beacon
Alex
They would be much closer and much more
Connect people in Alex's world
Super everything that's right I did my prep
For the for the trial
I kept encountering them because it was
What were the Wolf Gang you went under a couple of several of these
It's crazy man with Nixon.
Has backed on a white nationalist show
I would say this is a
Conservative us
Estimate
M250
P-unit of Alex's
Crew
Earth-like roster of
Of gas. I've appeared on Red Ice
It would be a lot
And obviously it's not
The amount
Anti-Semitism in white supremacist
Alex Jones
Baking in tub
Conspiracy theory
The way that you
You come to see it is
Through the people that he is
Working West because
But then the people that key amplifies if you go onto their shows they're not
Right he's crazy laundry
You know
Play some point he had Owen Benjamin hosting the 4th hour
Before he had gone
Full
Stop talking to him
And he was just hanging out drinking in his backyard
So it was a middle space
Alex
I mean I don't know if
You could say that tired him
But he was hosting the fourth hour once a week
Birthday
Thunderstruck
Now it is it there
What does still has a channel on
On Bandit video edit post
Some bad stuff
Can I ask you if I could do you feel like
In your research you've seen
A lot of these people
Become more extreme or just
Stop
Laundering
It so much do you know what I mean like
Actually increasing the extremity of their language or they just
Being like finite
I can just say it now
Yeah I think it's a combination of
First of all you do have this
Interesting Dynamic where
Understandable I think there's been a lot of
Anxiety around YouTubers radicalizing
YouTube viewers witch
But then you also have this other
Feedback loop because
Viewers now Henry's Plumbing
And like on Livestream, and real-time and all these things
You actually have audiences demanding more extremist
Contact from Creed
Weird feedback we were it's like
Creators end up
Responding to the wishes of Their audience like I would say that
Tim pool is a really classic case of this more like
I've done the knowledge fight
Treatment on gym floor
Olive
Is content
Start amount of time
It's so interesting to watch him in a bit by bit into the positions that he has now
Imperfect being
Call Wendy Delgado. Stop.
Responded to it
Yeah
And I think maybe along the way he tried to convince himself of some of these ideas
Question of
How much is it come from Matthew we're kind of saying yeah exactly
I don't like
But the Republican Party
Husband going
Further and further to the right
Nissan
I believe the day or the day after Viktor Orban
Oh my God
We all love each other right
Weirdly
Find the YouTube
I think the people that were
Strategic enough
Straddle the line ever
Open Lisa a white nationalist are white supremacist
Still use that rhetoric
They're still thriving and their rhetoric
He's getting more and more extreme
Riley reiff
What are my biggest pet peeves is when people talk it up
Fringe
Friends
Sitting there
In some of the most
Powerful media position
He's an incredibly powerful
Attitude
I've done this important presentations where I just take
Replacement Theory
The Christ
Christchurch shooter
Charlie Kirk
And a quote of Jason
And there's more
4 quotes about
Great replacement Siri or indistinguishable
Courts
You take away though
Yeah that's gas something that I have
Long
Thought
Like
Bowser taken out of context
In context all of this
The stuff they were talking
I'm about
Ends up worse
The other thing too dude that I thought of what you're saying these things
These statements are the same
With the names removed the most
Difficult episodes
Was about the day of
Anders Breivik
Over his Manifesto
Does the
If you were to isolate just
The words of this
It would sound
Very familiar to the hours listeners
It was kind of a revelatory mobile
I meant for me I was like
How
Gross
Gateway you're saying like it's not friends
It is it's
The stuff that's in a brevik Manifesto is
Broadcast on
Places
Xterra
Exactly I really like there's a really good
Define
As
An in-group
But
Define
Their success
Only by
Punishing an out-group
Evergreen Lake
Owning the libs
Definition is like he says it's a misunderstanding
To say that
Extremism is defined by being outside of the mainstream
Because if you think of some of the most important extremist regimes in history
Beware the main street right Nazism Nazi Germany
What's the mainstream
UFO
He thought was the mainstream extremist
We still hang out
That like
Somehow
That's one of the jury members ask me the question of what
Which I thought was
Question
Couldn't put the lighter that right if you guys like call tell him I miss all the time that it's like
When is advantageous to him he's
Where does the nut start little you don't work for the underdog information
It was a really interesting part of your testimony especially when the question
Came from the jury because
Cuz that was almost The Identical question Bill asked
It is deposition
Define it and then see if
Don't fit all of those definition
Basically walked in
Conceding that
Himself and most of
The people he thinks are free
Are actually mainstream according to Zone definition
Exactly
Most powerful people I'm here you know
Of course
Yeah like a million times via traffic of CNN's somehow
Everybody
To CNN we have more business you are always knows everything
I was just going to say that
Free line on a on a recent podcast that stuck with me and I'm going to do is
Alex Jones
Tomatoes picking Everest
That's
Shop
Define dollars
A completely opposite
And somehow
In his mind and in his rhetoric
And also throws a hat on
Came out of my right
Just indignation over the
Volcano
Something
Who is the strong
It's been a long time since I sat down
Episode
Speech
I don't know
Have you had a chance to see Alex's documentary by chance
I have not yet I listen to your podcast episode about it but I haven't watched it yet
Chocolate
Good Luck Charlie
Confirmation bias
How did it
Field to be cross-examined by the defenses lawyer because
The moment he asked
You after what one he said two things that made me want to
Before you
Before even started asking you questions he was trying to imply that you were unqualified
The fact that we heard
A list of qualifications that can only be described as
The most
Qualified to sit in that chair
And then
And then later when he asked
What confirmation if you knew what confirmation bias was
I was ready to jump over the over the walls and do they like
Yeah it was it was a wild
Experience I mean
I'd be lying if I said this was my first time like you don't testify
Your first time
Part of me wishes by a baby been able to do like a lower profile
Open mic
Do you know the information really phase me because
Particularly actually with this
That one called
Such a stir among the
Amazed
That exact
Line of reasoning like at me and so
To me that wasn't a new
Thing that I've heard
It's not only directed at me like
That line being red
But the irony of it
Because of course they're using that line
Defensive
Target on Bayou
They might as well literally say I'm Rubber and you're glue like a piece of that
Demeanor
Exactly
I think that was my main thing throughout this whole thing of I'm a teacher and so like
Hawkins Missouri to me
I could just kind of be in teacher mode and that to me is really like
Natural
Academic I'm not used to having these interactions that are by their very
Structure
Adversarial
I would find myself
Questions and
Miami responses like
If I get the chance I can
Can really explain to this guy how things work not really understanding that he doesn't give a f*** it all
Rock chuck
This is not a teaching opportunity
Blacksilva lawyer
Different in that context to be like okay what
Pacific Catch
It really getting into the weeds
Statistical stuff
And so I was trying to gauge like okay how much do I prove that one
Nonsense
Well overdue
Yeah
They were getting towards I could ask questions he was getting towards basically like prove to me statistic
6 exist
It was leaning towards like
The bickering about sample sizes and what have you
Is is this a credible Outlet
Sprite
This statistic
These are based on phone interviews you don't even know if those people are real do you
I don't even know how to
Engage with a person who's like if you call somebody on the phone
It doesn't count as another human being
Easier to respond to like when you start getting into
White like what is statistical significance that was the part where I just decided not even to engage with it cuz there's no way
I'm going to be able to respond to that in like
Like 30 seconds
Remember
Actually answer the questions he was
We'd like to introduce exhibit 6
Before that is a 6 hour lecture by Becca Lewis on how to expand a deal with
Statistics in media literacy
What's an all-around
Unresponsive
Spot that I have two bad question
To this alternative
What's Network
Because you know
What you did
Lot a lot of blowback from people included in it
I'm not bad
Is the miac report of lying
These people around here and we see where they've gone sense
Your arguments are a little bit
I want to die
Because you know you're somebody who still watches a lot of this
Stop and you still are studying
This space
Outside
If YouTube
Who do you think
Is
Like
The big nodes now
Like who would you think
Sauron
On Radars or should be more on radars
And
Secondarily
Do you think
Babes
The people who are on here
It did
Anybody
Assembly
Or
I'm not sure
The freezer
Isn't great
Maybe get what I'm asking
He was really big for like 3 months
But you know what it was interesting to me is
First of all how much of this network has
The overlap more with kind of cable news networks
At this point I don't know how I could talk about these figures without talking about Tucker Carlson as well
Kellyanne Conway is a regular guest on MSNBC now yeah we're front
I'm like you.
Did entire segments kind of like
Christchurch shooter ended up
Before
Damn
I'm so I don't know how
I could do that without talk about him
Whatever
Endorse it Amplified Lauren Southern inside of a
Eclipse conspiracy theory about farmers in South Africa
Now
Doing that America
Sincere
Ecology will be reported as a 100%
Sent this to your apology
She's also still suspicious about immigration
I mean I really think that
What happens if
YouTube
Bunch of people you also had some
But then there was a
And I do think it was people like Glenn Greenwald and Matt Taibbi who stepped into it and so
It's a little bit lesson
Whatever they were doing
Was clearly strategic bringing them Fame and it felt like
Dave rubenesque move
Why I left the left
And now here they are.
With a little bit less YouTube eccentric but
It's still about the
Network of Pi Vincent loose network of influential people who are they
Hope each other out with networking but also maintain some type of plausible deniability
Glenn Greenwald
Alliance that Dave Rubin Hughes about interviewing people like Stefan molyneux
5 years ago
Freehold has about be like
It's identical essentially
I'm not on the right but the left has gone too far
Kind of
Mentality
And that's exactly what feeds into
Need a right-wing audience
Further right-wing audience
Anesthetizing them to the idea that they're further to the right than they
I think they are
Absolutely
And then I think the other big figure has been sewing
But somehow has managed to stay
So under the bed
Billboards
What side of Midway
Like it's not in Time Square from what I saw on
I don't know if those were photo ShopRite
Yeah I seen the ones outside of Midway driving back just going like what
In God's name is that I know you didn't believe it at
Further Evidence
That is not a real Airport
That's true
Yeah it's a bus station
Who is somebody who
Cover Maybe
And like people have ass
Stupid
You seem like somebody who is
Attention
That like you try to start a fight with me and I Ciara
More trouble than it's worth
And other people are somewhat paying
To have
You see some critical
Call Copper Ridge
Where is Whitney started
Like there was really anything
That was
Sort of pointed in the right direction
I always liked those why I left
That's why I left
The Democratic party poster why I left the left
That's for the
Never say
Millions of dollars
It's so weird how they suddenly get millions of dollars and they say it's all the principal position
That's one of Alex's like soda
Pieces of his
His own sort of Mythology
Believe like with me like I was offered all of this stuff and I turned
Turn it down or not but like
Toppers at Fox
The idea that you'll have a book that you put out and will automatically make it about
Resolute
Types of writing
People I think
Totally totally
Pressing and cynical and
In a weird way even more depressing than like the True Believers because
With a True Believer you can
Workout de-radicalization and
I mean not to be too flippant about it but it
It's like The Big Lebowski wine rightly say what you will about
Nihilism
Behind
Just doing this stuff for profit and thinking you're above the
The politics of it
Is just so disgust
With the True Believers those are the ones where I I still hold out hope
That you can somehow either people that work on D radicalism
What do you do with someone else
It's hopeless
Yeah I really do money runs out I guess
Just people into far as like
I respect
People who believe
You know like who really believe all of it
Contrite
Do the stuff
Even if I think it's
Absurd
At the very least I can see them
Processing this information
Leaving it
Singapore
It's the people who are
Manipulating them
Let's say a trillion dollars in gold
That they wear around their neck or whatever
It's like you're the most month
Monstrous thing I can
With Alex Jones viewer these people
It's a little bit like thinking about
Cult member to go onto Lake Recruit new cult members to take away the responsibility of
The Alex
You are too went on to harass the Sandy Hook
But it is to say that they are old
So being harmed by Alex
But his rhetoric because
Galaxy
Meaning of life
And they are trusting him to deliver the
Truth
They are also harmed by this
Even if they are part of the
Yeah right like leaving
Someone like
I was at Lucy Richards and the books of rastas
Principal I always
Tried to
Look at things as like
Empathy
Towards the consumer
Of this b*******
And like
Really real strong disdain
Producer
A being at least
Just serve
Sure ending in the
This case specifically
Part of
Holding
Alex
Accountable is that
The people who who harassed
Speedy family
They are the
There's a bullet
You know
And
I don't like bullets
Any more than I like
The person firing the gun
But if you
Try and like
Punish the bullet
It'll find mobile
Stop making bullets
Totally totally
Yesterday I told
My
My class about kind of
The First Amendment
Social media
Give you a standing ovation when you walked in the room
Something that like
Working on this thing
Historically thinking about the First Amendment
This idea that Alex
What's John's promos
First Amendment freedom of speech means that I personally as an individual
I want to say
Do not Bend
The first amendment has been understood like throughout the history of the United States
Regal
Think about
Communal sense
I'm thinking about you
Forest within a community
Part of freedom of speech is also
The freedom to
Valuable information
Whatever it's the sorry I'm rambling.
Noble in real truth yes
Yeah I think
I always
Find that
So interesting
But in noise
Makes sense
The notion of the First Amendment the people like Alex
Exist
But like
It's so boring how much they bring it up and
Completely
Lockable situation
The fan of Base
The true American Pastime is misunderstanding
Cabela brights if someone hits a ball out of the park and they
It's not just Alex Jones but
It's a social media pop
The reason that it's
That's
The reason they promote that idea free spaces because that's the idea
Is it crazy to think about how it's not just the people who use Facebook who are
Advancing this concept it is Facebook itself because they don't have to hold them
Themselves accountable
Hey Google spell this idea of like
You should be allowed to say whatever you want
You know exactly exactly
Yeah that's interesting
Picture then going to
It becomes more clear that there's a lot more responsibility to go right
Responsibility to go around I find absurdly high
Pretty
This is not
Responsibility
Saumur
I mean it goes
It goes all the way back to you know we discussed it a while back look problematique
She know like the the idea that Oliver
These things are interconnect
They are not a visual elements to individual things
They're all part of
A larger hole that we're not
Jordans
Open to an academic
The club of Rome
I pulled out the one thing I remember from our past
I know Jordan you like to say that
You say that you're not whatever you're about to
To say next do not say it he's gotten too much positive feedback over the last two weeks
If I remain a clown and I shall stay one
Till the day I die
How dare you madam
Make you angry for a second and say something another night
Quality junk food delivery was
The media
Homebridge
The Alex Jones trial I think have been
So necessary on spot on because
This is actually right before I wrote the my report on YouTube
My
How much
The mainstream media plays a role in the amplification
Hitting the nail on the head with all of that and the coverage
Journalists who have been there like day-in-day-out version
Elizabeth
But then the people don't forget Murdock
Sebastian Reserve
People that have left Twitter presence but like there's an incredible
Text Mom
Easy crafts
But then you get all these other people parachuting in only one
Push back a tiny bit on your compliment
2 Jordans
Please
I think that you're totally right
I bet the critiques that you were making and putting forth where it where it
But also let's not
Glenn Greenwald
The end of that
Critiques sure
I just I just feel like the last thing I said was
No I mean I do
One of the big
Big things that
The media absolutely refuses to acknowledge is that
Part of the reason
They like to amplify
These voices
It's so they get the clown on them
And then creating that
Owning the conservatives turns into another owning the libs
Zenit just created a speed bag
And they refuse to acknowledge their partner
Well
I think saved
In cases like that wrong
Lookout ski
There it is
It's kind of the same criticism released
That I had of the documentary
MMA like you're not giving
People context
So you're showing me something
He would probably stand Bhai
And already know it's not right
And already have some sort of a criticism for it
But instead it's the
Just being broadcast to
People
I don't think it gets the effect
That absolute or putting it for
Seemed to think it was
Richard Spencer
Because
Anytime
Wanted to talk to him he was
More than happy
Oh yeah it's going to prevent worker profile about him
Are we mean to them
Ninety-nine out of a hundred people read
She doesn't care it's that one person who wasn't so him and says maybe he has a point that he's trying to reach out
AI thinq
People like
What are the reasons they can be
Effective is because of
Very first
Fraction of the first part of what they're saying
Is a valid critique of the mainstream media
Take it from there and taken wildly inaccurate awful directions
Sensationalist
Is true
Well that's a problem with a lot of his
There's a critique of the government being
Ineffectual are not representing
Necessarily the will of the electric
There's things like that
Yummy just
To be totally clear
False flags do eggs
It is a thing that
Kernels
Of something
You get some too much mileage out of there is there is the simplest protect that there is to make honestly
Please like
The same thing that you could safer the Democrats like what your real elect
Stability comes from isn't what you
You say it's
If you govern well people will be like hell yeah
Because you're also failing maybe you're doing some good
Maybe you're doing on the whole more good then
Been bad
But at the same time
If you're not willing to
Engage with all the bad you're doing then you're just going to
Total
I just want to
Pearl's I think so
Dangerous
Because
A mechanism by which took out of a snare people in
Hundred percent
Hold on I didn't get I don't think I got an answer
Search my question from earlier
Who else should we be afraid of
Oh I think the exact people that you're
B l u B10 Tim pool
Some much more
Institutionally powerful have in common
What's interesting is that for a while it was this group of
For lack of a better word like internet weirdos
And some of these people who are in this you-know-who or people you
Are people who have ascended to more
Eczema
Institutional power like
From having
Like a YouTube thing
Do now he's on
Glenn Beck's net worth
Steve
Crowder is there la
Significantly sent
This point
Nick Fuentes
Do you know back then was just sort of the Nazi who would go in
Argue with people on
Cozy streaming platform
Certainly more centralized Milo yiannopoulos
Rapallo
Now I guess is
Working with Marjorie Taylor Greene
Right
Marjorie Taylor Greene
A literal members of Congress
Who are on board with you spoke
That has
Significantly changed the landscape as well
Yeah I mean there's also an argument that I
Coming back to of like
It is very easy to get
Caught up in this sort of recency bias
While at the same time
Being like well
You know things were different back then people were more in the middle and maybe there's just part of it there's that
Because Society was so geared towards White
People
To say anything you know like
Extremist during slavery uo
After the government you're like not the government gives me
People to do things for free
I think
But I think you get
People claiming that its all the earnest balls and I don't think that's true at all it's like
Republican Party
That was starting
In the 1960s
The tweet that I was still good lawyer was trying to catch me up
So funny
It was racist
He got
Got you good
The southern strategy wouldn't have
Unless there was a demand
Yeah exactly
Yes
100%
And none of this other
None of this contact the production of it they were discussing
Yeah
Is there tapping in July
I know I know this
Curious to hear how
How you are feeling after what he's just been like a roller-coaster couple of weeks
Because
Yeah I found it to be blessed
Sleep then I've ever not had a bad week for sure
He totally clear
We're recording this after the
Compensatory damages
Puppy
They're still deliberating the punitive
The full outcome of everything
But yeah it was
You know it it's
The case itself
And going to the trial was
Draining
Pretty
Rewarding and I think I'm starving
Starlux testimony in particular was something that I
Think we'll
Prenote stay with
Many people for the rest of their life I won't forget it
I don't know baby I'm in a unique
Position because I was there for the depositions
Daria
It's so
Heard a lot of
I'm Turnt
The first few days
And so for me it was kind of a
There was a lot of
A lot of
Some of that stuff was a little bit of a
Exhausting
Everything
New
For my brain
That I really notice
The trial is that
Well I'll say there's two things like
First off
That job open
Putting Concepts that I really feel like
Glen and Matt
Just jumped in
I feel like we just jumped into a job open
There should be a media outlet that is
That has a
You know just people who study
One subject
So thoroughly
Oh god dammit
Chick-fil-A job openings
The other thing is that
When they were choosing
Jury
The concept of you should
Know anything about
Alex Jones or the Sandy Hook
Not a jury of your peers
Like the only peers metallic
Have our people who
Understand why Alex
Is never telling the truth
Or Never Lie
He just doesn't care
Whenever you get them
Caught out in a lie you know
Getting caught out in a perjury
Situation
He doesn't even know
Yeah you know
I think it was really exhausting
Think about the trial to was the
Constant
Pretend games
Defense was playing where they pretend to understand it was a damaged
Just hearing
Jimmy was
Exhausting
Yeah I just don't like a lot of emotional whiplash
Because
Constant
Thing between like
The clownish nusenda
Constant chaos of Alex
Don't world
Sense of tragedy that was there
And forth between those
Two incredibly
Emotional states
Chewy solid yes
The Tuesday where it was Neil and Scarlett in the morning and then Alec
Likes testifying after was
Just like
We both went home and we're just
Done
You know yeah absolutely
It's like
No you all have been saying it's just
And then I find my phone
Charlotte
I feel I feel like that's
Such a great point
Something that I
I feel privileged
I've been able to
To like
I did a few interviews
The things and being able to like
Stressthem
Yeah
I've been really
I think Airport
Might be able to have that voice
Out is when I have
The reporters have seems to
Fry's
Only talk about Alex Jones
Kind of makes me a little bit
Forest for trees is going on
But we got an email
From
The
From a t-shirt
I can see you're getting a lot of heat for this trial thing do you want to do a special on your shirt
I just
Replied back
Hey listen
Are you saying that we should
Profit off of
The families of Sandy Hook is that what you're really trying
Can you tell me right now
Cuz that's what you are telling me
I want to light you on fire
Yeah yeah yeah totally
Like
Absol
Appreciated
But also it's like it's not it's not about me
Surrounding this it's about
Yeah it is
I think
Is great about our listeners
I do think that they are appreciating you because of it
Hundred percent it is on
Madea family
Because it's
It's
You know you're a presence that is there helping
Highlight this
This thing
So what about you like
Experience of being there
Get a chance to meet in person
Future schedules
What specifically trying to lay low before I went on the
Yeah
It was very funny you didn't know this but actually at one point maybe you didn't know this but actually one point I was sitting
Directly behind you while you were having a conversation with
Mister zip about your upcoming
Testimony
I don't think he had any idea who
You also sitting behind her
I thought you guys were
A couple of times in the courtroom
Are you there in person
What is hell what is hell
That really does make me good
In person but I saw them beans about the thought
Yes way better
We better do
Through the news
Kind of felt like
Like maybe you would be in a
Appropriate
TED Talk
Elsa
So because of like
Your status as a witness
And speak to anybody I tried to stay smiling
It's possible
Technically as an expert witness I think it would have been fine but that was my
I'm not going to go up and introduce myself to them until after I
Testify but then we didn't
We didn't get a chance to you
So that's funny that we all knew who
It's like
It's really similar like I found it to be
Shrilling at times because if it really does feel like this
This is the start of
Snowball of accountability hopefully
At other times I found myself feeling like it doesn't matter how much money
Ends up
Coming back
So much damage has already been done that can't be undone
I don't know I just I find myself
I did find like you
Commentator
The Dynamics of the
The trial and the media around it and everything are fast
There was like my directions
Oh she responds to it and then there was also the like
Celebrate life
The way that I was
Are trying to
Abused the justice system in the same way that they were
Abused the media so
And succeed
I don't know if you had the same response that I kind of did but as I know come home
And I have a little bit more
Distance from that I realized I felt a little bit of a dissonance
And maybe even a little bit of a shame
About the
I tried to as
Much as possible
Despite my
Empath
Speech at the beginning of the Greenwald episode
I tried to keep
Sort of
Distance
From the tropics
Should we cover
Do not
Just be you
I don't mean that
It's it was really difficult
That I have a
Huge interest
And
Attached
Approach
But we have this
The person that I've been studying
And this is
This is
Ridiculous
At the same time
Possible
To not have an emotional
Connection
Experience of seeing
Me and Scarlett
In the
In the courtroom and test
Aspiring
And their therapist
Get that back
Conflict
Was
Was really difficult
Olivia really a fan of weeping in public but
I mean
There's no other way
In-N-Out
Completely agree and I struggle with adjustments
Adult thing
Sometimes I think that the dissonance
Take me to sings against each other
They don't need to be pitted against each other but
Yukon Yukon
And this is maybe a little bit
Trying to get across when I talked about confirmation bias that like
2 beer
Starting with the data
Having confirmation bias doesn't mean you can't have opinions or emotions about the things that you're
You're studying
Start with the data
And you let that inform your your thoughts
Opinions
You still have those thoughts and opinions are just informed by the data
I also
She was in any kind of ethical way
You need to approach it with Humanity
Otherwise you're just going to get
Swept up in their propaganda
First and foremost and think about the
People that are being harmed by this rhetoric
I'm so just write a lot about how the families want money and Alex Jones is
Very sorry
For what he did
Admitted that he was wrong
I think that's a good way to do it someone who like
In 2016 there was this wave of scholarship that started to come out about the alt right that just came from these people that
Fascinating
Coming from it from a place
Thinking about
Why does this matter
And the minute that you start thinking about why does this matter there's going to be a motion
It's actually
Important to hold space for those
And I don't have to
Contradiction to approach anything from
Appreciate that point I think that's I think that's it
Definitely right
It's still
It still can be
Difficult but I think you're totally right
But I think
I think most people especially in America
Believe it
Expertise leads
Tobias
You know like
Because you understand all this stuff
Can't think about it objectively
AAA
Because I
Think that most people
Refuse leads you to be
Like sort of a cold
Passionate
Professor is in like classics
Philosophy
But the lot of them are pretty
I mean
The reaction to experts in well I mean like a reaction to dr. fauci
To these people
Give me doctor Faust
There is a bias
Against people who knows
Yeah
How could I not
You had a
Position and then they hired you is
Tired
Off the Dome I'm going to go and say Alex might be good
Let's look at another unfortunate reality and that is that anybody who is
Is probably
Assertive
Credentialed to be in the position you were in
Has a negative
Text with a different opinion there were none
Nobody was like Ali
Jones is really bringing the world to a better place except
Maybe Steve
Selective insurance
In social science to write you have people that try to
Say that you need to take this completely alike
View from nowhere
And then you have
People that are more like
Sonographer
Escape around 4
Perspective it's about
Understand
I'm so it's like yes
As a woman
All of the things I'm very conscious of how that effects
The way that I read
Let's Go Crazy
You say conscious of that when I'm reading anti block races
I'm not going to fully understand the pain that that bring
Of course they're ways to understand like where we all are
Situated in the world
It's not about confirmation bias it's about
The
The very academic you word about it
Positionality
You see things and
Yellow
It is it is a little bit like the idea I saw University of Chicago economics
Study
About
Slavery
That treated slavery is like
Purely an economic system and like
Was this a libertarian
University of Chicago economics
To do stuff
You can't say I feel like ethically that is just a wrong
Nothing to do
The libertarian study on
The economic impacts of
Feeding your child
What are we
Beneficial for economics
Problem is
You care about your child that's where this whole system is gone because it's negative you have no positive obligation
With the wrong
Inside of it
We should probably wrap
This up before too long
First this has been a delight and I hope we can talk
Again soon
But second
I have the livestream up up the courtroom
There's movement in the courtroom
Possible cab price
I feel like we all have an interest
He's probably a heads-up absolutely thank you so much for having me
How much of your podcast
Listen to when I was prepping
Thrilled to hear and and right back at you or your work
Published pieces
Have been really important
In terms of giving
Stand
Insights into a lot of it
This world so we will take
You
Listen to our show to apply Dan's life's work
Good
I'm glad that
I could look at
US Weekly
A
Exactly
Is there any clown college
I wish I had a hawk
Is there is there anything you'd want to direct our listeners to the place we can find you
Are you sure you can go to if you're interested read my research website
B u c c i l l e w. Net
Awesome
Thank you again for joining us thank you so much
Just a treat
And I like I said I hope we can speak again soon thank you for being a voice that centers the Families 2
@stephanie
Another episode but until then
Okay
A wonderful dreamy creamy summer
Alex
In color
I love your work