Jordan
Knowledge fight knowledge I'm sick of them posing as you're through the good guy or the bad guy
Knowledge
Alex
College.com
I'm a little bit about Alex
Indeed we are.
My bright spot today is
We
What fun I don't know what am I doing
What does has become weaker celebration celebration
Celebration
It said yeah you can celebrate the sneak candy do we have the interview with reliable so
Sources Brian stelter on Sunday
Monday we have of the world exclusive interview with the lawyers extended Bill Ogden
So funny that we do
Then Becca Lewis on Tuesday but
In order for sneak week to really be sneaky
You expect shows always playing
We snuck and we didn't have something on Wednesday and do you know what else when people think
We bag
That's when we're going to dog baby radio but I worry because Zog means
Occupied government
I have to put an embargo on that joke
Yeah but
We have about the trial time
Time and getting up to speed on a lot of that stuff right and then Friday we cap off sneak week
With an appearance on the majority report
I think I maybe I don't know I've been looking forward to that
I have been a big fan of salmon to his work
And so I guess I'm looking forward to absolutely
Septapus to Sam the entire time
But you're going to have a tough time not doing home movies
Do you remember when you played the the vampire guy
And you were like I forget everything you know about how you remember that be great
I have thoughts about like various interviews he's at with academics authors
Debate these donors libertarian
Stocktwits
Steven Crowder voice acting
Yeah there we go
My bright spot is I put it up I finished it I compiled all of the
Annoying tweets that I made and I got rid of all the insults and all of the personal tax and all of the anything that
At the trial because
I wanted to share a disorienting experience with people there's going to be way better
Books written about it
That make more sense in that will be enjoyable to read
But you won't get the real experience of being there I think it was disorienting a none enjoyed I think a lot of people
People are going to resolve the lack of insults I think people are going to want salt
Well problem you've cultivated probably more like now
Here's the problem the final draft
Fifty thousand words in
I don't know if you recall what I said the initial amount of total words I've written over the side.
No 20000 cutout I know how to take care of things
Play ratio my website the quiet part loud it's the front page
DeBarge
Existed
All it is is that you can download it as PDF PDF
Don't pay anything for it I don't give anybody anything for it donate
Body or just read it
Well
What fun for everyone who is wondering where are those
Had a good time you're at your new job you refer to
I got a gig one time and it is death for me it is
Schoolboy night anyway to describe
Because somebody's paying you to do it
Edits sad
One of the trial coverage
Surrounding
Iora in some
Surrounding stuff will be a little bit more in the next episode is going on
Over the
Testimony that Alex gave at the trial
Which I didn't expect we were going to cover cuz I thought all that stuff was like you can't make copies of this but then
Blonde crime that so
Nothing you can do about it videos
Are you smell that audio
So we're going to cover Alex's
The the
Direct questioning from Reno and then the cross-examination
We're going to get into the aftermath of the
Compensatory damages going to leave off Alex's response to the compensatory
Damages
Waiting for the next day when he will end up in the punitive fiction
Okay so that is that is what part one will cover and then part 2 will pick up and go from there
One is is far from home and then the next one is endgame
I forgot how these
Movies of titled I haven't seen any of them
Geico yes
Good call 100% perfectly accurate Marvel metaphor
Let's get back
2 something we haven't done in a while say hello to some new walk
Responsive thank you so much right now policy walk
Next astynomia podcast you inspired me to fact-check my local butcher
Great weirdo in podcast form
Can you remind me next year in Middle technocrat drop make me feel three years younger thank you so much you are now
Thank you very much
Justin and Tony
You're going Sim Bob way
Got that what I thought I thought it was baby you're the one
Aspen Parkway
It may be easier to just pronounce the Michaela my mom was a creative spellers
Michaela
Ewok
Thank you very much
My husband
He's going to be so happy he's now a technocrat thank you so much
You are now a technocrat
Don't get mad and tell your brother someone sodomites
Has a Caribbean
I don't want
Jesus Christ so much we begin
With Alex being sworn in
I do think
But this isn't going to be a complete play-by-play of everything that happened
Honestly anyone who listens to our show be like this is boring
This is
You know
That was a lot of experience of us being in the room for especially as first day of just being like
Are you doing an ad read right now real include that but Alex
And he's try he tries to take
A piece of paper up to the stand with him
Which causes a little problem
I do
Call Alex
Steve Jones
Water and
Pretty good volume
Look at any
The lawyers
Myself
So I'm going to ask
It's fun about that is that you know Alex is so invested in the teleprompter
You know and I need strength to bring handwritten notes
The fact that they were handwritten to likes come on
Really yeah I mean on some level I get it I get the impulse
I would rather have.
Answer whatever question is
Butts
Yeah you can't you don't get to do that
Yeah I mean
We were this wasn't day one of the trial no
You know like we have already saved live
We've already experienced was Tuesday
I know this would have been a 7
V6
Yesterday six of the trial proper
If you don't count count Arizona
So
But it like
Weird scene for a week everyone come unprepared and then they had a weekend
Cuz what we have not discussed it up till this point you already had Owen Shroyer you already had diarrhea
You already had Becca you already had will zip yeah yeah mister Crouch
And so if you're already had like a real contrast and the Infowars people and the
Witnesses that were being called by the plaintiff's in terms of variability
Sure
I do Alex comes up all I also didn't include the part where he was scolded for chewing gum and then tried
We have some things to talk about
So when all comes in with his first question the things they
I think becomes abundantly clear really fast is that Alex does not appreciate
The notion of not being able to ramble
It's one of the things that he has it's the most sacred to him
He does not respond well to being told
You have to answer questions
Alex Wood
Yourself to the ladies and gentle
How are you feeling today
Instead of the corporate media
I want to
Start bike
Letting the jury know a little bit about
And where
Questions
So you can see here the in the first question Alex's asked he's already off track
He's trying to monologue in control the entirety of the conversation because he
He think you should be able to
Imagine that rental has had any success ever trying to keep Alex on point
Like off the sand so why should this be any different
At the end Alex says that it's not fair that he doesn't get to talk but she got to monologue
This isn't reference to Scarlet Lewis's testimony from just prior to him taking the sand and there's a reason why she got to monologue
Guess I'll explain it
It's because rain all knew damn well that he wasn't going to objecting interrupter
There is much of a s*** head is he seems to be I don't think right now is so detached from his Humanity as to deprive Miss Lewis
Of her chance to speak her piece to Alex
After all this time and him dodging the moment of having to look her in the face and hear her words
Truth be told
Louis probably was a bit off subject at a few points in her testimony and if reynald have ejected there's a real
Really good chance that the judge would have no choice but to refocus the question
But he didn't do that
And that's what Alex is mad about
You hit your lawyer didn't stop it
Right right right yeah I mean
It does seem like what is really causing Alex Eyre
Is that his lawyer did not
Badger Scarlett Lewis with questions
Or interrupt her answers of rush into that says appointed attorneys right
Sprinter you understand why we're here
I think that it would have taken a really cold cold lawyer
Your son.
Dark.
Alex doesn't want to stress as he was trying to sidebar that he was going down
I'll bet he apologized and he's sorry and all that so
Have you been one
Apologize
Yes
What would you like
Intentionally try to hurt you
Couple years ago
Questions questions
Hanover that
Her sister.
That's really been
I personally
This morning
I said I believe
That
I believe they're being manipulated
This apartment
Pizza Perfect
Oh my God
I was just lost power through my God so the clip he's talking about is something we went over on our
7-Eleven episode
Alex talking about how Jeslyn appeared slow
At all that's use he's trying to argue that this is a
Got a selectively edited everybody whatever his argument was essentially
You didn't play the whole clip
See what happened is the first thing I said was I'm sorry and then I said that because
Slow and that I
Think he is on the Spectrum this is not an apology that is Alex attempting to defend himself by saying that he
Mean to hurt anyone and he didn't actually even say things I would hurt them to begin with because
No people just take things he says out of context and attack him
This is pathetic
It's not about recognizing and respecting the pain that other people experience due to your actions
It's about pretending that you care they were hurt and that it was someone else's fault
It's cowardly but it's to be expected
Yeah I mean if you follow his words he's essentially saying
Basically
You're not smart enough to understand why what I did was actually okay Maya Cusick
Is that you just don't understand like you're mad at me
But really it's your fault
Right I didn't hurt you it's media lying about the things that I said I don't even know who you are
I never said your name
Yeah a very respectful thing to say in your defamation trial is a honestly I didn't even know who you were
It doesn't matter to me who might hurt it's almost Dickies and bison in the Street Fighter movie
Little bit like wow you are a real villain here today that I came to your village is the most important day of your life for me
Not great
Serana wants to humanize Alex obviously a part of this is walking through some of his earlier
Your life
Cut clips from all of it
Some stuff that just seem like this doesn't match up at all right now it's usually talk
Years of the first of that
Let us know where
Where are you from
How old were you
Add
You tell them
Why your fam
Too much crime in Dallas
Hoo-boy
You lived in Rockwall
Too much crime and Wealthy suburb
Documentary
Everybody's rolling around and rolls-royces and doing
There's too much wage stuff going on let me know there was a lot of crime going on in that neighborhood
Service employees were paid to little people he was
Round were not paying their employees well
You know what I respect that he knew better than to do the
I grew up in a town where a Satanist or trying to recruit me
To worshipping the devil because they knew that
I threw psychic powers the devil gave them I would be important to God's mission in the future
And I uncovered a drug ring within the Rockwall police department and they threatened to murder me if I didn't leave town
I think that maybe he knew that the jury would
Not take kindly to that it's clearly ridiculous
Be a little bit like the jury's punitive damages at that point would have to come back with like and he has to wear a straitjacket
Forever like that if you say that on the stand punitive damages stop being money I think I was pretty lucky that
This is not one of those in Upper formativa judge
So
Alex talks about some of his early influence
And this was one of those points were almost had to leave the courtroom
How old were you
Felt that you wanted
17 hour radio
Dylan radio
Radio
Also like Howard Stern the volume is fine
You like CNM you like the Clinton News Network
Please
This is a strategic answer on Alex's bar because he doesn't want to say to the jury that he was brought up listening to and admiring
Extreme far-right demagogues
And Christian identity radio preachers
He doesn't want to say to the jury that he was a devoted fan of the British Israelite preacher David Jay Smith
Or have you as a regular listener to the holocaust-denying preacher text Mars
Who is church Alex has said repeatedly that he attempts
He doesn't want to even tell the version of the story that he related and his documentary Alex's War because even though
Larry King and Howard Stern are largely mainstream touchstones and they do sort of shows that Alex wants the jury to
Think he does
Its total b******* but it's also very clear why he's presenting his inspiration to get it to mediate this way
So the jury doesn't get an accurate sense of what his career has actually been about
Also kind of makes Alex leave Moyers editing choices look even more embarrassing
The use of swelling music over Alex telling the tale of how he discovered people bring the fight to the New World Order on public access
That was the moment he realized he wanted to get into this field
Particularly dumb now
Just imagine the same music that she played over Alex and I really like Larry King's radio show they Wanted host
The chat program like
Knock knock. Quite so then let the same flare it is maybe you got played or maybe you wanted to be played
It is so very funny to me the idea of having made a documentary and then only days later
Hear your subject
It's almost completely disavow every single thing in that documentary yeah Underoath
I'm also like I don't know I'm getting recent Awards Vibes in terms of like
I think it was a lot of
Ramping up
Do it and it seems like no one care done
I don't know I mean I feel almost like I'm dumb for doing as much work
I kind of thought it would be a little bit more widely
Disgusting and maybe viewed
Then it then it was
Preemptive
For the creamer I mean they had some big names pre-marketing it you know like the interview is Greenwald it feels like
That should move the needle somewhat right and there were ostensibly order a lot of priori
Orders online which take however you want
I don't know
Alex's early show
30 did beginning of the
Different yes then the current weight
And what was the format of
Early shows
Amazon
TV
Just watch.
Okay
That's complete bulshit
Baby Alex did do a bit of goofing off on his show but it was also straight-up conspiracy contact
When is early public-access co-host Jeff Davis made a documentary together titled are you practicing
Communism if that gives you some time to the vibe he was working with back then
Hit really hard to get your hands on the shows from back then but the ones I've seen are complete b******* and conspiracy late
Nonsense
And it's super easy to find accounts from people who worked at the station with him back then
He was a raving conspiracy lunatic even back then he was an a****** and no one like working with him
That's why that's a big part of why his career took the trajectory
It would be it would have been more fun if that was like a PSA where it's like they're like
Are you practicing your piano lessons your like are you practicing your communism you're working on your confidence
Practice makes perfect Ru going to communist in Carnegie Hall is the question that you should be asking yourself
Yeah yeah I tried to watch that documentary I had to go
Get a table complaining about Tommy
Yeah it just was like
I can't I'm not going to do this there was no flayer
Nothing
No worries nothing anti-communist
Terrible
But look man Alex Alex
Love Letter game
Courts
About Larry King
Who would you say
Do artistic leave
Format
Your show
If Alex's dad listen to Larry King it was
Yelling at him
Larry King and Big Mike's Service f****** communist
I would almost believe that
And here's why
The Alex's need to interrupt over the TV
Sad to have come from somewhere I think it's entirely possible that he did watch his dad
Just interrupt Larry King screaming at the TV all the time
It's an interesting Theory
I think of that could just be a style he developed totally totally
Attention span highly knee-jerk reactive
But yeah I know you do what you see sometimes you know I'm just saying that I'm aging and now
Recognizing my my father's actions in my own and this is a tire lie about me I have no idea what we're talking about
Can't relate to that at all locked himself in a room only works all the time
Touches on his first documentary
A real fun climb
Did you also start make
In order to
Supporting for
Did you also start
Documentary
A documentary
America's Choice
Oh yeah that right
See this is like so indicative of Alex's s***
Like this
Pretending that his first documentary was about the great reset
Something that didn't become a Hot Topic in conspiracy circles until
2021 death basically like
This is so
This is what he's about he's about Reckoning
These things that he yelled about in the past and then applies modern
Labels and contacts to them in order to make it look like Alex Jones was always right
But you weren't yelling about the great reset
Texas the road through what was it what was it oh yeah yeah yeah
Transatlantic North American Highway corridor
Sign up sheet in them
You get off at 8 was it is like
We talked about it with with Market bill just a little bit but it is like
You can't really have a jury of Alex's peers
Out of anybody that's that doesn't like
How can you say oh you're you can't lie under oath to that
Like you and I both know that that's a complete lie I know I was going to say it I don't know if that's a substance
Reply to the totally totally maybe it's
Kind of fine for the proceedings of this that
No it's legally all that it is but there is a certain part of me that's like
You have to be able to know that Alex is lying even about
That
You know
Sure
Yeah I agree with that
I think that this runs into the issue of the separate realities
Because you know there's a part of Alex that probably believes
Absolutely had I was two years old
Reset the Lord spoken to me how does narcissism work and its effect on whether or not you think
You're being truthful
Yeah I know like and that's something they'll be difficult to unpack but I would say
Beto Thornhill oath
You're a fool if you think Alex is ever going to like
Actually give you truthful answers
A x answers
So we get back to talking about
The time of Sandy Hook
Alex's show
And what was his show like what was the environmental Infowars
You tell us what
Segments are that would appear
Hiiraan
Awards
4 Hour radio show
I want to watch online
And then
The primary goal of Alex's answer here is to downplay his own relevance in the size of his operation in 2012
He wants the jury to think that though he's a big famous boy now back then he's really just popped
Talk show
Unfortunately he's lying
He didn't just have a webcam on a desk at that point he had to Studios each with multiple camera angles of a
Available at any point
He also had more than just his show being broadcast daily since the Infowars Nightly News was in existence at that point
The Nightly News started in 2011
Instances of Rob do covering Sandy Hook
Alex knows all
But the goal is to create the perception that he really wasn't that big back then so it couldn't have been him that was so influential
And getting the Sandy Hook conspiracies rolling and causing the harm that was done to Niall and Scarlett
It's a fraud pretending a show he produced all the way to 2017 doesn't
Exist
Knox
Never heard of it before what's this I never heard of it before
I was I was thinking about this I can't think of any
Testimony
Real or fictional I have ever seen
That may be more Chuck filled with absolute non truths you know
And it is
It is like you were saying you know like
That's because in this world I don't think we're ever dealing with a truth or a lie that doesn't exist through dealing with both
And neither simultaneous know what's convenient and useful to me is the truth is the truth
And I believe it under a lie detector
Yeah
And I think that's
It's bizarre because you know
Narcissism for Alex Works in this way of like
All right when I need to inflate my self write in 2012 the biggest show in the world in 100
Marine radio station every world leader on the planet items to my shopping list
President
Owned one of those explicitly say that
Narcissism here is that he needs to not be very big
Because
It's important for him
To not have the grand title of the things that is make it right
Psychopaths is that the manipulating based on what they people think want to hear in any situation is that one of those
That sounds right
So with this next place is where Alex gets to talking about the
Howard talk show host
And
This is bizarre
Time
How did you
Stories that you
You wanted to come
Talk radio
95%
For what do you make of this
Is that
We worship with you and talk radio.
Fat collars when you think of that do you buy that
What do you think's going to happen next
Basically keep noticing
Who has made the best protection
Showbox
Is people speculating
Gyros
Alondra Park
Okay
That is one of the most absurd descriptions of like five different things I've ever heard
Exactly
He thinks that like his audience is sitting there with a pen and a pad ready
It's like it's like their head they have baseball score cards they're like single on this one
Draw one lights
Rush Limbaugh hits one out of the park I mean look from the time that we've been doing this show and the predictions that
We've seen from him if anyone was doing this
And talk show host who were judge by this
Qbr business
Outlier
Cars
Fortunate no one is keeping up a notepad goddamn
The world would have to have been destroyed multiple times over by now in order for his prediction said Annie
Decent tracker absolutely would be constantly getting nuked
Write the globalists would be
Starving everyone and we would all be dead of
A plague of locust and this is how Alex always kind of gets into your head
I dislike that is so insane that you almost forget he said that free speech is really just a dude stand
Sitting on a box in the corner he was in London screaming for 6
2u Jungkook by their predictions
But then you judge their predictions by how long they stayed in the stocks
I think that might actually be a better situation for us
Ma'am you have enough bad prediction to go to the stocks for a week I think that that is your right there
It is one of the tools of Alex's absurdity
There's constant heightening there's so many layers and up there to die so you're like
Part B is
Parties hilarious part D what are you talkin about what happened
Emma in a conversation about sources Alex
I said I want this person
That person
Five more control of the jet
Touching
Because
Costco
It's b******* that Alex is saying there's a moratorium on this kind of sourcing like some things on 4chan
If you want to take this seriously at all
Then what Alex needs to do is take a cut like a real hard look in the mirror
Take an inventory of the things that you said based on
14 posts
And retract all of it he needs to go back and look at the like
Soros antifa contract
You need to go back and find all of these things and really wrestle with like OK Google know this to be
A completely unreliable source do you need to figure out what parts
Of your mythology what parts of your worldview are solely informed by that
And work to get those out that make sure that people don't still believe them cuz otherwise you're still using
Orrtanna thesaurus essentially
Are two important thing
Yeah I know if you find out a single cop used to be a drug dealer for 10 years
Every single case that that cop worked on needs to be re-evaluated and thrown out or whatever so
It's the same thing it's the same fundamental principles it's hard work
It is very hard work
Did the result is going to be good for him to find another way to try and prove it Soros has
Tifa contract
To burn down cities which is
A real big part of your whole bulshit opposition to the black lives matter protest
Why you're protecting
Flagrant racism
Hey
Don't talk go ahead and do that cuz that's it's too it's too complicated
Finding the things that she was asked about
For two years while Wikipedia that so Alex
He doesn't like the news anymore
Philosophy
Gaston
Scott Moore
Christian
GameStop Christiansburg
The world
Self-help
Asparagus
Resume
Dim manipulate other people
Running inside
He's on the stand
Yep
This is rambly
I mean look
Hand
I guess he's just saying what you kind of could tell if you watch his show
Kind of pivoting into something
That is less grounded in reality televangelist
You don't have to pretend you have proof for
You can lie about the Bible all day and people really don't care
Sure I think that getting into philosophy in the big picture is of generous way to say yelling about the devil
Yeah I think I think this is true Alex has given up the pretense calves being about news and documents
Then all this
Because it never was real to begin with exactly what's interesting about that is
That
This is something that I noticed throughout Alex's testimony is that Alex was clearly the best coach
Because I really don't even know if Dari are Owen we're given instructions on what questions
Reynald was going to ask bright right
But right now is clearly giving Alex prompts for these answers that they had talked about
Because they don't look as terrible as the real ones do right yeah and then Alex
Just can't not be Alec
So he gives his gives his prepared remarks and then you can see him kind of scramble
And then start rambling off and on all the sudden he's like and so that's why the Democrats are in here like
Yeah but that's like what
To get out on the sand
So part of the reason he can't stop himself is cuz he he's just
Over-prepared
How many hours a day
I'm only year
Southport hours today
And
Been on the air
Navigate
In order to prepare
4 hours
Well let me ask you this
How many days are we
So in order to
Prepare for 4 hours
How many hours
Her debut
Marshmallow
Research
That was a far cry from the 16 hours a day you're studying the global is really did seem like he was over play
Playing his hand and now it seems like he's down play good huh see it seems like on air
I do literally nothing globalist white papers and documents write all of them
Their dirty laundry Sabrina Diaz that are filthy
Reading these documents exactly
Audio about 2 hours of the morning have you two hours a night busy
I really don't even know like I really don't even know what this is he also being
Used for because here's why I can explain
What he says on his show would be laughable the jury would never believe
It would be something like
Yeah right what are you doing for 16 hours
But the two 24-hours is believable
Right that is a believable amount of Transportation 24 hours of a show you do an 8-hour workday
You would expect for somebody who's doing a job more or less
And it's you don't want him to look like I just shoot-from-the-hip entirely
Cuz then there's an approach that is it's structurally irresponsible
I do like what ended up happening
But the same time you don't want to make it look like he does nothing but do the show cuz
First of all don't believe of all second of all if so then you should have vetted Wolfgang halbig
You would think
If you're working today I had to take out the time I mean I meant more for like the defense's case
It's because part of what they're arguing is clearly Alex spend so much time
On are you know
You smell like 5 minutes telling these people you know all of this stuff that kind of thing was 1/10 of 14
Percent right right right
But it could also be that look
He works so hard
These things are going to fall through the cracks you know he says 95% of my time as I'm not doing anything like this that kind of
But either way
The problem is
He's already been found guilty of doing the thing sure
So we can't really reduce the damages can it or is it just like
See he's a down-home country guy
I think that's a large part of humanizing him
A small a propaganda Outlet
News at this point is
You know a limited amount of employees that he has and perception is is kind of
Making it
More normal right as opposed to the absurdity that is
I meant continues even into this next clip which actually just made me really really sad
When did you start
King on other hosts
Alex knows damn well that the Nightly News started in 2011 but that would make his operation to look much more professional if he worth
Be aware of that so
Pretty important that it started well after the. Of Sandy Hook
Even worse is that Alex has completely forgotten about his original companion show the info Warrior featuring Jason bermas
2009 H4 Infowars in those early days
Madera
This Omission is insulting
I poked you and said
Forgot about Burma you sure did
No it definitely not and I was his best interest
Producing other shows on Infowars at this point in his career
Like I said is a mom-and-pop propaganda Outlet possibly
Boogeyman that led to so much pain he wasn't the CEO of what
Maybe what Owen would have to eventually describe as a mainstream media TV studio
I mean it goes all directions
We're small thing. No other shows
I put in an honest 925 day at work but then of course there was actually another question about like the war
Working on admin stuff
Let's park
A little bit about
Where you get
When's the last
Sorry what
Operation
2000 +
I guess I was just forgetting about his decades-long business relationship with Midas resources
These couple of attempts to Branch out into selling his audience to a multi-level marketing scams and was fun
Bunch of money from Mike Lindell and My Pillow pretty recently she wear and his affiliate links with my Patriot Supply
Respectable sponsors like a car company but it's pretty important to pretend
Outside no institutional support around the time of Sandy Hook
So much for having his principles
This is why you have to tell people you took one
And you go with diamond gusset
Sure you say we took one sponsor
And they couldn't even get anybody's jeans right
Diamond gusset jeans and then we were done
Self-funded from there on out
I think it would be really difficult to pretend that diamond gusset decided not to sponsor Alex's show
Because he was against Obama
Yeah that would might be tough commercial I do like his bulshit on this
Like a thing that people would believe him ye hide your gun
You want to be involved
Jerk
Anyway
Alex decides
Maybe a good idea would be to try and red pills a jury
Couple of in here we go
We'll take that clip earlier today they are
What
You'll feed all the bulshit man moment where I was like holy
Please share this can't be allowed to stand was like he was trying to
To argue that
Like
You and I both know what this is really about to the jury like he's saying to Jerry like Hey listen
I know you know that all this Glitz and cord is nonsense watch the Clips in that hole
You'll see that I'm right
You're going to be one of us at the end of this trial believe that
Trial by fire in The Crucible you have accidentally annoyed
No boy another moment that I found particularly distasteful is when he started talking about his product
Do you sell
Yes
Are your B
Why not
The ones
Whole Foods G
Ready.
Equality
Because
I'll give it to Whole Foods
They got molly Pirates
There's all sorts of crap
That's not what I
Underoath I'd like to tell you about the 4th of July special
Mad that I wasn't allowed to laugh the moment he was like
We buy our pqq from the Japanese like Wholey's like everybody in the courtroom was going to blow up
Everyone everyone knows that the Japanese do not sell their pqq to just anybody
Yeah delivered it to
You like holyshit I'm going to blow their mind
Yeah God damn what a what an insane person
Yeah yeah that's a
Really threw me for a loop
To prompt him
To sell
Well no I don't think so I don't think I'll be in Alex's head I would imagine it rain all
That the setup of the question was to facilitate the
Exploring Alex's Revenue sources it is much as he sells vitamins and people look down on
Live because of it but they're actually good that is the thrust of the question in the attorneys
He's mine
Not that Alex is going to talk about getting pqq from Tampa this is where I feel like
Trying to apply the rules of normal logic to what's going on is because it's clear
That right now thinks something is true
And Alex think something is true and it's supposed to be on the same team it is not the same thing I think that's
Probably a fair assessment
I get it I get it yeah so here Alex
How much
Email
Does
Infowars
Discovery
It was still in the box unopened
Billion Auto
So Alex is said that he complied with discovery which is going to be a problem later immediately later
Because he said something else
How many
Infowars
Email everyday
Going back
There's a
True Circle
What does
Alright
We're going to
We're going to take a break
So Mark has stood up and said that we need to make a contemporaneous motion
That's because Alex cannot say that he or his company are bankrupt in this part of the trial that they're in at this
Stage
Claimed he could make in the portion about net worth which is separated from the compensatory damages phase of the proceedings
But it also probably be inappropriate at that point since it's not true
This is why Mark asked to make
Steve these motions
Alex has now said that he's bankrupt and that he complied with Discovery in front of the jury which are both deeply and
Appropriate things for him to do
Can't do it he raises this concern Mark does leads to judge Campbell dismissing the jury and then saying
This
Watching party
Just stop
Yep
He is
Confused
Flummoxed
Something that was pretty cathartic for a lot of folks
You've already
Stop
You must
You're sure
Further
No estas
Comments about
Understand
Everything you say
Just because
Protect you
That means
You say that
You understand
I have been
They don't talk there is
Yeah I believe what I said was true and the response
That is
The Crux
Of why debate with someone like Alex's one
Step there is a complete disconnect from any objectivity
Any any belief
In a reality that exists outside of what you want to be true
And
That is hard and a courtroom setting
Yeah I mean you know we've we've said before they like any communication begins with the definition of terms kind of feeling
But that cannot be possible if somebody is speaking bird
Well you're trying to speak English
You can't be like oh okay cheap cheap means now it's just not going to happen
You can't do it and so I can like talk to birds as it is satisfying to hear somebody have to be like
Listen
Objective reality is real I don't know how to
Like she's
Flabbergasted by the idea that that might be introduced into court I have to introduce to you better
Concepts of
Object
What is the abysa desk tell me what is and is not for you so we can continue
You back later I think that I was I was subject
The notion of
Alex being under oath in those first the first deposition that came out excited
But like the idea that Alex is finally going to not be able to lie lie right and I myself
Was intrigued by the possibility with the trial as a
Preceded I was not
Expecting the same things that a lot of people might have out of this trial
And I feel for it the judge
Preside over this is a impossible task
And
Notion
I think a lot of people are entering this with other perception
Is that this trial is it doesn't exist in the context of the case
That preceded it
You know like you see her being kind of annoyed and it's because Alex has pulled this s***
Over and over and over and over again
No I think it in one interview that I did I can't remember
Who was with it but I made a point that like
She looks like she's pissed off
But she's being so patient of this is missing
If you only watch the trial coming away from it with the perception that like
I do not giving Alex an inch but there's a reason and that's that's unfortunate
Yeah there's not a previously off before the trial or whatever it is
She is doing such a great job
Because she is giving
So much preferential treatment to the defense
Like an event and let me try and explain that better job like you right right right so
If Alex was a normal person
The fourth time you tell them they can't lie on the stand
There has to be some consequences
Get that far so we don't even know
How to deal with this
Because you eat you if you do that
That's what he wants he wants you to say
Oh I have to go to jail for lying there locking me up for telling the truth right you know that's what
Hey Alex you put a sticker on your mouth for real
Constant push and pull between her being like I have to treat you like a screaming whiny baby and at the same time I have to
To treat this like we're in an actual Court
Do you have to be treated like a screaming whiny baby because that's what your behavior is at the same time
Treated like an adult
Because you're facing adults consequences for your adult actions
I am yeah it's a it's a
It's a difficult position. I'm not jealous of that there's a lot that you wouldn't have ever allowed the plaintiff
Just to get away with locally simply because she's like
You're a dolt I have to hold you to a standard that I'm not holding these fourth graders to and that she did
Give them that preferential treatment is both like starkly unfair and yet at the same time the only way to have this trial
To be totally fair
I don't know if it's appropriate to call a preferential treatment
Gave a lot of patience
A lot of wide berth
Are all right I'm not going to
Hold you in contempt
For clearly lying under oath for doing the thing that we hold people in contempt there was a lot
A generous approach to
The punishing Alex and he still couldn't operate within that space
So we go to the second Bay now cuz the this is where the took the break for the days when
And so Alex returns Underoath
And there's still the direct questioning retinol is still
Giving him questions and unfortunately
The Lime Crime video of this is missing the first 10 minutes or so
The beginning of this is establishing that Alex kind of like had less connection with those weirdos
Close then maybe he actually did
Werewolf game
On the bus pretty hard
Reached a comment
Which is subject first week of the trial
Steve pieczenik was one of the names that rain all brought up to Becca being like
Whenever he was on his array of this person's racist do you think this first of the races do you think that
Stevi B's name come up as as like a defendable name along with Stefan molyneux
Stefan molyneux racist
Yabby the beginning portion of this is really trying to downplay the connection right in Alex's associations with
The major players
And some of them I think they're kind of like
You could you could actually get away with this like I don't think him and James Tracy had that much
Connection end
I think Alex should be hanging his hat far more on the fact that Paul Joseph Watson interview with James Tracey the initial one
Was
Like
A little bit adversarial
Maybe not as much as a like of actual responsible journalists would check
Call didn't push back on the idea that there were acting grades on a curve for the
Fifth graders Paul
Has proven himself to be in 7
Centigrade
So Steve has come up here and Alex has it interesting perception on what he did
During that time you interviewed Steve pieczenik
About the story
Did you reach out to reach out to you how did that
Video
Other subjects to leave came up or
This isn't really accurate
Alex didn't argue with Steve but it also wouldn't
You'll be a mischaracterization to say that he gave Steve a full backing his client
Alex was interested in the theories I'm just like we got top experts saying it's fake
He didn't really commit to it in that interview
For something else
He was pretending to be Alex's on-the-scene reporter in the demilitarized zone because Alex was trying to drum up Annika Bettendorf
Carrillo's going to start a nuclear war god I remember that said he was in Korea
He said he was inside hanging out with soldiers from both side Hunter
Korea
Yep yep
From Florida he claimed that
I have no evidence that there is a really decent
He was on a vacation to South Korea because I have seen some pictures on he posted
Sorry I missed welcome.
DMT
So we're in this course of questioning I think that Alex the goal that he had was to present this
Image that like
His life was really in trouble around the time he hook happen
Can you tell us what
Glad you two have Wolfgang halbig on in 24
River bullet points
Leprechaun
What is anything else
What's going on in your
My family is falling apart
Weird like attempt to paint a picture of like
If your if you weren't divorced you wouldn't have booked Wolfgang halbig yeah that's weird
This guy.
Weird
Yeah this whole section where he's
His whole woe-is-me thing
Was
I mean I know that they wanted it to come off as though he was like a person who was also suffering
But it really just came off more like
Are you going to do this
And also tries to blame Steve more which I if I receive I would not appreciate I would probably attack our
What's mangos
You're crazy old man and you got nothing to lose
We've had
A video of
Received
Of you stating
Your belief
At that time
No one died
Set the whole thing
Do you understand if you sit here today
How crazy running
No said before
The past than I was under a lot of pressure
And I truly want to share those
Play Say Something
Tupperware my wife is divorcing
And I was basing that off of
Absolutely response
Especially since I've been to Paris
Harbor Central
Somerset real
They won't let me
In the position of being
Directions
Private Steve needs to get on YouTube and cut a video
About Alex under the bus
The Sandy Hook man come on
Great for both of them
But mostly for make who's David Knight going to side with
Dudes against Alex
Okay
Old dudes against Alex's young guards I would like to see
David Knight and Steve pieczenik reach day talk at you like
But some desire to Spill the tea on Alex
For a lot of final team up of Grumpy Old Men 3 is this the first time that
They talked and spill the tea ever do stupid things
I don't know the French had a lot of things to say
Accurate now that we're going off the rails
So I Alex says something about his
Realization that Sandy Hook was real in this next clip and I found this deeply troubling
At the end or the middle of 2015
July 20th
You stop
Infowars stop cover
Why did you
Because
How big was saying that I was involved in Sandy Hook because I wouldn't have them on and I started finding out that stuff
I just get it
Stop
For a while
Probably
Not everything. Everything stays
So this is disturbing because there does seem to be a pattern of Alex discussing his drinking as it relates to his actions involve
Calling Sandy Hook
We've seen it in interview and now under oath and honestly it's indicative of a very serious substance-abuse problem
Drunk or sober Alex's an a****** and deserves the consequences of his actions but I want to draw sharp Focus to the difference in
Kirin Court Alex's discussing his realization that Sandy Hook actually happened about sometime in
There's absolutely no problem for him to bring up that he'd stop drinking for a while as an explanation for his supposed.
Clarity but he does which leads me to believe that it means something to him
I don't think that it's true but I do believe that he probably was going through a lot and stop drinking for a while around the edges
This is all being Sudden Service of humanizing Alex in minimizing the things that he did
He's going through a lot and drinking a ton But realize that he was wrong and changed his behavior
Accepting reality he didn't
He was still doing a show Wasted Years past this point and he didn't change his behavior in any meaningful way
He's still just ran with b******* stories from bolted sources and defame people regularly
But he wants the perception to be that this was just a bad pocket in his life when all these negative influences let him to drink
His judgment was weekend
He doesn't want the jury to know that he got right back to the heavy drinking and bullshiting with Steve pieczenik basically the next week
Because that kind of cheap and whatever fake display of penitence he's trying to put on here
But the other time Alex discussed his drinking a relation to Sandy Hook was a lot different
In the Glenn Greenwald Q&A Alex was joking about how he defamed grieving parents and caused immeasurable pain in their lives by
I think that he didn't know what he was doing and drank a bottle of vodka that day
It wasn't a person expressing this is a negative thing it was Alex trying to appear cool because he wanted to impress the
Cool kids like Greenwald who can give her access to a new audience
I find this Dynamic deeply upsetting
And the only conclusion I can come to is that Alex was drinking on are all lot during this stretch
Everybody probably has a way bigger problem than even I think
And I have been chastised for begging people in his life to get him help a bunch in the past true
Anyway a lot of This falls on deaf ears to me in a courtroom setting
Like I would take him more seriously if you took the time that he did in the q-and-a while on the stand but that's not going to happen
Cuz there's no cool kids to impress their like
We like all right
I'm here interested
How do you say that in the in a courtroom
How do you do that because to me what you just said is
Nah come on it wasn't that bad whenever I hit him I was drunk driving
Like I don't know how you say that in the courtroom
In-N-Out
Situation that is ostensibly you also saying that you believe it's 100% rude you were only driving because you
Decorated ugly divorce
But even then you're saying that you're saying that you said that when you were drunk
And now you're saying that it's a hundred percent real
Are you drunk or are you sober and does it matter
I mean if that's why you're ravets your reasoning here then it doesn't matter you know when they when they were boarded it yours never was
A hundred percent truth there's a part of me that's like well was he drunk
Because
Finn would amuse the same amount either way
Write a man it's just it's just stay away for him to contextualize his actions by looking at his pass
Past self as
The drunk self that's not me that's a different
That can be definitely true for people who get help like I'm not saying that you know who you are when you're
In your addiction is necessarily who you have to put the rest of your life recovery is possible and all that
Right but I was not done any of that stuff
Answer him trying to pretend like this past self is somebody that I owned up to being and it but it is not
A characteristic of perception
Of people's understanding of Mike Tyson
Trucking show
A month ago I mean part of
Listen
You do have to own up to consequences for your behavior regardless of
Whether you are an addict or not part of recovering out that's part of what it is and he's not even owning up
2 is behavior
In courtroom
Because all this is in genuine and just an attempt to feel less bad about himself
This whole situation is not about the parents for him it is entirely about him
Trying to feel good about himself rationalization
So the Kraken comes up adande
Alex definitely does not want to be associated with him
During that time there was a reporter working
There's a gentleman who at least
We got yeah you should have said reporter remember
At some point
Infowars
Danza donde are you familiar with that
Can you tell us who he is
He was a part-time reporter
We're supposed to say that
So Rob's like this guy's like Howard Stern
Funny stuff
All babies like your Wack Pack
The comedy the damn batondy was doing writings like going to that for you hearing without
Hilarious
Hilarious hilarious interrupted the Boston bombing
Be at the press conference does Arnett brothers were still on the loose and unidentified
At least you didn't say that he was specifically harassing people that he said he was being a hilarious jokes to write
I mean
Look this is such b*******
For every reason
He didn't approve of this dive like go back and listen to those Boston bombing episodes
Over the moon and just like
It's celebrating dhanbad on deed interrupting this press conference of yelling infowars.com yep
Yeah you prove all of it
You're making a joke of serious things
You were doing with him
And
You just don't want to own up to the pain I caused
So this whole defense is largely circled around the idea that you have to watch the full clips
This point reynal puts on a very long video
Nothing better a problem here but also
The video includes Alex
Repeat and yep the claim yep that Wolfgang halbig correct
Why did the school have no traffic offline
Yeah I know all this isn't true
Yeah it was wild for them to insist on playing the full clip the full clip of which
Was more damning than the shorter clip
Yeah I would argue
Outside of the
Just a repetition of Wolfgang's point and the conspiracies around Sandy Hook
I don't help their case
There were some other things that I thought would be interesting to point out you're the first one
Yeah it's back then molyneux was
Define nationalism
Molyneux Paul Joseph Watson
You know you had had a real difference
The climate in the time that I'll explain his video all those players are so different
I mean they didn't have to snub mama do because he spoke a little bit too openly
I get to be coming back did you ever see that video of Owen Benjamin after the intellectual dark web
Started not liking him
There's a video of him drinking beer and complaining about all the like intellectual dark web people who don't like him anymore cuz he
It's just the same thing
I understand that
Like yes
You should be pissed off right your friends who don't like you anymore because you spoke to openly but I things that you all believe
You all believe the same s*** absolutely you just said
Some slurs
I feel like Stefan molyneux should definitely feel that way
Like
The concept that he was putting out when everybody was buddy-buddy with him is just as offensive
As the stuff
Betty puts out later later
Describe the feeling
That they must have is like
They're all over the line
Like these are all people who are Wylie Coyote who have already jumped off the edge of the cliff
And you if you say the slur that's who like you telling everybody else
Oh look we're floating and then you fall in there like
Good thing we're not floating we're so we're just standing on Solid Ground I was never running with that guy
In this clip that they're playing in court this coverage of him that is actually pretty good
You either sell one person
Who's done a great job
Zerohedge
Turn on flashlight
0. Maui is the person who wrote the article that Owen was relying on when he defamed
Pastelon
So A Towing is 0.9 puppet
Yeah yeah
To see this pop up here
Because this is also in a very close timeframe with when Owen made that video
Talking about how he doesn't want the Megyn Kelly interview to air after he shot it
But before it airs
It's in that pocket and then Owen Chu said video pretty-much
Closely after the Megyn Kelly interview airs
As a response to it so
What you have here is to hire the person who wrote the article that Owen relied on
How to create defamatory content
Yeah it is it is amazing to me that
The defense
Only used the plaintiffs evidence
Which is usually about sign to
That's in so doing
They have made the plaintiff's case really really well
I would think so
So rental
Comes back
And he wants to have Alex say that Sandy Hook is real and not a conspiracy
Here's the first attempt here we go
As you sit here today
What are your
Police
Around
That's an apology right
Because
I'm sorry wait are you questioning Sandy Hook in the sand
But surely died
Florida
Rambles gets caught off into talking about Uvalde doubt there's a
Patches onto the idea of a cover-up to defend his cover-up idea so he jumps to Uvalde
Get that gets an objection so now here's the second attempt go for it again
My question was
As you studio today
What is your
Your position your view
What happened
The murders
Sandy Hook Elementary
Young man on
Psychotropic drugs
I think we're coming really close to can just hear
So Alex now says his Pharmaceuticals and feels the need to defend the pharmaceutical stock
I am so he goes down that road hits another objection at
He said I'm going to move on and then Alex of his own volition decides to try a third time
Anywhere sitting here we go
From mileo psychopath
Zaxby's
Right now there's actually no question
Question
Answer to the question asked
Yes I only said three tries there to say something
Yep very simple could not help himself from creating conspiracy
Barnes
In my entire life that I never hear mark
Say something with the amount of smile at 11 I don't ever want to hear that that's a bad sound
Glow stick until it that's how bad sound that makes me feel like something dangerous around the corner
Like I said Bruno is one last question
They were going to look at and it's a doozy
When you look back on your
Twenty-plus years
In the media
What are you most
Sprouts
Close
Spell Shepherd
World record versus was that
Definitely wasn't the first report on wmds in Iraq in the questionable intelligence surrounding the story
Even though he was correct to be skeptical of that story his skepticism was childish it was just a knee-jerk response
It wasn't based on anything other than his own William so I guess he can brag that he got that one but he can't really take any car
But if we're doing any work on the subject or even covering it competently
As we've seen his Iraq war coverage in 2003 is embarrassing stuff from the insistence that the bath party
We're being reinstalled to rule the country while do pacification was taking played unsupported weeks long as
Assertion that saddam's kids were killed and wore in Belarus with their father they still are
David Kelly suicide
The larger picture that you get from that time as a person is not really worth accepting as a source
It's not worth it
He wasn't the only person saying that wmd intelligence was sketchy and the other people who were expressing that opinion didn't
Overwhelmed that accurate opinion with an avalanche of embarrassing bulshit
As for Epstein
I really want to challenge this because I don't believe this at all
I listen to Alex from a lot of periods of his career and I've never heard him bring up everything except after larger media covered
The story
I don't believe it all but Alex was covering Epstein let alone covering a by name 10 years before the mainstream
I believe that Alex has convinced himself of his own b*******
Like we talked about earlier cuz I can find Alex basically believe the satanic panic
Stuff was real
Things like the McMartin School case we're actually real any based a lot of that all that and same s*** detect
Gunderson apparently had told him
I do accept that Alex has talked about his fantasies of satanic groups kidnapping and abusing children for a long time
And I think what he's done is retroactively connect Epstein to that cover
So you can claim he's on the story all along
Like how his first documentary was about the great reset
Right I'm open to anyone providing me with evidence that Alex was talking about Epstein by name about his island in the sex
Crime 10 years before everyone else and if they do I will re-evaluate my position
But I've looked and I can find no evidence that this claim that Alex is making his true at all
I didn't look through the Alex Jones prediction section on his website where you post all the videos of him ostensibly being right
Write about all these things way back in the past
I can't find any video of him being way ahead of the curve on Epstein
Advice
This answer Alex has given
Feels accurate
He's asked to say what he's most proud of in his career and what he comes up with his one story that half the country got right and the other
Thirtysomething
Is almost certainly not true
There's nothing in his career to be proud of
He spouted meeting was bulshit for two decades and I'll definitely applaud him for dragging it out that long but beyond
His career has meant nothing but other people's pain
And profiting from it
Yeah yeah I thought was if that was me I wouldn't I would have said nothing I've been like
You know what I really want to answer this question
We've lost so many megastars like
Reset Wars oh no that's not good what else do we got
I made a lot of money
Jakari Jackson
Published a children's book I think that was pretty cool that was after
Cross-examination start autoboy this is fun
A little bit down the road yeah but the first
Mark's initial strategy in the beginning of this is to impeach Alex as a credible Witness
And so to do that he sets a couple traps
I talked to you about the details
The history of Escape
I want to know
Taking the straw seriously
You're pregnant
Absolutely
You and your company
12world
The Fish Joint
To make sure that a
A literal
Is being formal
That's what you want
Corner Bar
That works if you answer a question until there's an objection
Ewing
You want the world
Is reading
This court
And I mean a literal
Is being followed
That's what you want the world
That food in Fort Worth
Question
No I believe the jury is real
Your honor at this time we'd like to offer a clip from Infowars on Friday for the purposes of peachment and which those exact words was
Whoops
Oops
So that happens and then immediately leads into another trap
You've been talkin about a lot
On yourself
Is your allegation
That government official
Are aiding and pedophilia
Child trafficking in The Grooming of children
Yes is that a yes
On Thursday
You and Infowars started connecting those allegations
No
You're telling the world
What happens in this courtroom
Because the judge
Work boots
Do you say
Is involved
With pedophilia and child
I'm asking you.
How many
Not
To believe what's happened in this truck
Because
Is involved with CPS
Who is working with child traffic
No that's not what I'm saying
Your honor this time we would like to show clip from the gun show on Thursday where those words are so
A of course why wouldn't there
We're telling the world
Inside Travis County
The jury song
Don't know what
Planets
What's going on
I would be happy
We would like to know offer up
Video from mrs. Jones Show on Fridays
This reminds me so much of the the deposition where it's like
Okay how have you wear on try number three how do you not realize that when he says
Did you say those words
He's going to play the clip
Right
But you know answering yes
Is a chaotic
Options you have to answer me that you have to answer
Yes
It's a show like you have to answer with yes and then something you can't say no because he's just going to go
Go to the clip option
No matter what you end up with is like okay we've demonstrated that Alex's
An untrustworthy person
This is all bulshit
It's not a witness that you should take seriously your trust
Right position
So Mark tries to bring up the the video that rain all played and the whole thing about how
Hey
You just repeat it all the
Clams
About the
The school's not it being real and you realize that if you do that then you are once again denying Sandy Hook
Yeah and I think
With this is a this is about 2 minutes and it is a really good capsulation of why it is
Useless
To try to get Alex
Recognize
Pointsbet
He doesn't want to record
Yep
Do you remember them talking about
Whatever
BFDI did not have a Crime Stoppers
Mr. Jones
Weaver Deluxe
Testimony about
How about. Wrong
So you messed that up
Really happen
You in 2017 we're staying yet
Yeah just like Megyn Kelly said in your interview
You want to have it always
It means that there was website traffic
Food Insider
Video you say no EMTs entered the building you remember that
Brooke from your break when your attorney put up a video that you really wanted
Affair you were being about Sandy Hook
You said no paramedics
What do you mean by
Talking about
Do they get in the building and they see there's no Bots
You told me that
This is the next stage of the you have to watch the full clip never going to win because they watch the full
Clip and now it had some stuff that Alex probably didn't realize
Or forgotten was in it didn't want that I am so now these are questions that are coming up we have watch the full clip
Context
I need to see the timeline
Or whatever there's always going to be an excuse for why there isn't complete information in front of you
Exculpatory in some way
It's fascinating to me to listen to this into realize like
This is also confirmation bias
They watch the clip
And saw what they wanted to see and then we're like we'll obviously
This is a great clip
It didn't even occur to them that the other stuff inside the clip could also be used to question Alex
I think I think maybe they approached it from
Maybe a perspective that I had when we were going over the Sandy Hook
Immediate aftermath
And that is that I had a singular focus on trying to figure out like the actual literal claim
Name of actors sure so when I was going over the time frame at 2012 and 2013
There was a lie call Alex isn't quite there yet or without yeah we did have that conversation
The Cason understanding a little bit more about what was going on and
I am and all that like my perspective has changed
In terms of like oh yeah you said it was a false flag like immediately basically
Incarnations of what his theories words.
But I when I was approaching it with like the most generous possible approach
Reading things
I might even say something like
Why didn't the paramedics arrived or whatever and not be like okay this is him denying
Probably when looking at the clip
That might be just part of how
They are oblivious of what is being said to them
Feel like you just brought up a really really good points
In in the way that you view that is like
When we talk about denying Sandy hooker Alex denying Sandy Hook
I think a lot of people are talking about him saying this didn't happen
Write what it is is a an amorphous blob
All of what he has to say is denying that Sandy Hook didn't happen Innocents like
Okay so he's saying I 100% believe it's real but I question the official narrative that is just
Part of the amorphous blob of denying Sandy Hook when he says that what he's really doing is signaling
That he's still denying Sandy Hook on whatever level he can cling to their will not be
In a resolution where he says it's under it's a hundred percent real if he also says but I don't question the orb
But I question the official story
Percent real and then rattle of all of Wolfgang halbig
Reasons why he believes it's not wish to question
Then you're saying that you were right to question them
And you were saying that there are questions about Sandy Hook
Think that first of all what Alex was doing wasn't Quest
Have your falling into the framing there but they're not because I think that it is okay to
Question thing
You know like
If dick what is a journalist doing other than asking the who what where why when how you know
In court that day when he said but I still I questioned the official narrative in court I mean that outside of that
That you know like
If he saying if he still says I have question
News about the official opposition
Exactly
Unspecific.
Mark is a big a big moment
In the cross-examination courses the revelation of these text messages
But I think it was a lot of the coverage surrounding this is missing the point
Of these text messages
Obviously there is the juicy idea of what could be in there for a lot of people are setting themselves up for
Real disappointment
Like Geraldo found everything in that safe
This isn't based on any kind of like inside information that I have or anything so like don't don't take this as like me being a
Dino
I see stories about like
The notion that
Trump's raid was about Alex's text or a blown wide open
And I think this
There is a there is a desire to
Expand things in like
Take the what-ifs and and give more Credence to them and I think people are falling into that whether it's their headline right
Fighting or Keats
And I would advise caution just to like a we'll see what happens we'll see what's there
That's right I mean you get that though you hear we have this how can we not say it
Trash of text messages
And and you your main your mind immediately goes to like oh what could be
Not think to yourself
It is entirely possible
Because we live in the weird world we live in
Alex Rodger Trump and Mike Pompeo might have had a group text for the like let's overthrow the country on the six
Like you can't not think in your brain like that kind of ridiculous thing possible the world has gone cuckoo
But then you also have to remember no that is not how it works in these are Alex's text messages
This is not a big
Player in the game you know
There may be pieces of information that are relevant to things and
We'll know when we know but for now
Don't get ahead of yourself
Because if you do
You end up cooking yourself or backing yourself into a position where they are like
You've basically created storyline and if reality doesn't live up to that it's disappointing and I think that I think that
If we've learned anything in the past
Couple of attempts at impeachment maybe should be a little careful about
About setting expectations in a reasonable place
The reason I started at this I think that the media is absolutely missing the concrete
Reality
Of the text messages use
In this case right
Came up in the cross-examination in the way that they did
Enter Mark begins to get into this
And this is really where the pole
Text is most import
You remember
The company has learned from its mistakes
Abreva
Upside down
And they mention Sandy Hook
Planet Smoothie
130 + 7
To the lead into this question is Cohen's testimony that they had learned from Sandy Hook and their behaviour had become
And so that's why it's important
How this is revealed
Mr. Watson
Screenshot
Infowars.com
Video shows
Hospital using dummies
Indeed
Coronavirus
The first
Read along with me mr. Jones
He said
No problem take your time
Mr Watson said
Makes us look ridiculous
Suggesting this means covid is fake
Sandy Hook
All over again
Wichita
I get it
It's true
That this article
Right now
Why
Infowars.com
I guess you guys got balls
So that's a sad response
Cuz Alex is already said that this is his phone either text
Between Heaven Paul
It's so deep the notion here is the setup
Of the question
Is he learned from Sandy Hook you agree with that that's what Owen said
Yes
Here's a text
During covid
That Paul was telling you this is Sandy Hook all over again with you doing this b*******
About fake patients
In hospitals to pretend that there's covid patients at the hospitals
And you said I get it
Yeah I understand that this is Sandy Hook all over again
And the article is still alive
Today as we are in this courtroom
This is a
Damning
Picture that is basically do you have not learned
When reminded
This is Sandy Hook all over again when you're in the middle
Of a lawsuit about this sort of behavior as it relates
Sandy Hook you say I understand
I get it right I don't care right
And not just that
It is not a message from like
You know your son
Or or just
Some stranger email from your literal
Head editor for your most of your career you should pay attention right and the person who
Who likes throughout the course of this case
Has had maybe the only moments of like someone having Clarity in his death
This out. This is bulshit
He's he's literally the guy who is like he's a person if you had listened to him you wouldn't be in this situation if we were
In a movie that's different from the one that
This trial turned into
Which was this song
But
Paul would be the guy who gets roped back in for one last job
But in this movie pause like
No this is a terrible one last job I'm not going to do this one last job you guys go do the one that job and then he's watching them
Like that's what's happening
Like he sucks obviously into the the lowest of low bars
He have cleared it
In terms of
But he is not stolen 100 million dollars from a bank
Congratulations you are not being prosecuted for stealing $100 million dollars from
You have this situation where Paul is if you listen to him you would be getting sued
Situation crazy from
Fairly recently
If you just you should have listened to him
And you should not have had this text
Cuz it illustrates how little you give a s***
And that doesn't play well known I love this here's the movie
Cuz this is the Perry Mason moment the Perry Mason moment while they're amazing moments coming up
Feeling we have all your texts
Right
The parity is whenever it goes
You're reading it upside down that's where we that's the encapsulation to me of this like moment in testimony
Funny is that combination of like
Hi drama like I have revealed
F****** Tom Cruise's text messages to you right now and then the f****** hilarity of like
It's upside down Alex out so anyway Alex tries yet
He's trying really hard to figure out like what
What the f*** can I do here
You can choke
Here we go
There's was fun
You know how
What does it mean if the messages are in blue
Whose phone is this
Text robot
Very bottom left corner
SEPTA phone number
Yes
Show me
Nice trick
So this is the beginning of the Perry Mason mama and this is like
This is what all of the
You know John Oliver show and like all of the clip shows
They run this moment because it is
I mean it's made-for-tv and I mean it's literally made-for-tv. Bill said it's like the biggest
Legal moments
I understand that because of the way our show Works in and I'm so much more interested in
The reasoning in the context or it's okay
You have that Paul reveal
And
The reveal of the text messages in the nature of them tabs
And so that's that's your let's all enjoy that
Nice trick
Justin Trudeau
You didn't give this text message to meet and you don't know where this
No
Did you know that
12 days ago
Your attorneys messed up
An entire digital copy
Of your entire cell phone
With every text message you sent
For the past years
And winning form
Did not take any steps to identify it as Privet
Or protected anyway
And as of two days ago
And that is how I know you lied to me
When you said you didn't have to text message
Did you know that
I told you the truth
Did my phone
Elementary
In your deposition
You said
You pull down the text
Inducer
Sandy Hook
That's what
Subtle difference
My lawyer said it to you
But I'm okay
That's sad
Mr. Jones I love it yeah
Yeah I mean like all of these attempts to wiggle out of this I just feel like have backfired for him and made it worse
Do you know what the craziest thing the craziest moment cuz whenever I went back through all of the stuff that I
There were so many moments that I really that you do just lose because it's
Absolute non-stop insanity but the
Craziest one was on
Tuesday
Day 2 or day one of the trial proper you know the day after jury selection opening statement
Yeah in the middle of one of the brakes Alex is talking to the HBO documentarian on stream and it
At one point he does say
They don't have my texts
How crazy is that
How f****** wild is that
That was the wildest thing like going back. I was like that can't be real and I checked and I dates
It's crazy
Well again we have to
But makes the point that
Couldn't talk about other text Bono your tweets may or may not depict reality in any way
So even happened are you imagine that
Fair enough
So Alex has said that he searched his phone and didn't find anything right
Map of it
You may have just committed perjury
In Discovery
You were at
Do you have
Sandy Hook text message
On your phone
Correct
I told make sure you know before we go any further you know it is
I told you I gave
Did my text money
The phone
For whatever
One more time
Please remember
Will you testify
Underoath
Previously that you
Personal
Search your phone
For the precinct
There were no message
You said that under
Yes
When you say something that is then later found out to be not
True right around her up and you knew that it was not true
Because
It was you who said you did it
And you didn't
What is that called
Not good
Also applies to emails
Aquatopia email using it
Okay
Do I have emails from
About this case
In the past couple years.
You know in this case you were asking produced
Your email
New York
Right
You said you didn't have
Underoath
Sworn to God
You said you don't have any email
I mean
Gmail
Infowars.com
Monopoly
He keeps trying to bring it back to Infowars email as opposed to another email up thing and
What Mark is doing is very clearly trying to establish like you lied again cuz I have any mail
Well but like
Be the attempt to wiggle out of it is just be constantly bringing up Infowars the Isles
It's just not
Not going to help earlier in the trial right now
Triad been talking to Daria as the corporate representative that he objected to
And then talk to her as the corporate representative
He said like
Alex doesn't have an email address right and she's like all it wouldn't he did he'd get a hundred million thousand emails a day
So he got rid of it as though that would be later the excuse for what
Now happens
How did it go
Also we go back to the text messages now we've already Illustrated that
Paul had texted with Alex
And told him it's a Sandy Hook all over again I get it
Is the
Another smother text
Pierre from Tim fruge who's the business manager
Of Infowars answer here's how this goes
This is benmark
Yes
Operations manager
And we requested information about the revenues in the sky
Alaska
They didn't even look through text
No
Remove 2132
Latest 132 is admitted
I just want to make sure you understand something about these email
You understand that when your attorney
Send me your whole phone
Since we're discussing
Discovery is
Is a process that occurs and concludes well before trial
What's lawyers say isn't evidence
So
We don't know whether it was on accident
Debbie Doo
They don't have evidence about that
It wasn't properly turned over
When it should have been
But there's no question
Okay so there is a fair objection there because you're asserting that he
Did this accident LaRue
You can't prove that
Mommy kind
What you have is text about finances
That are
Like here's the numbers for this day
And then Alex
Just didn't
Turn those off
That's real bad it does appear that
I do think I do think there's an argument to be made
That you can say that he didn't mean to do it
Because the original did email back like
Please disregard
Yeah which isn't legally doesn't mean anything
He can't he can't do that without without
That email response
I'm so one of the things that critical about the revelation of these texts
Is that they illustrate financial information that was demanded and ordered from Alex writes that was not
Turned over
But more for my purposes
They also reveal
But Alex is full of s***
Victor Cruz
Bruce
How do I say
Agree with me
The pretty much everyday
He send you an update
How much stores are sold
And sometimes you let you know how much property
He says 110
Gross sales in food
Equates to almost
Hey
Pure
Okay
To look
This makes total sense
Yeah there's a 20 to 40% profit margin on the food and like
You just let that go in your car
She's not paying anything for the food
It's not like he buys it from my Patriot Supply and then sends it to people he's not resale
He's essentially getting a cut of what the business is no overhead
It is all pure profit yep
Tonight also illustrates testified to earlier just that.
20 to 40% profit margin
Is lotus
100 / 7 no risk
No exposure on the food
Maybe things are different with the private labeling maybe with his supplements Inception he has to buy a bow
Bunch and then resell it possible but yeah for the food that's not the case at all let me know even did like
Dropshipping from
The my Patriot Supply
Goddamn
I-70 Caso only 110 units is 70,000 a prophet
Think that probably is an unreliable statistics at like Universe lies because I don't know I wouldn't I wouldn't have two different
Print size
Buckets and then things that they sell
So like
It's not a uniform
Commission I am
Pretty sweet not a bad gig pretty sweet molly have to do is say stuff and then they give you money all you have to do
Do is convince everyone that they won't get food tomorrow I may need a rifle bucket
Yeah so here is Mark's dismount
Install
Your revenues
From 20
Cioppino
A couple of months
But not a whole lot of sales
I'm not drink
So remind me to talk about 2016 28
165 mower
That's gross
That maybe doesn't we have to calculate what your property
All of those Millions
Are you aware
Have your attorney
That your company
Admit
Underoath
Do your corporate representative the cops real
Your
Dear creeper
Slamming the door
I don't think there is any reason to ask you anymore questions what a great way to just call it now
So good so yeah
You know this a little theatrical inasmuch as you pull out a dollar and be like this is it
That's what we're doing come on his moments
I'm fine with it in this context but but yeah
Not correct
Is so funny
You trusted your
Lawyers to produce the relevant document
Yes
Cooperated with us in every way
You trusted us to do
A good job in turnover will you turn over
Turn it over
Norfolk weather
This is the end that is that is one situation where Alex did not realize that his lawyer
There was no longer working for him his lawyer was working for right now
Cover-your-ass he said no to all of us
Testimony took
Place over the course of Tuesday and Wednesday
Tuesday afternoon Wednesday morning and then
We get the Revelation on Thursday
That Alex is it with the compensatory damages of 4.1 million
And
News breaks past the point that Alex is on air
Oh and so on
Is hosting the War Room
At this point
Complaining about
I don't know
The Chinese
Probably sounds right
It secures at him at discussing that they're the Judgment has come in
TuneIn right now
Because
The news is broke
About the first verdict
In
The Sandy Hook case
And they got
4 million-dollar judgement
And now they got a for million-dollar
Verdict which
Is
The shooting 400
Line their pockets I guess
That money goes
Jeremiah
There might be a statement from Alex Jones soon
He might go live he might pop in I don't know
Okay
Good news
So
Just stay tuned there will be a statement from Alex
Shortly
That is such a funny wine a way of dis
Look now I can't even cover the news
The news has many words
Look at what these
People have done to me and who knows where that money is going what an hour trying to make suspicious stew
Of a lawsuit
And so he's right
I would still pop in later share so that's one thing I was right about Scott he's winning in the talk show predictions
He's right about Alex was filming a statement
Before he came on
I took here is that
We're going to go to that right away
The Democratic
Tire corporate
Lined up
The judge
Anytime
The last
In Austin Tech
Surgery while I was
In the courtroom
The Alex Jones
Is guilty
The lawyers
Million
Dollars
When
I admit it I was
I admitted that I
Politician
Information but not on purpose
I apologize
Understood
What I did
What's wrong
I didn't lie about
And I ran a god
I
Question
Anomalies
That other song
Sherry under
Your money
My company
And I purchase
What a great guy
So I think the three billion number is meant to make the judgement look even smaller trying to figure out
Where they came from and I think it's the sales figures that Mark showed from
From the text messages
That proves he was sending over okay they were like it was like what eight hundred
$1 a day late it out to like 300 million in a year
Over 20 years overtime overtime Sandy Hook
Even remember if Mark
Made any statement of three billion fright but it's like Ok Google three hundred million dollars a year ten years since
If the theory 3 billion dollars yeah sense then
I think that's where Alex may be taking that number from that I never heard that as like what he
Should be penalized I really really really really wish that
The way that that amount of money was reported
Was
Abased on why it was chosen like I understand that 24% of America
Kansas 75 million Americans
So the idea
Is $1 for each American symbolism
Do they want money or it was about how huge the sum was if they really just like
Listen
The Sandy Hook
Families believe that they that
Because of Alex
Alex owes them $1 for person that believes that they're a liar
You know that makes sense to me
It also makes it feel like the Judgment isn't that high
Because if you'd said that they owed $10 per person I wouldn't think that that's a huge judgment and that's 1.5 billion
Dollars
You know you don't start a negotiation low number that you
You don't necessarily expect you're going to
Misunderstanding of the symbolism I agree with you that could have been
Was really important about the money and not the money and that's what was so frustrating
Alex's statement goes on
Judge realize
I walked
SeaWorld
Today
Course he did
Punitive damage
Tomorrow
I
Cannot testify
And my lawyer
And told her
And now she's saying
I trusted
I trust
So this just isn't true
Retinol gave a defense in the punitive phase of the trial just as wested for the plaintiff
The defense wasn't able to call any Witnesses because the purpose of that phase of the trial was to determine net worth of
Systems
And after repeatedly failing to provide Order documents and repeatedly sending an incompetent
Corporate Representatives the sanctioned Alex's defense by disallowing him
Her being able to participate in the Networth discussion at this point
Essentially this is not a silencing or an instance of Alex being jammed up
It's just another case of him
Not doing the bare minimum he was required to do in the discovery phase of the case and now it's too late for him to pretend
He wants to be involved
Plus
Alex violated the rules on multiple occasions the prior today including the line to the jury by saying he was bankrupt so I'm
Alone
He should not be able to be a witness in this part of the case
Nothing that you said can really be accepted as credible so his evidentiary value 10 unless he were to have produced
Documents backing up what he says
Which brings us to the next problem
What are the primary things it was brought up as it relates to his text being disclosed was the messages from Tim fruge which discuss
Detailed breakdowns of sales number
These numbers did not match the revenue numbers that Alex's claims and even more importantly the existence of these texts
Which were not turned over in Discovery
Revealing attempt to hide information relevant to the determination of net worth
And the company's value
There are three major reasons that Alex is not being allowed to be a part of this phase of the trial and it has nothing to do with the demo
Democratic party or conspiracy against him
It's a simple consequences of his stupid action
You can probably get the basic tone of this announcement already it's Alex taking this for million-dollar judgment
Because it's much lower than he was probably fearing
His tone is essentially no different than when he's got another bad news in the past where he's using it as an opportunity to fund
Andres off of it
More less trying to get the audience to flip the bill for him so he can remain insulated from the consequences of his actions
It's pathetic
But it's what you'd expect because he's always been able to do this before
Whether it's his dad for the medical bills that Katie almost killed or his dad buying advertising on his shows or radio
Station with air hammer Leon
Or the audience donating to his suspiciously time to money bombs or this suspiciously * 8 million
Are Bitcoin donation
Alex has always had people to bail him out of the trouble of his stupid action
He probably thinks based on his $4000000 figure this is just going to be another in that series
Yeah little reason for him
Not to think that I mean if if
If it were me
An Alex issues I would have received that judgment as
A massive victory
But that's only because
As if it's me and Alex issues
I much like Alex have forgotten that there more trials coming
I have completely forgotten that that means
More judgments are coming as well so I am I'm Overjoyed I am announcing my victory over the demo
Democratic Party
So yeah the plaintiff lawyers
They were not happy about
They don't like that Alex won
I'm at peace
Patricia Steele
Play major
Victory Ford
And the plane
Employers
Screaming
Yelling
My lawyer
Joe
Andino
They thought they were
Shut us down
But that jury
Addresses
Besides it's not at all
Match
My experience with the flight to Sluggers
I mean I don't know I don't know who these two sources Alex has but I think that their lieutenant colonel's
Probably
It is it is this
Exact
Video
That it should be played
Further in in in the other trial
Just because
This was
After the judgment
Yeah if you think that damages are going to make him stop
And he can still be in business that is not how this works
He's in there and he is doing his s***
Or he's out
There is no getting him to moderate
Yeah but I think that's difficult to think you and I can save
I think is
You know 100% the future which are you can't do in a courtroom I assumed but it also presupposes
It is appropriate to be like
I want to bankrupt him as a punishment
And I know is that
Is necessarily healthy
So important
It is not that
I understand bankruptcy in this way
If the points of the trial
It's the point of the damages
Is to punish someone to get them to stop their behavior
Right
And this is what they do
After that judgement
Then it's not about money at that point it has to be
How do we make this Behavior stop
I don't care if the judgment is 10 bajillion dollars or it's literally just a guy going like Hey listen
You got to turn the lights off that's that's just what's got to happen it's not about the money kind of thing you know what I said
Translate that from
What I think you're saying that makes total sense in this conversation to a courtroom I think that's a challenge
And it's also an incredibly difficult because you know when you have something like this happen
It's just an opportunity for Alex to
Mail truck is audience and then I get more money
Where in Bangkok
Your sovereignty
Not your fault
The fight we have a
Plan to stay on here
Through the Spectre
You don't fund
If you don't buy Prada
Dot-com
Your decision
Right now
To stay on
We are
Broke
Even worried about that
I'm worried about
Our bank
Emergency
To do that we
Underoath have been proven to be great
Wild
Just wild share
It's exactly what you'd expect
X2go the direction it does
Because
When there's a direction to go from there if yes all God he starts talking about kneeling Scarlet
No
Mike Mike Mike
Animal
Calm and keep
That is so
Woke up the
Stop talking
I was wrong
I admit
Prouder than
I don't
For tomorrow
These people
Trident missile
Represent what I said
LG video
They showed the
Backfired
Yeah so he's creating this perception that
Like
Niall and Scarlett
Are info Warriors now
Woke up to
The fact that their lawyers were manipulating the comments about the previous clips
Said come too soon and I would like to reiterate him about that clip but like twice as much
Locked up
And my lawyer
Cosmo
Carl Lewis
Is it about Duncan
Control is about
It's about teaching
Auburn love
Take a passion
Not hateful
And I've invited
On my shelf
Email organization
If I see her tomorrow
That I am
Gladly
Hamper on my show
Next week I'm going to raise money
For her organization
On top
Of the big judge
Because she's a real
She lost
Child
I'm not going to let
Claims that I'm a Sandy
Beautiful
Creighton
Call lawyers
The ambulance Chasers lost
America and
Corporate
Charlotte Lewis
So this is a big
So close
Deportes
Have Scarlet
Their lawyers are
Stop
You'll try to follow me
I'll never
Foxes
A dog
I'll see you tomorrow
I was in the courtroom during his opening statement asked the jury to return a judgement of $1 in Damages
Call he asked the jury held the dollar up it was very smart was he hurt
Closing statement in the cross-examination
Such a disgusting liar and it's just exploited audiences obvious lack of awareness
So what's actually happening in the trial
Galaxy
All this is complete s***
More importantly
Alex knows fully well that he's just lying to his audience
So they keep giving him money
Also like to eat Scarlet has a great organization
He's corporate representative Daria Underoath testified that she suspects that it's a front
Yep
Also this is Alex's attempt to portray himself as the good guy which is all based in bulshit
Further
He's putting meal and Scarlett into a trap where he's casting them as characters in his personal image rehabilitation
As far as the audience is concerned they either get to play along and act how Alex is setting them up to which they aren't going to do
Do suspiciously by the audience all over again
Why aren't they speaking out in support of Alex after they realized they were being used by the lawyer's to attack the First Amendment
Maybe the evil lawyers won't let them or maybe their daddy just said that to Alex to pacify him during the trial match
We are in League with the Deep State Democrat lawyers after all
Come to think of it that would mean that they would have put on a pretty good performance to trick Alex of all people
Tractor Central
Maybe that's not the direction it would necessarily go but Alex is forcing meal and Scarlett to exist in terms of his bulshit show
Into the future because created these fictitious pictures of them
He's helpful in terms of making Alex feel better about himself
What are you really should be doing is leaving them to the f*** alone which they've wanted all along
But Alex is kind of like a child whose broken something and then he's trying to clean it up but he doesn't know how to clean sew in
The process he ends up breaking more stuff
You just want them to stop trying to help because they're not helping that is making things worse
But they're dumb kid and they don't get
He's kind of like that kid except you broke that original thing on purpose he claims that he didn't and then he's breaking other stuff
Stuff to distract from a messy initially made
It's like a sociopathic version of that kid who broke something
Yeah
He's a f****** a******
That's so funny
But that's another part of the amorphous blob of denying Sandy Hook that's it now
I get it
I say Sandy Hook is 100% real
Because I've changed the goalposts
To now the lawyers are manipulating these people that is just the same thing it's always
One bright big thing is not that he denied Sandy Hook happened it's at Sandy Hook is part of
Whatever it is he want you understand that that is exactly the model
You have you have you have to play the full clip Play the full clip oh I need a timeline, timeline
Mine doesn't be another excuse
Even like think about it in terms of world events like you have this lead up to the 2016 elections like we need
Need to get Trump in because if you have a democrat in now it's so bad Trump gets in Ono there's enemies Within
Upstate is everything sucks yeah it's always something else
The conspiracy in the narrative has to shift because that is where the money is Fright that is where the
Ability to keep his audience interested is that
Like oh
We we 1 or 0 I was actually wrong let's move on right doesn't play
There isn't an angle he's just a coward
Well yeah that too
So it does have the balls
The show up on the in the war room
Hello boy hard-hitting interview with earlier adversarial
Patient with the Press conversation with Owen wants a paycheck. Clearing but
Now it's friendly
Alex's recorded this announcement and statement and he comes on with Owen
This kind of rehashing some of the same stuff
But he has some other things that he says that I think are really shity
Titanic violin
Baby
Not very good at it
No not because he told you about the globalist corporate world government the carbon tax is what
They've destroyed him now
And the lies get to permeate on Twitter
Defend yourself
I tried it here we are
The jury came in
On the big verdict tens of millions spent by the Democratic party law firms
And the jury came in at 4.2 million
When I asked for
150 million two days ago
3 billion yesterday
I don't have $2000000
The banker
Anywhere
Seems like a bland version of Triumph
For him do you know how to use this Victory to it but it's also also
Spent tens of Millions on that
So I guess what do you need to think that cuz then you win
Right
Yeah Alex can't be like listen the law firm that they're specifically when
Went through
I've ugly plaintiffs attorney said that he only eats what he
He kills
So obviously they spent yeah
According to Alex on war room
The good news is it's very low verdict for what they're asking for
The bad news is we don't have the money
Banda.
Morning before that's why I want to see the War Room
Are you want to see I'll show you want to see her you want to see
Did everybody here we need your support and infowarsstore.com
And I would testify tomorrow which under Texas law
The judge ruled after the ruling today
I got that low ruling sounds a person it is odd
But for the RAV4 small
Cannot speak tomorrow and my lawyer can I put on evidence
Because words of faulted so she gets more and more desperate
As she rigged this whole thing but not matter what the Judgment was he would not be allowed to participate
Dissipate is no bearing on any of that
I mean you just can't commit perjury one day and then still come back the next day about financial stuff
The the sanctions in terms of the default judgment like
A big part of it is not cooperating with this stuff
There was a time to provide that
Very much didn't
I was given multiple opportunities to clear that up and fix that you don't like swoop in
And then be like aha
Now I will reveal
It's that example of
But you're never going to win you know like with Alex lives in a reality where he
He always wins so you're never going to get him to be like
Oh are your right
I I f***** up you know in a way that means anything
Exactly so you just switches into a different world and if he's guilty in this world even switching to add a different one
Crazy MC you buddy
So obviously this is all
Just trying to
Get money
And the Alex. He'll be making more money honestly and he's a little disappointed
I don't say this
Where in bankrupt
And I thought
And bankrupt
We can bring in the money we need it right now or not
Show
It's a pyrrhic victory if you don't find infowarsstore.com
Order book order of films
Get bodies on September formula
Vitamineral Fusion
All the great products Infowars you've invested
So much you know
We've invested you were in this together over the last
28 years on air
Critical juncture in the fight
The last game as the basketball game
Are the football game where everybody is
Is it is it a
Now
The big boy pants
Now is the time to side
Where you're at
I'll Never back down I'll Never Surrender
I'll never go away
But I could give out
Please Deportes
Where should I go
It is once again big boy pants time
All right big boy pants time
I regret to inform you it is big boy pants time time
Nick Walker
Sure that meme
Someone made
I struggled with it a little bit
Because
A little unfair it's a little unfair also think about it like
You know you're the Nick the Doughboys comparison picture of us on rivals
You're married next married okay
Mitch has cat okay
Squinty eyes both of us have squinty eyes
I grew up in Boston for a while he's from Quincy
More than I'm comfortable with that I didn't realize do you like hot salad
I've never acted honestly I have no Dough Boys references whatsoever I didn't know whatever people whenever that may
Season came out
I was like
I really don't know who Nick and Mitch are I was like wait
Hi I love the boys and I would honestly say want to me to come on
But I do not
Think the cakes or pies I was like
I don't have any I haven't shaved in a while that was my reaction to that picture I'm sorry cupcakes
Cupcakes
That is not a pie
Until the day I die that is not a pie
That threw me for anyway
Big boy pants
In this interview that Alex is doing on the War Room
Keyframes
The why people are mad about him but Sandy Hook in a particular way
What's correct the record on a couple things here Alex
The media today says
Alex Jones
We barely less than one-tenth of 1%.
But when Hillary ran against Trump
Dreads
The question
What's the Monopoly but it turned out
Probably
So the whole thing about why people are mad about Sandy Hook
Alphabet something and Alex's easy
You may remember this as the entire framing device of how Sandy Hook is covered in Alex's War
The shity documentary made by Alex Lee Moyer
And I think that you see how
Patently absurd this is and how
Easily tricked
Yeah I mean that is that's that's a moment where you either got to go
I'm going to be 100% complicit in this Ava Braun or you have to go I might be shity at my job
Whoops
So
Let's not dwell too much on this cuz I already did that episode and
I was
Blocked and then unblocked by their Twitter account about it
What happened
There's something really terrible about the way Alex precedes
To the end of this episode
In that special report announcement thing he did
Now there's a characterization of scarlet and Niall
And it's unfair yeah it's inappropriate
But what Alex does
Now is worse
I am very thankful to God everything for the listeners
And I want invite start Lewis who doesn't have a gun control group
She has a
Group about children learning
And helping
People are being bullied
So they don't become SI
Totally
Supporter groups use love
Play My Worship by and gave me a hug repeatedly
I told her regardless of this ruling
I want earlier
So tomorrow I'm barred from speak
At the trial but I'm going to go with the letter I'm going to write tonight
Reply
Watching them on purpose I I didn't try to hurt them
Once I messed up my salt.
Why I was
I was brought into stuff that was
But you never even said their name
Still
This is harassment
Could Alex is planning out on air
Yeah yes
Yeah this is me to talk to them
So I'm going to write a letter and slip it to them
So I can invade their space I'm going to go to their house when they're lawyers aren't there and I'm going to slide
This letter underneath their doorstep you know like a sane person who's not harassing people would do right
Wow Scarlet in particular Alex seems to be wanting to paint as
This is a new best friend
This is just
Awful
Tuesday
The morning show
Brower you came in and took over
And I said
I believe
He's a real person
I believe you
And I'm sorry
They cut it down to a minute
With me saying it didn't happen
Video so blurry
It's all blurry
Oh my God I said
Charlotte
Go to the
Go to 40
Go to 33 after in my show today
I said you're real
I said Your son's real
Whoever gave that to use a liar
She got up and left him back an hour later crying it was like
So so we broke through
That they're being handled and manipulated this way video
She said I'm staying I was given it by
My supporters
Your point is they gave her a minute edited video
Echoes I believe you're real
I believe your son. I'm so sorry
I want to work with you
And I believe that your ex-husband
Sean.
He's a great guy
I think they
Smart
He's a cowboy
I've been like that
So
She apparently
And watch the full video then Alex's referring her to
She wept
And then told Alex
That she gets it and she's being used by these lawyers
I genuinely
Genuinely
Think she should sue for defamation
I mean I don't know what else to say about that that is defaming you might I would I would take that as defaming a character
I really would
Yeah I really would take the idea of you
Claiming that she
A person who I f****** don't deserve
To be anywhere near her she's so strong
And powerful and amazing
To claim that she is your friend
Alex Jones
Is so f***** up
Yeah so f***** up I think that one of the
Central things about what makes
This soap like the experience so painful is that you're being like is the parents of this
Child who was killed
You're being deprived of your ability to experience your life on your own terms someone else is curry
Creating a caricature review
And it's deeply painful and Alex's doing
So here's Eric happened
Alex created a diorama
And then dropped it around them and trapped it in there for years
4 years and they finally f****** got out of it so Alex is just building a different diorama that he's trying to
To trap them with
And here's our last clip for episode for today and
I don't know
It is like
No I have no words for this this is so unacceptable
I mean they are they are
Desperate
And then
Atlanta Braves
Hazel said hey buddy I appreciate you thanks for a bit my son. I said yes sir
His lawyer went
We're reaching out to them
We're going to Connecticut or meet with them where's the port and what they did we're not going to accept Wesley's family somewhere not in Abby
Part of the CIA New World Order propaganda operations not Sandy Hook
What's the media control
Job
That's right God bless you
So obviously when he says we're going to Connecticut that's about as other trial
The Lafferty case
I think
That saying we won't be kept from these families
Is something that
Is
So wrong
Obviously the way he's trying to portray it as like
Me and families are on the same side of his evil lawyers are trying to keep us apart because they're of the power that we could have together
Weather in this unity and love and all that switches nonsense
The real world the place where the real world intersect with this b*******
Is exactly the same kind of harassing behavior is encouraging those from the audience
Because
You know let's say that Scarlett or Neo or some of these other families don't behave in the way.
If it you would expect based on Alex's rhetoric
Well you should go talk to him why aren't they
If you're not allowed to while these lawyers are keeping them from you got to
It lends itself towards encouraging harassment
M i i
Going to beyond anything that you know we talked about in terms of the lawsuit
This response
Is
I mean I agree with you as someone who has no legal background at all
I think it should be a cause for another action
Because for God
Creating a mountain so big he couldn't move it
Writing leave them the f*** alone on it and then dropping it on Alex's at I think you just
I mean look
I don't want to use the kids terms but you got to take the L on this one Alex goddaughter just walk away
Coronavirus
Leave them alone just leave them alone I don't know what kind of bulshit game is doing to try and say
Save face or create
The enemy is these lawyers and not the families and now I'm best friends with them
But like
That this is exploiting mean it's abusive it's disgusting
And it's the kind of behavior that lends itself towards his audience
Not behaving in ways that
You'd walk
I just
Digest I believe exactly that what he did was what he did
I believe it wholeheartedly knew it was going to happen
That's exactly how it was going to go
It wasn't going to be a
Hey listen I'm sorry we're never going to talk about Sandy Hook again
It wasn't it wouldn't even have been just a quick one like Hey listen
Judgment turns out it was better than we hoped for
Frankly I was f****** up
Let's not talk about Sandy Hook ever again now they honestly put the words on the board bareboat
Now I am going to actually instead does a great idea
Going to go for the challenge mode of life
Family experienced players only alright I guess if you want to go
I don't know
Yeah I found this deeply upsetting inoffensive for
This episode
Because I don't
No I don't know how else to like really put a button and stress like that is what Alex did after
The compensatory damages were made after
And it sucks you'll never learn any lessons
A spaceship
Andy Murray will tomorrow with another episode rapping this baby up
And also tomorrow you can find us on the majority that's true
So that'll be noon Central 1 p.m. Eastern
Yes
I don't
I can't do time laugh
I can't I don't know why I said I couldn't
Anyway what are you I'm tired man tired
Remax Jordan but until then I'm Leo and easy access
And now here comes the sex robot
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work