Important
I have great respect for this knowledge B
MoneyGram
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Worship at the altar of Celine talk a little bit about
Alex Jones
My bright spots baby Jordan we are recording this
Late
To do to some logistic and so I can play with my brights body is just
Got done recording the majority report I guess it was recorded
But yeah it's so I didn't get a chance
It's to say some gushy things that I invited
But
The that show was very
Important
I think early on during that do this a lot of people ask me like how do you stay sane right listening to all this
Alexander was really critical for me was
There is a groundedness to reality and a lot of the interviews that's a man
Do
With people surrounding like
Political things and policy issues
And I found that to be very comforting and anyway that like
I don't know my parents listening
Dude watching like the MacNeil Lehrer our was a kid
Well it's granular
Yes that's what you're you like that's ran you in its real yes
Talking about real stuff is right next to it so much of what Infowars is
MMD entertainment value of just like
Sam and Andy Kindler
Breaking down Dennis Miller s*** doesn't get better than that and so
You know that when we started the show that was something that was really helpful in terms of keeping me
On the level
And the notion of being able to be on the show and
And
Just crazy
I think that this sneak week has been really bizarre
And no disrespect to cnnr Brian stelter but like
Doesn't compare
Being on being on the same and they're the majority report
Something
I'm not.
Who is Steve but you know it's something I'm
It's big
What's a red spot spot is first off
Obviously that too
B i s
My mother's in-law
Anarchy
Nice things about him all the time and never enough never enough
No they invited their daughter to go to Ireland with him and then I married her so they have
To take me now too so
I am going to Ireland tomorrow
Yeah yeah
New Order the Lucky Charms there is like it taste better
The lot like in Paris
The Lucky Charms in Ireland you just don't get them anywhere else I was trying to think
Think of something that I would like you to bring me back and
I don't know that I just think of like
Maurice's
That has like the peat moss
Be worth it illegal for me to bring that back to claret
Village of Enon things to declare I don't drink that much these days so I can't answer whiskey with no
Not really not not nothing
I'll come up with something I'll text you I'll come up with something and then I'll text you
Something probably very thoughtful I hope you have a great trip
And
That leads us to I haven't really fully decided exactly how we're going to play it yet exactly
You're going to be gone next week
Ansel
Our ability to record any episodes
Is it going to be
Gone basically reduced
Right if there's a giant emergency we could like Skype in the middle.
That is a possibility and I don't like taking time off so there's a decent chance I'll come up with something to
To do brats
Temper your expectations
There may be a creeping away week
He'd at least
Some breaking the only way to in
Force that
Is to leave the country
Doesn't work
There may be one episode next week there might actually be non
But we're not entirely sure we will
We will see what happens
I mean there's no way that we
Put out you know like
12 hours of content in the past seven people need time to catch up on
Emu picture
Good time to go like
Because I'm going to happen
Today we're going to be finishing up the trial recap coverage
He's talking about Alex's shell on Friday which is the day when later in the day
And then B of the afternoon
Special Report Alex put out on Saturday discussing
The punitive damages
Wait a week to find out what he said about the radon Mar-A-Lago
How under attack we are and how the FBI is got to go and do the
Anyway
Hello
The first
Steve thank you so much you and I'll probably walk
I like mine with lettuce and tomato Heinz 57 and french fried potatoes thank you so much
Boo
You're now policy walk
Call poison ivy
Buck the horse that gave me a little breaking in my arm thank you so much and I'll follow siwa
Thank you very much
The other Patty not the Patty the other one thank you so much right now bausa
Thank you very much Mike knowledge fight is cathartic for depression but not as much as UT
Nuclear reactor Art thank you so much you're now about as you walk
Thank you very much Johnny
This is your dad
You got to start listening to knowledge fight I walk the dog and do your schoolwork siwa
We have something very exciting
This weekend we wanted to wish a very heartfelt
Congratulations
Two couple who are getting married
And Mister MP
Getting
Time the old knob
And we want to wish you nothing but
Years and years as many as you got left of happiness
I'm not good at these things may all your somersby is dreamy and creamy is the dreamy creamy summer you're practicing for
I understand
MP is a mod on one of the Discord
Oh okay there maybe
Walks at the wedding
So that is very exciting we would like to declare your wedding
A raptor princess
Four Star
And tell your brother
It's over for Humanity
You're Beautiful song
They're coming for your balls
It's all over your God
Very few people
You make it a practice
When they are
Hey juicy
Congratulate
So Jordan like I said we're going to get into this
One of the series would you put out earlier we looked at Alex's testimony from the Sandy Hook trial and reviewed is respond
Fox to the announcement
How the compensatory damages which ended up being a little over 4 million dollar
That took us to Thursday afternoon and the next day the trial entered the punitive
Before we enter the week
All this episode we going to pick up where we left off in tune into Alta show the morning of that Friday August
And track the response as the reality
The punitive damages sets in
NES to wrestle with a very large weight that he is now carrying
Both in terms of financial consequences as well as the potential Fallout from his texts being accidentally turned over
Do opposing counsel and what they could
Good meaning for
His future
Well
I mean is Future
If you're approaching me from those would like a reality yeah but if you're approaching it from Alex land
Here is how we start the show
Friday
August 5th
Plywood Studio
Rochelle's in
One of the things you've been talking about on your show is your allegation
Official
No-No No-No No-No No-No No-No No-No
Oh my God
Your allegation
That government official
That you're dumb
Eating and pedophilia
Child trafficking
Wait we're doing it twice
Same one
Love the great me makers out there great job love you all
So this was his cut to make it seem like Alex's dropping a truth bomb on the court but if you listen to the larger
Clipper really just marks
Response
It doesn't actually feel that way in Rialto
Is your ally
R18
Pedophilia
Soundtrack
Roomieofficial
Alex brought up Epstein mic drop moment and honestly it wasn't even meaningful in the context of the quest
Mark just says yeah sure
That was a question about Alex making accusations about the judge in this case being involved in pedophilia and child
Again which is conveniently not included in the meme that Alex is playing
Because it wouldn't
Support the fun truth-telling thing that they were hoping to
To convey with a meme
In the real world this question was part of a setup for a trap that Alex walked himself into
Peach him as a credible Witness
Listen to trial
I went to the paint
Complete unserious person and this should be a great example of that
What do you said isn't threatening to anyone it evoked more rule dies than anything else
The courtroom
It was part of a line of questioning those pretty effective in Devon
Menstrating Alex was not at all a good faith
Participant in the trial
I'm a testimony was not something the jury should be taking a place value
But it has the appearance of being something that owns the lives or something so people made memes and Alex decides to start his show
With it cuz that's
Yeah yeah yeah that's
That's sad
I would want at least more than one
Clip
Of that difference
You know like
There wasn't much
Gulf Arab more sad than a few you know
Going to make memes out of Alex like coughing a bunch and like oh you got my phone
That would be more fun
I would like that
It's harder to play boxing commentary after the
Then the messages that Alex is one of got knocked out when I convey this
That one thing I will say
Is that this episode
Involved a bit more news than I expect interesting I mean there's plenty of navel-gazing to go
Naturally
There are some headline
Signs that Alex covers
Our little bit
Fun
Okay we have the official announcement
Elizabeth good
Cannibalism is good
This is just Alex playing fun games with headlines
The great the perception that we're on the path to eating each other which doesn't really make sense
I thought Claus she wanted us to eat bugs but never supposed to eat each other if this is dumb
In the past we've
Discuss why cannibalism is inefficient as a diet and all but the most
Extreme circumstance
The calories expended to kill a person and eat them would likely not be worth what you did
Get from
Piano
Bunch of issues even leaving like societal taboos
It's not a good it's not
It's not a good plan called the most delicious game we're called The Most Dangerous Game
Sprite
That means it's
Challa
What's going on is that the show Yellowjackets is really popular and that's show that involves a girl soccer team
Brought a plane that crashes into the wielder
Oh Canada
They have to survive for a long time and apparently cannibalism is involved in the pilot episode
Kind of like a live but not really like it at all
The crash in the show happens in 1996 and the show includes tracking
Sing the girls who survived in their current lives
It's very heavily implied that they're resorting to cannibalism
Isn't entirely based on a need to eat human flesh to survive or no
Is it there's weird stuff going on
You've watched it I would admit that I haven't but from the reviews and breakdowns I've read it's
Seems like it has a little bit of Supernatural nonsense and the lord of the
The Flies kind of vibe minute to discuss the plot more but that would involve spoilers and honestly from reading it explained
And I've no idea what's going on with
That show and I bet you don't either
It's kind of one of those shows where it's like what if we imply everything
And then we'll get a second season and will will f*** it up then right out
I think it's
Seems like one of those shows that if I hadn't
Gone along for the entire ride of Lost
Yeah but also flash-forward
Yep many other shows
Maybe I would jump in tell her they fight
I'll wait
See I didn't see lost I didn't see all these things so I'm fine with it for now
Is going to be garbage and I got to be like we're going to explain things and that we midichlorians involve so whenever baby. You never know
How do I in the wake of that shows massive success he was released on DVD in mid-july
So there is renewed conversation about it including discussion of the coming second season and the cannibalism scene
In the first episode and it apparently wasn't even explained by the season finale
People are talking about this show that they're enjoying so the New York Times published
An op-ed about a couple of pieces of cannibalism related creative
That have come out recently seemingly building on the premise
The cannibalism is a Hot Topic in fix
These days
Naturally the right-wing went batshit over this and created an entire new cycle based on the nonsense idea of the time
Was trying to tell people that cannibalism is actually really cool and maybe they usually pee
Alex is a shallow thinker and a shallower reader so he's not read this op-ed and I wouldn't be surprised
If you didn't even read the full text of the breath
Breathlessly outraged response articles that were written about it
But if you had read the original think you would have read this part towards the end
According
Miss Summers cannibalism is always symbolic
Burger novel's protagonist
Is eating human flesh can be seen as a way of holding onto a relationship
Ended
For Miss Summers herself the plot of a certain
Hunger can't be uncoupled from quote my own personal experiences with disordered eating
With the tamping down a summon an appetite
The way the media choose up
And spits out writers
Boozie consumption and boujee Lady can sub
Auction Tucson
More generally Miss Summers thinks that the recent Spate of cannibalistic plots could be commentaries on capital a
Call cannibalism is about consumption and it's about burning up from the inside in order to
Exist
Bernard is essentially over
Consuming yourself your own energy
Your own will to survive your sleep schedule
You're eating schedule your body
The article is a thoughtful examination of some of these social commentaries that are possibly being made by themes of cannibalism that
What are being expressed in a very limited set of pieces of media
Including a very popular recent series
But of course for people like Alex it secretly the times telling everyone that eating people is trending now
Idiotic
Kid s***
That's the Tiger
It's but it's fun like at least at least
It's something I mean here's a here's the thing for me
I'm trying to imagine
What the real world would look like
If a
Positive
Cannibalism article was released you know like
What would that be on right-wing freak out right like we all live in a world where suddenly the New York Times as like a guest
But we talked to the scientist
And he's like actually we're super nutritious grandparents in front of
What would that look like I definitely get the
GoDaddy
A conversation surrounding
Hey
Wonderworld does
Eat insects
And that's not something that is weird to everybody
It's a cultural thing
There are a very
Station
Protein
Reeb read a million times I understand that conversation
Conversation
Never
Happen as it relates to
Human flight
It just simply could you would put a name on it
You would be like you'd be like oh yeah so yesterday we had Grandpa Joe
I thought everybody better have to stop for a second
The only place at themselves the only way it would exist
In like
Any kind of publication would be in
It's some kind of bee swiftian satire
Kind of
But yeah it is it is funny too
I do appreciate that cuz it does feel more normal for Alex to be like
Either going to make millions how to make you eat people
Haven't been on such a long like
I'm a victim
Right it is kind of nice to have a little bit of something else even if it is
Is entirely stupid will accept that that was a breath of fresh air in a certain sense
It's so rancid but it was fresher than
So there's some other news down in Florida
Songs are going out this before the debate on our luggage don't get too excited
We're going to hit that right the huge development with
Police go to the offices of
Pharos operatives inside the government
But I can't
The big guy
Oh so that that made us before Mar-A-Lago got raided so this kind of ideas pretty good
The government figures home
It's pretty cool to do that cuz they're corrupt but
So this is about
DeSantis firing the Hillsborough State Attorney Andrew Warren
Because he refused to prosecute cases regarding trans people
And reproductive Healthcare cases
The reason is a big deal and a clear abuse of power is that the state attorney is an elected
Office
Yeah it's what I think
You can
You could there are processes
To remove the person
The governor just sorted
Little bit
It's a little bit dicey
Yeah I mean
Do you know it's
Probably bad if a governor is willing to just
Risk being a fascist and see if it plays it pays off
You know like that so a bad sign is when the governor is like
You know what f*** it I bet there's a 50-50 shot this one works
Cuz I think that he really got people voted in
Maybe laterally I'm dictator now I own Florida
It opens up a lot of doors
So Alex is not going to be hosting the show the whole time
And then Mike Adams and Studio always amazing
Wow
Coming up as an hour and he's going also have some big
Gaston
With him
Because I've got to go back down to this kangaroo court
In 15 minutes
I'll be back this evening I did last night shooting first reports
Free 6 p.m. I should be in there during a lot
Like our today
Mike Adams is going to come sailing
I'll tell you what
I skipped it
Health Ranger
Don't dare
Nope gets throat sounds a lot better I'm glad he's feeling better
Smile Bright Now
So much better that a while
Like he says he has a cough button and all that and I know that he does
Foods
Attractive
Have an excuse why it was so bad
And it's great there was some bad
Still some navel-gazing there still some talking about his own
Victimhood
And it involves Alex actually accusing the judge
Do criminal Behavior
And you're not going to believe
What the judge is doing public
I believe it's Criminal
I believe it's
But again
We'll be right back
Dancer the judge is committing crimes
In a larger sense
He did speak a real truth which is that we can't even be good to
Blackwell
Ham
Is is it in
You know you got two parts that
Run is unable to be at
He's arguing he's not being allowed
To be a person is telling the truth
That looks really wants to get into this DeSantis
Kicking out the state attorney story
To bring in a buddy
Derive sidecar with a
Great work DeSantis is doing
Deep State Soros operatives that violate
Barrows office
Just gets better and better
She's actually going after the Deep state
She is doing
Roshaun had
Special guest Pastor Rodney Howard Browne
At the bottom of the hour
Prosecutor is the one that had him arrested
Now he's been fired
By the governor
Show
2020 Rodney Howard Browne divide Public Health guidance and help church services when large public Gatherings were
He was charged with some things like unlawful assembly but Ulta
Those charges were dropped and he didn't really face any consequences
Very impressed this guy how fun
You don't Trump is giving them a taste of fascism and based on Alex's
Current comment about a elected official absolutely wrecking any and all power structures
I think they want more fascism
Yeah you could get some of those indication
Clues
I think I'm picking up on here
So Alex has lost
The in the cumulative
Satori phase of the trial a little over 4 million dollars
Answer here he touches on that a little bit
Let me do this now
Because a lot of people
Into the show
Wanted to get my response to the 4.1 million dollar
Judgment by Austin jury yesterday
Video
Eyewear I
Play out about 5 minutes
My stance on it
Where I stand
But I'll do that again
By the tuning lives in a lot of your tuna in their new viewers
Going to get my view but there's last night's announcement breaking exclusive Alex Jones responds to 4.2 million Sandy Hook
Verdict 628 thousand views
Legosi
It's very important video
Self-employed
Briefly
Chronicle
What's been happening the last week and a half
Almost
As of today
Kangaroo court
And how's the model for the rest of the country and the world
George Soros
And the operatives are literally
Coordinating and running this man
That's quite a scoop
I would not have said that
Said that
Why not that's just me
You know I'm because and here's why I wouldn't have said it right or not fun
Right and it's more it's not so much the jury now or the judge
It's more the sanctions that are coming
Sure you really should also like
You really casting your bat
On
The other trials aren't going to happen
If you're happy
Some of this post-trial Behavior
I could easily see it being introduced as like
Look how do you know where you that he behaves how do you not
I mean in another punitive hearing how do you not go okay
We did one punitive hearing
And this was supposed to get him to stop doing this
So here's what he said
Hours later he decided that he was going to imply that he will not be kept away from that
Sandy Hook family
And then
Accuse the judge of criminal Behavior
So the media
In on it
Drudge
Soros operatives unnamed
Right but definitely in on it
The corporate media in the courtroom
Who is coordinating with the medium
The judgy is altering the record of the trial in my view
By recording
Just say I'm guilty until the jury
Guilty
Ziebart us
She barred us
From
Being able to respond to the punitive damages
Dover
Today I'm an Acura
Net worth
Iceman
Complete list
Under court order
And then
Argument or calling any Witnesses we could only cross-examine
Literally is some
Drift covered
Just joking
There's like five names
Yep that is my new alias
Can I give you that that's a good one
His name is Bernard Peta guilt
Snip snap
It sounds like that name is missing an Esquire after it though
Yeah you can hear it better but yeah you can hear it choir for lawyers
Something like that but so what
People's Federal goddamn
That's good bad good stuff
Stratford-upon-avon
What about the judge
Falsifying the record
Or whatever
And so I was I was kind of in
Interested to hear what that
Matt is that what he was talkin to
Here yesterday
Running around the office
Trying to watch the verdict
And she was killing stream every 5 minutes or so
Because she said she would live streaming
But we kicked their butts so bad even though we had our hands tied behind our backs
Most of my testimony
Law & crime
Can only put out edited clips of me
Mason moments
Those
Text messages all come for me on my phone I gave it to all the lawyers
Now you have it
You guys should act like you didn't have it but his phone
The most generous explanation for this is that Alex is an idiot and doesn't understand that lawn crimes YouTube channel
Posted the long-form videos of the trial
And also publisher Snippets of particularly exciting moments like when it's text messages were revealed
Alex doesn't deserve a generous interpretation and the reality here is that
He's just lying to make his audience think that the judge in this case
Shut down the feed and only allowed these shorter clips
To go out which is nonsense
It's likely too late for it to matter but I have to assume that this could constitute
Contempt of court
Type thing
He's literally accusing the judge of
Yeah I mean
They are there still have to work out the exact sanctions for both
Renaldo and Alex
Like that is still in the air it's not like there
It's not like they
They wrote down the number and they handed it to Alex and they're like
Okay you can keep being a piece of s*** but you're also going to owe us this
You know they're still doing that man
I both watched
Feromonas
And was there in person and I can
You can play with
I need a bit of confidence
But Alex was not kicking their ass so bad
Even with his hands tied behind his back
That they would need to shut down the feed the same thing as the courts
Which Alex is intentionally
Confusing
Respond yeah it's meaningless
But he does stress this quite a
Televised televised
Real porch so they do it
A pool camera
That whoever speaking and Emily judge
They're all pet media
And they all run the same script and the same Clips out basic
And turning it off
And turning on and turning it off
She just killed two strings
Show people the trial
And then
But I'll certain parts the trial that was something you don't like having to kill the Stream
He's going down and it's January 6th and all the stuff
Talk she turns it off
None of this happened
No not of it
Not even a little bit
Wild I mean it is
It's just a manufactured Narrative of
What happened
It is
So convenient does it shouldn't it be
Too convenient now for even his listeners that
Everything that proves he's innocent is
Unable to be found
Not
Of course not we're not going to go and look and find the feed like the fool like
6 hour videos on
There's no way
That you could I mean even though do you think I pulled the clips for our last episode also what
Knows how to competently turn a stream on and off at
His lawyer couldn't even figure out how to use a
F****** 8th grade projector
No I think we talked I think I have notes about this later
Bring up at like
We were there in the courtroom
Fan
The Lime Crime
Their camera person was sitting next to us
Through a lot of the time during the trial
And
They would
Fixing things sometimes
Problem
They had with their their stream
There was at least one occasion where I remember that they came in late
There was like that is a separate entire feed from the zoom
There is literally a moment where the battery got down to like 3%
That's because
Somebody a jostle their their coordinated popped out
Like you don't know this is just a boring defense for Alex but I think it's what do you want
To go full-on with it
But it is what you're talkin about you know it is a dynamic of appealing to the unknown
It's like there's this other stuff somewhere that proves that I'm
Yep I'm innocent but you can never find it
Evil judge
So Alex
Certainly pissed off about being jammed up in this trial but
He's got to get to the
World news
The Restless broadcast
But I got to finish up
Please
What's going on down at the
Courthouse
Railroaded
It in the in the
A second phase of the
I guess we're not getting
The news
I guess we're going to do this for long
At least it's kind of fun
Two middle names
He said it on the stands I was there this morning
Paraplegia
Goapele
Google command
Petroglyphs
Mom do you smell
Find him being sworn and he says his name is Bernard Francis petechial Junior
Don't remember goo to the mountainous
I got even at Ozzie mandamus
I can't stop saying that it's so good
Yep
So this is this is quite a can
Conspiracy that Alex's got cooking
Here there are
I mean it's
Its sprawling are there a lot of players in the game now soulmate
The judge
Cold all the news
I've authorized all of you to be here
But no one else is allowed to film interview to I'll have you arrested
Like that
Do you want tape
And then whenever we speak she cuts us off on YouTube
So they can then add the new screws at it down
Down to the same section
Somebody
Everybody on YouTube
12:50 comments for me
And all the sudden they all get pushed out and deleted a bunch of hateful comments you put the top
Boats
Car push the bottom
Let's take a step back and try to forget that we're listening to a celebrity racist demagogue here and really listen to what there
They're saying
Anyone
You knew was talking like this about how everyone was out to get them would rightly understand that they aren't well
But for Alex it just kind of his
He sounds like someone Raven about black helicopters because he's literally the same person who is Raven about black helicopters
20 years ago
He's delusional and he's not enough people to enable and reinforce has delusions that he's been able to make it profitable
Did inflate himself from any consequences of his actions
But this just sounds
Dumb
Alex is getting on the show to complain about how unfairly he's being treated which is evidenced by
Completely inaccurate description of how the live streams are brought
Then he's heard from other people there's a conspiracy about silencing supportive YouTube comments
Which is just pathetic
Alex isn't even able to make this claim he has to say that other
People have told him this is happening
He has literally no idea this is real at all but
It feeds into his victim of status so
Not only is it real it's also probably way worse than it seems
And it's being directed by the judge in coordination with Soros
Alba live stream
Commenting was disabled for obvious reason
As far as the longtime videos are concerned you can go to those and still see a ton of bro Alex comments
Mostly in the live chat
It's silly to think that YouTube comments mean anything
A lot of them are Bots
Many of them are people just rolling and they're plenty that just don't
Even make sense
Really sad to see a 48 year-old adult whining on his show but how he's heard that there aren't enough
Positive comments
How about him on some YouTube video so it must be a censorship
Conspiracy issue
Nonsense it's just
Yeah I really thought we were done with allowing people to b**** about YouTube comments
I just thought that was done I'm done with allowing it to
To mean anything
I mean nobody
It speaks volumes about
You if you're complaining about it
Everything eats been in movies
From like 2015 where it's like hey
Don't read the comments on the YouTube to everybody
Just knows that it's a horrible place
There is still something
Have a conversation in terms of like a
Abusive and directed abusive harassment and stuff
Don't that that does still exist
Commenting
And what have you quite
Trying to argue stuff it's like
Oh my tweets are getting enough likes I must be hidden
Must be too dangerous to The Establishment or whatever
Yeah the concept of maybe I'm uninteresting is just enough of a property
Because he's got Wilfred us TV boring
Turn away yeah the judge
The cover-up man deeply involved
Tell the judges in lifetime manipulating what the world can see
They don't want you to let it go last week and a half of the trial
People not figuring out she's doing this
Everybody's going and finding it
And going and finding
What they weren't supposed to have
Because
There were several other groups they're screaming
The didn't completely
If anybody else was recording they were committing a crime
Thanks I made based on
My experience of being there in the courtroom
I don't think
That was happening
A couple read
Yeah if you actual cameras
People like the lawn Crime Check folks documentary
You also had
A fair amount of
Security interlock bailiffs
Yeah and like
Sheriff's officers or whatever
Court officers
Hey there's someone was recording and they were
They didn't have permission
That would have been shut down
Almost instantly
I don't I couldn't stop myself from laughing a couple of times and I got to visit
Yeah it's
Looking around the courtroom
There
Packed their word a bunch of people there
I don't think there were people who were
Like bootlegging the trial I don't think
Part of it is just
It really wouldn't have made sense to fit more cameras in
No but have been pointless
It wasn't a big courtrooms in that big and there weren't that many people there and I mean ice
Yeah and I think they knew be interesting and
People would watch it I don't think they thought it would be
That big of a
Will the courts
Zoom was
Aaron the entire thing
The Law & crime had a slightly better camera and they were
Screaming most of it
With some limitations of Defense
Alright whatever was going on camera I think maybe two
Where to get
Better shots
Yeah or the battery
That it's
I don't know any
The judge and answer for this behavior on air
He's Bass
Basically creating a large Target on her by fabricating conspiracy
That the video in the courtroom was being manipulated in this is
Just completely unacceptable Behavior
Yeah if I was in the middle of being two-faced being
Kingzina Sudan about to get a huge judgment for defaming somebody I would not in the same time. Want to see
People on the judge of that
Places me
That's kind of what he did when Rodger Stone
I don't know it seems like
Just behavior that he can't stop himself because he put a million-dollar bill
It's not only the judge
Tulso the lawyer
Everyone's against Alex
Noticing
Up to three or four times
Every 10 minutes
What
When y
Signaling each other
Cut the feedback 10 minutes okay
Ayo the justice department
Everything else we got his whole phone with they don't
Okay rahner and she's like
The feed
This is total
Coordination
I do I just I don't
Don't think that this is okay
Okay
This is a pretty serious accusation that Alex is making all things considered
Ultimately
Almost right
I think your people know that
He's full of s***
There are real dangers that you could be putting people in by making accusations like this
And you just can't
Do this
Yeah
You can't accuse people of criminal Behavior
In criminal coordination between a judge and lawyer
I don't know if
Monsters come out of topsy-turvy world to attack people
You know
Alex lives in topsy-turvy world so we look at it more like a listen you sound like an absolute
Nutjob baba baba baba baba
What do you send to people
Eddie's putting Targets on people that there that are being sent
The crazy
It's not okay it's not okay to be some sort of a check on it
Yeah okay
Alton got to get
Honestly this
Case
Is meant to distract him
From this large work
That is so important that he needs to do okay
They're trying to distract
Acme
From my work
But they're not
And that's why I'm not down there at the
Enphase the trial today
Is because
No matter what the globalist
Breathing air
Moana locked up
Present
I am going
Fighting
Stay in the fight with
They want me to talk about their attacks they want me to
Sending myself but you you understand where to stand
Not going to let them
Attract
What is it
Distract us from welders this
That's tacky
It all comes
Back to this tacky
Distract us
From knowing about
What I'm about to come
I'll be back
Today
In the fourth hour
And I'm going to tell house with Robert Barnes
I'm in the war room
Because I'm not going to let
Let me hear most the day
Daughters begging me to take her fish
She has no future if I don't do this job
I'm not a martyr I'm not a big
But I'm going to work harder
Because they're trying to silence us because I know it's hard
But we've done together I realize I've got a
I'll cover this morning for Saturday
Then she's not wind up there
The sideline so you know it's coming up
I hate
That like
Every time
There's like
You know the globalists are really acting up and duty calls
The real thing that ends up happening is that Alex's daughter doesn't get to do something fun
How many times has he not taking her fishing
How many times
Don't tell me about how you need to take it better fishing
When you haven't that's
Sad for me yeah there's a
Beam of light
I got to fight these globalist
I'm going to take my daughter fishing imagine her sitting
At home with a fishing pole he said he was going to come today
This is a willful
Re contextualize Agera neglectful parenting
Cheers be good news
What's a good plan didn't exist to begin with their 10 fishing trip
Dramatization anyway Alex is going to do a fun run of headlines
And so I decided he's like these are all connected
And this is what the globalist
We're going to go on this run with him
What happened
So here's the first headline
Swedes eat
The headline from 2019 which Alex doesn't know because his team just Googled cannibalism imprinted out everything
That seems like a good work
Ouch Alex does no prep for the show so he's cooled reading headlines have been making up contacts for them and then miss Casey
He's pretending that it's a current story
This was about Magnus soderlund
Two went on Swedish TV and was interviewed about some research he was doing into social taboos about food sources
Basically human meat was used as an extreme example of something that pretty much everyone
Consider past the line but where exactly was the LIE
Lab-grown beef
Artificial meat
Insect
Where do people feel like I don't know
He doesn't want people to eat people and that wasn't something he was advocating at all
Magnus very astutely deduce that his words have quote
I've been hijacked by people who don't believe that global warming and other climate issues should be
Be taken seriously
One of those people was a writer for
For the epoch times who wrote a headline that Alex is now reading on air
This is a bulshit story with no connection to reality that was published three years ago
So this string of headlines
Is off to a very strong start
So you're saying that the swedes have not started eating each other
Not to my knowledge okay
I truck I don't have anybody on the ground
Oh no
Video transcript
Transport secretary again towel
Expensive electric vehicles at solution for high gas
So you have Pete buttigieg
Said that
Maybe electric cars
Maybe we could get some subsidies for people to be able to afford electric cars that is related to eating people have
Because he said that this sweetest person said that you should eat people to help with climate change
Which isn't really true
Sylvia maybe the climate change aspect of it is
I appreciate you trying to track
Because they're specifically all connected
Electric cars
Well let's see let's see if we can find some more connective tissue
Hypocrite Trudeau
Hypocrite
I thought it was Obama who didn't want people have air conditioner
Our car which
Isn't truth begin with but it's a lot
I guess it's
Now to go
I'm starting to suspect the baby Alex really is just gold reading headlines and hasn't seen in any of these things at all buddy
We have a three-year-old article about cannibalism
Matt Smith Pete buttigieg made about
The electric-car straight and a picture of
Trudeau not wearing a mask
This can't be the super important work the globalist want to distract Alex
Text Rob because this is ridiculous you know I wrote down earlier
Whenever he was saying like
Confirm my work and I won't allow it and it's like
If that is true
Just on its face
The news currently B
Gargantuan
You know like
During the trial now maybe maybe you could even consider like trumps
Ray being gargano's actor
Holy s*** you know there is there's
Fires going up inside of your home right now because then Alex would be able to cover it
That would justify the distraction Arrow
But I feel like the news was mainly like
Now we're going to try and lower gas
Taxes Sweden has given the green light
On eating people but Alex doesn't know that and he's presenting his current so
So I guess
Eat up
I guess I guess we had to sue Alex Jones to make sure that swedes could eat people let me see this
I know what the swedes do with meatballs
And
If that's the president of how they're going to serve people
I'm out I'm out to let him know thank you I'm just saying that Scandinavian food is not bad
Food but there are way better for you're not going to trick me to eat people with lingonberry
I can tell you that right now
I won't even eat their fish let alone their people
Call Boo
Climate called is eager to take advantage of Europe's energy crisis
Control remotely they would
With the smart meters
What temperature do you set your house to no lower than 8
This is just an op-ed on zerohedge that's completely meaningless as proof of anything and doesn't even include
Any B
It's about remotely controlling people's thermostats
That stuff that Alex is writing his own story about
But it's very real issues surrounding energy rash
Proposals
In countries that could be more directly affected by Russia's ability to control the flow of oil and natural gas
It was a question of remotely
We controlling smart meter thermostats in Moore city council is being asked
To do everything they can to conserve enter
After this is a string of headlines about reducing car ownership so I
I guess that a bunch of these headlines could be said to be connected but
I'm struggling to make
The larger meaningful connection
Cannibalism is just flashing and fun
I guess
I think that I understand what Alex
Once the connection
Centipede but it's
Pretty much just in his head
He's basically laying out the climate change advocates
It's an elaborate plot
Destroy Society through making people unable to have energy resources
Which I make them unable to get any food so I guess the media's trying to
Prepare people for the idea of eating other human
Mind you this is entirely different than Alex's big rant about how he's willing to barbecue is Neighbors
The Beatles children
Alex discusses cannibalism it's actually genius
Eddie's making a larger
The point where is
When people he doesn't like do it eats proof of Insidious plan to depopulate
This Alyssa headlines is legitimately depressing
Eddie does not need a lawsuit to distract
For doing his job he's
Doing fine on his own and his job is
Completely meaning
Yeah I don't know you just don't get to complain about cannibalism if you have already made the plan in
In your mind that your neighbors and feed them to your kids
High public profile publicly
Cut it out loud you're on the record as bad as being an acceptable strategy
When it comes to that
I feel like you shouldn't be able to do
To talk s*** I know it was a pretty
Like
Accidentally hit his window with a baseball bat day
So we have a couple more headline
Even though I had lost my page
With this
Australia's Great Barrier Reef
With record Coral come back
The truth is coral reef grow they die they come back they die they come back
So this is reading off Breitbart but it's kind of a dishonest framing of the story
Well it is true that parts of the Great Barrier Reef or seeing considerable healing that's not true that as a whole
The northern area of the resau gains and hard coral cover but
The southern section actually went down
This is good news but it's part of a larger picture
What are the main concerns about the reef is hard coral cover
But another equally important aspect
Is bleaching
Bleaching is the result of a temperature or weather anomaly that leads to the coral expelling
The algae that give it its color results
Sing in the coral becoming White
It's not Dad at that point but it's at a significantly greater risk
And importantly Reese
Are complicated system
Dogs that are capable of feeling so if there is some bleaching the coral can become home to algae again and and
And come back to what you call like a vibrant light right right scientist is that weather events
Because large-scale bleaching have been increasing in frequency
There been for Mass bleaching event
In the past 7 years
Experts don't know how resilient the reefs are to this height
Pressure
It's an open question
Frightening
The implication
Another aspect that is up to
Concerned is mentioned in a Reuters story about this
Quote the growth in cover has been driven by acropora corals
Switch the Australian Institute of Marine Sciences said
Are particularly vulnerable to wave damage keep stress
And Crown of Thorns starfish
This is coral cover that is increasing which is good but it's a type of coral that
Highly likely to be susceptible to the sorts of weather event
Better be coming in
Increasingly common
Which is a big reason to be worried
This increasing cover could lead to
The false hope
Or conversely to people like Alex ignoring the details of the story in order to use it as a prop to attack climate science
It says invalid
A usual Alex has no idea what he's talking about but he's got a Breitbart headline and that's enough
The trick is already into the pygmies next
So yeah we were at we were at
Museum and
Butthole
Area in
San Francisco
Few years back
And they had
There's a massive section of the
The place now
Like it used to be something different and now it was just all devoted to the coral reef
And the way the coral is was dying and everything was so f******
Sad cuz that was their goal was like
You used to walk in here and see some cool stuff and then be like well that was fun
Now it's
You're going to be like I'm going to go fight
Australians to save the coral reef like that's how you walk out of there and it is a tragic
Tragic tragic
I meant some of the positive news that ends up
Coming out you hear about the Great Barrier Reef is the result of
Very aggressive conservation app
Yeah
Does people take Advair e-cigarettes can with everything they've got
All the time and they will have my
Yeah I don't even I don't even want you reporting good news about it because then people that can be like all things are getting better
Reporting enough news about how it's
Dying every single day
I think that balance is tough to strike a little bit difficult
To get another headline
Sounds fun
New findings are reanimating not just dead spiders
Eggs
Stein is real
Holyshit
Get the Torches
I just he think that the soul isn't
Included with the real anime
I don't know he doesn't he doesn't
Expound on this at all.
Goddamnit Alex probably just saw a headline about research that was done at Rice University where they found
Dead spiders as a way of gripping things
Essentially it has to do with how spider legs been
How old are you really need to do to manipulate them
Is apply a hydraulic
Pressure inside the spiders abdomens
The researchers used a needle to Puff air into them and found that they were able to expand and retract
The spider's legs
Personally I think this is a little f***** up
I don't know how much of a high horse any of us has
W about like how you going to respect
The sanctity of dead spider it's weird
Pretty interesting if I stepped on it a few days ago I can't be mad if somebody's like look I can make it it's legs work
Baby Back video with the researchers to one of the things they bring up it's like it's kind of tough to argue with
Is that it is like
The great biodegradable material
You know like s***
Something that you
Okay you end up in a strange position do if you're like a breeding spiders in order to kill them as respect
We talked to hope that would not be the past thing
Anyway that's not the application but Alex has taken
See that's the issue
As for the pig thing Alex just skimmed a headline about this but it's a little closer to reanimation
Not
This is nothing
He getting reanimated it's a cellular thing
This has some considerable philosophical implications and could stand to revolutionize processes
Used in organ donation
But it's not Frank
Anstine or at least not yet
I do find myself unnerve slightly by this portion of it NBC news article about
Quote
The pigs treated with Organics
Startled researcher
During experimentation the dead pigs heads and necks
Moves under their own power
The animals remained under heavy anesthesia the researchers do view the naked jerk as an indication
Muscle function was restored after
Death
If you're someone who believes that all science fiction is secretly real I can see how you might respond to this like Alex does
It's silly
But I get it anyway I'm still having trouble with you
Connection of all these stories
Even these two stories allegedly about reanimation aren't connected in any meaningful way
At this point I was so bored of this list of headlines that I was getting
Getting really redundant so I decided it was time to move on from this Fun Run
Yeah but
That story about the pig
Is like
That is something I wish
Someone was like Alex
But not Alex yeah maybe a little bit more in touch with reality would have a take on because I think it's
Think it's a little bit like your reaction
It there is a place for that
Right
To restore muscle I think what's interesting to me about this
Is the idea of
Consciousness you know like okay you're worried about Frank
Consign and all that stuff
But are you telling me that
Bebe
Consciousness returns
You do with it
Of course not
Otherwise what you're saying spiders have a meaningful
Reanimation is possible then when I die
Right I'll dye my Consciousness will end and then
Suddenly
I will theoretically awaken
Years later
End up in the same word different body like that's not how it works
No so you don't get it so there's no such thing as a soul is what I'm trying to
That's fine that's not even close to anything that is implied by these right now
The only thing I care about when you talk about pigs coming back to life I'm like I'm worried their souls aren't going to be okay
It comes up in articles about this
Is the turtle philosophical implications in terms of like what we categorize as death
Cuz like the ability like if someone has a heart attack in her heart stopped
Which is
Is the heart a muscle if they're able to pump the heart
Like a creep
Bring back
Muscle tissue is that something that they would be able to
There are all kinds of questions that are raised by this but
It's not like
You've been dead for a week
And that we can bring you back
I think I mean
Okay so you're brain-dead
They can't bring back
The function of your nerves so so far as we're aware
I mean what are you just going to jolt people with electricity like in Frankenstein
I mean
Based on Alex's coverage yeah I think I like that's the plan
Okay
Yeah I don't know I think
What what I've actually read on this
I think we'll find out more when there's more research done
Pretty early stages on a lot of this stuff
Probably not Frankenstein or not it's a Dolly the sheep level of bringing people back to
Gotcha
So you brought up the torn lyrics
Actually there's
There's a suspect
Studies show 5G causes major asthma and problems
Congress
This morning
Show
Coughing
Never caught to my wife
Did you know what the studies are
5G causes
Serious breathing problems
Coughing like this
5G areas
They need those for self-driving cars
All the sudden afford self-driving car drives by
A robot car go by
Wild robot cars make him cough
Oh that reminds me outside outside of the courthouse I was making the jokes
And I didn't erjon reference 5G
YouTube to Rob do Skydive friend
And now here is she didn't even know
The 5G from her phone was causing Alex's coffin the courtroom
Resume my courtroom is full of 5G
She was the one who had the biggest phone though I noticed that on the stand Alex didn't a 5G is making me cough
Crazy flies on his show
He comes back
After having gone to the courthouse
We have not figured out yet
Exactly what the judgment will be bought
For summer starts
Display special reports
What's going on here
We get 20 minutes in okay
Alex finally shows up
With Barnes until
Well even update on that
But also I should say it Advanced Alex uses an R slur here
Play just want to
It's no good
The Ransom promos earlier cuz for some reason
Nursery left
There's so little human communication now though like
And that's how the global chart
People don't
Communicate with each other
Shopping mall
From all of us
Doxo
He wasn't on there for 20 minutes because Barnes
Thought you were
You didn't need to go on are so you left and they was trying to call Barnes and
I mean I mean that
Dart cars
Absolute Insanity in the courthouse I was
Why was screwed on my phone the whole time screw you could have texted Martin's when he were going to be back to go on there
Activate the 5G
Everybody's right to look man
Alex said he was going to cover the news when he came back in the fourth hours are but now he can't cuz Barnes isn't there
So sad
I'm so sad
Demi Lovato
Good save
Gorilla Snot
All matter service was getting cut off energy
We've already killed somebody
Russia starts
All the wimps that have lived opposite
All the frogs of hidden mine
RBS
It's all over now.
So I guess we all deserve to die cuz Barnes isn't there
This is a mood
Quick
He's so mad
Die
Yeah right
Okay I feel like
This isn't like the Judgment hasn't even come down and
Oh my God
A bad mood
I can tell
You will die
Oh okay
Because you're living the dream you will be judged
Aren't you going to die in the west
I don't live in a Fantasyland I live in a real world
But nevertheless
Everybody's got their own idea how things work so you go ahead and
Do it your way
Okay
I have a
Video clips on a play here
And one of them is Dick Cheney the war
Criminal
The torture master
The globalist criminal
National TV
He was an enemy of America
Has the nerve to get up and say people running against his daughter
Are the enemies
Trump is the enemy
What angle on Dick Cheney putting out a video saying Trump sucks is to lash out at Cheney and say who are you to talk
I bet that's fair
Another way to look at it is a journey of the f****** monster of historical scale and even he realizes the Trump is a pile of s***
I guess this is a glass half-full or half-empty thing and yeah
Yeah it was you guys have fun
Cool
So Barn shows up
What
Yeah why pull the car around don't show up Barnes you just going to get his bad mood on you
No actually Alex's mood changes
No he perks up a little bit
Makes me think that maybe Barnes is holding or something
But here's a little secret
Really close.
Under Texas law there for million-dollar judgment
If they do a huge billion-dollar putative
At one point something million
Spinning to the media
How there could be there's going to be a
Completely got on the meeting was recycling this as if it was the truth about sex
YG
Call my wife
Boulder yard
Longstaff
In tough times if you think if you think that in Vera's YouTube
Yard
We can't afford her Gardener anymore
Staff that has more than one God
Oh God so yeah I mean
Alex I think you know there's something about Barnes they just
Brightens up a room
And I think you can feel it Alex is so much happier now that Barnes is there
He's got his buddy there is something about barnes's ability to like weather so much b*******
And kind of like spin it into like a little positive thing for Alex
Gifty has
I think he hypnotizes Alex with his like
Phrases
Blank and blank
All of the time
Arna
Always alliterative and it's
There's something about those speech patterns that I think Alex
Gets sucked into a bad thing to learn
So look
Most of this
Fourth hour is Barnes being full of s***
Ryan
Advertising it's really just trying to get money
There's my problem I could get major national foods guys
They're on Hannity and on back
Babies are smarter than 70%
I have this weird erotic thing to give our lives for the best
Oh man that's wild
Did Alex get to survival food buckets from my Patriot Supply
My Patriot Supply to an iceberg years
I'm not sure if Hannity actually sells food buckets at this point but he definitely did it the past in the past
Luther mypatriotsupply.com and have sponsored
Ben Shapiro and Rush Limbaugh and countless other right-wing ship stalkers brightness
You need emergency food because the government's going to go full dictatorship
In the rhetoric which is justice
Strange coincidence
Really f****** work so what you're telling me is that I can even if I'm a huge Shapiro fan
Or even if I'm a huge
Glenn Beck
Stan
What I should do
Hey is instead of getting my trip Patriot Supply from them I'll get a cheaper price from Ali
Correct
In theory yeah but I don't think that's true I mean I have in the past gone and looked it like various
Deals that were offered
I don't think that's true
What I think is
Going on if I was just describing anything that's
Real
It's that he has such a
Bad negotiating position that he gets a lower cut
Then Ben Shapiro or Glenn Beck.
That would be my hunch
Yeah that's more like
But yeah it's all
But the same
Company that
It's buying all the
These people there
Probably not Jim Bakker though I think he probably has a
Different operation keep puts his own food in those bucket
Yeah yeah yeah
He cooks it himself
He self interesting Theory
About what's coming in the punitive
Kate's here
Even join in the verdict
In for the punitive damages they need you Nana
Steven get any punitive what's your prediction this afternoon
Show me kiss your ass what you said before haven't you
You said I think
Seven-figure verdict I don't think the punitive damages
Just going to come anywhere near what they're talk
Because the cap
25 between both
Before Alex
Be going in the direction of
Yeah they're very much downplaying
What will come back part of their like
That's that
Storyline that's still going on that they like
Impaled the jury and like they saw through it and everything
I mean it's going to be a little bit of a deflation when the
50 million
Number comes around
It's interesting to hear about the cat because
The more I read about it the less
Clear it becomes
And from what Mark told me is that part of the reason
That this whole thing is going to get weird
Is that
If they want to they can there's something written within the Caps of like
If this is extraordinary bulshit
Beyond what anybody who could reasonably expect
F*** the cap
Let's go hard on this guy you know like that kind of thing
But that's going to lead to appeals and appeals and all that stuff
So I'm not sure but
Whatever anybody is reporting about the
To cap it is
Up in the air still a number of different Dynamics. Play
Oh yeah and
Is as far as I know like
About anything about the case and about how this all works
Let's see what happens
No idea
Wrote this law yeah and I think that Alex is entire bankruptcy situation over complicated even more
And could work to his disadvantage
Right
Tulsi
Barnes decides he's going to jump in with Alex on this whole life
The judge is committing crimes
I'm staying great idea for a lawyer
Criminal
Savage judge say this televised
Then she cut the YouTube off and we speak
Warriors
Having their people
I mean I think that's wrong
Because even a liberal Democratic jury in Austin that way
Selected by these planets
Lawyers rejected
The core aspects
So their Theory
C u r a l
And you are not
At the caricature
They tried to make you out to be
And even though they played
Video sometimes only 5c
7 Seconds
Like 2 seconds
What about he was five seconds
I personally
I would not
Put the allegations
Concerns about The Judds into the
The trial you know who else didn't want to put Barnes into the trial
Barnes
He was Alex's lawyer until she got too hot and he quit or got fired and now
Themeforest corporate Rapids testified under oath that they're exploring suing a malpractice
Such horseshit
Barnes is a week loser hiding on Alex's show pretending to have an expert opinion acting like the reality
Then he took an active part in this didn't happen
How does he pretend to be a lawyer and then get on air and say that the case was scripted in the plaintiff attorneys selected the jury
As if that wasn't a process of the defense was equally involved in
Poorly
We're just low
Yeah this is nonsense he should be
Like
I don't know he should give up his own license
Engaging in this s*** is if I was the defenses lawyer whenever they chose the jury I wouldn't have
Will you talk to me
I don't think he even knows anything about that
Vicky does either
Show me one last clip here from Friday
Show Italy
This is just
Here is the same lawyer
That the worst part is I said lock her up
We're here because he criticized Hillary here it is
I know he was Reckless
Alex knows he was Ralphs
Immediately going
Megyn Kelly
The truth
The runner website
Hillary Clinton
Wow you guys are good at fake laughing
They're like
Literally
Hillary Clinton's butt
Politically dead
Have to ask yourself of Alex even thinks his audience is Concha
It's clear what Wesson saying that clip that Alex is trying to dodge responsibility for his actions by saying
Other people said things too
And then he punctuated his Claim by joking that he was surprised that Alex didn't yell lock her up
I was just pretending that this is somehow a statement of
Support for Hillary or did mention that this case is only happen
Nothing because of Hillary
But it's pretty tough to get there from what the actual
Clip that is played at that is so impregnable obvious
Yeah that is its this is if
This is the most gaslighting so that you can do
This is too dude lying their asses off about the situation they're in trying desperately to put on a triumphant face for the audience
They need to keep giving them money
If there wasn't a resolution they could be spun as a victory here the audience who probably get it through their heads that sending Alex money is through
Throwing your money into a pit
So it's critical.
Keep a stiff upper lip and pretend that you're having a great time being sued
You actually won
What do you think about it
I mean rejected the theory and thesis
Ninini and assert
Incense
What has happened
Is that Alex Jones is money-making operation
Is now a savings account
For the fam
So
The more money he makes
You know it's going to them
At the end of the day
Unless he's getting real fancy with some bookkeeping if he's if he's getting real fancy with
Bookkeeping
You going to jail and I think that'd be better than having a savings account
Well it would certainly limit his ability to
Bulshit
So
The world comes on
Santa our boy
Duck Destroyer
Aka the puppet comes on
I'm sure
And
Is a little bit dramatic
A little bit this is Mike Adams level dramatic
Burning point
Dean
The political paradigm
It has happened in the West
That used to Value individualism
Freedom
Prosperity
Life
Creation
What and we now pivot into Ada's
Western world
Good values
Oppression
Humanity
Population
Satanism
Anti-freedom
Anti truth
Portent
Turning Point
Is that
Now
American left
The liberal Progressive
America
I'll take it off the mask
And they are now
Embracing it
Now in human his
This is some serious babyshit
In all the course of human history
Good or bad decision that ever been made the Ted geopolitical consequences many by left-leaning politicians
Nothing compared to the day that Alex Jones learned
He has to pay people for defaming them
What's at the end of the Free World when Fox settled their defamation suit with Seth Rich's parents or when CNN settled with Nicholas
I feel like it wasn't
Probably because Alex is narcissism is so strong
Such an important part of what makes this
Show and everything on Infowars work
For the audience that onesa tap into it in order to exist in that environment
This is really pathetic to act this way and I have zero respect for Owen or his proclamations of us announcing that we are the bad guy
Guy butt
He wants to act this way I've just one thing to say to him what's that
Hey yo
Basketball reference you would have got back
Scott Hall was the bad guy
Can't see nobody
It's just you and me here
So you do know an audience you know but yeah
Bad times don't last bad guys do
Okay
In the tradition of Alex before him
Oh and decides he's not hosting her show today either
Ladies and gentlemen it is Friday August 5th
Infowars War Room broccoli by infowarsstore.com
And I have to tell you today broadcast is going to be a great one now I am live and studio right now
Play Clark is about to take over with
So many great guy
That it
It's going to be a great
Transmission
So quick Clark is this guy who does the reawakened America Tour and they go and do these like
Qanon adjacent speakers and lightning
Alex was at 1
Jim Breuer
Does anybody work there like when they look dude I understand what you're saying but
Far as Owen goes imma give him a pass
It keeps like having to host his own show and altitude of True Life true I have a little bit of sympathy
For him cuz they are making him do double duty of a
Alex's punitive
Alex just decided I want to go to the core is like
Some big gas
Sure clay Clark has a big gap I was like I don't believe this okay
Clay Clark
Sparked start
Gerald
What up my brothers
This is quite a Duo
We all know Mike Flynn but Peter Navarro isn't necessarily someone who's been on Alex's show in the past
Not to my knowledge
He was an aide within the Trump Administration and overall he's basically a s*******
He's currently facing contempt of congress charges for refusing to
Comply with subpoenas in the investigation into January 6th he's also in hot water for conduct
Official government business on a private phone and then refusing to turn over records from that phone
Insisting that he needs to be granted immunity Before He'll do so
For this whole thing is setting.
Here we have a real qanon adjacent government overthrowing Enthusiast panel
Happening
Not quite sure what I expected from the war room but I'm open to seeing where this goes I mean that is
That is a bold
Statement to come out with
Welcoming General Flynn and Peter Navarro today and it gets better
Crazytalk okay we go
Mike Lyndell here who what
What is happening
He all he says
Mike
We know that you three are going to somehow be in that white house
Serving what's President Trump
What what
Everybody America
Needs to know right now is p
People are being this
Discouraged demoralized
What would you like
The same thing I did on the
Everybody we've got all the
You need to watch
August
21st is called the moment
48 hours
Spokane
Forever
So when like the president to the former president calls
Mike Lindell the best advisory
What that translates do is he's a mark
Is a hill fund anything
I wouldn't want to be called the best ad buyer
No
The dumb thing to call someone better ask some real serious questions if someone calls you that
Mike lindell's
Has sounded like
He's starting to sound like a Graveler
Older Jesse Ventura
Well they are both her Minnesota right will that make sense
I've heard in the past
Yeah Mike Lindell holy
So he stopped himself from doing these telephone in the middle
The last one is going to prove that China stole the election was
Complete disaster in this one is
Is not going to go better
I went to the website for this Summit there's actually really spitting image on the landing page
It's Mike
Mount Rushmore waving American flag
Conveniently he's obscuring Lincoln's face with that flag
Something of a symbolic expression intentional or not
Of his and his movements desire to rerun the Civil War and undo the whole emancipation thing
On day one of the summit Lyndell is going to have a Premiere screening of the film selection code which goes into how the
Election was stolen
It was funded by Lindell and largely is about to Tina Peter
Who you may remember as the election
Conspiracist who was arrested
For allegedly facilitating a security breach
Vidmate 121
He was a county clerk in Mesa Arizona capacity there she enable data from the
And to be leaked and ultimately publishing Acumen on telegram Channel
He recently lost an election she was in running for Secretary of State
He lost in the GOP Primary only getting 27% of the vote but of course
She insist that you want and the election was stolen because
Why not
Anyway Lindale pay to make a movie about her and he's tearing it at his big Summit
Then
On day two we get something truly exciting that I might actually tune in for
From 11 a.m. to 6
30pm we have the trial of the machine
Except on the site they misspelled trial so it actually says Pray Love
The machine
My God there's no explanation for this other than quote
Mike Lindell puts the voting machines on trial
Seven and a half hours
Madness
Are you telling me that the boy Pope has dug up the old Pope and we are putting the pope on the sea
Yes if you're lindell's kid and up by the way I don't know if he has kids
You got to be pissed at a run
He seems to have an endless supply of money to waste but you got to know that eventually it's going to run out in before your very
Very eyes your inheritance has turned into a two-day vanity livestream with a seven-hour fake courtroom scene
We're dad pretends to indict a laugh
Grim stuff man
Anyway
This is quite a painful of gas Towing
This feeling is put together real bunch of top-notch it heads
That that
Quote
We're going to see all of you in the White House when Trump gets back now
Like you know in the normal corrupt World we've lived in for a long time you know your big donor all of a sudden after
You get elected holy cow you're in bassador to like Switzerland
What a great job
Sure you offer giving us all the money there's some corruption but everybody lives their own life
If it's Mike Lindell and Trump
Please like your treasury secretary now you're the best at Beyer I've ever seen
Nobody can control the flow of money better than Lyndell my God
Bedtime
So he can't help himself he's got a pop in
Jones covering Allen
Call Jones
Live on the air
Listen going 4-0
It's not meta that self
Narcissistic
It's not metaphor Alex to complain about his own perceived victimhood on his show it's just any other day on Infowars
I understand Owen wanted to dress this up as something other than vanity but that's
What size poking around on that reawaken America Tour website cuz I was really bored during this interview and I found that
On September 24th
Tulsa Oklahoma
They're putting on a comedy show with Jim Breuer that promises to be
Bee quote like a non-communist version of Saturday Night Live
I know very little about SNL personally but I don't think that the workers can
Control the means of production their boy from what I understand of operations
I think says SNL is a pro-fascist situation
Character based around him with the whole nature
To that show is quote
Steve Jim Breuer is Biden for a night Joe Biden won't remember
I guess the joke is there Biden
Forgetful but the joke kind of works the other way to know about it
He's a bit doing
He couldn't care less about some skits
Jim breuer's doing the front of a bunch of
Qanon aunts and uncles
But also torn
Try to get an opening there's a spot
50 rattle it off no big deal
I've seen Breuer standup
And you could open
I could close
Station Apartments
But yeah via the flyer for this is fun
Because it has a picture of Jim Breuer in a gray wig
I am worried I'm worried for swery carry because now we've got a new biting in the mix
Oh no this one's clearly a clone that's gone wrong
All the American fighter
Hoof
Open pops
And it's because there was an expectation
That
Alexa is going to be on
Dorrough
Talk about
The damage
Came down
And unfortunately Alex
Will not be appearing on the War Room
Three wise men
Johnny Jackson champ
He ain't going to be in today
Add comment
From Alex
This time
However
He is going to be issuing a restraining
Bond that
Directly uploaded to band
Video
Infowars.com
So
Be on the lookout
I am on the lookout
I thought you might have yeah
Is an hour long video no you don't need an hour to say fuk fuk fuk fuk
Mostly just like iwantmati of greedy bunny
And
Barnes
It's here it's just whining
Credible time
Lay out how this
Show trial of
Century
That would make
The Nazis blush is
Robert Barnes
Robert simple incredible
No doubt I mean Bass
Physically
Even the Soviets tried to
Show trial Italy
Good show
The show trial that
It was so one-sided
So evidently part
Made for the movie
Scripps
I was talking to Mark Rober the other day in this
The Hollywood screenwriter
And even he was shocked
To hear how it was basically
Design of quorum
Design like a
A set
With three big movie cameras
With the judge alternating
To be sad when
Should be sad and how it could be set in
And who could who could say it
In such a way that had nothing to do with the rules of Evan
But it's nothing to do with the rules of law intact
Nothing to do with constant
Douche to Liberty Center
And everything to do with
Escrip
Working a case
So that it would have it for
Killer outcome
And in particular at a future media narrative
Response and ultimately an actual
Future movie
Do these guys know what the Nazis did
The Nazis with a blush
This trial I mean little offense
Yeah I was in the courtroom
For a lot more of the casement mediastar Bobby Barnes and I can see very clearly with no hesitation that the courtroom
Was not laid out like a movie set
And it wasn't following
The script
I get that
Convenient narrative for him and Alex to push because they lost
Austin The Fallout in this case is going to be spectacular but this is a weak attempt at damage
Control or whatever they're doing
There were few cameras in the courtroom like I mentioned but they were all the same people's cameras
What was the Court's zoom camera wanted the lawn crimefeed there were HBO cameras for the documentary
I do not know there was a sign on the door to the courtroom that advise people that there was a crew from HBO filming and if they didn't
You consent to be in the background of shots
They shouldn't come in
Beyond that there really wasn't
Much of an effect of cameras had on the actual case
The place where cameras were much more involved in making a scene relates to Alex's action
How the first Tuesday the first day of the case proper Alex Hilda Mini
Press conference in the hallway for all the cameras
Yelling about how you been Railroad and how this is a show trial
That was the video where we're standing in the background
People remember that
After being scolded about how that wasn't appropriate at lunch Alex tried to do it all again in front of the courthouse but there was no
Omerta watch a movie tantrum
Alex wanted a show trial vibe
He wanted there to be tons of national media Crews there covering the case but he didn't get that
I think it's instructive to understand that this complaint that there were all these cameras actually expressing
Alex and barnes's disappointment
But there were cameras there that they could exploit for their own purposes
It's less about the cameras and more
To control the narrative which is something that they're fully used to being able to do within the Infowars Bubba
Adjudge pushing back on that knee for Alex
Control all aspects of how he's allowed to speak
Represent
Himself it seems her trying to create a false narrative which makes total sense
Actual reality encroaching on the fake reality he lives in is it
Experience doesn't attack
Because it's the only way that fake reality can maintain it
Its existence
If you are
If you're a lawyer
If you're a
Lawyer
Right
I should not be allowed to play that clip
Before
We get into a law
Argument or something you know like
If I if I'm in it if I'm a lawyer and barnes's across the the the hole for me and he's on the other desk
Should not be allowed to play that clip and be like Barnes is not taking law seriously.
Like not at all
This guy is not a lawyer
Stop
Stop letting him law
Just take law from him
I think
I mean look I'm not involved in law so I don't know what is and is not relevant to our various things but
I would allow it to the law
Yeah I would say so especially after this next
Let me hear this
This is incredible Robert Barnes continuing with your observations both
Watching the trial on tv being down there
Having live coverage of it why you say it's the
Most insane
It is because well first mother
How much was in a right to
If the judge didn't violet
First Amendment right
Expressions
Association freedom
The Press
Second Amendment right to speech
In favor of the second
Fourth Amendment rights of private
She violated that
Repeatedly through
Knowing what went on into this
Discovery being unduly
Invasive but in fact turning over in
Telling the plaintiff
Why are you could turn over
Protected by the
4th amendment 2
Virginia
Or whomever else
Fifth Amendment rights to due process
Denied rights
B-flat motions
Denied right to bring
You brought all of them
Judgment motion
Do counseling conference
Infringed by the
In the right to confront those making activate
Seventh Amendment rights
The trial by jury
And that means a right to trial by jury on all facts
The facts
The judge decide
Can be tried
And that all of those same analogous Federal
Provisions have analog
In the state
Constitution
Wendy's dude laughing about the case couple hours ago like fake laughing
So weird how this judgment change their mood a little bit
I would like to give a rebuttal to barnes's claim
On the First Amendment front he gives no explanation for how the judge violated Alex's First Amendment
There's a certain of the fact and I can test that
Barnes could never make that case in court because if he could
You kind of expect you would still be Alex's lawyer
Considering those a huge part of barnes's argument back when he was Alex's lawyer
On the Second Amendment side is he saying that the judge didn't allow Alex to bring a gun into the courtroom
I'm unclear on this
I believe he's saying
That by not allowing Alex to describe as his reasoning
The Second Amendment
That is a violation of the second
No cuz that's just the first amendment thing all over again it's not also at a violation of the first month
These rights are violated
I know it's a Barnes isn't accusing the judge of violating the 3rd Amendment which is good
I would hate to hear that Alex was forced to quarter any soldiers during
The trial
Judge Campbell didn't rule on whether or not mark
Could turn over Alex's phone data
She specifically said she wasn't going to get in the middle of
Either way it's not an invasion of his privacy because it was accidentally disclosed by Alex's the proper channels before bring
Can get up if Mark had gotten the text through clandestine memes and that would be a different story but this was rain all f***
Walking
Also nothing about discovery which Alex didn't even cooperate with violated Alex's 4th amendment rights
This is stupid
Alex's Fifth Amendment rights are fully intact
He was not compelled to testify against himself and he had all the due process and a****** can get
You had every opportunity to participate in the case but chose not to
Civil and Criminal Courts cannot operate if people can just decide that they've made up their mind that they've
Jammed up so they don't get
I have to participate in the case
And any attempt to make them for 2
Exactly the state railroading
Sometimes
It does happen that innocent parties get caught up in protracted process he's defending themselves
And that sucks
But that's also why there are mechanisms in place to compensate people who have to go through that
NYU can powder sue if you need to
The sixth amendment doesn't apply since it's about criminal cases
And 7th Amendment only requires jury trials for civil cases in federal court
Asceticism
And Barnes are saying that their analogs in
State Court then why you talking about the Constitution dumb dumb
Good golf Barnes of the lawyer
You should know better and he does
He just doesn't
He's not a lawyer he's someone who knows lost
Happy to use fat loss.
How to draw
Justified right wing
Idiot Sancho's like this
Amazon podcast with Viva Frei
Small point
The guy who tried to storm that Ohio FBI office allegedly posted this on true social
I'm having trouble getting information but Viva Frei said Patriots are heading to
The Palm Beach where Mar-A-Lago is
I recommend the going it and being Florida I think
The feds won't break it up
If they do kill them
Firebarn Zyra and I really wanted to like evoking Amendment for Alex I would go with it
18th
Nasher
That was repealed by the 21st amendment but
If there was ever a right Alex could use right about now it's the
The prohibition of alcohol
See that
I know I am sponsor Islam
I'll give you that calm down the booze Alex you know it is it is
It's so annoying when people are like I ever more polarized than ever
But
There is an argument to be made that
Somehow
More amendments were passed
After or before prohibition was repealed do you know what I'm saying
Like
Everybody agreed that post-prohibition was a bad idea once it
And then they still managed to agree on two more amendments before they could agree on repealing prohibition
We couldn't get a half an amendment passed through now no probably not the only one I would guarantee
Absolutely repeal prohibition
Open today
I bet we could
I would take that back
You might be right you might be right
Like I said
S*******
Dumb dumb
Repeat that
I will rely will double down
The same standard was
Applied
Do axios
That was applied to you
They could be sued in the bank
MC tomorrow by running a headline that says
Does the new it
Questions whether or not there's a
School shooting cover up to be clear they didn't limit this case
ISTA just one or two
They said any state
Questioning anything
Concerning
The Sandy Hook
Narrative
Did a death penalty
They gave you a death penalty
In the default
Midstate then gave you another and they asked for a death
From the jury in the punitive
Barnes has a total s*** head in a liar but he doesn't actually believe what
He saying he's also not so dumb as to be unaware that what
Are you saying is a lie
Obvious
This case absolutely did not include any supposition the questioning aspects of public events constituted FM
The reason that it might appear that way if you're not paying attention is because the plaintiffs attorneys brought up a ton of instances of Alex
Repeating and defending talking points
That he had used to argue that the shooting never happened
Long after he claims he stopped arguing that it didn't happen
In fact I was repeating those claims in the middle of his supposed to
Apology video
Imagine this scenario using one of Alex's bulshit claims from the Sandy Hook times which he got from how they Confessor and Cat
Continue to repeat long after supposedly realizing
The shooting happen
Imagine uconline the people are claiming that the school wasn't
Even open
And there was no internet traffic to the school's website in the year before the shooting
You'd be totally free to discuss this claim that people were making online and hopefully
You have the decency to take like 5 minutes to look into it and see that it
Bulshit before going on air
In mindlessly repeating the claim
But even so if you repeated as a question the folks have you aren't
Committing defamation
This isn't what Alex did
He use these alleged anomalies as a pile of evidence that he would drop on the audience to support his claim that the shooting didn't
When the plaintiffs attorneys
It would demonstrate that he was still making these claims in the fairly recent past
What they're doing is illustrating that he's still making the same
Deconstruct this a little bit
Alex is making the argument
If the school's website. No traffic then the school wasn't
Open
If the school wasn't open to school the shooting could not have happened
Therefore the shooting did
Inhabit
It's essentially a setup of a faith and be
If B then C
A therefore C
It's a perfectly fine construction for an
It's called a hypothetical syllogism
And assuming all your promises are correct it follows that your conclusion will be as well
When Alex has made the argument repeatedly on the show the audience understands that a is proof of
See whether or not they understand this logic
Check path
So when Alex is claiming he believes the shooting happened but then still insisting the premise a is correct
What he's doing is still affirming the conclusion while pretending that he's not
This is one of the ways that Alex has his cake and
Kinney's at 2 or as Marcus edited
In the trial he wants it always
If you pay attention to his show you'll see a bit of this behavior and in the case of Sandy Hook you can plug in a bunch
Different narratives
In that place for premise egg and it works the same
Paramedics weren't allowed in the building kids walked around in circles FBI crime stats say no murders
Happened in Newtown that year
All of these things are the first premises
For that hypothetical syllogism structure
Barnes understand
This sublevel Alex does tube
Alex's actions as it relates
The Sandy Hook are so much worse than just making claims public
His promotion of Wolfgang halbig after the point where he could be reasonably expected to know that Wolfgang was
Harassing victim
Family members
Including Scarlett Lewis
It's something that you might notice Barnes doesn't even touch
The defense of Alex's grants
And that grandstanding only works
If you have a straw ban version
Of the accusation that you need to defend
Add yourself against
Hey Barnes
Knows all this
Total s*******
Yeah it reminds me of my favorite
Moment in the trial
Was when
I believe rain always questioning and then there was this
Massive objection storm because his questioning was really really terrible and obviously against the rules and stuff
So the judge shut them down
And then they have to have a sidebar in right now
Afterwards
It's claims he's like
Here's the problem
This is a sanction by the court
Because they made us look dumb
And then the judge said the only you can
Do that
And
That is exactly how I feel about Barnes right now he's like
The court is doing all of this stuff
Record is doing his only you make yourself look dumb
That's what happen
You are the one
A sound a little desperate
To do you making yourself sound a little desperate by way of
How much this is Justin in Fillmore
I'm quite frankly
Brazilian
But they're like okay we'll just
Oblivion
A little extra
Support but not
Becomes evident where we actually do start
Shutting down
What a lot of support and then we'll
Organizing
Do something but
Now's the Time
Because this is
Keep simple words alive on a monthly
The pays all the salaries
I don't understand why you still doing commercials while they're planning to sue him allegedly
Are trying to do understand it's all.
Anyway the conversation of Alex's phone
Comes up
And there is a
That's being played here about the idea that their intimate photos there's a little defense
Defensive
These people with their
Anymore
It's on
Your email to have the phone and
Contacts
Be going over to Moscow
Sooner whatever
Let's talk about that
Six months of my phone
She packs.
And it's pictures
My wife and me
I gave
Do phones
They were searching
And
The paralegal
Netflix
6 months
We all went through it there's nothing there
Nothing wrong anyway
And
Please like we have two years
We have the whole phone
Like they have underbites laptop
There wasn't photo I said
So
Wow
There's one naked picture
So
That's what they got
And
No dick pics donut
This is uncomfortable
Super Bowl
I wouldn't
Put this out
Let Mark tell people that you're a shity person on top of a monster I will say this with absolute certain
Nobody who has access to that phone
That I'm aware of
Wood
Ever
Release naked pic
Even if
It's like a dick pic of Alex's
They could hypothetically be on foot
Like that is
So uncalled for an
No I mean it's like Alex could
Just not say anything at this would never
Be an issue morally it is a horrific thing to do
Yeah and a picture of somebody that's not
Somebody else is adding information to this that is making it quite odd that part
Hey you could have said it and then you didn't have to add the part where you're saying I sent it to a third party
Without
Well he's trying to say I don't know I don't know cuz Alex is trying to say that he just sent a naked picture
His wife to his wife
I think
If you follow what he saying
Yeah but I think
I don't know about Mark told the real version
I don't know we'll see will I mean
We will never see this end
And thank God for that
Because honestly more importantly is
Like the stuff that means up
Like the Paul Joseph Watson text it was
Absolutely
Barnes and Alex intentionally missed the point
Yeah it was more fake news
And it's a in attempt
Extraordinary
They got to
NCA microscopic
Up close view of Infowars in LA
Alex Jones
Any incriminatory
Formation that's why they got one text message about Paul
And he is exactly what had nothing to do with
We have your phone
Blue skies there's no base
Criminal case
Whatsoever there's nope
Perjury there's no lie
There's two things the first is that that text from Paul illustrates
That Alex has awareness
The story that he was doing about covid
Was bulshit
And it was Sandy Hook all over again
And Alex admitted I get it I understand that this is what we're doing and I don't care
Yep we're doing this
The second thing is that the
Existence of this tax
Is full evidence
Commit perjury when he said that he had looked through his phone and turned over everything
That have the word Sandy Hook
And that because you was not turned over
That is
Call Sandy Hook
Yeah he's correct those words were there
Lots of that
It's an issue you're in hot water
If you if those words were in there and you search your phone you would have found that text and you was specifically chose not to
Just one of the great legal minds of Infowars
It's very clear from disappearing
That is true great legal mind could come up with an argument like this about why everything on out
Alex's phone is totally cool
Animatronic
Rodger Stone tattoo
It's like Rodger
Saying yeah my wife
I fell and broke
Flags
Gotit are they
Sorry man
I mean all of us just one Fitness
If there was anything there
It would be on the front page of seeing in the New York Times never will do it already been fully
Disclose and reveal and release
Is there isn't anything
It's like Trump
Do they get to do a macroscopic microscopic
Take a look at your in
Entire life
And all they can come up with
Is pretty much nothing
Such bad reasoning
The fact that there isn't
Anything that's been revealed beans there's nothing to reveal
I mean I guess
That works now but
That may not work eventually I mean is argument
Unfortunately
The way he put it
It is essentially
You know I didn't get caught robbing that bank so I didn't read that back yet I haven't been arrested
I knew I'd robbed the bank then they would have arrested a guy
Yeah
So legal mind not to not to like be outdone by Alex accusing everyone of being petted
File
Besides getting the mix
The Fever by implication
Of being petty
Take a note
Fontaine
And that is why I've been saying that what the
Heading towards
Is there going to be a large
Set
The planets
Courts of info
And over the course of
The process that can
Very very day
Because there's going to be a new level
A financial
And if
You know
Some lawyer like me
Basically find out that he's hiding the keys
The candy store
Pulled out in front of them understand
I Can Only Imagine
So yeah it's going to get in
They think Infowars
Candy store
What you eating
Is that
You Shana Finance
Either drilling dry well
Projectors.
What what do you make of this
Till I mean I think
His eyes lit up
I don't want to know why
Wow
For somebody who got his ass
White
Bye
Mark in every possible way whenever he was involved legally
It is a lot easier to make fun of him when you're on a talk show and he's not anywhere near you
Confession by project
Another one you should write down that's another it's like the blank and blank
So Alex makes a really good point Kira about some of Mark's,
We have a bunch of plaintiff
They're going to be splitting up
The corpse of Infowars
Alex makes a great Point here
Mixed feelings about it
So that's the thing if I wanted my enemies to fight
Acme
I would say I will just
You you're over
I'm going to dominate
Like when you said that
Don't they know what
What they're doing like
Do they not know the gold
With our audience
I'm saying we're going to cut up his
Corpse
We're going to we're going to
We're going to shut all these America
Literally just declared war
The middle class in America
Completely
What Alex is saying here can be translated as
Don't these people understand how much I'm going to be able to fundraise off a quote like that
I was just business model operates off
Fear and he's able to monetize his ability to capture the audience
Cinestate
Kefir
When there is a statement like Mark switch
Can be translated as a direct attack on Alex
Alex
Repackage that as an attack on the audience which will allow him to more easily fleece
Some of them are continuing to throw money into the pit that is in
Infowars
Alex is laughing because he feels that Mark
Has made his job of raising money easier but there's a larger reality that Alex
He's trying to distract away from which is that no matter what he does
There's a Sword of Damocles hanging over his head
All the posturing in fundraising
Isn't really going to matter much to a bankruptcy
The audit what do you step into that Arena it's not a civil matter if you try to play games
You could end up going to jail
For the sort of crimes you end up pulling
Consider what could come with a very clear cases
The perjury that Alex was caught committing in the course of the trial
I don't know any of the specifics but I wouldn't be surprised if that was something that could lead to
Huge fines or possibly
Even be referred for prosecution
Alex could do this song and dance with Barnes all they want in it
Fun for him to pretend he's won this trial but
In order to do that he has to pretend a whole bunch of other problems don't exist and are nipping at his heels
I guess is
Yeah
It's a grim picture
Yeah I mean I don't know how to deal with
Whenever you find out somebody perjured themselves on the stand when they're still on the
You know like I feel like that's almost a moment where the whole thing should like
Every like the light should turn off
You should be able to run away
There's no way cuz they cannot just be like later on he gets a fine
That cannot be the case
You can't
Tell me that I could just go in lie to a judge
And then pay $1,000
I'm not sure it would be 1,000 but you know what I'm saying like that cannot be okay
I agree
I agree but I also think you should be able
Well no no smoke bombs you have to evade
The court office
Get out
You got to come back to this American Gladiator make it through the whole then you win
Thunder a holder whatever the f***
Turbo
Go to the Texas Supreme Court maybe the US Supreme Court
And he had some really fun ways of a
Expressing how close they are to winning case like that
The bondable judgement
Go to the Texas
Will be decided by them it's a
Enterprise
Access Industries
Gets involved
Game over for the plane
Pedro Optical
Entirely
Half-up
We're one short a half holy ones Justice
Just short of them taking it in
And throwing this out
The very beginning
Because the very nature
Violates the
Always have
Has also violate
On the definition of
Oh man that's really fun way to say you lost
Wow
I'll be like what are you going to like do you think you're not going to still be one Justice short of half
Do you think I could
Have you changed
The Supreme Court of Texas
They'll get that just too short of half
Because they're not remembering
That they're still despite them being conservative
The Texas Supreme Court or whatever
These people are still lawyers and judges
Cousin Chet you know true and I imagine that when they start looking at
Somebody abusing the court system the way Alex did
Even though they're like olives Rob Glick Trump
Speed
They're still give me like we got to take that this guy can't be doing that s***
View the entirety of the case you'll
Like that you're might be like well we got to take this
Is perjury stuff a little more seriously
Could backfire
Baby. I don't know
The end of this special report
It's mostly just
Rambling about how
It's just the same s*** yeah over and over Garren over I want spiders
That was great that was funny.
You could grasp something with the spider just were there
Yeah whose idea was that
Weirdo it Rice University
It's a question that I don't think anybody explain fully to me
Nobody saying that was watching the video of the lady who is like as a grad student who was working on it.
We thought it would be able to do it in me to put the needle into work the first time
Cool
I was doing the other day and
Spiders kind of look like a man
Okay
Alright alright okay okay so we're coming to the end of this
And of course we're going to have
How to dismount on
Some
Salesmanship
But also
You got understand that Alex is a hero
I don't know if that's true it is
Clear Lake
If you buy the product
The word yes
Will be shot down
It's not of this
Sjw judges hands not the Hillary Clinton's hands
It's not in Satan
God helps those that help them
Shelf
Your hands
Helping
I'm going to fight a hundred percent
Do the best job I can
But if you take me out of the game
Time for me to get off the field we've had
Nothing
NFL quarterback radio
But I
Can't because this isn't
Our children's future
I'm telling you
I will never give up
But if you don't back us
And if you don't get out serious this is
Your neck
So I
I can't quit and I will not quit
But if you quit
I have no power
This is such a weird abuse
Listen
I will never quit but if you quit I've already quit so that's his no situation so I will never quit fighting
Are you f****** hero for the children and I will never quit
If it does, but I do quit it's your
Listen there's nothing I can do I would love to I would love to not quit but
I don't have a hundreds of millions of dollars will
Never quit and if you stop paying me I'm done and it's your fault can you imagine the kids will all die
You imagine a sadder person than the one who is like I will fight my
Holy Crusade
As long as I get a good salary
Like a person is dead
That is the sad version
Okay
God bless you all
Thank you for tuning in
Cher
The live feed of this
We are Tyler
Or roll over to die
I know you're not go
Either
And I pledge do you all
I'm going to redouble my efforts
That took a turn
Got to have that but yes
Die
Man
Boys
I can't imagine
Like watching The View be like
Everyone must see this
It's.
It's not really even a response to the
The news of the
No
Doesn't clear anything up
It makes things as confusing as possible and then says will get them in the Supreme Court
You said
One short of half
Over and over and over again we're going to Susie's
These people and we're going to win
And they never Sue anybody
Why would you believe that they're going to win in the Supreme Court
Even paying for the lawsuit this time they don't have it
Yeah after that whole pageant that Alex did about like
Really respecting Neil and Scarlett and like I'm wanting to support them and all this right
Drag this out Eva
Further
Anyway
We have reached
What I will call the end of my patience
Tensor the trial cover
And
Yeah it's been it's been something else
I'm glad
Has closed
The chapter
And and I hope you have a good trip
But we have a lot to
Get to it and you get back
Right now I mean this
He's been looking on Twitter as we're recording us
Via the war
For trumps
The search
No they released it
I think it leaks and was released
There's a lot man enjoy Ireland but at the same time now I understand
Be conscious of the fact that chaos is brewing
Will do
Kind of Druid she at man you are a druid
You are outgoing
Outfit
Yeah I got to
I don't know if that's even Irish
What's your name what's your character's name again
I'm not going to keep that moniker though the craziest
Few weeks yeah I think either of our lives
And you have been an absolute f******
Kingstar is well
To take a little break
Yeah me too you can kind of tell I think
In this episode my exhaust until I am I am glad to
Atlantis play
Absolutely
It will be back indeed we will talk about Trump
Respond it's crazy
Jordan.com
We will be
Back but until then
I'm Neo I'm Leo I'm dzx Clark
I'm Wilford Snapple Snapple in the crippled Pitbull
What the sex robot
Thanks for holding
Alex
I'm coloring my huge fan I love your work