Hey everybody this is an hello I just wanted to drop in
And give a little bit of a note
I'll before this episode begin
And the reason for that is because
I kind of screwed up a little bit on the recording of this episode and so some of the levels are a little bit
Eufy
I'm open using a technology the chance be named less I be shifting
Some some business but a remote recording and it seems like everything was totally fine as
We were recording
And our guests actually very generously offered to record on their end
Because I had so much confidence
Then they suck this deck
I thought like that there's no need to this is worked just fine at the past
I'm and unfortunately some of the audio is a little bit over
Total bit distorted but it still sounds fine it's just a little bit
It's it said it could be a little cleaner
Anyway this is a rambling long-winded way for me to just give you a heads-up about that
I have to take responsibility
The sounds of a messed up a little bit
Anyway we'll be back on Wednesday with a normal episode with Jordan back but for now please
Enjoy this the special app
Air Jordan
I have great respect for knowledge b b
We are the bad guy
MoneyGram
College vype.com
I love you
Hello everybody welcome back
2in olives fight
We are here and we have just had a week of a break
And if truth be told
I was under the impression that Jordan would be getting back over the weekend
And that we could get back to work
And do our job as normal but
This is not the case
Jordan will not be back until
Til Tuesday
It's an order to get an episode out I had to
Dig deep
And find someone who's capable of
Of Jordan
Turns out I found two
Very excited to Welcome to the podcast host of the dollop
Reynolds
Welcome gentlemen
Thank you Jackie Jordan
Yeah Jordans out
Permanent
We can go trios
I like that Jordan is a great or do you mean
If we like the way that we got it set up was pretty smooth and eat like so I feel like we're like
There's a
There's a synergy
Yeah definitely
I know that over the course of the time doing your podcast
You've touched on some
Of the I don't know maybe some things that are connected to my world
Do you know like the Jade Helm episode
Cliven Bundy
Perhaps
Yep our God
Yeah we did we did
Listen to on the Bundys
32 on the bus
Syria
I was wondering how much connection do you have to Alex Jones
What's a Whataburger Olivia the show 0
Offline
Tons
Yeah close to Alex
Dave and Alex are really good for a lot of people say that they get Dave and Alex confused
I think their personalities would match amazed
World
We just
I would call it vibe
We Vibe
And we have we have a lot of the same sort of philosophy
Sophie's and just outlook on life
And protein powder
Climate change real
Let's hear one
That's me
Lizards
Do you got
I don't think we real
We've not no it's not really gotten
Into Alex
Ever if anything it would be
Yeah maybe just mine early
On the show yeah little avoided I've always
Avoided him
Completely black I really know about him
Is listening to your podcast yeah
I'll pop interview with all this he was going out to Jonesboro
But I
For the most part I don't really pay
And it seems like he's had a quiet couple weeks
Yeah it's been it's been real time
He has
I think
Abandoned Trump again
So that took it that's a good sign for the
FBI rate
I know someone who
Who punched him and knocked him
Charlie
2020 some-odd years ago in
Texas
Exist
No this is a guy named Charlie
I'm a conversation we're having fun
Sidelines right now
Is it space Hitler no Charlie Sheen
Now Charlie is a guy who is
Associated with
The Fest
Someone Austin
South Bay
Southwest
Oh wow he punched him huh
88fuck
Could knock them down
They were working at Radio
I believe
They got into one
Tribeca
Charlie to this days
Still gets free beers
In Austin
You get you get local hero status
Ambulance
That's that's pretty
That's pretty awesome I guess
I mean I'm not thrilled with violent citipointe but
If it's violence 20 years ago and it
It's funny like I said I would
I would like
I would like to say that I am
Just if I did have another just paid him
Yeah I think that might be the same guy
Cuz there was a dude who would like troll him on his Public Access show
And the and they ended up getting into a fight in the parking lot
I think
I think the space Hitler
Was there
And
That was the same night in
Into guys
I hit
Can I just sit there was also involved
Different guy though
Oh yeah how much that sounds like it would be something on Infowars what just was said
I think I think space Hitler was there but there were two guys in the parking lot.
Infowars.com
Hitler was on the grassy knoll
Cena's didn't even like even before like present-day so did you
You didn't have any kind of like impression of Alex Jones as a figure like
Oh yeah it was somebody who existed
No we just never talked about him on the show really but yeah obviously I mean I it's hard to even remember
When
You first heard about him but
Yeah I mean obviously been following
His lunacy for
The better part of a decade
Yeah but I purposely got them away not too
Washington I just don't
Watch anything with him or like when I see clips of them online
But I've heard about him for a long time now and I've definitely read
A couple articles about him
And then your
I listened to both the documentary episodes
Which were long but
Crazy
Yeah that they got me soap tweeted by the director
Really
I got white
It to her right is not yeah yeah yeah she said she did a terrible
There's a lot going on with Alex in the in the present day
Like you mentioned
Slow week
He's going through a lot of things
He's having
Tantrums
But I felt like
Getting into all that might be too much might be throwing you guys into the deep end
And I didn't want to put you through that that's all
That's what I wanted to do is I wanted to do something a little bit special for
And
Yeah a lot of X listener
We'll get in touch with us and asked us to do an episode about their birthday
Like what happened on my birthday on
On Infowars
Answer what I figured I would do
Is I would take us back
Due April 25th
The day you guys put out your first episode of the dollop
Was doing
This is around I mean Jade Helm was starting to kick up
That was a veteran that heat was a little bit more in the 15
You know right wasn't it wasn't okay
I believe so
Is the Bundy I mean our first episodes the Bundy
I was right in the Bundy rage
Yeah he was there already was into that
See ya this that there's a lot of news going on at that point
In 2014
He knows there's plenty going on
And
I think will be disappointed to learn about what most of this episode ends up being about butts
Let's let us dive in here at the beginning
This is how Alex is starting off the show
Ukrainian helicopter hit by grenade taking off
Ukraine helicopter
Hasn't crippled in a grenade attack in Kiev warned Moscow has engineering
Taquan Telegraph headline
That is
By the way home for their bikes El Presidente
Miniature ready to fight
Is the headline from the associated
Depressed
Together we have we go back into the past and receive something
Pretty reminiscent of recent news
Wow
Yeah
Who took
That that's one of the problems
Them is that sometimes he sounds like that and then other times he's
Well here's the problem that's just him reading Headley
Eez to sound fairly rational when you're just like
Cold reading
Here is a things that happened
Yeah
But then you get into the the analysis of it and it might be a little bit a little bit silly are here
And that is in blaming essentially the West
Is what caused the 2014
Outbreak of hostilities between
Ukraine
When in three months ago when Ukraine voted to not
Enemies
The Russian spider
Cyborg
Spider
10 times bigger
More evil
Happy to be in power and control
A larger ruski population
Pens attacking anything
I see I see you're trying to make make sense of this day if you're weird you're tracking
I've trying to track this out
And it's
Very hard to track but I will say
I do like the idea of calling the EU a spider
Moscato Webb
It's going to suck you dry I like the sucking dry spider it's almost like
I mean you know how it is like when you do a podcast you'll say
Stop your bike doesn't make sense and you kind of let it die
Quadrupling down on the spider talk
Yeah because he's so insane you couldn't you're like you towards the end
I think he might ask
We think this is spiders that are doing that
Yeah yeah just watch Wild Wild West the night before
He was Uncle cough syrup
Kevin Kline is behind the spiders
Recline was just elected to the UN Council
So yeah you have you have this
Worldview in this presentation that is fairly consistent throughout time that is
You know it's anything that involves Russia ends up being everybody else's fault
Right that's not to say that he is like
You know obviously
Is not on the Russian payroll or anything like that
But he is
Deeply into making excuses
For everything that involves Russia
He's also saying Russia is collapsing at the same time
True
But it's in a sympathetic way
It's okay so there's a big victim sort of
Yeah the victim spider
Yeah there's a victim spider
Put them spider situation
Yeah it's it's um
Soaking with the taking of chromia and that bad kind of actions that were happening
This like they're collapsing is kind of an excuse for why they would take the
He's like oil-rich areas
Write these resources
I need to breed more Russia
Yeah regular Fighters yeah
But Reese mobile
Literally no one's ever said that they need to breathe
Battery better by humane
May not be the best like prognosticators on the
Do you think
That Alex thing
The outbreak
Between Ukraine and Russia is real
The guest 2014 Fighter the one today
No no God no it's something they've shot down right
If it ain't shot down out of the sky then to Alex is not real
Like a a spider spider
It's too similar to Black Hawk Down
Well here we go let's see
But we've always known that a large global war and was supposed to bring in the final world governor
Now it looks like you're trying to do it
Awesome backgrounds
Well there we are
Mdlp between Ukraine and Russia or between
The spider eat you
Which spiders though there's three spiders involved a zipper spider
McKay's uninspired you fly
Yeah
Okay
Russia and the EU were working together
Yeah he's saying the possibilities are that it's a real violent outbreak or
There's backroom deal between the EU and Putin to split Ukraine in half
It's just great because it's like
Heat the way that don't with the way that he's able to like
You know bring that up and be like I mean my gutters that's not what's going on it's like dude it's
That
If you're not rational Olivia like
But that's what that might be what's going on I'm open to that possibility obviously
Yeah that you do be like someone being like that you know there's a lot of signs that's a alien invasion is right around the corner my gut
It says it's not possible
It's highly possible
It seems like you only are talkin about that distinct possibility that you don't think it's correct
You know it's going to be great
What's going to be great one day is when he's just doing his show and he's going to collapse on the Infowars desk in his belly's judge
Just going to open up and you're going to find out that he was just a master egg for spiders and they're all going to crawl out of it
Yeah it was never a metaphor
Yeah yeah he was living like the Vincent D'Onofrio in Men In Black
His whole life
So you might
Think based on what we've heard so far
That this was going to be an episode that was largely about Russia and Ukraine
It is not
Things take a turn
Alex's discussing have one of his reporters David Knight
He has been taken
Some time off
And because of that he's ended up listening to
Doesn't talk radio
And this
This is some real chaos
Is that one apartment into a house while he still try to buy a house
Our local affiliate 590 a.m. last
Because
Brother-in-law
North Carolina calling
And tell do you better
Glenn Beck
Last night
Really badly and do something about this
Broadcast
Driving up here right now to be on the next track
This is an emergency
Glenn Beck is talking some s***
Here we go so he's calling in the guy who's
Taking time off to move
Into a house cuz he's buying a different house
He's having that guy come to the
Studio artist days off
Because Glenn Beck said some s***
Yep dude nailed it
A lot of a lot of people are thinking there's not even a second house a lot of people to thinking that the second I was just kind of a false house
Spiders nest
I mean the amount of detail like you could just be like coming up next weekend to talk about Glenn back
But it said he likes toys moving from one house he's listening to 590 but he's also he's leaving his apartment he's got these low
Load up to U-Haul
He's on the way
Beyond the way his death part of his magic is that he throws in details about stuff that
Don't doesn't need details of it
Makes it sound like he knows more than he really does
Truth about this guy moving and being inconvenience
Yeah for sure Grill
The Accidental trucheck I am starting to think this guy might be moving that's all I buy
And it sounds like Alex is a shity boss
Yeah totally
He's taking three days to move
It's just got a f****** ridiculous
And also the guy apparently doesn't listen the only excuse he has to listen to radio that he's moving other than that
Motivate yourself on your move and see if they're on a little am talk radio to just kind of get
Set the gears in motion
Did this story actually shifts a little bit as the episode goes on
Later we find out that David nights brother lives in another city and he saw Glenn Beck and Tori
Call David Knight to listen to a
But there are some wrinkles
Entirely sure what's true
One thing that sucks is that
He's coming in
Because of Glenn Beck talkingshit
Not because
Russia and Ukraine
A ramping up hostility
You know that
This is the kind of news organization that's like Glenn Beck
You got to come in
Yeah
World War 3 might be happening but Glenn Beck as an iff 590 a.m. show
We got to get into this
Betsy the problem is basic
Sickly The Glenn Beck is just jealous
Alex which I think we all
Could be,
Yeah he went offline for him and he went off and went online
Operation there and he's
Never going to be a successful
Alex
Well that's true but the blaze has so many cool people working now
So many greats like
I guess Steven Crowder
Is there right guy
I think you might have yet to its
It's f****** two failed comedians
Well I mean that's most of the right-wing right now
But let's be honest
So anyway Alex believes the Glenn Beck is jealous
Notifications are on Carey
Program director
Premier
Yeah
Wow
Is beating Rush Limbaugh
Well yeah
Mildly delusional but
And again Blake notes letting him know like
I put in the thinking of dropping a nuke hold on a second
The rush is actually also intimidated by Joe Reardon
We have a strategy we're like
A drug dealer and I put my show on your Sunday night so you get a taste
People are moving if you want to move in this New Rochelle put us on
We are we are Healers
Brag about a Sunday night slot
It's like the worst baseball
Alright
Are we fighting Infowars or is this like a kiss
When do we go back to fight again for Wars
I think that this is
Something it's kind of
MIT like maybe underknown
Publicly is how much of his show ends up being kind of like this
Where I had no idea
Why does anyone lie
Who cares
That was one of the things about the
The trial that was
So exceptional was
To actually have someone there
What are you talkin about
Boston to be able to do that like to pull that move because
We just need yes or no
Yeah he's not in his depositions the best moments are they like
Mr. Jones
Do you know what question you're answering
Almost invariably the answer is no he has no idea where the sentence started
A back to webspace Nazi and Charlie
That night
Back there in the radio Sean he was a failed radio guy he it still
The radio guy still nosdam it's still
A deep-seated
Thing he wants to be king of f****** radio that's that's what he's talking about like
Is bracket things better than
Yeah yeah there's a bit of projection possibly
I thinking that I'm picking up on some of that too
And yeah he has a chip on his shoulder that's something that
It's also sort of
Ubiquitous
Throughout his career
Where is this this like
I'm the best but also everyone
Is jealous of me
And
That's why I
That's why
Trying to kick me off these stations could Glenn Beck is jealous of me and he's talking s***
That kind of vibe
Guys have always talked s*** about each other they can't not do it
Now that is very true
It's such a it's such a community
You know it's such a forgotten
Community
Yeah it was like
They were the rock stars in the 50s
Yeah
Oh yeah Wolfman
And now
Brought low
So Alex is going to bring up some of the accusations
That's the Glenn Beck is made about him
Important
The devil down in the
They important
I mean this is
Definitely the top story
She heard back say last night
Then I guess we're going to dig through the video audio
Although yesterday
We're basically covering up the racism we were out there
We all now know this was Saturday night by report
At work we reported on
I mean
And
Everyone in the house now I'm around here a minute it's
Literally up middle of nowhere
So
Yeah so you might just be a fossil
Elisa is not race
Is it possible he's not wrong
It's really
Odd to listen to Alex Jones
Alex Jones
Like
Talking about himself and his little orbit in the way that he does about everything else
Nothing if not like self-obsessed
But what's it like
But the way that you're like talking about posting audio files at like
Like honestly nobody just
Nobody cares what are you
What's actually important
Well what's actually important is the Glenn Beck has said that Alex wants to overthrow the government which
Kind of does
Yeah I may be
Pretty clearly
Is 10
Super against the federal government
For twenty years
MN he's covering up racism
Bye
Collingwood
Cliven Bundy said racist
Which I don't know if you remember but it's basically him saying that
Hey maybe black people were better off under slavery
Play A1 in his house he's not opposed to having a black person in his house which is
In the Bundy family
Considered Progressive
Basically though everything that Glenn Beck appears to be saying about Alex
Transfair
But bye-bye he's doing that thing where
If you're going
God damn it now I agree with Glenn Beck you a******
Yeah that is that is the battle
Sometimes
It's like oh no
You made a good point about Alex Jones
Yes yes
Cliven Bundy
That was your guy's first episode right
That was our first episode I was before Dave thought he was going to have me on the show permit
We were just going to his garage
Talk about the Bundys
It was magic
In a bottle
And the same day you put out that episode this was happening on Alex's show
Talking about
And how he is he's just old-fashioned man
Understand Papa say the n word
Parkwatcher
Yeah no
Right
It sounds
Really weird to Modern trendy to Metrotech
One thing I will say that is the bunnies were against gentleman Square
Put like the more the backhoe zodd the more it's like Jesus Christ
What is
Is he mad living
He left he loses the thread quite a bit
He's like a guy who starts running downhill and he can't stop
Let's start a GoFundMe to get him running down the hill
I would love to see that but reality shows because you get to watch the word
Literally be
Taking out back at abused
He's quoting there is they are literally from The Time Machine
I think one of the problems that liked it with that entire
Like roll downhill in the momentum of it was that there was some
Like there was something true to it like
Essentially from a time machine
But they're coming from a racist time
Yo
So you're you're making an excuse for this by being like no no no no no their minds are back from slavery
Yeah exactly that's a problem because I feel their time traveler
Okay yeah well in our time we're not cool with that
If they are Time Travelers
Then we need to teach them about the modern world
No not that the whole space-time Continuum that you're jumping in the middle of the ripple effect you'd understand what you're doing to the universe
Open you open up the weather spiders
Time spider
So we have a little bit more Russia and Ukraine news
Is the comes up
Glenn Beck
They're either murmurs
Of this
And the Council on Foreign Relations
Anti so we get to the possibility of nuclear war coming up but only after
Like in incessant amount of time talking about Glenn
Preservation
Family Auto United States right now
That means we're going to have a nuclear war
Percent chance
Warm
Get your family out of major targets
Percent chance of robbers were coming to kill you
Would you get out of your house at night
Change a tire
We're going to Clearwater
19 years
He always talks like that
Very regular
He also does frequently say you know I don't talk like that so
If you didn't listen to a bunch of a show you wouldn't know that
Right
You seem to have maybe a bone to pick
Protects
I just made me laugh. Hehehe
He put like the main targets
Alright yeah sure
Oh yeah the great threat of Central Texas
Cuz yeah I'll hit them right where the economy's heart
Pulses crop of Texas
We've long known that the Kremlin wants to take out Bevo
University of Austin then they will be putty in our hands
You see the Red Dawn we have to take out the football capitals first
Did flight Texas NM is where these
Ascribed
David Knight
The guy who was not
Guy with moving he shows up
And he wants to come in and talk about
How Glenn Beck has been talking this s***
And this leads Alex to make
Quite a bold pronounce
About Glenn Beck
I knew from the beginning
A red flag
Anything that you were constantly pushing for revolution
Not
What happened there
Is exactly what
Planes he wants to see how
With loaded guns in their face like tenement Square
I didn't see anybody down there with a gun on them but
Well actually there was a couple of guys that were holding rifles
Showing that picture from multiple lines
Okay
The black comment
He was making those comments last Saturday
People
My right arm
Glenn Beck
Oh my God it's like beautiful it's like
Jazz nonsense
I mean it is
There's so
Much phenomenal stuff in there
It's also amazing that okay
You have
The audio of Glenn Beck saying this
But in order to preserve the illusion of news
You're bringing in the guy who just listen to the a.m. radio
First-person account
Of listening to the a.m. radio station
Yep
What is the clip wouldn't be as fun
Glenn Beck is there
Evansville have the balls to be like
Anna what should we lay underneath that still a little Joe Cocker Help from My Friends
Glenn Beck is beyond
Board important question
Do you think that Alex knew he was going to make that accusation when the sentence started
Hello
You know I
I again everywhere outside re
But
Is it is there's just there's
You know the difference
Connection Pointe
And as he starts to advance and run down the hill
It's sort of like you don't never Plinko on The Price is Right
We're just wanted drops and lands in a sort of like that his mind is Plinko in
He's a regular and then spider false flag and then it drops in the air
FB Inc
BFDI
Yeah but he's going to stick with this
For now but I should say in the present-day Glenn Beck likes Alex
So Alex likes going back now
In 2022
He must have been wrong about the FBI thing cuz he still has his right arm
So
Well yeah and
You know
One of the great things about Alex is it
Every episode is a bottle at
You know nothing really
Fluoride
You don't have to hold yourself to any of these predictions like
Nuclear war
Write the FBI
It all just washes away tomorrow
It said it's awesome
How many
Groundhog Day cast
Conspiracy man
No continuity
I wonder how many times he's like predicted like
You know something like
Nuclear war like
If you could go back in town
It would be incredible over 20 years like
On our show
I would say at least 50 times
I've heard it so good
Yeah intelica is often the target
That he brings up
I'm very frightened by his false
Now that David is David Knight still with Glenn Beck
I know he's got his own radio show on
IHeart or whatever
David Knight
Used to work for Infowars
But
He
Got fired
Maybe like a year ago
He got into a fight with this guy named Steve
Chanoc
Steve pieczenik is this b******* artist would lie to Alex about stuff
And that he was saying that all the ballots in the 2020 election were watermarked
And they all were like
Track my blockchain
And so Trump was going to reveal the election was stolen
And David I was telling Alex not to believe this nonsense
David
You never say that to never say don't believe anything to Alex Jones
Yeah fired
Yeah he was there he was a long
But standing employee he had had a heart attack not too long before this
He'd come in on his day off to talk about Glenn Beck years in the past
No consideration given
I've always kind of been a little bit fascinated by Infowars as a work
Place
That's what you know cuz like weather.on are obviously something
Yeah
I bet I bet they're exactly the same I bet they're just sitting on the water coolers
Talking about the same ship they talked about on here I bet it's no f****** different
Do you think that they actually believe the stuff around the water cooler or it's like Comics pitching jokes to each other
Going back
You think there's something here
Yeah I think they believe I think you're the kind of guys that just
Endlessly
Talk nonsense
Is it goes back to when the Bundys took over the Wildlife Place in Oregon
At one point there were eight guys sitting in a circle talking about their military histories
And then when a documentary on
Invested in the none of his bed in the military
But they're watching once it's just like that like I think once it got started
Every talkin and they're all your sanding and they all
They on some level know it's not true but they're also so f****** deranged that they
Be inherently believe it
Yeah and I think that is what makes like the
Like the
The grifting of today more dangerous cuz I think
Like it's like if you put them on a lie detector
Detector Atwood they pass
I don't know but I know if they're around each other they're not going to admit
That it is
Bulshit
They are
Because
You know they
You don't want
That's what a grifting is
Not okay but if you believe it hard enough
Then potentially it is true
And that's really like our
Entire
Structure of
Government
And
You know half of the sea
Successful
People who give commentary on it
Are just finding their footing
For their own personal benefit
And
And you know and find fight when you find an audience
Of course you're going to keep believing it
Yeah
AMV first person to like
Break kayfabe
And that sat in that environment
Is going to get eaten by the other group
Spiders
Write a note
Right and it'll only reinforce the the kayfabe and play Kono you were the one who wasn't
Real the day when Alex Jones just goes
I've been like
I know I like
Is that'll take some serious
AA meeting
Things I think she get there
It turns out there's one rule
Any info wars
There's only one rule
You won't believe what it is
Driving directions and I'll talk about
No
350i
Tell the truth I guess abstractly and
Leave
You don't want to attack our other allied with fighting against the globalist
Think about it
It's the only bucket rule
Realonerev Infowars donut at Glenn Beck real number two
Donut at Clayton back
And that's it
I'd love to moment of our there any other directive
Watch it I I think I'm supposed to
To say no but that's a
Crazy answer
I thought I walked these golden me to say no
Now that's it you can punch me
Has around are you can feel
Just leave
The f*** a lot did not hurt that
So one of the things that I find
The most fun and these episodes is when people bring out quotes
Because they're often wrong
Sometimes it's a little silly like this tight with David nights at UB with this one a little bit
I don't know if it was his original expression
Easy to mix up
Came up with the Supra
Oh my God
To live in an environment where that is
Not
Like
But that is just a passing moment
Ventura and Gandhi again
Fun fact it's actually not even a Gandhi quote
It did sound a little like aggressive for a Gandhi quote
Don't shoot until you see the whites of your eyes that was gone yeah yeah from my cold dead hands
That was still Cold Steve Austin
You're getting about f***** up my air
Gandhi
Dundee 3:16
Jiraiya
Dang it they have a
Brought relationship with quotes
Infowars
Like it
We covered his documentary endgame
And I was fascinated because every quote
Like it was just like
Wall-to-wall Jefferson quotes
That weren't real couple of Hitler quotes that were fake
It was just it was wild
It's I don't understand
How you can
Like
Take such stock
It needs quotes
And just be like well that that's actually just remind me
I didn't know it's not real
What are stilts very pretty good meme
It's always good to get meme it's very good meme
Yammy what you see it in writing then you know all bets are off
It's a thing
So in this next clip we have Alex
This is all be honest with you I'm not sure if there's much of a point to
Like I'm playing it because
I want you to
Feel what it's like
Like to have some Rambo
In your life
Like it's it's really just
Aimless
I know why
Vermeer World Order
I knew
Add appointment into
Getting into
What just
Narcissist
Now that I know is real
And I want to believe another libertarian talk show host
These people I want a better world
I want to hold my family name
I want to look at the facts and try to give you the most reason historical morally base
Analysis I can
A myself
I'm not perfect from my horse
I'm not here lecture
There are long stretches of his show that just are like that
It's clear he's talking to himself
Right here
Chest
Rambling nonsense
Well and it actually reminds me a lot of the Hulk Hogan
Valdosta
Protest too much
That was actually check
Oh sorry
Dammit
Either way the points 10
It's it's kind of fascinating to go in like listen to as much of the show's you do because there are these moments of life
You basically just
Someone who doesn't go to therapy
Talking to yourself
Talking about yourself and you in your feelings
On air
And it can feel a little pointless
You know you're in a good
Rhythm
When
You're saying I'm not a
Things are going pretty well
Generally means you've been accused of that
But even for him because it's sort of like the unwinding of his own mind he's accusing
Himself and defending himself against
Themself a little bit
Well you know it's it's a self-soothing behavior
He's expressing this idea to this like
Yo yo you
You get the flak when you're above the target
And that
His way of justifying like
Every negative consequence that comes his way is actually a sign of his
Right here
Every attack is just because I'm so right about everything yeah
And it's yeah
Pretty sad
It's a it's a bummer
Sometimes you're just a dick
And it's it's
Been so effective that it is it is like
It is it's what I mean even then like he wouldn't you know he was
He's such a
Powerful figure at that time
But to think that that
Cuz even grown
You know I'm grown out of that is is so depressing
Because it's why
It's been so a fan I mean people like
My friend's mom was like my watch Fox 2 News cuz it
Is it fair and balanced
And I was like
What they're saying
It's that simple to hack are dumb little brain
Catchphrases man they work
Yeah
So what are things that actually is fun
Sort of
About Alex's show is that
He will come in from brakes with music sometimes
And he like really gets to feeling
One of the best that we've heard is Glen fries you belong to
To the city
Do you get rocks out over that and it is amazing
This is a little bit
Weaker than that but still a pretty good example
Of him about Viber
We are Marching my friend
Call Spectrum
Lead
Nuclear war
Supersonic
Wrestle up off the coast of the United States
So it's a little dramatic
That being like that could be like
You know
Eater some Gorillaz
Music behind that even got a f******
It is
Is it is a mash-up
But it's like
It's the terrible remix
There is something to be said before Alex talking over music that unfortunately I think I'd buy it
An album of it
It would be an interesting late-career pivot
Trimmed
Duets
It's sort of just cease bringing his
Is spice to the classic
Great American Songbook
Yeah it's mr. music while he's just
The reptilians
Yeah it's real with William Shatner
On his album right yeah it really is a little angrier
Maybe
Yeah yeah
Talking about Russian nuclear subs off the coast ready to Launch
Haha yeah
I don't I don't I don't think that's responsible
Probably
Now but I mean that version is going to be stuck in my head all day
So we get back to Glenn Beck
Because like I said
This is the this is the top story of the day break of nuclear war plus that guy heard Glenn Beck while he was moving
Wait
And it involves Alex
XOXO
Very important
Foxit told Alex something
Inserting their about
Level people
I mean repeat Atlanta
Reviewing
Whatever to do I am singing in
That big of a deal but
People
Don't you know don't want you in their lives
And I'm like what do you mean
Wow
I'm not going to
Okay
He's not going to name names slow
Is the government
Yeah no look
Would naming names really help his case cuz it's quite a claim for sure
But Alexander going to do that
No he's above his class
Yeah he's a classic classic
He was actually on The View
He was yeah he was on talking about Charlie Sheen
Charlie Sheen
Had that meltdown on Alex's show
That was where it all like happened
He got invited on The View
And just yelled infowars.com a bit
It's pretty surreal though to see him sitting there on that side
Green screen I also like the Glenn Beck is climbing the walls like Spiderman
So
Glenn Beck
Is both
Freaking out
Over the existence of Alec
Love Jones
And the infringement upon
Glenn Beck
Orbit at some of these
Cable news operators
And at the same time is so powerful that he's the governor
Upgraded from the FBI to the whole
Yeah she's pretty impressive-looking hour
Yeah
Spider-verse
If ever you ever seen Glenn Glenn Beck's Christmas show
His one-man show
About Randall the boy
In the bicycle of ever seeing it
I have not I cannot recommend enough
The man is
Adams f****** mind
And it's it
We watched in the theater me and Josh Olson
And people got mad at us for laughing
Yeah like the
The right way people are very and like they were decked out in their
Are you don't fool flag and all that s***
Environment
Like that it is a it is a deep
Did the jury into the mighty Glenn Beck and his
F****** outstanding
I know I've heard some great reviews of his book
I've never read a book
If that means his
Buckeye broadband
I've Heard naked and previews of his books
Alex MB
Name names
Nope
That is a
The policy that he has
Yeah I made it so in a way it shows you that
You know
He is Honorable when it comes to not outing these sources
Sure but it's also
Goddamn would it really help some of this
Stop just to really become elevated
F****** hell did you give us a damn specific please one maybe maybe name a name just so we can be like
Okay yes that name was right now you don't need to anymore
Maybe he will
You wanted buddy son
Leave me alone
You were spouting White House Coffee
Point
It came out
You got the memo before they did Bud we got your ass
What
You want more people now
When I realize your little baked over there
This quite a threat
Dciaa FBI
Substation
Stop.
Yeah a blow ground
CIA FBI
Substation from which
He runs
The federal government government
Because
He had the same Turkey Point did Media Matters did
3 days later
Cooter motherfuker
It's all good
And I I should also say that we only know that this three-day thing is happening because Alex is saying it
And he's iffy on dates
But again once you get the dossier compiled which I'm sure they were and put
I'm sure that that was validating a
Corroborated
Wellshire
Yeah and going back went away cuz he was shamed out of the public
Nobody was the government and that's over
Yeah and then the post I guess cuz he's no longer the government
Nope
Nobody still runs the FDIC a substation
We got your ass
Kind of implies that it's in between a couple stations
You know like
Chicken quesadilla
People need to camp out there
For a mission
Or
It's actually a station on a sub
Think about what
In the middle of Texas
Operate out of town
Maybe that's Bhai leveled but the nuke was going to hit operator
Navigate me to Jade Helm are we
Wow
Yeah
Just got to figure out how the spiders play into this and we are onto something
Man he must
Hema
I mean
Idaho
I mean what is the level of
Drugs to
To keep this up
Is it get I mean we're thinking like what is the belief on him is it is it adderal is it
Is it booze is it
The cocktail
He's definitely a drunk
For sure
He's he doesn't show drunk sometimes
Less So lately but in the past he would you'd be very clearly drunk like
One Christmas Eve Eve was so drunk he threw a hatchet it one of his cameras but he wasn't
Who is madness
Oh my God also
He played 70 have a hatchet
Why wouldn't the other half because I'm dummy
Sometimes he has big knives in the studio sometimes he has like a Barrett 40-cal by like Cannon
God
Where is there's a cereality to to some of that but yeah that was a good day
Rogan has said that Alex told him that he has a problem with adderal
And so there is some kind of a stimulant
Keeps like the words running
Yeah
I am just like I think
Piano from performing and doing so as you know it can be exhausting even though it doesn't
Look like it's exhausting
Yam
He does is pretty high intensity
Not have some kind of supplement
If you will get started selling that as the
The ad adderal booze combo is pretty f****** ridiculously
In the way that adderal can
Heap
Gears
Going
No matter what you're throwing at it if you take a dump
Is pretty remarkable
I've certainly had some friends
Tell me
That if you're drinking
Pretty late like maybe you're at 3 4 a.m. bar here in Chicago
And someone gives you some cocaine
It might hit balances out a little
You know that a fact
Brendan cell
But yes yeah and I know from having done cocaine at 3 or 4 in the morning
But it is at but
You bald-headed a lot of times it will be the
Appearance
That you're in control but your memories will not be
They're too really
Back that up
Tell you both seem fine
But you are out of your mind
This is how Alex gets away with your getting that Glenn Beck is the government
Right
Is holding its memory
Sure
But looks he's going to put together these dossiers right on Glenn Beck staff
And to do that he's going to need some help
Until he calls out
He puts it out into the universe
Obi-Wan
Kind of thing
What is this one f****** day of a f****** show this is one day
Crazy
Davis
Honestly this is one of the less
Crazy
I was worried that some of these clips would be very boring
A while
Here is Alex calling for some help
Anonymous is going to do about this
Bring Me Down
What
Bring a real liberal media.
Call McEver comedian down
Thomas Jefferson media
Set anyone I wondered like Anna's because if there's no real information but it's just evolving it is like
Psychosis
The point now where is like
Look Anonymous you're the crosshairs now you're you're just as exposed as I am here
You know Glenn Beck because he's the government
Blendtec will
Undermines qnt E-Town
I do love that that isn't Point Alex's looking at Anonymous is like some kind of a like got my back
Goodbye Brothers
Do we even know
Wait have we heard what Glenn Beck said about him yet
He said that the a Wars wants a revolution and that he didn't want to get involved with the Bundys
Involved
He just made a very nearly
Offhand comment
And this is what
Alex was excusing the racism of private Monday
Please comment wasn't but again when you're dealing with races Time Travelers you have to be open to the races
Cuz I'm a little bit
Right you'd be time tribalist if you didn't
It's just gotten so crazy people to
That it's like I can't remember where we started from because it's so
I mean this is
Yeah because he made those comments now
Now they are taking
King down everything
Anon anonymous
Yeah I found all of Glenn Beck's operation
Dave this is part of the globalist deathstarr you should be freaked out the ready to fight
Fire in 5 minutes worried right now
In the past 90 minutes Glenn Beck
SS card from an AM radio show host
Cable news shows
To now is the government who is going to unmask
Can take down all of these people
If you don't stop it now he's going to get his a88 he's out
The storm your base
I hate I hate to say this guy is because if you're having this much
Of like
Wonderment
At this point
Yeah I know you can handle the next
Let's go I can't f****** away
Because this is business something
Kind of normal on his show
B
For you this B
Bees like a lot to take in
I'm going to throw a hatchet
Okay
I'm going to say a prayer
Recognize that this is a
Juncture point the enemy realizes that we're going to eventually become a with her Opera
Humble servant try to be the best I can
And queen
Please protect us please help us
Foreign & Domestic in
Please allow me to continue on my work so that I can do a better job
Destroy me
Please let it be an edifying message to all
We can learn from it
215 Conowingo Dam
In the name of your
John Jesus Christ,
Mount Michael I mean
The best players always have
My enemies foreign and domestic
Man
To the
Balls
The up again I mean it's like
If you're just surround yourself with people who will let you get away with things this is how you get to the point
You're doing like
Pretty much
One-on-one public prayers
With God
It said there was just busy religion was really the only thing separating him from Jim Jones
And then
Boom
He preys on are more than you think
And it's suspicious
How often the prayers
Seem to be a foreman
LOL
There's a little bit of a he's talking about Glenn Beck in this prayer very clearly
He see some praying back
If that wasn't too much
To take in
This lexcorp might give you whiplash
Jarring
Because this is immediately after he prays
This is what he says
Broadcast
And pray
That reveal
Religious
Gia frontman the FBI frontman
Obama
This one.
Wow
And I just prayed that happen
But I am very humbled and honored presence
Yeah when Alex does it it's classy
Yeah yeah yeah
I'm looking down on Glenn Beck for evoking God and bringing God up after
You just prayed about
Mad
You know how to rap
It would be it would just make so much sense
If the set of Infowars was just like multiplicity where there were five of him
And they just kind of swapping in and out you've got the religious Jones books
Conspiratorial Jones
The musician Jones
Sure
You terrified of spiders Jones not just reading headlines Jones which is the one where like this one's not
The best copy
Is the Spider Guy we should let him out there too often
Be very red Alex Jones from that picture
Before and after pictures
Man I mean lambrou Jones
It's not the act like a Florida Alex Jones
Board shorts and Hawaiian shirt
I added
It's
It's really
Remarkable
It's fake that nothing is Jade
No
In this
2 hour.
Nothing changed except for potentially the level of intoxication or something or just like
The ratings are whatever just save the fact that he's
Just going
I don't think he's drunk to be Fey I can usually tell like these you have little Tails
And he seems pretty sober
But here's the thing
Every episode is essentially in adventure
You know his front door when he starts
The show it who knows
Philadelphia in Mordor
You could end up just the other side of the Shire who knows
It's Madness
Deepika
Is this
Cabeza
We have we have learned
Just mentally
We have more to learn about Glenn Beck
Good cuz we've learned he's the FBI
Hold on
Maybe not
Oh maybe
He's above Obama
Marshalltown
I'm so tired of Dishonor
Believe
6 months ago
Hardcore insidelines
Not later
Progenerate
Hardcore game
Dallas Texas
Advisors
What if you're wrong
Bragging
No nobody's talking to me about this stuff
I'm just riffing this s*** out at the later that I am coming up with this
Gilligan's like if your
Glenn Beck
You're like okay so how do I
Yeah well your people you're going and you're going to hate just so you know I guess Alex heard some of the things
You said that what you saying he's pretty pissed off I mean whatever you know that this is Media this can happen
When you have a second we haven't know someone told me about the Alex Jones no no it's
It's gotten a little bit more out of
What what do you mean
Yeah yeah the last 15 minutes he kind of I guess now his pitches that you
Are pretty much
Inside the government working for the government
Well that's crazy
Do you have a sub
FBI CIA station
Hey Glen
Glad you have sorry I know you're trying to get some work done
Yeah there's a new update
So
It seems now that he is suggesting that you're sort of coming up with the talking
Key points for the government
And
That that
You're no longer part of the government your maybe our are the government
And he better as right arm on the fact that you are he'll cut his arm off if you're
I guess sometimes I just think about how I wanted to be a stand-up
Hey Glenn sorry I know it's only been eight minutes
Yeah
You're above Obama now you might be Obama
How is that
How am I supposed to
Say anything
The shows got another two hours
He's been running for 17 minutes
Yeah
So we'll keep you posted
Can I get back on can I get back in with Samantha Bee to talk
Aerobatic apologize for something
Can I talk to him
This is definitely a heavy day
For Alex in terms of like Escalade
Yeah
It doesn't always
Snowball quite like
Like this it feels druggie it feels like he's pot he's been popping pills as this has been going on
Or maybe they just have a fog machine in the studio but it just releases adderal
Vaporize adderal
That's right there a rock something here
I don't know I mean like is anger a drug I'm a kind of his for some folks
Is the Devil Type
It isn't a way to where it's like
He is you know it's not even
Shouting in Uno at his friends at a bar
He recognizes the
Pedo people are listening to this s***
And if they're eating up the
The trash
That makes him want to throw more trash
And as the day goes on the trash piles have to get bigger and crazier
And so now he's just sort of
Slamming around in the
Bile
That's one of the problems with like this style of broadcasting
Yeah but hit medium and I've had friends that have gone completely insane cuz they're just
In a in a room talking himself on YouTube like
That's a bad it's a bad medium if you're alone and no one is going hey
Check yourself a little bit here
If you don't have a boss and like a lot of the stuff that you're talking about his kind of extreme
Then
People respond to the extreme stuff
Yeah man you kind of lean into that
And how do you get a how are you exciting if like you're used to
Saying extreme
It's like it's panda
And tomorrow
You need to say some crazy as yet
You have your going to be tomorrow
Zubsolv ready to Nuke America and Glenn Beck is above Obama
I'd already knew I saved
Merge patch
Would be what's Glenn Beck going to be tomorrow
Eminem Jordans
Teepublic
Yeah I never coming back around and then being friends with this guy
After Debbie like me being present Jen Kirkman it's not something that can happen
I think it'll happen
To be fair I think Alex has said way worse things about Glenn Beck than this
This could be argued to be a compliment
It's a scary compliment but in a way it is
You are higher than Obama
Yeah you know it's higher than Obama Alex Jones
Where is Halifax
Definitely
An insult
Or an accusation that involves competence
Yeah you are so competent that you are above the
Anonymous let's go
Yeah I need a giant
Team of faceless hackers
In order to take you down
Nationalize that is being a positive
Yeah I know I will
It's a scary compliment but it's a compliment
This was from 2014 so did it on his come to help him I can't remember about the grave
Yeah Glenn Beck on Master time
Okay
Obama's birth certificate
Yazbek
Actually Alex doesn't believe the birth certificate stuff
Didn't
What online
You didn't initially believed it
But then he realized that it was a
Trick because the people that your mom has put it out
Knowing that people like Alex in the right-wing Community were racist
And so they would jump on top of it and
Like take the bait
It's a false flag.
You bet
You bet in reality Obama's dad is Frank Marshall Davis
He's a communist guy I don't know
I don't realize
Taking this line too much further than that
He made a documentary about it at some point
Is the documentary about it called Dreams of My real father
Oh my Lord what a title
To be honest with the different time Dan
Alex is a time traveler that time for God's sake
So at this point
We've entered the sort of homestretch
To the show
And Alex brings on Joseph Farah the guy who runs WorldNetDaily
Ayyaantuu the program God
Wrecking to listen to it will just one clip of it because
It's a it's pretty boring it's mostly about how The clintons Wanted
To take him out
And I don't know how that's relevant
Takeout
Alex are the world
Back in the 90s
Yeah yeah yeah
It's an hour in 2014
Started getting credibility
Today
Murder images
If he got murdered in this is a
Quotes because he was asking too many questions about Vince Foster
Where's the buzz name
OG
Sarah it one of his big point
Is that like
We got it we got a stick
Together there's not many of us who are you know in this
And he accidentally included the Glenn Beck
PS4
I wonder why nobody else
Degree of success here
After
Infowars
Make sure
Hairs with them
United front
But I'm erasers covering up for Monday
I mean here
Go to iron my interviews but really every lunch I have anybody I understand, and I'm glad you're not a coward
That's always how I end things
I do it after someone orders
Glad you're not a coward you have a friend that a potato salad
I mean it really is amazing to
Have said all the things you said
A guy drop Glide Becca be like will look to be honest I'm not a huge going back fan it's like
Obama
Yeah there's a dissonance
How do you not say to that guy he says that let them back in Hugo you know he has a substation any runs yesterday I didn't see it like it's chill
I think this question answers itself
And that is
But Jose Parra is not a coward
Right
Would inevitably lead to some pushback
And I think that's probably why just go along
To get along this means anything anyway
But it's just so it's so clear there that that's
The case because he's just eat uses in the wrap-up
Well to be honest I'm not huge but back fat he says Civil War but anyway you know potato potahto great Avion
Myself
I got myself a little bitty might be in charge of the globalist Death Star we're not sure anyway
Anonymous
Yeah it it's it's it's silly
Things don't make sense
And that's just part of the infowar
Amman
Man
Wow
In this a third hour of his show he was interviewing Joseph Farah and then the premise was basically that you was going to take call
What time
Essentially Runs Out
And
Too much time complaining about Glenn Beck
And so there's no calls
And Alex's
Alex's
Feeling a little bit like
You know
I'm cool I'm a cool guy
That's kind of the vibe he wants to go out
I'm out of time
Creepy
Glenn Beck
The average person care what their neighbor thinks.
Calculus Global of Cloverdale
Community
And
The credit card
Now you just have to talk me about
I always find that to be like really sincere and convince
When people
I was just at a community pool hot tub
YouTube of disgust you a little bit you were taken aback by the community pool hot community pool
Like I'm like is Alex Jones going to a community pool but that's not crazy
But Community hot tub just has like weird kind of orgy vibes
Bears Club, it's like a community pool I'm like alright summer for the kids to go on the weekends at 6
Community hot tubs like you f****** grape
Depart after the slash was hot tub
I'm picturing Alex Jamie
Remind me like a
You know they put Bugs Bunny in a cauldron and try to cook him like Alex Jenner Elmer Fudd
Getting him up at just
What color does Alex Jones turn in a hot tub
It's Lobster town man yeah
Seriously you must start crustacean
Well here's the thing you guys don't listen to a ton of this you wouldn't know but a lot of Alex's stories take place in hot tub
Okay
He has a famous story about being in a hot tub
And a couple of globalist caveman and
Where can I get you there like threatening him in the hot tub
I meant another time he was at Hot Springs
Instant hot water a lot
Hotbodies
Is there a space in here I'm a globalist
It says six people at a time is that six regular humans having a global it's me squeezing
I don't mind my eight legs and I parted me
Comes out
And what are you do sir I'm a globalist
Globalist we both in the globalist business
This brings us to the end of this episode and I don't know if you eat Epsom
Some feelings on
Making it through
Your birthday
Your shows birthday
Yeah
At least everything's gone so much better since then
It is like
You know I mean
Chi-Chi's
Do you know he's just such a Trainwreck
Figure
But
It's almost like
I guess you think of him when you don't know as much
As as you you all do
You know that he is his damn it is dangerous it's only ways but it's also
This is the mind of a child
Yeah
It's just a child's mind
And it's just
Pretty simple what's going on and it's
I guess very effective for those who are in
But
There's really not much
Just trying to keep this bucking
You do keep the Train Running just keep the words coming out
Create
Strawman
Is it always got his terms they're very effective had to what you were saying like
He walks out his door at
Irene
At all everydays a Pixar movie for of you
I'm certain he has essentially no preparation for anything
Just B just seat of his pants
These ridiculous things like an entire show
Where he's escalating the accusing Glenn Beck of stuff
Lisak well I have
Nothing else really to talk about
I've already made people scared about this nuclear war thing
I got nowhere else to go with that Tammy
What can I say in between Hocking survival item
But he really is like
When people like
But you have a friend that did something and then you just in your head you like all I'm going to say this to him in this Tim that it kind of spirals out
But then you're just thinking about the 7th
But he's definitely doesn't show like it's it's the kind of bocce Avenue it's just Frankie
I just I can call him
But he just goes for hours
It's a guy spiraling out for f****** hours
If this was so hugely important
It probably should have gotten on his radar in another way than a guy work for him was moving
Again like I said the guy who is moving brother heard it and told the guy who is moving
Rihanna
God Hill good
You even his sources and what he does it's got to work for me brother has brother
One of his big sources of information in the present-day is his wife
Tennis partner
It's a lot of deep until from her
What's your stupid
Soap2day
Is he
It just over completely on something else or does he continue on will he continue on with something like this or really just dropped
It changes I'm not sure I haven't listened to the next day's episode so I couldn't say for sure
Sometimes it becomes a little bit of a crusade
I meant something to get to fry and buy
Sure or a Mikey went on Piers Morgan show and yelled at him but guns
Alex
Started a petition to get beers Morgan deported
Man
Yeah and then he got he went on Piers Morgan showed started yelling at him about how like
You guys tried to take our guns in 1776
Answered
That became like two weeks of his show
What tell Alex that
Gazebos for weeks
That's what I'm glad that's actually what the word many fences about
Yeah it was good complication
Oh my God
Well thank you for having us on there
Thank you I know I'm sure almost everybody who isn't star show be aware of y'all's show.
Dollar but is there anything else you want to direct people's attention to that they should check out
I mean
I keep your eyes peeled I we have a virtual shower doing September 8th
Boring
Chingada dollar podcast.com
I'll be recording some
Shows in Seattle Portland and Vancouver you could go to Gareth Reynolds. Com
For those stand-up shows
Respect
Save
I got nothing
You know
Fair enough
Check me out on Twitter I'm yelling at people
Trt1 get into Davis Twitter bar
Jay-Z Twitter ends with me having blocked everybody on Twitter just yelling at myself
I think it ends when you realize you can block yourself
If you do end up blocking everybody in your just yelling at yourself eventually this episode of Alex is going to be
Yeah well thanks again guys it's been a real pleasure and I hope we can do it again sometime
Yeah love to
Fake awesome
Holding
Alexandra first in color