Damn important
I have great respect but knowledge by knowledge
Dot-com
What's Alex Jones
Jordan
Today buddy my brights
Spot today I guess we're back at my saddle everything a normal yesterday
And a big thank you to Dave and Gareth
For filling in your seat
The job I would also like to apologize to the audience that apparently that whole spider thing is maybe
Play songs by piece of Medicare conspiracies from
Also maybe it's just a spider sometimes this spider is just a spider it's not always a penis
It's hard to say in this case
Said that I didn't I didn't realize that at the tonight buddy
Yeah absolutely you for the bath bombs
You are very welcome my friend spoke Irish Bank
Only be found in Dublin beautiful beautiful Dublin little shape of the Blarney Stone in there
Each one has a tiny piece of the blade
Dan is I mean my bright spot is obviously
Quote vacation was a little bit
Longer than usual and that's
Because
My partner
I is on Mental Health leave from
School and school has started and rather
For those who don't
And yeah so
The amount of nonsense that
Immediately out the gate you know like
There's only two art teachers
And one of them now has
50 kids in her class
And rather than hire a different art teacher
The administrative staff hired
Three more admin people
So I think we know exactly what their Folk
Admin
Yeah and it ain't it ain't teachers and so
Brightspot Mental Health
During that time.
Was
Revelatory you know it was after after all of the stuff I mean
Reset for her she she's better than
She did not stop climate
She slept better than I think I've seen her sleeping in a long time and not like
It's not like that you know I slept 12 hours kind of sleep at that healthy
I'm waking up on a good time and I'm happy and I'm doing a good job
It was
Beautiful to watch and it just
Filled me with so much
What's Joy
We have left that horrible place where she was happy
I'm back to Chicago home be abused by everybody but we got Vienna beef hot dog
Give me some of that relish
Text no
That's a really don't there's an embargo on relics in Ireland
So Jordan today we have to go over
There's been a lot that's happened
Incense
We recorded a present-day episode right
Because you were gone and you know them the trial stuff was no pretty
Dominant es gas caused a clog in the pipe
Yeah it worked
And I decided that we should do is focus on the thing that I think most people were talking
Sing about
Maybe the highest-profile piece of information and that was
That last week
On Wednesday
Alex turned on Trump
Right or 1 would be led to believe that which which
So this was last Wednesday
Knots for months
Not a year ago
Not a year and 4 months ago not a year and
8 months ago 0 point is made that
Turns on Trump.
Teeth 2822 how do you do
That will present a stop on Friday but
That seems like something that has an immediate
Need
Indeed
Yes I want to dress one thing really quick
And that is that there is a widespread perception
That
I took a week off
Because you were
Out of town
This is not true I would give anything for you to take a week off we did not put out any episode
But I took a week off
But I did not and I have something very special to announce
That we are doing another round of butt
I would love to but everybody
I'm really thrilled
With this
Style
This route
This time around my dear friend
Angela Lansbury
She's designed Ava Squatch has no Heroes button
Everyone who responds will get one of those
And then
There's a random
Pick
Yes number of them made by the very talented large
I need the number of different buttons themed on Alex things like
Great job is one of them
And to those are there
Also
Our dear friend Sarah Shockey
From Marty and Sarah love wrestling solutely among other things she designed
A dreamy creamy summer but
A man screams a 2020
VRBO
Inexorable yogurt
And there's two important things to bring
Is that I have learned over the course of doing these button things
That
This is the best way to ruin an inbox
So I have needed to create a separate
Email address
4 buttons
Sprite
I wanted to get KS buttons at gmail.com
It's taken
I don't know
Fighters
You're talking about so
The email address that you need to write to if you want to button
K F button
That is just how could it not be
So
If you want about
Just send an email to that with your address or shipping address
Smelling address
And I will get those turned around
Ideally I'd like to get those
Maybe males
And all done by the end of the dream creamy summer
The answer to Celebration of the end eventually
But I'm not totally committed to that
Cuz these things
I don't know I mean we had way more people want them last time that I kind of just going to have those absolutely
I said I would do this again I did it again
You did that's what happens when you go out of town
You can't not work
Now one more important thing about these button
Is very
There is a desire
That is a what's your bright spot
Design
Kava bar
It has a little treasure
I've made three
Oh my god dammit wanted to make a Willy Wonka thing
There are
303 golden tickets
There are only three
I've only made three
And whoever receives them will also receive an ironic punishment of some sort
Know if
Do you receive one of those and send us a picture of you with
The botanist
Your face or whatever
But
We will make a donation
Turn to a charity of your choice in your neck the way we're going to walk at it
Punishments necessary just
Kind of fun something really cool I like
I thought it would be silly but I also thought we should just do one
No we can't
Maybe not getting to the person exactly right so 3 cm
The Sweet Spot
Yeah what I'm saying yeah
This isn't true at all but I'm going to say it in order to scare people
I can tell a bootleg a mile away
I will be able to tell if you're trying to run a fast one
Post your butt
And picture publicly otherwise somebody will get the no no.
We both know it
Let's say hello to some new walks also because we were out of town
The backlog once again
Sorry
Coming from the outer regions of the universe it's damn Tron 0 and Jordan 8
I'm a policy wonk Antron 08 Jordan a dress
Text Jordan
Physics
Awesome doctor of physics
Thank you very much
Dino lot actually
Weird
So tell me something about this
Well an electron is not really a thing it's actually kind of a superposition
So you can never know what an electron is until it's more
Considered a field at this point
If you put it through a particle accelerator
All right you're going to get all kinds of wild
I hope I do enjoy that Lily
I love it when Jordan says bananas thank you so much and I'll probably want
I feel like that's okay
Pasta cuz I say it too much
No this was initially explained that the that they chose the name cuz they like it when you say banana
That's a very literal bananas thing to say
Indeed
Just kidding it's as dope as it's ever been thank you so much
Oh I get it it's not cool I thought it was cold
Oh good the open mic
The bar the bar
Yeah just getting it the dopest it's ever been thinking about you or not
K'Nex
The magical mystical Master Sergeant Daniel Jordan's mystery conspiratorial Time Machine band
Featuring the doctor dreamy creamy
Featuring The Dream creamy dr. Toots and the Amazing Technicolor Squatch
Thank you so much you are now.
Zoo the pretend race team
Thank you so much
You're now.
I'm a policy wonk
I have
Risen above
A list for me
And then we're going to
Comeback
And I'm going to
Start the show over
F*** you
I got plenty of words for you
At the end of the day
F*** you and your new world order
Horse you rode in on
All your s***
Maybe today
5 years
Maybe I'll walk out of here tomorrow
And you never see me again
That's really what I want to do
Back here again
I apologize
Yesterday that I
Was legitimately having break
I'll be better tomorrow
He's not Ono so we start off here with Alex
Being in a mood
About death
In the world
There's a lot of death
Well yeah
Recently
I intake on it might be a little off though.
There's no turning back now.
Freedom ranchman
We are now inside the operational phase of global
Cultural and economic societal collapse
4C population
That is already
Insurance
I'm sorry what now
In every Western country that has taken the experimental
Injections
Credible time to be alive
Solo
You look out
The claim that all Western countries are seeing record dances just
It's not something that Alex can make in any meaningful way
The type of Statistics you need to prove that are available and the only thing you could possibly be working off of his like anecdote
Little stories that is anti-vax
They're telling him he's on social media
For that weird Steve guys substack
Yeah I mean what would you say Sarah
Running tally of death
/ 12 months
Time.
That you can compare going back
Several hundred years props to the Black Death
You know what I'm saying like what is a record number compared
What is a good point he says record
It's not very specific
The only place he ever pulls vaccine data from a severe
It's because it's a place where all reported
Have any side effects that anyone experiences after getting vaccinated are reported
Godless
Of whether or not the vaccine cause the side of
Up to August 10th 2022 there had been 606 million doses administered
And 15930 reports of people dying after getting the vaccine
How that have been entered in Tavares
That doesn't mean that almost 16,000 people died because of the vaccine but even if it did
Represent p0026 percent of vaccinations
The CDC has identified nine.
But they can causally linked to a vaccine for covid
And those aren't even the MRNA once those are people who got the Johnson &
None of this makes any sense stupid
Alex wants
To be very extreme
About
The vaccine
And I got that sent
Security immediately. And I think there's a good reason I think you'll see as this goes on why this needs to be heightened
I made as severe as possible
See how we have midterms
Oh my God why does everybody why does it keep talkin about
Is there very important
The Republicans might want to take over the country
But also maybe they need to take over the country more
That sounds right
Republicans running around
Wetting themselves with excitement about to take over the country
Even if we get
More
Show me Republican
Yeah yeah
Problem
Good news is this
Ron DeSantis
Bolsonaro
Viktor Orban
And others
I understand what's going on
You've been ramping up his
Name-dropping of Orban
Definitely happening more lately
If you're really be clear
We don't have leaders like bolsonaro
Show pictures of robots spoken control over the US
I feel like if I was DeSantis
I would be like
Please don't put me in without naot fascist
I would like to still slide under the radar for at least a little while before I get to become president and fascist
Yeah we'll talk a big talk
Pinpoint that was circling around social media after this episode was that
Alex has turned on Trump
In favor of dismay
So it's obviously a high praise for him to be put in the same
Category is
Or Bob
So Alex
Does still like Trump
And that's something that's important to recognize
Despite what
The sort of
Just turned on Trump
Yeah
I'll say this I like Donald Trump
Supporting
Sure that made me kind of pig Henley support him
Speed
What
We had an office
Is the nightmare scenario if Hillary
If this is true and Alex afforded trump.win operation warp speed was happening because of need
To keep Trump in office
Then he was lying to Azadi
Alex was super clear that he had like these really high-level back-channel intelligence sources are telling a metropolis
Sporting the vaccines
Trap for the globalist
Handsome
To force our hand to reopen the economy
Alex's also said that Trump got tricked into supporting the vaccine development but he
He's never said that it was a
Purely partisan political consideration
On his own part to excuse their behavior
Yeah that's f*****
Yeah also covid happened
After Hillary had lost
The 2016 election
I've no idea what she's
Appear
It's pretty insane to think that Alex good of acted the way he did an excuse all the s*** that he's
Completely philosophically again
Just because of a desire to keep Trump in office who I should remind you isn't
The person who is doing all the stuff Alex is philosophically again
He supported vaccines and boosters
He didn't get Alex in the weirdos back on social media he didn't lock up Hillary he didn't build a wall and kick out all the immigrants
He didn't free Julian Assange
All of the stuff
Should be fundamentally disqualifying for Alex and yet
He turned a blind eye because he didn't want a Democrat to win
The presidency
That's weird I mean
You feel
And this obviously doesn't apply to him
Obviously
Text meant for me personally
I would feel shame if I was telling you
That by the way
When I said all of that stuff
I was betraying all of my principles are for no reason other than that
People made me feel like I
Should
I was coming up with elaborate stories to pretend that I wasn't giving up on my my principles
Giving up on my principles for several years
I have learned that I was rationalizing giving up my principles for several years you motherfukers I made up
So many Lieutenant Colonels these last five years there were so many people who are fighting against
The Deep State who let me know that it was okay for me to
Betrayal
What spread
I don't want to sound too mean but this is pathetic
Alex rejected the opportunity to stand up for all of his principles because he saw possibility that someone who he
He kind of knew might be able to
Hang on to power
This isn't the sort of thing a person like a who Alex pretends to be would do its what a coward
I guess what
It didn't matter
Find still won the 2020 election and here we are
Yeah Alex sold himself out for a presidential election
Something is Passover
Would never let him get away with
And what does he got to show for it
Basically nothing it is it is funny to go back
Can think about all of those posit
Comments from Glenn Greenwald and Matt Taibbi about house
He was ahead of his time and he's sticking to his guns and that's why people didn't like him
Is because
He refused to be a part of the two parties
System
And then to hear him say
You know
I'm thoroughly apart of
The two party system
Sad
Quite sad almost
As we're recording this I'm seeing on Twitter that it looks like Laura Loomer might win her primary
It's a heavily GOP District so he's probably going to be a thug
She's in
Oh my gosh
Popemobile in the
Like in Congress they should be
Put behind glass
So everybody can sometimes turn and look at them and go
Look at that
We have what we have pets
Oh my God now
It could be great
Like Pam to herself to one door of cars
Beautiful
More
More dumbness please
Because he's getting
Impaled as hell
I am supporting the Santas
Gone for being awesome to me
Unbelievable
I can also look in his eyes
HD video
Sheila Wilson sharing
I'm a father
And a husband who loves his children this country
And that he's getting red pilled
More and more each day
None of these white pills about the future we stand up
I'm sorry what
Bill blackmail thing is convoluted
If you believe that there's a chance you can do something to alter the future then you can't be blackpilled
This is just Alex wanted to throw around to language willy-nilly
Haley Miller
If you will
I won't marry
I think Alex may have some problems with the Santa's that he
He doesn't expect
So, because he doesn't really know much about him
Is that the s*** he talks right
Fair amount of s*** I think some of the position
Ocean City holds could end up being a prom
Alex to
It's fun though that he has a shiny new aspiring patches to to cheerlead for but
Overtime as DeSantis fails to live up to
Comically extremist
Expectation
Also this is just a bummer
Alex can just support no one
That's what he's supposed to be
The guy who isn't backing any individual because
He's too busy rooting out corruption on both sides of the aisle
Haven't candidate years
Supporting kind of makes our Watchdog things a little false and it's really a repudiation of his entire character
And
I put Ron Paul on the side he was a perennial Loser on Paul yet
Even if you did win
His function is to destroy the thing he was elected into so
Different
If I were Alex I would have gone back to Rand Paul
Or I would have just abandoned drop without using a new hero
I have a strong sense of why Alex is doing the thing this way and we'll get it does over the course the episode
But it's just so sad to see him go from a guy who's like
I'm above it all to being like
I'm going to
Had to my bats with a different team
Be kind of problem with
All of this
All of it
Which is one
He's supporting DeSantis for what
President
No for the governor of Florida he's already the governor of Florida
Define
He has not announced he's running for president
But even then okay so
He's supporting DeSantis now
That doesn't mean anything but he's supporting for president in the 2024 election
But it's 2022 who gives a f*** who you're supporting now
It's Freddy's and neither is Trump
Presidential election the world is burning now
Because I think that there's a dynamic going on that Alex got bit by the presidential
Election bug
I'm in 2015
And you do
Just can't get enough
Like I think of that they've been so successful for him
In terms of
Marketing audience
Attracting all kinds of things
People get really caught up in it it's kind of
There's a sporty element to it
Very much and I think he didn't
Tap into that much for his entire career
As much as you can clearly for Ron Paul during the early parts
To the GOP Primary where he's involved
You just got to talk s*** about all the
Exactly
Great
Hooray
Now
It's it's
You got to
In the same way the people started talking about the midterms after the general election you know Alex is jumping the
Gunn he's overeager
For the general election
I don't care
And I feel like if you're one of the people who wrote that an infinite number of Alex Jones finally
Turned on Trump stories
If you're talking about that then you're talking about the 2024 election
Of which there's no reason to speak
Yeah I wish I had a couple I wish I had some name
But I did see a couple articles that did a good job of finding out
Maybe not in the lead
Of the story but in the body of the article like
He has done this a bunch of times when he has been speaking with
Attention or publicity stunt
This a bit but that definitely was not the prevailing
Attitude on
Social media
And a number of other media places in the body of the
The article and the headline is still this York using his bulshit for your click
That's what it is
So regardless of how well a job you do in your
Writing if the top line is bull
It's a tough line to draw tough balancing
Maybe some people didn't
Some people
I don't know
But
This is not
What
It appears
This is not a
Throwing out Trump
And bringing into
And that is the perception that you would get
If you didn't pay much attention
Basic self-preservation
And
And if we can use the same as leadership
But
Talk about is poison vaccines anymore
So yeah he he just
He's really interested in
I'm getting Trump away from the vaccine
This is
Solid thrust that Alex's bushing
And gold here man
Fauci
Trump needs to do
I need to come out all the way and say hi
2nd couple
He is pig
What
So you said earlier
What do you want
Admit he's wrong
What
So we can stop poisoning the newborn babies in a six-month-old
Everybody
Public Schools all over blue cities
I think he's editorializing a little bit on bolsonaro's comments but
I apologized after he went to the hospital 2/5
The one that's
Just so you know he's got his head up his ass I think he had an impact
Bow for a while and then they removed it
And then he was anti-vax
I think that's how it went
So Trump is pigheaded and what-have-you but Alex. Alex said
Earlier that he supported Trump
Because he was being pigheaded
It's an interesting point
Shouldn't that make him support Trump further
Nah okay
Big headed but if you're headed in the right direction
Then everything would be fine right
Alex is saying I'm a big baby when and where please listen to me
Achoo children over Trump
Can I get sucked into politics
Democrats
Again
What does it come out
Against
Children
To admit there's major problems
Because
I don't want
Kamala Harris
Call Momma organelles
What
I cannot
Support Trump
Killing all these people in maiming others
Baby continues to do this and I think we should open the phones up today on this subject
Here's what's going on
Experience throughout the course
Episode
Panda Santa
They're pros and cons with bow
Santa's he's got a lot of policy positions that the audience wants to hear and most importantly he's been a strong opponent
The vaccines or at least that's the way he's allowed himself
Be portrayed
Call the flipside the scientist is not going to give Alex the opportunity to pretend to be his friend
He's an actual politician who knows better than to make that kind of an association
Going to be crippling in the long-term View
He's too young
He has a career ahead
Conversely Trump is fine letting weirdos into the Inner Circle and Alex has the best shot of staying relevant
Los Altos bodies with Rodger Stone so the connection with Trump there is
Pre-boarding
They probably not talk anymore
Well it's more likely for Alex to get some sort of
Pardon or whatever should that be derived from Trump as opposed to DeSantis
That is true
No
Things Alex could be pardoned
For by Trump I mean at this point you want a preemptive pardon from the president for whatever there's a
There's a good chance you're committing a crime just by being around just in case
Trump supports vaccines
This is a big deal because Alex is already into the grass of Lee anti-vax and they don't like Trump
As much because of it
Ceases to be a problem if Alex can just
Convince dropped
Baby, if you back
That would be a
Much easier fix the trying to get
Infowars guy
I think that's what this whole pageant is been about
Over the course of this episode and then this video that Alex puts out later
There were two goals
He's trying to threaten Trump
Like you did with Rogue
By saying that he's going to eat
A pig
As much free publicity as possible from Rubes
To feel like they're actually dunking on
Probably an element here that he soft pitching to the audience the actual idea of becoming intuitive
Santa's fully the audience response that you sent your it if they were to take some
The Feelers out there
Right and also you've got plenty of time for the election that is several years away
Certainly do
You have plenty of time let's put that in the news Alex changes his support for candidate who is that yet running for president
Another guy who's not here
Another thing I want to point out here is that runs lipkowski this Twitter account
Clip of Alex saying that he was supporting the scientist
Which as I Was preparing this episode had over 2,500 retweets
By almost 900,000
Some people
This clip is
Inaccurate
And it's actually manipulative lie edited in order to present an image that Ron wants to convey as opposed
Go to what's actually being said by Alex
And is episode
His clip entirely omits
The part where Alex is clearly saying the problem
I think that's a major component of what Alex's sink
It'd be one thing if this was actually a straight up episode where Alex is like I'm done with Trump let's just go with the saint
But that's not what's going on
If you posted an abbreviated clip of that and it captured what I'm saying
By every said I was going to
Shove
DeSantis up his dirty a******* that's a whole different story cuz he's never done something like that but
Accounts like this Farm attention and social media Cloud by posting things that Their audience wants
To hear
This a Ron fella knows that they're there is a pretty solidly Democratic voter base that follow him
They don't give them a sense of schadenfreude
If you hear the trumpet lost is most
Zealous and rabbits
Sporter
Answer this is the clip its provider
He's off really well
Actually conveying what Alex was saying wouldn't be as emotionally appealing to
To the people who he's hoping we'll Retreat this because
It's complicated and as much as a pain
And we can save it
Makes sense
Alex is actually pretended to turn on Trump
Far more Extreme Ways in the pasta this isn't even really
Attractive abandoned
It's very clear that this serves to possible purpose
Get Trump to be anti-vax so the ship
Can Be steady or create a paper trail that
What can you use as a rationale to full
We detach from Trump later when he needs
I feel like the story that I'm missing from all of these people is
Shame I would like more shame for how many times I've seen Ron filipkowski embedded in a
F****** Guardian article on the Rolling Stone or whoever is embedding him
Feel shame why doesn't anybody feel shame anymore damn I kind of understand the reason why
I think that a lot of these Outlets don't have the time
I get the wrong Clips you don't answer their
I feel like that is a legitimate excuse you know if you don't have time to do a good job
Do a shity job and then acts like it's fine because you don't have time
You make a point
I really resent people who act like this Twitter account do because it's essentially doing the same thing that Alex
Hit me up if you just say Alex chose DeSantis over Trump or make implications that the rats are leaving the sinking ship
That's essentially the equivalent of Alex giving a headline and then do you know
Party here
It's the narrative up that they want to attach to the headline
Show based on what they want the headline to me
But then you're saying that the people who prepared him are doing the exact same thing Alex does
Quit skipping that lesson knowingly perhaps
Maybe you put that
I don't want to I don't want to belabor the point but there's a reason I'm stressing this
We're going to get to in here
Little bit after this episode couple days later Alex put out a video that supposed to be an emergency message
To drop explaining that he was
Trying to get his attention and get him to ditch
The vaccine
This
Is completely in line with a message that Alex was putting out on his show on Wednesday but
It is not in line with the narrative that Ron was selling on Twitter
In the video that almost a million people watch
And so when Alex without his emergency message
This
Video is kind of an opportunity for Ron to incorporate it with a narrative that keys
Constructed
He posted
35-second clip from the video with this
Quote
Getting some blowback after he announced Thursday it was
He was back into Santa's over Trump now has an emergency message to Trump saying he was simply too
Disposition on the vaccines
With some tough love
It very well may be that Alex got some blowback from the audience but I'd be surprised if it was very severe or if it would
Even matter at all in changing Alex is mine
If you gauge
The temperature of his audience
From user comments on his website and callers they are really that opposed to moving past dropping
This isn't really appealing option
For the extreme right-wing
Making that pivot would likely only cost Alex's proximity to power and probably
A couple gas
Might stop coming on
Rodger that might get iffy
Sorry I don't I don't know how
I don't either I don't know if that's a bridge that out
Can't afford the bird
Roger's already on Mike lindell's Network it's not like
Intimately entwined anymore
Right I mean
It's it's just one of those things where
Why why are we why are we doing this
It's feels like everybody is making poor choices simultaneously
In defiance of the very obvious good choice
It's terrible
I think that a lot of people don't realize they
The game that
It's being played
Right they don't realize what they're playing with a shady character
Also it's
Makes sense
For the people not to give a s*** if he abandons Trump because we've already done cuckoo bananas in the White House
No I'm I'm sure that Lee
More than enough people are like
What if we tried somebody
With a Pacer
Check level of
So Alex knows that there's not really that much of a consequence
Cuz he's done reply
Has he gets more attention
A couple days later
Is incongruent with the message
Message that he was putting out on his show
And that's not true
And this is a huge problem
In order to explain why I need to play the 30 second section of Alex's video
That Ron posted this is from that emergency message
He won't
What
Contrary
I understand
What Alex is saying is true
If people got the impression that Alex was abandoned
Drop and they took him up on that challenge of listening to the 30 minutes the first 30 minutes of this show from Wednesday
They would come away from that with it
Conclusion that the clip they were shown on Twitter actually was out of context
And it didn't capture what Alex is saying
The only real problem I have with what Alex and saying there is that Ron filipkowski is not the corporate media
The danger in this is that Alex
It's always says that he's being taken out of context
Text any basically never is
Actually is taking Alex out of context and he's running a serious risk of giving people the reason to increase their low
Level of trust and Alex
And decrease
Their trust in
Critical voices of the extreme right
Right
He is being taken out of context to your so who's the
To say if he's actually being taken in context about all that Sandy Hook stuff
You know
Hey
Let's do a bad job we don't have time for a good job come on
Playing Alex's game you expose people to Alex in a way that if they look into these clips any deeper
They'll Come Away with
The conclusion that Alex is right and they took him out of context
And this isn't a small deal either
These videos get hundreds of thousands of views on Twitter and spread all over the
As you've already mentioned many news outlets don't have the resources to hunt down these video clip so you'll often see them repost
It's from his account
And by proxy they are taking Alex out of con
He's dangerous
And more of note it's a pretty predictable system you could game if you wanted to do if your Alex
Now there's a second thing I need to point out in that this is a short clip Ron is taking
Prominent
This run this emergency video
Is approximately 5 minutes until the video that Alex put out
The video does involve Alex restating that he's trying to play hardball to get Trump to go anti-vax basically
I'm really leaving this time I totally that's fair
That's not what the
Videos about
The first five full minutes
Breakdown of Alex's main covid vaccine
Pinpoint
Basically he's distilling it down to like
He's pretending to have a briefing for Trump
Giving talking points
Alright
First 5 minutes
Of this 9-minute video is
With the last two minutes
Commercial
So
Actually is
Is Alex
Clarifying
And providing the talking points
Should Trump
Watch that video
Why are we even posting it anyways if it's
Theoretically
A message to someone who will never in a million years watch it
One capitalize on the
Media attention that he got out of trending for supposedly turning on 2nd
Alexandra video claims that some people that he knows who no-trump were like a f****** deal
I do believe that he emailed
The framing this video is being Alex
Backpedaling only serves to strengthen the original out-of-context frame and it was crafted by Ron's original
Innocent he's putting out information that just lives in a false reality that he's designed
For his audience
Whether intentionally or not
It's 1:30 probably thinks it's benign like this reality and information but it's a bad idea
Even if you accepted this series of poorly contextualize clips
Are being put out as a result of a
Honest
Innocent mistake is not
Good
It's one that plays directly into the games that the people he
Discovering use
And responsibility to do better
Because
There is a massive audience
That is viewing this content and as you pointed out
8 something
It's being used as a resource
For larger media
And
I
I don't know like I have a really tough time with it because I see this stuff come up all the time
I see these clips all the time from his account being
I don't know enough about a number of the things
To know if he's out of contact
That I can see these
And I can say that's not fair
Alex sucks
But that's not fair it should be required
For everyone who posts
Anything about Alex Jones
To listen to the first how not to cover Alex Jones episode because
Over time we've done several hundred how not to cover Alex Jones episodes
And I feel like we're back in the same
Yeah it does it mean unforced errors are made a bun
It's unfortunate I think it's because people think that
They're dealing with
Something that is not as dangerous
As it is
You know what I mean like I think that there is a blase nature that is taken
Towards coverage of this
Like haha
You lost your your cheerleader guy haha and it's it's
I can understand how it's emotionally gratifying
Do do that
No we're never going to defeat the dopamine Russia feeling good for 2 seconds and then going back to you
Your day
Flip side of it is
State like
Say you know there's
A million people who watches video
Let's say
I don't know one
1%
Go
Look into it and see that Alex was taken out of context
That's not what's actually all about
What how many people have you misled down a terrible path
Even though they're ninety-nine percent who don't look into anything you have just given
Useless information
Into that isn't back yet
Yeah one of my favorite things not it's not a
Like it's a waste
One of my favorite things about the the the media whatever that maybe you know the
Is that
They after Trump was elected
Did they took stock
Cover themselves
They realize that they to play depart
In destroying the America that we used to know
And electing Trump
And then they change their model to
Weight did they do that
Island View
Box braids
Anyway
I just think
Do this maybe just had a couch to do better
Anyway
Look Trump
Has made some improvement
I don't know okay
What's what is that
Around
All the wrestler
All the rest of the way.
Okay
Around
The opposite direction
Of the poisoning of these six month old babies
Globalist
Sure welcoming in immigrants with open arms right
People on both sides
Is he really looking for more of a an extra hundred and sixty degrees to get
Am different clockwise angle because you don't want to go.
The important thing to remember is that Alex is saying like
You're doing some good
Stop chewy the messages Trump doing some good stuff
You just need to stop it
With a vaccine
My audience will not
Tolerate
You not being a ex
Because under you and operation warp speed that's what brought these vaccines about
YouTube
Except that it was wrong
Exactech course
It's too big of a hurdle for you just to ignore
You're shutting up about
But you need to go the other way
How about the new headlines for this are
Alex
Attempts
Carrot and stick towards person not paying attention to him
We give him more attention for it if what the headline was like inside jokes
Cross like Alex tries to give Trump the Krogan treatment
Alex re-litigate 911 with Rogan
Synthesis better than Trump
But I
Kind of hear this statement almost as a like
You hear this Trump
Absolutely
DeSantis
Is
Over the top
What he's doing this is
Presidential material
This is what Trump should be like
And he's doing it now
And
We have someone
That is better
Trump
Way better than Trump
I want Trump
But I'm not going to sit here and hold my breath
But
Is opening the door
If it does change
My breath
Making Trump erdogan trump
He's a complimenting DeSantis cuz he's trying to f*** Trump like that's what's Happening Here is even using some of the same rhetoric
Call flourishes gourds
For what
President-trump
Encourage
If you continue
Check
Coming after
Going Through Hell
My conscience
All these children
You're stupid evil warp speed
But you got roped into
He's just trying to escalate this negative threat on the other side in order to be like
It's keratin
Temperature
Yeah this is this is pathetic
This is stupid also I forgot about that I forgot that he still believes in that
Trump election
How can you switch to another candidate
If you think
But the entire election is is a f****** fake and that Trump should legitimately be
And if that's the case then Trump shouldn't be allowed cuz it'll be a third term
And you're supposed to be the tip of this
Beer you should be the people not even talkin about candidates usually like we need to continue the fight to
Back in the office know he theoretically
You've already got a got a warrior on that front lindell's keeping the fire
Regional book vaccines
That get them
Metallic spruce
And a very succinct
Look at this Jack Purcell been retweeted
Patricia
Polish
Look at this this is a real tweet
I just had my fourth dose after receiving
I just had my fourth dose
Covering
Three months
Chad my fourth
Josh
After recovering
3 months from
Actively having covid-19
Do you have the
Regard
Read it again
I just had my fourth dose
After recovering
Actively having covid-19
What's the Stockholm syndrome
Which of the Mind Control
I'm very happy
To be boosted
Thanks science
If you murdered logic here doesn't see what's being done
Like she's just Trump
Can you imagine like an actual news Outlet doing
Any kind of coverage of like
Someone tweeted that they got vaccinated and they didn't get covid-19 facts
Haha I mean
Here's the even weirder part letting you know this is a real person's account this is like
This is like 1920s
Newspapers
Ed and including the part where he has a misogynist comment about her
Hey listen sweetheart like that.
That's somebody writing in the New York Times in the twenties like this lovely young woman walking through this
I got a vaccine yesterday for polio in this sweetheart is looking good like
It's insane
So this next clip Alex
Precedes
Talking
He's still sort of responding to this tweet
I don't know I don't know
That's it should be
That was the funny thing about listening to David Garrard other show that they were reacting to it
Episode we did especially when the prayer happen
Has like this doesn't even
Phaser setting
We're heroin Jody yeah yeah there was something really
Sort of I was taken aback by that because I had forgotten even that like people
Normal people who are exposed stories on their own podcast
Is this is still surprising to some people
So why is Alex's talking you're not even going to be
A cross coming in will you be able to handle it
For some reason Alex's brain think so
Maybe a documentary that he seen about sex
I believe he's talking about hookers on the point
Okay
Alright I just leave
Attracted
Rambling
About hookers on the phone
The show
It was on
1567 years ago about
Play Pandora dish
Prostitutes cigarette Burns all over and broken arm and leg beat up by
He's in the hospital room in the pit
Thomas and
The sex slaves
Mother
Baby
He says the pimp I'm going to get better I'm going to get back up on my feet I'm going to get back down the street baby please don't
Oh baby
Start interviewing the pimp and then go how do you treat a Rico's I treat her bad that's how she likes
How much do you pay
I might give her a bucket of chicken
And that's the American people
Okay
4 Shots
She's been sick for months after the first few shots
This shot was a hundred percent of
Gives you the disease
But she can't help it
For prostitute
With broken arm and leg
Cigarette Burns all over
Hair falling out
Beautiful woman
And then comes the swaggering arrogant devil
From the mother
Hey baby I'm sorry I'm so let you down I'm going to get back on the street right now soon as I get better
Not good
Christ in the mother looks
What have you done
To my baby
What have you done to my baby
He said shut up you old
I can't believe I missed you and Michelle first of all
Is really getting into the
Embody the character
Yeah that was a method actor
Little problematic
He said pimp and shot so many times they both lost meeting to me yeah
I think
In my time I watch
Hookers on the point
It was titillating when I was
I think this is a
That but I don't I don't remember this
Particularly I only recognize this from other times Alex has told this story and played these characters
I really don't like how much he
Minor like
Complement
The Pimpin
You know what I'm saying like
In comes the swaggering devil
But the swaggering devil is kind of a handsome devil
Compliment the voice in the voices not a a like
He's he's trying to be like
Cool
I did say that fortunate I don't appreciate it I wanted to keep that clipping
Full just to get the really deep
Experience of how long this goes on
I don't think Ron filipkowski his is posting that
No Maybe
And how he is
Maybe
Spreading some b*******
About how the SBI planted bombs
On January 6th
Totally
Richarlison
Is taking it into the danger
Call Everybody's happened
I should point out this is right after he came in from break to the danger zone so it was
Alisyn Camerota
Ethiopia's Prime
Play bombs away.
January
Is it just came out
I planted the bomb
Call coming out so
It's an incredible time
Eli
This is unfortunate bulshit for Alex to be spreading because on August 23rd the day we're recording this episode The
Final two defendants in the witmer kidnapping case were found guilty by a jury of conspiracy to kidnap
Adam Fox and Berry Croft jr. are definitely going to jail and their defense try to use the entrapment argument
Which was unsuccessful
This was their second trial after the first one in April resulted in a hung jury
Alex's sightings at in this episode unaware that a few days later they be
Two other accused conspirators were acquitted and two others plead guilty so honestly doesn't seem like this whole thing fell apart at all
Call actually
Quite the opposite
Something along those lines also the prosecution alleges that Croft actually made some explosives using mortar
Michelle's
From fireworks that were packed
Shrapnel
Nothing else says any connection
Into reality whatsoever
Can you imagine like
Carlson saying this s*** is actually
Absolutely insane
Like there's this is been normalized so much
But can you imagine if a major News Network
Came on
Shortly after JFK was assassinated like
Okay
Sure
It could be that guy but maybe
FBI murder jayapal
And then everybody would just be like
Interesting point
Or
Eunos
Maybe JFK wasn't even real
It was that it was a paper mache cutout Brian JFK June
Actually is an immortal JFK absolutely
More sense than anything I'm getting an update from Twitter
It looks like lunar might have loss
The primary
She look like she was a head for a bit but it looks like you might have lost it all breathe a little bit easier
Don't know there might be a recount so who knows
Anyway let's get back to some actual news here I was reading some headlines there
Snackeez
But it's okay
I just had my fourth dose
Recovering 3 months
Actually having troubles after the first shot
Doesn't work tall I think science
Mileage of a tweet
Don't really have a conflict of interest really
She didn't work for Pfizer she work for a Consulting
Confirm called skdk one of his clients
Was Pfizer
She also was the Obama White House communications director for awhile in 2009 is working a shitload of democratic
It's campaign I think I remember her
But maybe it's a big deal but not the way I look
Cuz making it
Alex doesn't know the basics of the story he's covering but he's
Something you can work with
Supposed
It's a gas has a dunk
For him
This is just dumb
There's nothing going on
Fine with considering that a conflict of interest
If we also
Considered Obama appointing like
Geithner
As treasury secretary a conflict of interest like you should not even
Start to unpack Trump
Appointments so let's leave that alone talk about the culture in Washington
Let's go for it
That's a different conversation
So Alex
Does take some calls
And the first one who comes in
Suggest
Maybe we get MTG on the tick
Got a lot of legal problems right now
He's getting older
Is that a real real good record of endorsing candidates
You should graciously step
Decide
Endorsed
MTG
The Running Man
Vice president
I love it
Trump
You know I don't know whether it's
Is this family
All weather Heating
Just don't listen to people I don't know but
This is way out of
For him
The whole message
Vaccines
By doing this
Beautifully said anything else
The prosecutor in the judge or Not Human and your trial age
Regular suggestion of something that is pretty
Crazy 8 in the White House
And Then followed up with
The judge is a replicant
Should really disqualified the earlier
I honestly I'm I'm
Willing to believe it's possible he was joking
But I don't know
Xactware in the where in the danger zone if you will
Joking about whether or not someone is a rep
Yeah
I think you can tell from that call he is not
Someone who is like
Do you have to stick
Side is pretty hardcore let's get rid of trump
So here's another caller
How you doing just total inside on
Or Trump in the back
Maxine are you there
I am sir
Listen to want but I've never heard this brought up a red Anthony fauci
I mean
Kennedy's Book on a
Fauci
If he expresses in there
Trump took a million dollars from
Never heard anybody bring that up
Yeah why didn't you bring that up and I like seems like now that you're talking about a conflict of interest for a needed done it really seems to be
To bring this one up right
It's just
There's that fascinating thing that Alex does with his awareness
You know like all of a sudden it becomes okay to
Admit the reality that everyone knows
Is there like
This guy saying why doesn't anyone bring this up
The pointed question
That is not isn't there
About this
This isn't like his 2020 campaign this is 2016 right like this is
And Alex hope presentation has been like Trump funded his own campaign spent Millions
Self-funded take money from these other interested that's why he was such a straight shooter
Hey this is
Totally
An indictment of Alex's
False presentation that he's had four
For five years
Alex is so casually like yep
He did and not only that it was more
Such proof
Or demonstration
That what he's doing is
Gatekeeping this negative information from his Auto
That's pretty sad
And they themselves should be really bummed out about everything that they think
Personally
If they are not
Capable
For one
Of applying these criticisms
Retroactively to Trump
From the very start
You know like
Oh I don't know why he's being pigheaded maybe he just doesn't listen to people
Well
Go back
Go back in time
Let's go back
Do that earlier time. We were all so young
Maybe he wasn't listening to people then do not under
Yep
So here's something slightly positive about Trump
Trump at this time is working to boost the primary candidates be
Fishmaster following
Which would also help DeSantis whether he runs as VP or runs his
Accident because
It's going to help create
America First agenda no matter what we know
That's why I'm still behind him
Still behind them
So ravenous positive but the audience
Kind of like wishy-washy they don't really care but also there's mother
We don't really care who brings it to us
Unless it's Marjorie Taylor Greene then maybe we'll make him
Butts
Because other things about Trump
Apparently Alex
Just decided not to tell his audience
Hello Alex
Courage the United
Is to realize that Donald Trump
And his
His family are working for the world
Economic
That's why we're not going to get leadership
Donald Trump
Is because
He's in on
Until he proves otherwise
He's in on it
Daughter is the world economic Forum young Global leader
His daughter in a way
Start a conversation
He's pretty
Maybe this color does
Oh that's true that is now know what this caller believes fully but yes
I wonder also I made some of the stuff really makes
The question that 9895 percent right about
He's already he's already several things wrong but
Actually I no way around it
Alex in his heart
New all this stuff so he was right
About these things
He just lied
I was right I just told you the wrong thing on purpose
Chris because it works better is a different story if you're like what he's lying to us for good
He was right
Hernandez
Scams on
Oh
Yeah that's about the right response
I can't stand list
Link to her
In the same way that I have a tough time with Patrick Howley guy
And Harrison Smith
The three of them have a real baby reporter Vibe tap
I don't know there's just something
About their delivery today I find
Like I am
It just
It's
It would be good voice acting for a cartoon
About child
They have zero chop chop
But right now
No chops
Maybe
So she has a big
Scoop here
About The Whistleblower
About to Some Humans
Trafficking going on
That
She should be careful
What was my fear into defamation territory
So this is government corruption and like you said
Essentially child smuggling
A happening
On a federal level and Vietnam the same company that was already caught shipping migrants in the middle of the night
To New York City they signed a federal contract with Joe Biden's Administration back in 2021
Million-dollar so I want people to understand at the biggest and most Sinister angle of this story is that we are passing offense
Innocent children
Do unvetted
Properly identified adult
Via our taxpayer dollars still biting funding all of this
So there's a rare incident completely false
It's just that it's not a new story
The Daily Beast reported on the Biden Administration having contract with MVM Inc for transporting
Immigrants back in May twenty
Rue21
A report doesn't cover anything that
It's not already pretty well established
Does public information
But she does presented as coming from a secret whistleblower who has to appear with her face blurred out so it's big stuff
Conversely The Daily Beast actually did some reporting on the story because spoiler alert
A particle to the one that they wrote
June 2018 about the same stuff
Alex in Savannah probably don't want to think about that though because I was during the Trump times
Does NVM had a 162 million dollar contract with the government
Compared to the 136 million dollar contract they have underbite
The actual store here that their contract was lowered from this higher about the Trump hate them
Don't worry about that
Jesus story is pretty f***** up or kind f***** up I don't know
MBM was a CIA contractor Who provided security for CIA and NSA
Installations in Iraq
They may have some
Six background so they may be capable of helping transport migrants but
Their company's history does not Inspire much
Confidence
That said the claims of people like Savannah or making here about like a child
Smuggling operation or probably legally actionable defamation
Alex
Maybe get this in check a little bit I think I think
Especially now
It's a good change
Names for Ambien
To go from being war criminals to just being regular domestic
Criminals of some sort I don't know how many war crimes they committed while being sick
Security
Maybe some I don't know email this down put
Your point is taken
So look Savannah got hired at Infowars right out of college
That's that's
Because I only accept The Wiz
System to hire her right out of college
Montana College in Texas
Then she left to go work for some of the biggest
Major organizations in America
You can see her
Investigator
Infowars
Mission can you see her do that
And giving platform to launch from
Literally had a vision
Waterloo Ice House in Guyton
And I saw the future
The message was you are to build the platform
Watch the generation of leaders
The New World Order
At the critical point
Really happened
I told you four decades
And now you're witnessing
You got a lot of Visions man
Also your team sucks
This is the next
Scrap of untethered from the things that made the Patriot commute
Unity what it was in the 90s which is what Alex
Screw out of right
They are if anything
A withering Vine
On that
Tree
Because they're actually that's not entirely true it's just something will be supplanted
Or or
Grafted easily onto
Authoritarian
It will be consumed by that
Cuz it doesn't have the grounding
In some kind of a fellow
As much as it sucks
At least they can see communism is something
That like
It has the roots
It has some
Kind of a
Tradition
Traditions
Yeah I have this
This
That the cult of the Cold War roots of that in the you know
The Fayetteville
Conspiracies and I'd stuff like that is
A tradition
These people like Savannah
Like
Harrison
They're really have that background they just have the
Attention economy background
Going
To do the things that naturally gravitate naturally
They get attention and get a rise out of people
Owning the libs
Yeah yeah
Just not sustainable in any way it is only flows Downstream to
Blossom blast
Responsible
Own the libs
McNeil in Alero
I feel like we should have tracked if I
We could go back to the very beginning
We should track
What foods
Alex eats
To what
Vision T receive
Chicken fried steak that gives you a future reporter too much chili that gives you
Forget your teacher's name
Yeah I do think maybe he has indigestion
Get that checked out
You just got heartburn man
I'm thinking about this even more
There's there is like maybe David Knight
Is
Someone who actually was in the tradition
You know sure
Think about other people who are on are in the earlier days
I don't know enough about like
Where Dakari Jackson's head was at
Sure I don't think Leanne McAdoo
Was the light of those Griffin types
No absolutely not I want a contest to work their other contest winners from like whenever
Are used to have to have your hand on a car in order to win the
The car for the longest time
Kind of her tradition
To be fair at least the contest was an on-air thing not just touch
That's true that is true
I believe Owen just Cohen got his first job
Because he just needed to get airtime and then it for the lawsuit I or something along those lines right
No
Wrongfully
Wrongfully fired at some radio station 3 hours a night
Sports radio David Bell
But
II
Yet I think there's a
Big division
Alex if what he's doing now is it actually
To create the next
Proper Folk
It will be a massive step downward
Yuletide stroll
Yeah you're talking about the garbage patch
That's where that's where we're coming
So I hope you enjoy that chicken fried steak
I hope
In our time away was what does Alex think about the FBI raid on Mar-A-Lago
Does not care
DeShawn
I don't give a damn about that
Human smuggling
Closing comments about Hernandez
A hundred percent agree Outlets everybody's focused in on the Trump at The Irate but again there's bigger issues going on here
In this country right now we need to be focused and on saving our children and again
Just with the border right that crisis in itself is horrible but that we also need to focus it on the sexualisation of our children
School the targeting of our children by the lgbtq
Call my God
Wow
Okay so
Savannah protect children from
Lgbtq
Okay
I think I think
If and I'm going to throw this out at
Should
The FBI have rated
Let's say
Any previous presidents
That wasn't named Trouble
Or even biting right now
It would be a very big deal to Alex Jones
It'll be a huge deal
I think it's a good strategy for got to be especially after all the information has come out that
This picture is looking worse
We don't focus on nuclear secrets being torn away from the White House illegally in that be I searching about
What we need to do is portray
People as
Is pedophile is going on here is Alex's like
Is Dubai
Yeah it's bad but whatever whatever whatever
Don't think you should be allowed to get away with that
Whatever
Crying about this that it's bad news
Lord Alex duvivier like okay
Bush did 9/11
But whatever
Whatever
So Alex gets back to calls he has Savannah
Go back to making
Get back to your hole cover reporter Savannah Hernandez
I don't do that anymore she doesn't work there that's true
Better things
So you're back to calls
This is really really fun
Soap before the break
Caller it said hey Alex
I went to the library
And I know that they now
Instinctually
She says
I went in
And I know the
That they have
A system where you can
Request book
But they should get
I am so I
Decided I was going to request
Your book
What is Alex pink
Here's what I would think if I was a lie
I wrote a book
He dictated a book
It is mostly a I've heard him talk about it mostly just
The transcripts of things he said on air
Together or something
Also
What point of order Glenn Beck has already released a book called The Great reset LOL.
Obviously you thinking that the end result of the story is
They said no
Right
Listen as he's disappointed
By the news
Michigan
A new book coming out
We
Libraries
Thought she got so
Fisher story
Call Catherine
Hi Alex
You're holding me over
To the library in what
What's a librarian
There's a form that I can fill out to order the book
And they didn't have any form she handed me a little ripped
Piece of paper like a
Play the name of the book in the author
And we'll send it to our Central Library had
Quarters or whatever it is
I will
Ed and low and behold I
CU Library
And they obliged
They ordered
Copy
The great reset
And the war for the world
On order right now as being
2D District Library
The way I expected it to that's why he helped her over the break because
They won't even let my book in the library
Come on
Building that story up
Was leading to that
It's a swerve at the end when the book is ordered
Piece of paper I'd never see you again didn't have a form all of this is to build a conspiracy that they're trying to keep
I feel like her big
Storyteller big pitch was like
They only got one copy of the book like that was
I don't think so
I thought that was I think that was we got one copy in the library
Be surprised if she's going to a big enough library that they would be need to be multiple records
Irene shouldn't that beat shouldn't your opinion then be like
Libraries don't even have the resources for
Tearing
Printer paper up
And they're still working
For me despite the fact I went in there with a clearly confrontational attitude
They love the first man that does Library
It's interesting though I do think that
I admire her ability to tell a story
Cuz she she got you
You know like if I hadn't spoiled that
Do you want the father was going in One Direction was going the only Direction it could go on Infowars a reveal
Disappointed
It's not fair it's not fair
For you to not
Give a s*** when you're not
Answered
But that's kind of what it's all about
Obviously
Call
A man there really he's really allowing a lot of that stuff that he kept behind that gate about
Trump to come out
Things that Trump
Albion
Completely different
Where Locker Rob
You know
Build a wall
Aldi's
33 word
Phrases
Things for rent
Friday corruption Citigroup JPMorgan Barclays UBS and Deutsche Bank
Thank you all
Sexual fantasies
The Howard Stern Show
Oprah
Good Morning America whatever
She wasn't his daughter
Chibi Mary tour
He was introduced
True Melania through ghislaine Maxwell and Epstein
Roy Cohn
Alan dershowitz
Lawyers Alan dershowitz
Part of the Epstein thing Roy Cohn
What do you think
I don't trust
Any of them
Better than Trump
People are just being
Arnold to DeSanto
People
To Trump
By Alex apparently even the proletariat Houghton
Waiting is beginning to figure it out
Well except for he's not realize what he's talking to the person who did the thing
Used
Funneling us towards DeSantis
You know the same way they funneled us towards Trump
It's almost like somebody earlier on on the show was like
Doing that again
And then they're funneling me towards
You didn't you just ask me that question right now is a way of implying that you are funneling me towards
DeSantis
Or it yeah you're at least they've been playing around with that to see if that's something
It's tenable yeah
These kinds of things are not
Stuff that would have been alive
I mean serious listing of all the people
In Trump Circle that architect
Epstein
Considering
Alex is big
In all Alex Jones was right stories
Isn't he was the first person on the Epstein
For them to now just be like hey did you remember the Trump is the whole Epstein guards
Constantly been like you met him once or twice
And the idea of
Is the Holden he may be too certain
Entities
These are not
Things that I
Except his reality
The gate is down
And I think that
That matters
Somewhat because the Overton window of conversation on his show
Seems to be a little bit more open
Listen to these things that are critical
Over Trump
The reality of trump exposed to the image
Alex's wanted to maintain
All this time
Stuff you would hand wave away with just like
He's not perfect
That kind of thing you know like I'd let's not be specific about that is that is so fun
Funny because
All of this stuff
Was widely known
And all of these people who you are literally speaking to right now
Work their asses off to make sure you didn't pay attention to that
Everyone in the Infowars orbit
And all the guests
Turn everything it was an active
Creating a false reality that would have
Skewer this
From you
So you wouldn't make
An informed decision about who you want to do it like this present
Realize that and
Not realizing the second
Impart that Ashley
He's still doing the same thing
And throwing around the idea of creating a false version
For you to worship right because God has given us to Santa
All the people in Britain
Like
Hey I'm
I'm starting to think this whole brexit thing was a bad idea
No
Of course I'm going to vote Tory for the rest of my life
And make sure that they are still allowed to do whatever it is they want
I'll see if we're crazy
Easy to lie to is just kind of fun
Is another color
Hey thanks Alex
Play some
Something here about that I just watched your
Aaron Russo were you interviewed him
And the other night
And that was it was pretty
Andrea Lee
Take a look at that 2000-2006
Yeah it was great
It was great
Great really compelling power.
I believe what was that America Freedom or fascism
One of those
That is heavily predicated on the idea that
Aaron Russo became friends
With a guy who was part of the Rockefeller family and he told them all these secrets
And Alex refuses to recognize
Is that the
The guy that Aaron Russo was friends with wasn't related to the Rockefellers
He's just a guy whose last name was Rockefeller
I might have been pulling us
Alright
Right so great documentary that came out I guess
8 Sharon years ago and still not made a correction on that right
Alright it's like
How many years ago is that I can't do math
It's like how Sam Raimi didn't apologize for Spider-Man 3
And I like you should have really said something before you got to do Multiverse of Madness
These words and put it into words but I think it's worse
31 Lasko clip here into Alex
Just finished calls
I was so f******
Confused by who the gas was
Special Forces
Two purple hearts
What
Wait what at this point I'm thinking
Russell Russell escaping from LA on this what what is happening
Horses
Bob Hawks a real person
No I'm thinking is it Bob how bad is Italy
Google what's going on
Bob house
Joins us lady
These folks
Sponsor for years
Oh no no no
Oh my God
Go to the website
Sprint.com
There's so many ways no that's survival gear
Really got
Even
Better Batter is apparently the name of the guy who's the spokesperson for the
Satellite company is a real person
Yeah yeah
Is the journey
Journey
Get to an infomercial
Apparently
The exciting new things they have is something you can put on your phone
To make it a satellite phone and on track
I don't know
Whatever right
Yeah it's it's a long commercial
Right right right here is as we come to the end of this me wrap this up
The whole narrative about Alex turning on Trump is fraudulent and
I don't
I don't think there's any way that I can look at it and say that anyone is responsible for it other than
That Ron filipkowski
The clip
That was widely disseminated that got over a million views that was all over the place reposted a ton
Was from that Twitter account back
Created the conversation
And it was not accurate
Yeah they created a false perception of what Alex was saying on his show
Yeah maybe that only matters to me
And I maybe it should only matter to me because I'm the person who watches the
I don't know you know considering the again
Considering the complicity that the media has had with
Elevating all of these f****** voices her
It's hard not to see them
Jump at the chance
They didn't they didn't like
See this and then they were like maybe we'll write a story about this
This was a
F****** full court press
Elated feeling of like haha
Bright money man it sucks
I think
That
Actual damage of something like this
Is something that's real you know there is there is a possibility that what you'll end up doing
Is eroding people's trust
In legitimate
Critiques
News out
Don't hurt credibility of news outlets
Possibly lead people to
Too trusting Alex more which is
A dangerous thing to do when you shouldn't
Engaging that
If you don't have to
Ultimately they're probably more dangerous things you could do right
And maybe this is not like
Highest can't
The Quints kind of f******
But
I think you got to hold yourself to a better standard especially if you have the kind of reach
Without account does
Hell yeah I find it troubling
Its cumulative
When you see all of the polls about how people don't trust the quote mainstream media
Every time they report on that they're like look at how bad the
The media are looking out bad the electorate has been
Bamboozled
Without ever acknowledging that
F****** you know what there's a reason people don't f****** trust you
You know and maybe it's not as bad as as the reason that you shouldn't trust a lot of people
But just because it's not as bad doesn't mean it doesn't
Exist it doesn't mean that I can't do better than you can do better
I thought you'd be something to strive for and I hope they do
Second
Yeah the notion
That
Alex's audience would be against him turning on Trump
Does seem to be not active
Yeah
Seems like
Especially from the
Picture that you get from all of the
Please calls
Bad news for Trump
Still obviously course and I think you'd be acceptable
If you would been to the whims of these extremist
Butts
There's not a problem with shifting over to someone else
I mean I just feel like
Bye
It doesn't matter
Because if Trump and DeSantis
Run in 2024
God knows what's going to be the
Every year has been
Crazier than the last in s*** is gone
Wilder and Wilder
So pretty
Addicting what's going to happen in two years
Seems like
I mean insane to do and if you think for a single second
If you think for a single second that
Carlos whatever legitimate criticisms these people
Are having towards Trump right now
If you think that when Trump becomes the nominee they won't immediately forget all of those criticisms bright
Balbach down in like a what we can't have Kamala Harris what any of that s***
You are in
You're insane it does not matter
It doesn't matter
Most likely will.
Ivan update
Laura Loomer has refused to concede
I read as far as a part of the narrative Arc 41 episode that is pretty God
Good look at Twitter while we're recording but you only got these primary music
She's alleging voter fraud
Why not
Anyway good me back Jordan
It's great to be back buddy
We will also be back on Friday for another episode will get a little bit more caught up on the Press
And get
Get back on a horse
But until then we have webs
We do have a one-sided. Com
That email address for butt
69 gmail.com
Will see you soon but until then daimyo I'm Leo and dzx Clark iamwill
Snapple Snapple of the Gribble Pitbull
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color