Air Jordan X swetik
I have great respect but knowledge B I'm sick of them posing as if through the good guy
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Worship at the altar of Celine and talk a little bit about
Alex Jones
Quick question for you buddy
My rights as a button stop
Yes I may have underestimated the demand
The sun is very bright and suggest
Very large brightness
Lot a lot of requests
You know it's hard to not just
Still be in the same headspace of like
We're just doing a podcast
On my desk
Right yeah yeah we're still in the exact same place nobody else working on the ship
Today of this feels
Was kind of the same there were 40 people listening and we did it like this
More like this
Yeah and I
Did you do I just can't conceive of the fact that there are
Katonah people list
In my head it's still that same thing
I'm so ya even compared to the last time we did
This is a massive I don't even want but I don't even feel comfortable saying that there are a lot of people listening I feel like
It makes us hubristic Lee
It feels it feels weird but I appreciate the interest in these but
And I should tell you one thing I've noticed in from the early reports
Yeah we may have exploded in Scotland
I don't know what it is
The Scottish Market waiting to get my chance at The Fringe Festival for
Decades now
I'm there baby
Yeah that was a trend that I was noticed
And Washington is staying strong
Lot of interest from washing
Washington State
Or the man
Okay good also washing
The
Concept
Look up
At least if you landed it the way Atlanta
Let's be happy that we have in front
Too many requests
I cannot handle much more we are closing
The request
Friday end of day Friday Friday
What is the last day to get require 0000
Meantime sure
Yes I will set the clock on my Gmail account too
The Grinch meme
If you want to have them
I can do about that
And another thing I wanted to say was that
A lot of people have
The people a lot of people requesting to help with postage
Particularly the Scotts
Another like International walk very appreciated at nice but I like to do this as a gift
Do people
And so I let you know there's no need to donate there's no need to give anything
I'm but if you do feel so inclined
Do I want to be disrespectful to people's generosity
We have started another GoFundMe
This one
Transgender Law Center
It is over on GoFundMe little button
Theme
A button on the dreamy download summer
So we've got a link to that will put it up in the show
Really
Today
Item number 7000 in the case against us being good with money
If you wanted to chip into the donation
Temporary
A good cause
How about you what's your price
Offered my help Sarah true
Obviously with the knowledge that it would be rejected
B B B B is
Xbox Twitter
Sent me bounds
Version of my book
Yeah with a beautiful cover and it was bound with love and inside it
Was actually my book it wasn't like a covers it would
No it was It was kind of surprising and amazing and
As a writer
I feel like the only way I can
Kind of express how I feel
Would be the word
Indescribable
So it's going to be through song
But yeah it's a it's incredible it's something I never thought I would ever see you and it's yeah I told you this
I told you that
Last couple months
To get you a bound copy
Angela Lansbury had designed to cover for it and everything we were
Fired against and I kept forgetting and well
I also sent some empty notebooks that are really cool
For me so thank you for me as well
Fantastic Sams
Sojourn
We have an episode to go over
Text Louisville
About
August 21st and 22nd
How you doing okay
These are Sunday and Monday
The reason that we're going to this day is because
Sunday
Evening
Being Russia time
Which would have been during the day here
Alexander Dugan's daughter was killed in a car bomb
Right as we know Alex is somebody who is on his show you out been on his show
And so I think a lot of people are pretty curious to see how this was responded to
They might be underwhelmed
So we'll get into that here Jordan but first
What's a little hello
Does
So first the Wayback machine spalti server thank you so much and I'll probably walk
Thank you very much
If you can pronounce them asara you can pronounce my name Sarah thank you so much
I'm not sure I can pronounce
That is where Wonder Woman's from
SMS Sarah
What
I don't know
My apologies
Nail juice
Text Smorgasburg
Doodle tips
Thank you very much
Next
Here I thought
The explanation that I still think I got it wrong
I assure you they're not
Next
Incredibox
Blackwell okay
Hey it's going great
Carissa happy 4th anniversary wife Marcus for us thank you so much
Technocrat
I have
Risen above
Miami
A list for me
And then we're going
To come back
And I'm going to
Start the show over
F*** you
I got plenty of words
For you but at the end of the day
F*** you and your new world order
She rode in on
All your s***
Maybe today
Maybe I'll just be gone a month baby
Walk out of here tomorrow
And you never see me again
What I want to do
Apologized
Was legitimately have
Better tomorrow
Happy anniversary I appreciate the anniversaries because
You do with so many anniversary request for a lot of people there like oh I know when
It's going to come in I was going to come on the day of our anniversary
But in this case
It's a surprise to both of you
Yeah you never know when we're going to give to wish you a happy anniversary
You might you might have been expecting it to come months later
So here we start and Alex says get to the news of the car bombing
Alexander Dugan has been on our broadcast before I've been honest with his shows in Russia
He is a Russian nationalist
Lita
To this open proxy war with the Russians
Republican Democrat
Lindsey Graham
Calling for the assassination of Latimer
People like
Standard
Himself a little bit in the way that this defensive Dugan begins with him saying that Duggan's been on his show
Expand on Dugan's broadcast in Russia
This is a person who likes Alex
Alex likes him and by definition Alex doesn't like
Just don't they don't like it possibly be one
That simple
He's just a good old-fashioned National
Alex
In reality is an ultra-nationalist imperialism
I don't want to quibble about whether or not his ideas would strictly be called fascistic like in an academic setting
It's fair enough to say that
Watching the ball
I am you know what when you go with
Warmonger and fascist I really don't feel like there's that much of a difference
Prince at the end of the day there are distinctions but I know what you mean
For those who have not heard the news on Sunday August 21st Dugan's daughter Dario was killed in
Car bomb attack while leaving an event
Pretended that night called
Tradition
Any aftermath Russia
Intelligences blame
Enforces from
Ukraine while Ukraine has denied all involvement
Others have suggested that he got tagged
Was carried out by Fringe groups within Russia or possibly
Even the Russian intelligence Services themselves
The very much unknown at this point who did it
And it may be something that's never really nailed down concrete never know
Books like just back up and let's
Spread out and let's
Take a larger view here
I'll tell you who did it
Someone who declared war
Somebody was up to no good that's what I would suggest is if you declare war
Declares war and then bombing start happening it's like your reward man like you earned it
That's how it goes
I feel like you don't get to be mad about it
I can see your perspective
I'm I'm less interested it from what I was saying
Citrus did in that position more like
Who knows who did it to be a discussion that a lot of people are hazard
We people like our
Like right you know it's a lie was it this side or that side whatever I you're saying
In Love and War kind go
Sure
Take this opportunity though here to call myself out for some of the coverage of Dugan back when he was on Alex's show
Circa 2017
I'll stand by my statement that it was a really big deal that I crossover was happening but I think I probably was too credulous.
The media stories that I was reading at the time
The painted Dugan as being much
More connected to Putin and the official government channels
That he may actually be
I'm not entirely sure how much of that is real that like he's he's
Spell really how much of it is Bluster
Approaching the show the same way that I am now back then I probably would have presented it a little bit
I still would have presented their collaboration is troubling
Because whether or not Dugan is closely associated with
He's definitely associated with International far-right extremists
In 2018
Lauren Southern posted an image of herself and Dugan meeting
And this was back when Lauren was making
Completely fraudulent documentaries meant to demonize immigrants
When was going on adventures to intercept migrant boats along with members of generation identity
Group with links to the guy who carried out the shooting at that mosque in Christchurch
And also going on tour with Stefan molyneux
Meeting with do getting her now softer like
Glenn Beck in a sweater with Samantha BS Rebrand
Fellow anti-immigrant agitator Brittany Pettibone was along with Southern for her trip
Tumi Dugan
Incidentally pettibone's go on to Mary generation identity leader Martin sellner whose home was raided after it was revealed
Set the Christchurch shooter
It donated a disproportionately high amount to his group
Great weird to that a guy from New Zealand to make a large donation to a random group in Austria without having any connection
There are other connections but even beyond that the influence of the ascending far-right Figures it's something that matter
Given his beliefs at
As he wrote in his book foundations of geopolitics
It is essentially a port
To introduce geopolitical disorder into internal American activity encouraging all kinds of separatism and Ethel
Social and racial conflict
Actively supporting all dissident movements extremist racist and sectarian groups
That's destabilizing internal political processes
In the United
This is a book that's been promoted by people like Jack the sobik
Richard Spencer probably not coincidentally figures or work
Looking to introduce geopolitical disorder into internal American activity
And encouraging all kinds of stuff
Yeah it is weird how that worked out weird
Anyway the point is that it
It's still super f***** up that Alex Fields this kinship with Dugan either they've been on each other show but I was
I think
In hindsight a little bit off base with how connected I believed him to be
Talked about it before
He's not
Come up necessarily and any large way but I've been meaning to address back
In some fashion
Well I mean it's regularly reported of him that he's being he's being his
Izzie Stevens philosophical architect of
The current
Russian imperial strategy yeah you could say that you know
Oh he's
Well connected in the Inner Circle but that's not quite the same thing as being socially and
And so forth connected in in that way and it's tough to say
I've heard enough
Counter report of that and I've also heard from some listeners who are in Russia
Or even
Just in the surrounding area
Who has
Very different take
Terms of what his
Position is Visa V food
It's not hard to think that
We can a trip
Beat that to him
And it have it
Have nothing to do with him actually
88 what is
The difference between some dude writing that and Putin just being like
Hey you know it's a good idea
F****** up America
It's not that complicated of a strategy
It's just going in there and Wrecking ship
Write a note
It's it's me
It's the difference between like being on the same page and someone like having your ear
There is a difference
Stuart has fundamentally the effective it may be the same
But yeah so anyway Alex is mad
At the media coverage
Course of this story
Maybe it was a false flag
Idea that in the Moscow
Suburbs
His daughter
Driving back in his car he was other vehicle
Eeyore Putin would blow up
His own daughter
The London Telegraph
U.s. headlines it's a false flag
Supposedly lose $40 lawsuit
System parking cell
Telegraph and others
Moon la
Just don't
Talk about it anymore
I don't know
I can confirm that at least the telegraph suggested that the the attack was possibly a false flag
Meant to incite the public
Sporting further hostilities in Ukraine
I'm not sure if that was the widespread media Theory actually suggesting that the attack might have been carried
Russian actors
Have specifically speculated that it could have been the work of a group
Unaligned
Right right right somebody who's a dissident comprehend Russian let's take a crack at somebody that we think
Number of
Suggestions the people have had and the argument that Alex is making where it's like a lot of people are coming out and saying
It was Dugan blowing up his own daughter
I don't know how I don't know how widespread belief that is
Fundamentally of where is unfair
Doesn't get to say s*** right now
The unfair
Yeah
Falls a little on deaf ears
Rimski I'm getting sued for suggesting that something could be a false flag of her questioning Ativan
If that were possible he would be getting sued everyday
Heater frame people
Which isn't the same thing
Also I'm not sure what defamation laws are like in Russia but based on the US Standard Dugan and his daughter or definite
Nutley public figures
So talked about the possibility that the attack could have been a false flag wouldn't rise to the level of actual malice
Required to be defamation
Against them
Just one of the reasons why Alex doesn't
Get sued for all the shity talks about celebrity
Public figure
So
About the defamation laws in Russia in 08
Are there laws currently are on the more like
If we want to get you we got you
Kind of side of the Majestic
This thing you know
It's defamation might be handled differently
Could be could be
So the Russians Alex has been monitoring
How the news reports are going there
They are not
The national Russian news
Mom
Journalist to talk show host
His daughter was also
Prominent
I guess in Russia they at
A1
Feminine
Sure
Brianna is
While
That's okay
You can say is if you want maybe
Making this about himself
Don't you say that the number one big that I should have expected with that this
Is about Alex
And somehow I was still like
Like so many of our listeners I was like I wonder what Alex is thoughts on this Earth
I knew what they were they were
Alex was right about everything
Defective because
Really
The actual bombing
Right
Seems like something Alex
Could use to be like
Nationalists are under attack everywhere it's a sweet spot for it there
But instead it's about the media coverage
Because he can relate it to himself
It is sad and sad whenever he feels defensive it always
Please comes back to him again Scott
Material to work with on
And therapy now you definitely got that to work through
I think that you know that
The mental illness Works in a certain way instead of Behavioral
Patterns
Is an issues
Once you become
Serta behold into them and they
Control you
Things become a little eye center
80s roller skating
Yeah speaking of that narcissism
He was clearly
A list of Russia he's the Alex
Jones of Russia
I'm sorry what
Populist the popular talk show host
Country
He's dead
The daughters dead
I want to make sure he died
Have the motive
To kill him
No the Alex's describing himself once again the globalist what you killed me
Not only is he like Alexander Dugan
Does the Target
But it is also that Alex is at Target through Alexander Dugan and in fact the globalist
We're trying to send Alex a message
That anyone can be God
Believe
I mean why why would the globalist
Alex's conception
Has the motive doesn't make sense
Like it's like obviously they don't want
Russia and Ukraine
So call me babe
No
Ukraine to join NATO
Even Russia out of crumbs
Assassinate
If you think it's
Progressed by
Bombing someone who's seeing as an associate
It's too hot now maybe is a dry run
Maybe they're checking their that they're their OSHA
The leavening like a practice
I don't think that
Can we Car Bomb anybody like how do we car bomb
You know I take that
I know I'm going to throw this one out and I feel like a lot of people are going to laugh at me but
Imma have to go with IRA
They have a
Proven track record of this type of thing with steak Knife I'm just saying that
It's in their wheelhouse
And maybe they just got a little bit bored you know the troubles haven't been as hot lately according to Alex
That's all
Yasso
Now it all makes sense
Hyper simple they always fit
They do
So look this is not a false flag
And Alex explains why
And you could say maybe
Climate Russia
Is it doing more in Ukraine
Putin into responding
Proxy wars for doing on
Braeton
Isn't that actually an argument for why Putin
Could have done it
Because then you would have a pre-tax
To do the thing that the people want him to do
Yeah
Ukrainian
Actors terrorist
Right
That
Alex's convoluted
Makes no sense I mean this is this is the problem because
Just yesterday
By being on our last episode
We're talking about Alex saying
I pigheaded Lee did something
Precisely because other people told me not to
To do it and we're seeing example of him just being like
I'm not going to call it a false flag
Because they called it a false flag
Dickwad will end up calling it a false-flag would require him to say they like Putin
Was willing to do something or something like that
Going to invade Ukraine
Right before Putin invaded Ukraine saying that Russian never does whole Flex
It's true so that you can go back on that
Yeah
That's your moment that's your moment to really pull it out and be like surprised this is the first
Russian false flag
So what made it so
Everybody should be able to ask question
But he's not
About this more
This is a false flag
Operation Northwood
CIA operatives and their families will get on a plane 8:59
I'll just change your name
Text to go to war with
Cuba and Russia
Sure
Operation Northwoods ABC News
Did she change her name
You have a right
To say that
Have a right to
About is silencing
The real disappointing again is evidence
Is true
What is describing a true thing
You can question this exact thing
What is the evidence that we are
Experiencing is that the telegraph
Did question this thing you are not being approved
But it is not for this reason that Alex is being sued by Alex is also banned being about ideas that maybe
No one cares
Interesting conspiracy
I will I look forward to Alex bringing that out
Around the midterms
Dissipation
From her dad but you couldn't get it in Russia cuz he's too closely connected to Putin
Now she's free
That could be so we have one last clip here from the 21st
From Sunday okay
Bobby Barnard roll solo
I don't believe Alex is just in for like
The first segment or two of the show
But he explains a little bit about his bankruptcy
Talk about the lawsuit against
We've done
After 5
Is reorganization
Survival
Continue on
Pay its debt
In the last few hearings
Coming out
Have the
Plaintiff lawyers
Fluorosis lawyers
In the meetings
We wanted season shutdown we don't want the money
You supposed to keep it going
But they don't want money from judgement
We do they do that we're showing that right now
Why is long as we
Opera
Bat for a year for the next five years here's what you can pay and that's what
And we stay on here
Hrdc my books I know haven't paid
Open yarn app
Everything I got
All the emergency
The senior real
Real
Big right now
Integrating
Are there like 1
Them shut down
Don't you want money for the plaintiff
The families are nothing
They're using and controlling
I'm so rude
What this is all about
Buy the products
Infowarsstore.com
That might be a new defamation I mean how do you not play that Envy we need to shut them down
Down here in part of like hey
This is never going to stop
This is just never going to
Listen to this this was yesterday
Guess what I'm going to
I'm going to call it now I would call my shot within the next week I will have another clip
For you by the end of the
So I don't know everything about bankruptcy law but from everything I can tell this is not a plan that's going to work
Businesses that have less than 7.5 million dollars in debt
He's trying to bankrupt Free Speech systems
They all like 50 million dollars to Alex's dad's shell company
And the Judgment in the Sandy Hook case the first one exceeded that amount already
Additionally this debt limit only applies a 50
50% or more of the company's debt is business-related which doesn't include defamation judge
Also the only reason that the cap is 7.5 million as opposed to the original limit that this
Subchapter had
At the original endo's 2.75 million
The only reason that's different is cuz of the cares Act
Bright Alex
Actually against
Chapter 5 is a subchapter of chapter 11
Eeyore the reorganization
It seems pretty clear to me why Alex Jose this route and it's
Because chapter 5 bankruptcy cases specifically do not require a business to file a full disclosure statement to the court
Let's choose the one that let us hide our lives
The thing is that chapter 5
They were
It was created because chapter 11
Normal bankruptcies
Require all kinds of information
And two small businesses were what chapter
If I was made for you to handle the intricacies of a normal real
Organization
Under chapter 11 of their debt is that they can't afford an incredibly expensive accountant
To help them actually do the stuff that they're supposed to do small businesses weren't able to take
Advantage of what they could get with a chapter 11 reorganization
And they just end up going out of business
So this was an attempt to provide an option
For them
To stay afloat
How much is basically attempted to abused the bankruptcy system and while he's doing it he's using the illusion of his persecution
Who sells dumb products
To the audience
The news is that he probably doesn't qualify for chapter 5 and as this progresses to the court will see what happens
But I don't think that based on what I can find I don't think of tea
Is this going to work
Sometimes I really do think I understand that the court system does work slow
And needs to but God dammit for this case I really feel like everyday should go and you should play the judge
Clip and be like
This options off the table that he said it
Right done
Okay then tomorrow you bring in a cup like we should have this whole thing
Burned out in like a week
Well actually chapter 2 chapter 5 subsection or subchapter
Is
Design to be faster
So
There is that at least it'll go faster
How many chapters are there is a question I guarantee Alex's asked and then has
Can we just keep using them
Another chapter
So we get to the 22nd
With Monday's
Cuz I felt like we have not really even scratched the surface
So
Dugan
To surface
Informative
For a while I must have put out his most
Important we Dear God
No no no no no
Can't handle it
I got to go
You know what it's like to turn on the show Heroes
I dunno
Okay alright
Okay 2022 let's call
It's one thing if you're pretending to be like TMZ in this is your leader
That's what you are Elon Musk
To be like I'm the most geopolitically important person in the world now man everybody world leaders listen to me
Elon Musk
Can you think of Edward armor obeying Lego
Rockefellers put out a chuck
Drawing on the sidewalk like at a bar
Sbl good Roundtable
There's a lot of news
Not just
Execution
Assassination
Kim's daughter
Massive
Economy news
So much on the great reset
And more today
Facebook
Advertising of the corporate media
Amazon.com number one
What platform
Waiting in the last 20 years to nobody looks better believe that anymore.
Amazon
Is arborescent real
Top 10
It is here
Israel
Tell you
Is there a few thousand bucks left
Dot-com
Dorney water comes in but
The new orcel be the only sign books I do and it's a fundraiser keep us on air
Razor
Copy of the book
Infowarsstore.com
And there's a fundraiser we're doing so thank you so much
The world
Is my magnum opus
Here's a Masterwork
Wild
Absolutely
Devastatingly
Lays out how evil infected
What about recent Wars
Alright
In the book
How does he spell Eva
Ebel
I have two things I want to bring up about this
Okay the first thing yes is that
Manny's making pesos a lot of money
I hope he's happy about that hey the Amazon charts are very little
At least I was thinking about
United sign all these books
But it's
He does
You going to be drinking while he doesn't
Progressively floppy flowchart
Show up yeah the last book
How do I kind of want to know
Did someone
Editing that's what I wanted look like
He didn't even write any didn't even write it
He said about dictator
Grab for Michelle Wright
Not even a surly dictated just people transcribe his rant
They think
Cut out
The ramp
Right there's no way that it's going to know that
I kind of want to read it just in case I'm going to read it and it doesn't come out until the 30th
And so
Kind of like how Alex's war was it the top of the charts and then no one cares
Whatever nobody care
Haha
Not even a book comes out
Definitely
I was thinking about doing a great reset
Special
Compared to Klaus Schwab book
The great reset
Well
Beck's books
The great reset
The three of them there's overlaps
Sure who's making up what
Here's what I say we do
First off what we're going to do is we're going to
Cut-out little passages from each book
And then
Glue them
Together
And then take that message
And mail it to Alex
So it sounds like we're holding whatever
Children
Holding the ecosystem
Will come get
So
Look they're big news
Musk
3 biggest whatever
Most important
Elon Musk
The New World Order whether he's being legitimate or not
Christ says you judge a tree by its fruit
Yesterday
Hundreds of thousands
Elon Musk
Please let me use the CERN Large Hadron Collider
Normal
The world is that
Racine
What is a demonic
Technology
They're trying to find the
God particle
Alright
Black holes
Traffic
So this is not an important
We must shitposting
Also CERN isn't trying to create a black hole to blow the in
They found confirmation of existence of Higgs boson AKA
The God particle
Decade ago was a great day I was really excited I watch the live
Stream is really really cool Alex has not updated his starting point
You know what else cry said people similar to
You know it's easier for a rich guy to go through Heaven that it's awesome rich people are the best
I'm on in buddies I will make the head of a needle really promise to have tons of white baby
Open the Large Hadron Collider Ono
Mandela effect
The Bible is a league
Saturday
Is that a movie I hope so
Play it's not knowing
No.
Dangerous
Blew up
A few years ago the last time they tried it now they're doing
Cast again
Rituals
Above-ground
So they had a helium leak in 2008
We could get to blow up
You don't even I can't begin to describe the Newsday
Yeah
What does Rhydon
The Satanic rituals keep it
Staples
Great ritual comes great
Particles
Bro winners
Hey listen
Quick-hit all headed to the left-field fence
So there's big news
Doctor Faustus
He has
Decided to resign
Good for him
Dr. fauci
Issued his resignation letter f
After 40 plus years
Different federal agent
MCS murdering people
HIV rollout
Discredited
Monster
This Hitler
2.0
This Bill Gates
What
Designs
Was that one mean
Today that I have
National Institute of allergy
Caesars
And chief of naive
Laboratory
As well as the position of chief medical advisor the President Joe Biden
I will be leaving this position
Getting some Arnold now
He now wants her B
Polio shots again
That impression was so inconsistent
How many do we go
I also like shifting mid Cent
He was trying to find his bearings and he didn't get there
Let's depressing from one of the greatest voice actors of our time who was offered the role of Optimus Prime
Every foot that he criticized Obama they said
They couldn't let him be Star-Lord if you criticize Obama
Also the CDC still recommends children get vaccinated against polio
Call April
The most likely due to low vaccination rates in some areas we recently saw at the identification of a case of polio
In Rockland County New York
Experts believe
That if there's even one case
There is a very high likelihood that there are more people who have caught it in the area
But maybe asymptomatic which is 8
Terrifying
Do us as a vaccination rate for polio of 93% whereas Rockland County is it about
Anyway this is not good and probably won't be the last we hear this story but
Let's hope for the
How much is ready to handle the news of a possible Resurgence of polio those until just say that it's secretly covid vaccine side
Back to being called Pollo
Lisa's audience selling them survival food as he watches them
Get sick and die
This is kind of what is busy
This model has largely evolved into after covid
Yeah
Speculate on that
When you got paralysis
From the poison shots
And the record levels of heart attack
Just he's already ready
I think
The number one thing I applaud couch
He4 is
Retiring
With dignity
Because
I'll be goddamned if I didn't quit that job
With the single largest f*** you to America anybody's ever like
Nobody has earned the right to
Give the double bird on TV to the entire United States of America
More than 50
Some
He might have a scathing book
Give up that's the name of fauci
She's booked give up on Hope
Yeah
So are we get to the second hour of the program
And Alex isn't there for the first break
Like this place Special Report
What happens
Stop.
Second segment starts and I noticed that it seemed important switch
To an instrumental Jazz format
No
The Works of Antonio Carlos
The most dangerous facts eating
Create
Saved by the Bell
I was asking used as I've ever been in for a long time minutes
I don't know what was going on there there's some sort of a technical difficulty that goes out on the Range
Puppy started play elevator music on Infowars
So
I don't know what
What the f*** was happened
Steve Kerr shazzan
Alex's anti-vax upstack buddy
What know what just happened so I don't think I would ever notice
No but there are further difficulty
The facts
The shot doesn't lb does it protect you
Well it's just like I said on Fox News
And
You know Brian egg
Who is the host
Was caught off
Off guard
And
So he said well we can't verify those numbers
Actually telling people the truth
Because Fox
Fox News has contractual commitments
That don't allow them
To speak
Poorly about the vaccine
So they can't say anything
Anti-vax
On Fox News
But skipping that you heard is on Alakazam
Record
Semantics
Steve is playing
The Fox News host Brian Kilmeade was Steve statistics are completely
We do be isn't he can't prove that they're accurate and expresses that by saying we can't confirm that
He's naturally doesn't except that he
In fact scant
Confirm any of the bulshit
Using the wording of this comment greater Broderick
Conspiracy
Of course you can't confirm this Brian Kilmeade here on the farm
Payroll right
Right
Scampi anti-vax I wonder what happened with Tucker
I am Hannity
And socks
And sometimes
See this is why we need to relax certain language
Requirements
44 like TV host
In this situation
You can't say we can't go
Confirm that
How to say is
Bulshit
Well let's not kill me
And I understand that but I feel like it should be required
Statistics Steve is talking about here because his sub-sect is full of posts claiming various bombshell things of
Vaccines and all them parently rely on
Legitimate
I decided to consult one recent post with the headline quote
Do you know how many people have
Been killed worldwide by their governments from the covid shots
16000 around 12 million
What's 40 times the number of Americans who are killed in World War II
It's more than double the number killed by covid
Let's aim to drinking
How was this number reach you're probably asking yourself first question
If I can even number first off here so Steve
Global death toll from the covid
But shot
In my opinion a reasonable estimate is to divide the number of doses by 1000
If you do that for 600 million doses delivered I know you did not get to 600,000
Call Paul no no no no
You just he just said it
That was his his
Basis for that number and extrapolate that up to the world
Expressing an opinion entirely nothing
This article is legitimately trash
Your Steve synthesizing his point which again is just
About him
Guessing based on nothing
Killing an awful lot of people but with world
What world leaders are looking the other way and saying nothing well all of us watch the high number of death reports in the media people who
Died quote
Play and hear no explanation for the medical community or the CDC
We're supposed to trust that they have things well in hand even though they won't
Computer on camera in front of anyone
Who doesn't have scripted pre-approved questions
The vaccine was never mentioned in any of these unexplained death reports
Get people all over the world have noticed that these unexpected deaths are only happening to the vaccinated
I wonder why
And I would say what unexpected deaths are you talkin to
Any specifics offered in the article so I don't
Know if I agree that there are
We are seeing a huge number of unexpected deaths
You know what bump
Cuz this is really
Suspicious
One of these
Medical professionals
Can we even call them that is the first question
But not one of them will go on live
TV in a
Pitt
Filled with
Hungry Howie near
Why not
What are they afraid of Dan
You're right
Time taken
There are occasionally like celebrities who died with no immediate cause of death determined and then these anti-vax idiots
Sandy was a vaccine death but typically
In all of those cases a death
That's cause is determined but it's after people like Steve stop caring about
Is using for the immediate dopamine Rush of like
Hey get this this person who you love was killed by fauci it's hard to wait a couple of days
Is to say that though after the
Already figured out the app
Yeah yeah totally clear
Steve curse of the Luna
This article also includes this
Cook
We are approaching the Six Million Jews killed in the Holocaust over. Of 12 Years
People worldwide at least six times faster than the Germans did
We're killing nearly close to 10,000 people everyday
The latest rate was roughly 8.46 million doses a day
Interesting Lee this is not self-limiting because 385000 babies are born everyday
So the killing can go on indefinitely even if
The birth rate drops by 90% due to the shots
In case you were wondering I just thought
High point that out
This is complete drivel
Benefactor
I feel like we need to really Hammer home but this
This obsession with comparing things to the Holocaust
Is Holocaust minimisation which is a subset of Holocaust denial
There's a reason that they are so focused on
To make it feel like the Holocaust wasn't that big a deal after all that wasn't compared to vaccination exactly
Giotto fronting about Steve logic
Secure 10,000 people aren't being killed by the vaccine everyday
Beyond that
This supposed
Could not go on indefinitely even if the birth rate drop 90%
Because of societal problems that would accompany that drop in birth rates would read your ten thousand deaths a day
A side issue
Everything would be over I mean
Just the devastation of
Everything daily
Crazy
Business statistics
20th
Steve poster
The blog entry were use begging people who work
Hospitals to provide it with internal data
How about their numbers of deaths NICU admissions based on vaccination status
This is probably illegal for them to divulge but also whatever results he gets from this Ark
Completely meaningless
He's Gathering data through the equivalent of a Google survey form where anyone could just enter whatever numbers they want
Pretend play work at a hospital
Right right right but also
He's at he's sending out a Google survey form that says
Please commit a crime yes or no
Pretend cry
Is data collection form is apparently something he's been using for a while but he's just now updated Hospital level
Before you can enter information about your family
Confirm to your household and how many people were hurt or killed by
Sure that's nice of
It's probably a fair assumption that he's been treating the responses to this as actual data as opposed to him
Targeting a
A very
Strongly self-selected anti-vax community
Potential responders do a survey
Women having literally 08
Confirm any of the numbers people enter into the survey
It's like
Bear's butt in Arkham Asylum
Yeah what it what would he be
Who did villain name be
I don't know
The sub stacking that's not good
No.
The Blogger now that's terrible
Information about putting out means
Exactly nothing
It's the kind of thing that could be used
To create an impression that it's something more legitimate and more scholarly than just
Apocryphal
Goats that the anti-vax
Community has
Do you think the usually reliable right
And this is a way that he can sort of mold those numbers
And it gives the appearance of it meaning something more than just
Suck tweet
Off the top of my head I would say that the way to treat these fairly would be to take the total number of ceviche
Submission
And / 1,000 and then that's
That's the number that are accurate
Sure
Now probably this guy sucks
Really appreciated him over this pretty pretty
Yeah they're calling for war
Steve sucks yeah
Yeah he's trying to explain to Alex here that the media is bought off
I meant something very true
Put something really tragic
20 people that a whole bunch of media Outlets
Got bought off of contracts
Pfizer 2 years ago
Yeah well
We know that the White House is
Suspense
A billion dollars
On influencing media and giving
Money to Media
To promote
These vaccines
And the drug companies
We don't know what the contract
It's pretty clear that there was no interest
Hello
Have we lost
We lost the show
You got your wish
The Giants
You can't get rid of jazz
I don't know what was going on on this episode but it was weird
Okay
Listings like a great time for Alex to bring up the the time that Trump got that donation for visor right
Like as we learned about that on our last
Oh yeah yeah
He's now it seems like Trump being involved with that that you would need that information.
Not right now okay
I do appreciate the lack of continuity
This clip is just dumb
And I'll see if
You can figure out why
I got this
There's not enough jazz
Snow this all this is really like
Keep your ears open
Leftist now
Are waking up
And I just look
Facebook
Everywhere
People are saying I'm paralyzed my mom's dad my kids paralyzed I dyed my husband died
What was what why did Eiffel.
I don't know he's looking on Twitter and Facebook and everywhere
Yeah
I mean
Okay
Right
I know he's just talk too fast but it's funny
Is my mom sick
Did Leicester City
I read once
Isn't that what a Christmas Carol was really all about if you're in the shadow realm are you shadowbanned
No I think if you're in the shadow realm you actually get past this shadowban because you can move through it
It's okay
Ativan is like a door in the shadow realm like a regular human couldn't pass through the shadow door
So you're saying that all the most popular Twitter accounts are ghosts
Absolutely
What is
Is drill but it goes
Steve at the story to tell my friends and this is dumb
And we see people in plain sight
I saw an Arab and bassador
He's speaking at a podium
Drop dead
But we seen that
Over and over again
Steve is telling a story it's very clear that the only thing he knows here is that he seen a video on social media
He has no idea who this person was or the circumstances depicted in the video at all
Big towels that he's calling him an air of Ambassador
This was the narrative that took hold of the video traveled in anti-vax circles online but it's not correct
It was actually a Saudi busy
A man named Mohammed bin Nasser bin was on
Al-qahtani
Who was in Egypt
For confer
He was giving a speech and he collapsed
Allegedly going on to die in another room is he will attempt it.
Provide a
The cause of death here is not determined yet and there's no evidence that al-qahtani was or was not vaccinate
All this is just
Forced conjecture on Steve's Bar because it's more profitable for him to make this suspicious
When it very well could have just been a heart attack
There's no reason to automatically be like
Why aren't they telling us
What's going on here
I can't get over the idea that we've seen this over and over
I have not seen a ton of videos of people collapsing at podium
Recently
Or infected my entire life
How many can you remember to
People collapsing podiums in the middle of
I saw this one that Steve posted
George Bush
I think I saw a cartoon once
Of somebody who is like in a debate club like a shave club off the points when he ran out of
Aaron just collapsed Arnold
Think it might have been
I don't know if something in that sort of part of my brain
Has been on a Arnold real monsters
It was Rocko's Modern Life
Sifl and Olly
No no
I need to do what's up
Just go back to some of that stuff
And see if it's any good
Or maybe I should
No
You stopped smoking weed you shouldn't go back
I thought I'd be a sister
So
Steve
Has these strategies in order to create is Conte
You have obviously this weird Google form
But he wants me to fill out with
Information they very well could be making up Google crime form
Is obviously there
He misuses various data in order to make points
Man fixes
Nuts
Obvious what is going on
There is no way to explain
Nearest
Vaccine adverse event reporting
Yes what anybody can go to
Open verus.
And there's something called the Redbox
If you go to that page and open bears.com go to the Redbox on Waze
And you flip the slider in David
Because it shows you by default that shows you
Flip the switch to go us only
Around 14,000
Now
The problem there is that the 40
Thousand
Underreported death
So
People don't
Report
So it turns out that for every death reported to Ferris Bill really about
So I'm getting it today
All right now
Escape that
The deathblow here
Look at the various numbers you'll see
14000 * 41
Sure
Great
See there's under-reported
And
This makes some sense
For some side effects
Headache
Right it's not everybody's going to report a head would you report a headache nausea defense
Picture
Death is a little
It's hard not to report it cuz there's other people who are doing the report self-report.
Tweeted that was
Yeah certainly better than musk's down by ship
Yeah yeah this is Ludacris and there's no
No defense of X 41
The actual website that he's using the open fares yeah
Says on the bottom
These are not causal
This is not causal data
Deckrite
You cannot be my Thursday qualifier
On the page
Go fuc yourself. Cause oh but you should * 41
What's 41 +
Get a Google form
Yeah yeah yeah
He's a fan of s*** and I can't pull the song title
Sum 41
Fat lip
That's what it is
Haha
Hanging out drinking in the back of an El Camino
1041 song
In Too Deep
Wow cuz I'm in too deep and I'm trying to keep
Is that really what they sounded like
Weren't they supposed to be like Punk or something
Papa
Oh don't do things don't
Exist together yeah everybody does
Doesn't everybody know that those two things can't be back and they can't do it works for a while there was a guy named Steve
Evo in that band and I always thought there was weird
Because he was around after jackass
So you just
Just took the name Steve-O
Steve-O
Wow there's two options
You're grandfathered in on the name
Yeah but you have to put sticks in their your drummer
Dammit
Respect that's a different store
He has a he is so stupid
So Alex
You don't have much
Tony fauci
Is making every time my Madrona shot is delivered into someone's arm
A lot
Problem
So we have somebody who's directing this entire vaccination program
Who has a huge conflict of interest
That is
Not something that should be allowed
Exactly how much she's making
On these vaccines
We're not
Allowed to know that
How much is fauci making every time someone get to moderna shot problem
I don't know
You've negotiated
Pacific 2 a.m. cut
Strange
Plus I thought
Steve was like a stats and facts
Dr. fauci is getting
Apparently by himself like the CDC
This is just rampant speculation and insinuation and if Steve was pressed on this question by a cop
Austin reporter
He couldn't even say that about you made a single
Anyone someone got him a during a shot
This conspiracy is internally stupid
Because here's where things breakdown
So far she's pushing me shots
To get rich which is willing to kill off
12 million
People in order to achieve apparently
10000 a day right
He's so money hungry just doesn't give a f***
Why was the Pfizer vaccine the first one that was a brewery
Wouldn't have stood to make
Way more money if
Madonna was the first one out of the gate that's too much scrutiny too many eyes do she ate with the second-tier
Get that red nose
He thought you were really able to orchestrate this entire pandemic and the vaccine rollout and a big part of his motivation
Was money
Why would a over 130 million less
Doses of moderna been administered than Pfizer
I'm sure the answer to this is attached to get the taste of both shots chair no doesn't really matter
But this is
Wow you got to figure that it
It's two shots for each
Maxine
Of course yeah that's the way you get energy gets you in a higher cut on the booster margin
Better
Yeah I got you I would love for Steve to lay out whatever stock holding
Things he believes fauci hazoor
Explain this nonsense but
He's not going to do any of that cuz he's just talking s***
It's easy to talk s*** when you just make
Suggestions and insinuate guilt on people
For fun
Steve Harvey wondering why people won't talk to him or take him seriously
A big part of why
This ship
Flies on your dumb sub stacker Infowars but if you try to go to the real world with it where words mean things
Going to be a problem
And that's even flick even Brian Kilmeade while you play this f****** stupid thing like no one else
Loan wouldn't allow you to be like hey how much does fauci get purveyor
Yeah but I mean that's crazy
2 crazy
You should go to Infowars
I might be by where you at
Yeah I think he was on Bret Weinstein podcast
Okay well we've all reached the Pinnacle of our careers I think
So Alex almost Steve gone
Another
The f******
Today
Covid
Denier guide
No I think it's because Alex is trying to ramp up with the Trump
Stop
I think that that is like
Covid is becoming front-and-center because
The midterms are coming up
And maybe he needs a way to
At like have narrative flexibility or whatever
That's
Maybe what's going on right
I'm not sure
I'm kind of feeling like by ramping up the vaccine talk
That gives Alex
The wedge
For the eventual or a nun eventual push
Or
Conversely
It could be the
The kind of contact you need to put out in order to get Trump to realize he should join the anti
Kind of has multiple Apple
Applications
Kind of interesting to me that he doesn't understand narcissism
Because ironically
There's no way Trump would ever do that
He feels
Proud of the backs
For doing
So in order for him to
Change his mind on that
He would have to take an accomplishment away from him
Samsel right
It wouldn't be one of the few things that he could say like I'm more or less saved million
Games of luck
That's a legitimate I mean obviously didn't
Do by bat instead like
A sentencing through his
Incompetents Milly the people
Better than nothing
I guess yeah
Can't take away the vaccines existence yet
It happened under $10 for
Even if you weren't a narcissist
Why you wouldn't want
What's 2 not proud of that
Unequivocally pretty good all the way from a dog
Actually sometimes it's not that hard
I mean I'm talking about
Imagine if
Richard linklater is Alex had to be like
I hated the movies that I was in
That would never happen
Or I hated my performance are outdated what happened
You know he wouldn't be like I sucked in that movie
Yeah probably not
Yeah
It's hard to say
This is why you need to have a
A mentality of like
Kill Your Darlings
That kind of writerly mentality whatever these Idols are you
Tear them down if you like something get rid of it right
You can't you can't sit around and think about a great it was that you made that vaccine
Burn the boats behind
Break a copy of Waking Life
Ammonia Lee it whatever you got to do
Yeah but I think
I think there is a way
You know you're making a
Interesting point of trying to find this sort of angle of like
How you could appeal to a narcissist
To get them to become antivirus
Right
And I guess it really comes down to like
What you want
What that person walk
Right there out for money or power or something
You could
Make an argument that there's more money and power on this side
True but that's still it does still run up against
Like
Disowning your own Tucci's mommy yeah that's
Seems like the the rock and a hard place kind of situation here's my pants haha
You admit you were wrong and
Exactly
Alright
You
Get on the plane with him
Alright hook him up to a machine that allows you to go inside
Is dreams alright you play Asian Orion regret wife
Alright
Then you go another level deep
Inside of History are you following me here so I'm okay now here's the crazy part you have to have somebody build mazes
For you why
Don't ask
Questions
Celebi ask you that what's that
Can I bring a top
Okay
Let's go
So Steve leaves
Alex
Talks another a T-Rex guy
I was fighting
Sleep Sheriff
It's mostly about actuary I'd rather re watch Inception
So after that Alex wants to talk a little business
Little bit coin
I saw no donation that he got okay
And I wish I knew now
Why she was one of few years I knew was bad but
I am
Lackadaisical
Really that's what you think
We hadn't gotten that
Dollar donation
Diamond hand because I didn't know we were
Who are $3 behind
We were
6 million dollars
Told me right after
We paid off the debt 6 million
Coming in
Can you be on there
It's all about God working in mysterious
You don't know there's a God
Who is this
Unknown donor that literally
New my finances better than me and gave us exact
And we play the cards exactly right
I wonder if Alex understands how much
More suspicious that makes
The donation to good God
I know I know it's God or whatever but in the real world that sounds like a f****** shady deal
Also based on intelligence doesn't qualify for bankruptcy
If you were six million dollars in the whole Divine donation
On what grounds is he declaring bankruptcy they're solvent now so he's
Declaring bankruptcy wait hold on
What
That seems odd
This is some real televangelist s*** right here this is like the most amazing to be fair this is something
What does from time to time always make exactly what he needs is because it's God's will
That's the s***
The televangelists can do it like I have two private jets
But they gave me just
The exact amount of money that I piss
This out on a daily basis
That keeps us going
Spun
Talk
All this money
Sure
He doesn't hear the need it
I'm sorry what he can
He could start a podcast tomorrow he should have focused more on making money as what
He just said no now he's going to say that he doesn't need money
He does but not for him okay I got
Gotcha
A big show trial
TV program
Conservatively
Country
Lying about us just attained a jury
Try to win a lawsuit they're not going to shut anything down
What cross street
Erica podcast reaches the same amount of people today
But you won't have the
And all these incredible
Adam Salazar
Nevermind
Everybody else to write the Articles and reports it does all this other amazing
Stop we don't want them to
Slowest sea level
You can in there
Power over us right now
You can shut
Support.com you can help me elude consequences right now
Yeah
I don't know if it's a good sales pitch to be like
What about Darren mcbreen
Spears
No I mean won't somebody think of the Darren victory
Stop what would happen to them if Infowars will go away
I saw that I saw that some Outlet track down one of the jurors and talk to them about that
Interesting piece would be
Showing one of the jurors or if you could all live
The jurors like these videos app
Afterwards
And seeing how they would feel about their judge
Meant that that would be a really interesting thing
Yeah
I wonder if they be like I did go much larger
No not all of this also wonder how much is it
You know the distinction between
The actual damages
Sure I have the punitive damage
I got I wonder if that would be swayed by him
Just being a total s*** head
Yeah yeah I think I mean I imagine that they they came to the camp
Transitory damages based on
Like math
Finish it and then
If they knew that the punitive damages
Quick come out to Alex's being like
Punitive damages don't exist
If the punishment is been equaled out by the guys eggs
You with didn't mean any
Anything that's not really punitive that is it
Not really right but it's Eric apps in Texas than that I don't know what you can do
I don't know it's a mess
Text
This Justice also Alex
Start a podcast tomorrow and get as many listeners cuz he
Please get your vitamin
I don't think Spotify is going to really go for a either
They're not going to give you your own so after getting rid of their most
Popular podcast
If you go to Stitcher well-baby
Anyway
Protected Bazaar sales
Did DNA Force get body
In our grade I mean support get old for 12
Super Bowl
That you are literally in
What is the arm
Infowars
A strong will
Holding position
So when I'm struggling you're struggling
It's much easier to just stop sitting here to still make with them
If you just to get the highness
Forest
Spread the word about us
How to polish
Their ass
When
And I've never
Never felt better
I've never felt
Stronger
Because of you
God works through Souls
What
Uvuvuevue Sonic rap
Sunworks alarms
Think about it we're the number-one enemy
Where do the enemy hates more than anybody why is that because I'm real
You're real
Recreate
Energy lab
What
A Synergy an amplifying network of goodness
I thought you were an arm during lockdown
WhatsApp
People coming together
We're doing it
Now
Together Sogo
Infowarsstore.com great products
10% off
Water ride
That was I mean I feel like you just watched over-the-top last night and then just
Wet off from there was like I've got this arm wrestling thing
I'm the arm that doesn't make sense
They're the body alright where do her any sport bag made with a belt stalemate
And now we're all Just Energy where is it
Feeding off of each other worse energy not even just answering energy Loop cuz I'm real
Your real what is that matter wrestling contest
Spare the Air
It was just the conduit with which he
She could ask you for money
So
Money doesn't mean it is
Annual high and dry in arm wrestling feel that kind of alone guy
In a deposition about it
I would
Say we don't need to give him for his money but now that I know that it's for kids
And what do you think about Greg Reese
I've never thought about Greg race
It's not healthy
It's a bad idea
So we learned all that much about to Dugan's daughter
I found I found myself to be underwhelmed by his coverage and
Lot of it was just about himself and wife
But why can't I do false
Flagstaff
Black stuff appreciate our episodes
Set start with a topic
And then end with you having
To remind me what it was
The topic was happens more than it should
The lot
It doesn't happen as often as people collapsing at podiums on live TV
All the
Knots
I like jazz
I wonder if that'll be a new feature the show
Yeah wonder if that's a sign of like
Gcn just giving up
The elevator music from now on
I can start an elevator music podcast across the street tomorrow
Ebony magazine
And when
Fidelity website
Indeed.com
Amigo I'm Leon bzx cork I'm Wilford Snapple Snapple of the Gravel Pit Bull
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color