Knowledge party.com
Pray I have great respect for its knowledge by knowledge I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
MoneyGram
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Everybody
Acknowledge
Alex Jones
Jordan
Summer
Naturally have been
Citgo in the end
My mouth
That it hasn't slowed down
Since I've been gone and it's been going at full speed I think I'm up around like
Maybe 60
60 ice cream I think so yeah
Part of the problem is
It's it can be tough to find enough variety
Easily accessible things special order
Get dry ice delivery
Listen to most of the best ice creams I've had it been in
San Francisco and you're going to have to go a long way for that s*** and a couple times I've tried to order like ice cream cake
But I think
I think there's obviously still a good couple weeks
December 2nd
But right now I am feeling like
I'm pretty close to giving the title to cool house
Cool house house
I think that their consistency is pretty solid okay like across the different flavors of ice cream sandwiches and
Novelties restaurant
Hole not like
Best ice cream
Producer of ice cream I think so I got sober at All-Star from them
Probably be the street churro cone
That sounds
Amazing yeah it's it's
It's quite good I enjoyed it it's
So yeah
I want to talk about is a little head to head challenge
I wanted to try now popovers any other
Insurers are regrettable yeah they're almost there almost enough to get me to buy a box of that sin
Cinnamon Toast Crunch churros
But I didn't cuz I assume it's
Cinnamon Toast Crunch
I wanted
They have some ice cream treats that are like
Palpable
Another little little ice cream balls in chocolate
Low class
I'm sorry is there a box of wine version of
Nestle's crunch
Poppables
Valve cores
Actually the problem is the moment you said it I was like yes you're right those are the
And then there's a classier version
That is like I think it's called dream pops or something like that
Maybe a non-dairy situation
Disgusting
Look they're both bad
Let's
Interesting at the head
One was slightly less
Right
Reputable suck
Okay
You know I found a churro cones
In situations where you're dealing with the subpar snack
Usually the snack that really goes for being the most subpar wind-up taste
Better remind me also I got in under the wire and got a Choco Taco before
Before the shutdown operation
Victims
Cancel culture
The ultimate cancel culture
Seasons
It was good
I will say that I remember being better but I think that's how are almost everything
You're right your taste buds
The Rose
Colored glasses
History you look back on these these Novelties of your
And you think like
God was so perfectly nice cream was
Just the right
Consistent Trail
I'll be almost every time you're going to get one of those the taco itself that the shallow is going to be a little bit
The consistency is
Gray wash or tacos are kind of like to squishy middle crunch
Lakeshore
Ice creams going to spell out that's almost
Still pretty good better than
Either of the pop-up
That's not hard to do
Deals Gap
So why would I
Like a dragon enjoying weed we talked earlier about how difficult we've been having a
Finding a video game something that simultaneously
Because it was on sale for like four boxes
It was fun but I think both of us found the combat a little bit monotonous
It's essentially the same game like all the sense of humor's they're all of the story beats or are very similar.
But there's something about turn bass
Jrpg
Geez being
Dropped into modern-day Tokyo that is hilarious
It's just very very funny and it's a good game I like it
Okay
Will be really a turn-based RPG guy too often are you
I think I was the person who told you to try
Three houses
For sure but I mean like
This is more like Final Fantasy 10-2 much of that
Maybe it's more than
I know I don't know
I think I'd enjoy that you might have
There we go
Fake
So Jordan
Episode
Let's go over this is
Unprecedented
But it's rare
We're actually going to go back to the past
But only like a couple days before our last episode
Because I realized that we missed something in terms of the
The catching up to the present
So we're going to be talking about August 19th 2020
Me to today
And that is because
This is the day after Brian
Shelter got canceled
Look I don't think I don't think there's a court like a direct
Text correlation cider no you don't know
Correlation
They let us on
His last episode understand the consequences
Cosmically I understand that maybe it wasn't us who got
Filters
Specifically
Cosmic consequences
Chicago Teachers Union shirt shelter in hot water
See I was looking at like some of the stuff that had happened
And over the course of
That they know the time that we'd messed obviously there is the tourniquet fake turning on trumpet
Daughter's death that like
He seems like actually important things
And in that I kind of
Just forgot
Feltre Hiddleston
I don't know maybe maybe there's a part of it there's block
M block it out of my mind since we were on it
Turn the TV on
No but this is important for Alex
This is way more important for Alex
Then anyone other than Brian
And seltzer right
I think it's probably
More important to him than still
Going to get another job somewhere
See how Alex takes
The news before we do Jordan that say hello to some doo-wop
Or at least she's sorry she fall asleep to this every night
Thank you very much to finally take Alex Jones's daughter fishing thank you so much
The worst Druid ever think
Very much
The dreamy creamy supremely thank you so much and I'll probably walk
Legal-eagle is a beautiful man
Can you very much
Steven The Bachelor Squatch of Ireland
You are now attacking
Four Star
Amanat Ali Aprilia
Someone someone sodomites
I don't want
Jesus Christ
What about Ireland which has fallen out of favour at Scotland
Play international listener ranking
Google Voice
The Celts are going to come for us van
Zoe riccio we're starting off the the show here this is how Alex comes in
August 19th 2022
Addition of the Avanti
Battle
Infowars transmission
Nothing yet
Uncensored unfiltered teleprompter
For free
Transmission of We the People
Interesting Man essentially nothing Alex says about his own show at is accurate there at all
Like I guess embattled
Just means
Consequences are mounting for things I've done
Yeah you can make an argument that he's teleprompter free but that doesn't mean anything and he has a screen in front of him the producers
But messages on he has a board that shows in the collars earpiece that the producers are talking to him through throughout
The show on
But he doesn't have a teleprompter that's true but it's not as
Lapeer
The show is not uncensored because he can't swear on the radio so by definition he's operating under censorship
I couldn't imagine a show that the more filter than this one
Just recently with the acknowledgement of trump taking money from Pfizer we saw Crystal Clear example of the sort of filtering
Acceptable to be on his show
This is a common thing to like
Alex will conveniently pretend to not be aware of certain things about figures he's trying to support
False
Slightly out of his good graces he magically knows about all the things that should have been a big problem for him before
We saw another glaring example of this with Bill Barr who Alex love but then when he wouldn't back Trump's nonsense at the end of his present
Alex suddenly had information about bars families ties to Epstein that never come up before
This is filtered and produced
It just appears to not be any of those things because Alex is too lazy to prepare so we have to fill his show with pointless
And his imagination is disgusting
Rambling about grotesque topics for long stretches
Glad to see I'm rocking out to a little All Along the Watchtower though
It's kind of interesting to really go back in time and think about how much of that type of music
Blue people's minds
Right yeah like
Adele
Nothing to me like music
Way Beyond that I used to I used to think about that quite a bit like the idea of
This being played on the radio first times you heard it
How could you get you were listening to f****** clog dancing before that and then all the sudden
It happened of course you're more than welcome over to Baba O'Riley
Fiddle player before this happened and now you're like Aleisha what am I doing in this small town
Oversimplifying things a little bit but yeah that wonder is kind of like
It's team
Maybe it's just because it's something that is inaccessible to us and something outside of our life experience
Imagining
You know what it is to it
To desire in a
To go back to a monoculture
Sure
It's like everybody was connected by hearing these songs on the radio
There was there was this thing that that everybody
Was experiencing
Your cohort stagedoor
You saying I'm going to throw up more towards like I'm longing for the days whenever a discovery was more like
You know
Pythagoras discovered a square + b square you know what it's like holyshit
Nobody's going to discover anything for like a thousand years after that you know
So with All Along the Watchtower
Nobody hurts it like that before you know but whatever Kanye comes out with
Jesus walks
Great
Awesome
Epoch changing but it's not like back then
Because we already had All Along the Watchtower If I Didn't Have Jesus Walks you know I can still listen to that chicken
Have anything
Nothing
Wasted
It's it was all just nothing and then Jimi Hendrix Came Upon
And I believe that the
The cover of about that
Another version of his phone already
Your your your point make sense
Alex is so dumb and boring that we end up
Being interested on going down that road
News story that I think we'll probably be his main focus
For today
Let me just do this let me just get me the main stack headline going to plow through Mall
Yes
They put out a press release yesterday
Podcastone
Pause swabbing others
And I have declared their number one enemy
Infowars
110,000
Information Warriors
Where we heard that term before the info lawyers
The people
I mean
Man
Really scared of us
Not just me
What
The fact that we've got the Death Star plans
How big big if true
Yesterday
Yeah just press release
A lot of Agents
41 Pressler
That's true
Are they able to find the story that Alex is talking
I'm about and it's an article in news punch about the world economic Forum hiring 110,000 people to combat missing for
Information on social media
This was a post those published on August 17th 2022 and it's based on a video published by a channel called the people
Kohl's voice
This is just like a junior varsity has Infowars Channel on YouTube main sources of podcast the world economic forum
Featuring the UN communications director Melissa
Fleming
She never mentions Infowars being class Schwab's number one enemy though she
She does discuss efforts they were taking
King to push back against misinformation
The first one she mentions is called
Verified
Which is done with the help of a communication
Confirm and it was an effort
To take solid information and put it into formats Adobe
Easy to share on social media
The concern was that so much of the actual information that you could have was buried and inaccessible p
PDFs enlarge documents
Misinformation is packed
Skitzo Sewickley and it's optimized for engagement
That's the entire business model for misinformation so that the primary
Concern for them
Where's the folks at the UN where baby
Behind on making the information that was provided good
For posting well I mean there
Fundamental issue is
Is that they're running up against
Learning is hard and chocolate is
Delicious
Yeah yeah
Essentially
Another initiative they were launching this called
Pause where they were trying to spread the message that
You should stop at
Think before reposting something that seems too good to be
Be true
It excites you so you want to post it but maybe it's b*******
Take a second to think about
You still want to share it once that adrenaline wears off go ahead
Apparently the belief is that encouraging the sort of behavior would cut down drastically on nonsense posting
I'm skeptical but
Mansion oh maybe it couldn't hurt
She also does say that they've recruited 110,000 information volunteers who are applying these kinds of practices at
Introducing good information
An intern misinformation space
I guess I would consider that information Warfare
He's right but I also think it is
Defensive in nature
All that being said yes was released
In November 2020
This is not news article as if it is
And because Alex has no idea what he's talking about
Thinks it's news to
Only he'd listen to Fleming's advice about
Before you repost something
Ironically maybe he would have gotten the story a little closer to Accurate as possible
Possible
I mean I was wondering
Here's my problem
They're okay
Dependa
You know with the news punch then came the world economic Forum just
Hire 100,000 people the volunteers
No that's what I'm saying
That's my big issue with that is like what are you talking about nobody has just the kind of cash
Surround at 110,000 let alone the world economic
For a bit and I'm willing to bet that a lot of this
Is Fairleigh unofficial
Some of this is just like
People signed some kind of a pledge
Some sort of a symbolic pledge percent accurate thank God for that
But I mean Alex is getting a lot of mileage out of this
2 year old
Podcast
Heard yesterday.
2 years old
Not good
So we get to stelter here at Alex's in a mood
We have some celebratory things
Here to make fun of
Brian stelter who already had no viewers so we already at show is already cancelled
If no one's watching
Local radio shows
Millions and millions and millions of listeners
How many viewers in its it's
Zombie broadcast
I think this is
Sad
You can't even really muster the energy to dance on filters grave
It said that
Yeah but you know what your greatest thing ever
Alright you can't be happy when your nemesis
This is gone because your nemesis
This is what
Juice to the heights that you couldn't have reached without said nemesis
That's true
It's not a formal anime an anime
Defeat but stelter
Filter was a man among men
We are about to play I want to play a clip a little bit later Alex
Repeatedly yelling at stelter is Anna
So okay well maybe I did my best
I get what you're saying though you have more of a bond with arch-nemesis will you have a bond with a t
Well I won't have him to pay
Around anymore there's probably disappoint like
When Alex doesn't have like a democrat in office or whatever it doesn't have
Easy tool
Give me a little bit harder for him
M2
I do deal with Wolf Blitzer and must be a must be Bittersweet it must be a bitter
Sweet feeling to know that you've perhaps outlived year-old
You're still an old waste
Stickman yourself Drew
We're going to get into a little bit of coverage that Alex has about monkey
And I'm just going to give a little bit of this is pretty intensely homophobic
And I would I expect
Yeah pretty pretty bad
By the way
Man having hundreds of sexual partners a month
We want you to go under lockdown we want you to wear masks
But we want to continue
You better wear a mask
But
These men can get together and give each other too much of diseases dis
Gaston
That's not good
Glenn Greenwald and Joe Rogan who look scary water for Alex like that
Kind of messages they're steering people towards
It's because that's pretty pretty cool
Yeah that's great
Well it is true that the available information does indicate that man who have sex with men
In the cases of monkeypox that have been identified at this point the way Alex is covering this
Is unacceptable and is essentially no different than the rhetoric you would have heard him spout in the early days of AIDS
Yep he hasn't intense the same for the lgbtq community
But he knows it's unfashionable to just be honest about that so he finds other stories he can use as cover to
Expresses hate
An important point about this whole dynamic comes up in a CNBC article
About 98% of patients Who provided demographic information
The Clinic's identified as men who have sex with men according to
To the CDC
That's not necessarily saying that 98% of people who have contracted monkeypox are men who have sex with men
There may be a percentage of people who sought treatment who did not provide that demographic
Information
That's said it would be slightly dishonest
To say that there's not something
Statistically relevant
There do appear to be increase rates in the community of gay and bisexual men
It's dangerous.
To create this Association
And even more dangerous
2 / 10.8
It's just an STD
It's a complicated situation
The people like Alex acting like this
They're going to get innocent people
I am.
What he wants
Incidentally there's no call for monkeypox lockdown
And in fact the reality is just the opposite of what Alex
The same
Tewodros the head of the World Health Organization said this
At the end of last month
Quote
Remember who have sex with men
This includes for the moment reducing your number of sexual partners
Reconsidering sex with new partners and exchanging contact details of any new partners to enable follow-up if
Alex hates the lgbtq
Kiki community so he makes up here to attack them with
Things they paint him as the victim mmse privileged class
Who the system wouldn't dare even suggest inconveniencing
He's pretending that the government is going to force a good people like himself to lockdown over monkeypox but they would even think of suggest
Behavioral advice
The game Madden
This is complete b******* because the World Health Organization has a goal to dealing with the outbreak by serving the people who are affected by
To minimize any
Stigma
It's going to leave that discrimination
Conversely Alex's goalies that discrimination itself
So furthering that goal is not best served by dealing with what the World Health Organization is actually doing
Fake storyline that conforms
Do your persecution complex
And it's complete
Yeah
Yeah I mean
First off
Only Wilt Chamberlain is headhunter
Did the partners in a
Let's start bright
Even if you want to take that and ground it a little bit
Close contact that can spread monkey
Gearbox
Is that something you need 100 partners
Absolute
You can have you could go on a date with somebody and have a great time
Even used condoms
Conceivably
And still
They contracted from
Skin-to-skin contact or eating is what happens whenever you have
Community that is isolated due to ship
Any disease breaks out in an isolated community
It is going to break out of that Community eventually but as it stands right now the only reason that it's
Stuck there is because of a discrimination that's already inherent in the f****** sister
Like this is a self-made creation
Again
Always
Yeah frustrate
There's a there's also a self-fulfilling this that Alex's
Kind of working
The night is that his actions
And a lot of the rhetoric that he's putting out either you would do
If you wanted the disease to spread for at the beginning he must have been paid for
Baikoko
I mean it that's the only explanation is that he was working Florida when we are subsidized by covid
Is is it possible for a virus to like
Congeal together a personality long enough to pay Alex 50 million dollars in order to spread itself
I don't think so but it is it is possible that's what's happening
It's worse even
Let's say about that's great
Absolutely disgusting
Sexual
Homosexual
Lick toilet bowls at the airport
Or you're going to go to a grocery store without a mask
Spit on people
Because he's gay
Because what you're doing
Keep doing it
Reality
Liberal
All about they can do whatever they want
We got to just put up with this
So yeah Rogan
How you feel about Alex
Suggesting that
There's a connection between being gay and raping dogs
Motherfuker
Haha
Years
Multiple years
Bitched and whined about having to wear a mask
To stop
Spreading disease
And now they're going to wring their hands at all my God
Someone spreading disease doing something I don't like instead of going into random stranger's home and spitting all over there
Coughing in front of somebody in Atlanta airport had an abortion
Play all of this s***
They are disease-ridden horror monsters
And they're going to come at me with this b*******
That's very
It is
It's very frustrating I'm more frustrated by the
Aggressive
Buddy buddies Express
Write everything that he says
Webcert
Awful
F****** awful
It is
Alex
It's you
Postage
Online
If I can swap
Publicly declares an information Warfare operation
Warriors
How old are you
As the army of Infowars
Information Warfare
How do you understand
If I were doing because
I don't want to be the best in the
That good
L
Bolsonaro
But you know what the enemy
As the number one anime
I told you 20 years ago
Oh my God
God showed me the future
You ready for this
Floating
Oh yes I accept the mission
Commissioned by God for this war
Wow yeah I know this seems like somebody who's like
So much
More reliable than the mainstream media
Yeah this is a guy who you go to
To cut through the b*******
I mean Jake and Elwood Blues were busy
So God had to commission a different a****** for this job
Saving a bunch of children
Orphanage doing a concert
I think it's fine
This is a little bit different maybe a little bit
So look out this podcast
Did he didn't yesterday play Warriors ago
Explain to you why
Here we are
The New World Order
Well the world economic Forum which is the mouth of the new world order the mouth
The mouthless lame-ass
Spokesperson
For evil
Has come out and said that
World
Continual
Enforced injection failed
There's a total rejection
Across-the-board
Billions of rotting poison
MRNA gene therapy
Sure
Is a declaration
Of War
Next
Mobile
Censorship
With 100,000
Volunteers
Inside media
An army of
Brian stelter Humpty Dumpty
Pennywise
Brian stelter
So filter Humpty Dumpty
Pennywise's
Is a barrage of imagery
Brings up something that I want to stress for a second
A lot is made of how Alex's make stuff up all the time
And rightfully so
Uber Eats
Peter recognize that he does more than just make up details and lie about concrete
He also writes stories out of these fake facts
That are necessary to
Explain them within the context of his made-up world
Winston's here Alex has this headline that he's done zero investigation into that he's presenting as the world economic
Form declaring war on Infowars
They hiring 110,000
Information Volvo
Want to use the counter missing
Information
In order to bolster the story he needs to connected to some of his larger storyline
In order to embellish the story
Alex says that the world economic forum is doing this
Because there's so many shots
But no one wants to
Taking all the anti-vax people are winning the war of ideas
So they enlisted in the Army too
Crush anti-vax voices like out
This is running a disinformation campaign against a campaign meant to fight misinformation
What is really don't like fact checker
Yeah I mean why would you not
What's critical here is it Alex's making up of the wife or the story out of thin air
He's got a piece of information
110,000 volunteers thing
But he has literally no other details about this story so he's just making it up
He doesn't realize this was a story from November 2020 before any of the vaccines or even available which is
Kind of sad
In order to make sense of why the world economic Forum would be
Be doing this
The present-day as Alex thinks they are
He just falls back on what version of this story would be most emotionally satisfying for himself and the audio
That's why the rationale for their alleged action is that Alex's side is too successful and they have all these expiring vex
Seems that no one wants
This explanation is a fiction that creates a sense of victory for the listeners and more importantly it frames their online
Activity is a critical part of the
Fight against the world economic forum
Information volunteers
Promoting Alex's contact isn't just about getting new people into his revenue streams and selling his dumb pills
Actually fighting back
Sam's Club Schwab cyber Army who would be enlisted because you all were
You're too powerful
With your previous posting
Alex's content
Really well for Alex on a couple of runs but it's completely made up
The simple detail the podcast but this is the basis that the basis for the
This entire story came out in November 2020 review
Old to just be s*** that Alex is making up to
Stroke is oneco
I'm convinced the listeners to continue working as his unpaid social media
Wild yeah I mean it is it is a little bit like somebody took a ren-faire too far
And it's just now his full life
You know just everyday is the Ren Faire
And whenever something like if somebody brings a
Phone in there they got to retcon the entire Ren Faire
To make sense of the phone being inside
And then every time you add a new thing now we're in a cyberpunk
Ren-faire it so now we've got God over there like it's just a bigger and bigger unfair
I was not listening
To you because I started
Think about Renfield rent
What would that look like
Maura Ren Faire
Enfield Ren Faire Brookfield
Regulate
I got distracted by wordplay
Hear Alex play the clip of that podcast
Start again
Is 2 years old
Wef announcers for recruitment of 110,000 information Warriors close Club
Infowars
We specifically in their documents are named
And others
Resisting
Design planetary collapse
Short clip of the
The wef spokesperson just
Verified unpause campaign entails
Also
Recruiting people around the world and so far we've recruited 100
Thousand
Information
Volunteers
This is all I mean it's just an elaborate
Fiction based on
Alex
Looking into
To the story that he's telling
Yeah
It's sad that we have any follow-up on these volunteers like it whenever she announces we got 110,000 vets
10000 people signed up did anybody actually
Do f*** off know but I know we didn't solve disinformation in the past 2 years
But I did see a recent thread on the conspiracy subreddit the people were like
Oh that explains all the shoes commented recently
Recently
Because they didn't look into it either course not they just saw this newspunch article that I got time
The date on the article is recent so
All the shells
When will the chills stop Shilling dad it relieved also brings it to Sharp
Focus the idea of what a joke
Notion of
Critical thinking
In conspiracy and like
Alex Jones e communities are
What did you did any of these did any of these folks
And their great leader Alex
Stop to ask themselves what
The context of this
Is there is there an actual story here what no
It's convenient
What you want
Tip to say you will not only accepted as real Andrew and current
You'll embellishing makeup details about it to make it even more perfect
Refrigerator
For your ego
I do appreciate
Anybody who gets an instant and a piece of information and then instantly is like
Well that explains this other thing that it doesn't have anything to do
Because there's nothing in between
You think there would be something in between but now you're just like that
That explains back
My world make sense
So Alex is mad at Sam Harris
Because if you want to talk about a Rosetta Stone
If you want to talk about something that really illustrates who we're up against and there
Hubris
Smugness
Bravado
You are wasting
Supposed
Dark web intellectual leftist
Course we censor conservatives conspiracy
Prompto dangerous
Sam Harris is in charge of all Media or whatever I don't I don't really care
But one of the things that Sam Harris was talking about was that
The corruption
That it got
You can find with vitamin
Hunter Biden share
It doesn't come anywhere close to what Trump
Is involved so
These kinds of arguments about the corruption in the
Concerns about it
Our kind of
Weird and dumb one of the things he brings up his Trump University and Jean to that
Sure thing really quick
According to Ali
Alex is worldview
The crimes of the bidens
Are much greater than Trump
Of course in the real world
Well
Not really
So much so is Alex's comparing Trump
University
What's the fake
Imaginary version of Ida
Then
Yes Trump University not that bad
In the real world
Trump looks pretty shity
He does and that's kind of the the detention does it play in this clip
Shity like shady Delaware s*** that he's been doing for the whole time Lego credit card companies don't have to pay Bubba
That's corrupt I get it but that still isn't
I got nuclear Secret side my house
Yeah I'm not a little different I'm not saying anything to like
Get let Biden off the hook for any corrupt
I'm just saying that he didn't
Kill kids in a basement in this clip
Gets really defensive about how we didn't go to
Nothing but you can do
The basement is of children
Compromised by foreign powers
Trump University
Weekends with Trump and top experts
Brainstorming and
High School
I went and got a job selling memberships
At a gym
$100,000 a year
When I was 9
Sports car
Nice two-bedroom
I was having the time of my life
Top dollar
3 years ago
Dolartoday
I was nineteen years old making a hundred plus thousand dollars a year
Working 4 hours a day
And I look good
And people bought the membership especially the women
Is that
A few times a day
I love herself Punjab
The point is
What is that
What is a happening
That that was a real value
That experience was real I should have paid to be a Salesman
Club
I mean
One of the hottest jams and also the time
Ensure
Memberships business about Sam Harris remember
Loser no
But that doesn't even matter
What are you getting at
Real Smogon
Nnnnn say yeah
You know
The number one evil of trump is his Trump University
As you're probably sitting in a chair
Happening
Alex's I mean luck II
I think
Vets
Fairly important to recognize that not everybody does need to go to college
Higher education
That's fantastic
I'm a big proponent of it but I don't think
That people should
Ashamed for not going to college at 9
The people learning a trade is
Is pretty fantastic
A lot of people find
A great deal of happiness
Great
So I just want to put that to the side just because I don't want to be like
Shiting on Alex
You're not going
College ranking
But he really is
I like insecure
Oh yeah
Very much what being expressed here is very much a feeling of
Why does everyone think he's so smart
I mean it is I mean maybe because he doesn't go into
Chit like his monkeypox nonsense
Right inlets
Before we go any further
Alright let's start with the easy smart thing to do
Don't defend Trump University lawsuit you don't even have to just say that sucks I have another smart
Things you could do
Not talk
Constantly about Visions from God
Defending Trump University is free that's true no downside to not defending University
There is a downside to defending Trump University which is where you go onto this
Weird tangent about how you f*** good when you were in when you work today
A club that's it
I also think
That maybe could use some examining on Alex's part
Is how he never stopped being a sales
Journalist or anything like that he is still just a Salesman
Dumbbells
Song is this
Vuori
That's really
Primary product
Yeah he sells you the worldview you internalized that worldview and it creates needs
Vicky can fill for you
There is a cult
Nothing that somebody would find unfamiliar if they just listen to like a whole richdadpoordad series and then watch.
Alex Jones Excel said maybe like
Oh yeah I know I didn't
Are you going to drop University
Actually I think you would get you don't get sales Gildan Trump University you get sold
You get caught
Sue stelter got cancer
Let's spend some time
Bryan Stow
Is a joke
But he had 100,000 viewers
For cable news that's not even a pulse
I got you was good
Fishes
Self
Serving arrogant
He was the most
Mug
Shemagh
Lake pomposity
And something million dollars
Plus it
What's the number
So there's a lot of theories about exactly why stelter and reliable sources got canceled
Precise reasons are but I think everyone is
Pretty comfortable with the idea that it's
Part of the aftermath of the Warner Brothers Discovery merger
That was finalized back in
Also it's a consummate throughout their properties like hbomax
And this is actually part of a larger story about big corporate Media consolidation but Alex is completely missing the
For the trees
He hates Brian stelter and the story he wants
So tell about this is It's tell there's a failure who got fired cuz nobody liked him and it showed no viewers
That's a story that's emotionally satisfying for Alex
And it's what the listeners Waunakee
The story doesn't matter cuz they use the tip of the spear he's the king of big Tech and media
Watchdog
Missing this entire life
What a great
Time for somebody like Alec
Text to like really dig into what happens whenever media is
Is monopolized and how
Powers-that-be
Whenever they be
Become a smaller group in a smaller number
All of them with control over the media a number of
Companies let's say
Smaller than 10
You know and those companies have CEOs and they all meet in back rooms
And they control the media literally
It would be a great time for somebody who is the conspiracy theorist
To talk about that
Well I think you're sounding a little bit I think that
There is a real wonderful opportunity for Alex here to rise above his
His enemies as it worth
Angie could instead of talk
What about seltzer
Put that aside cuz everyone knows he already doesn't like him at all desolated that be redundant for him just to do a little dance
Be like look
They're the sure we can all be happy about that but there's a bigger picture here and also it's actually a bad sign
Brian stelter
Got to show acts
It's a bad sign that hbomax has no streamlining and laying off all these people
Part of a
I love them
I know who's all coming together
That the story plays though you know that like
I would I would die today
Defend your I don't agree with what you say brister stelter
But I would die for your right to not be owned by one conglomerate
I demand that this man my mortal enemy
Be freed from his prison
Of corporate lock
That's there that's
That message
Plays everybody loves that s*** and it would be an impressive thing for Alex surprise
Mister stelter
The spirit guided me while you were
So eloquent
Some clips
Here here's an older clip
Love stelter that Brian event to Alec
We're doing this is your life
Not really I was just thinks there's a few that are like
These are Great Clips a Celtic
I think there's one
Okay so let's play the late great
The weather channel meteorologist
First let me bringing John Coleman he's in San Diego this morning
Thank you for being here
Tries to be on CNN hello to all your viewers are you busy
Denier
That is a word
And I want to make
I am he's the CEO of The Weather Channel now
The Weather Channel
The co-founder
Taking a very strong position
On global warming that is
Where is no consensus in science
Science is about
Kohl's back
There is no
In the future
There's a whole lot of baloney
The scientific
Conclusion
What I was when you see that
CNN
Hello everybody
Oh my bedroom
That clip actually kind of refute a lot of Alex's Boynton.
Mainstream media voices that descent with them on the air Dan
Right I mean it's actually one of the worst Clips Alex could have chosen
Play I know it's fun to hear someone be rude to tell her I guess that appeals to Alex in some way but it's actually
So counter to the the Eevee perception of media
Is essential
Who sell Infowars as the alternative
I mean he's literally saying
Thank you for letting me get my message across on the mainstream media and still there's being polite to this guy who's being a
Yeah and I can you
Imagine big reverse
Like stelter
Coming on Alex's showing being a dick to him and Alex being polite
You know I can't imagine that
No more famous nothing but a hostile platform to somebody who
Agrees with the media
Forbetterforworse
Often does have a
Deferential adjustable platform maybe not
Is vigorous debate as Alex would like which is
Damita translates people screaming at each other and saying disgusting s***
Call pedophiles and what have you
TV day
But I mean
Maybe told him to the different clip
I think this hurt you or argue
Yeah I mean it does
Help shelter
I think that's a fairly good clip to play for everybody to look at the media and
Just go like
We're not doing a good job whatever it is that is
That's not good
Certainly questions
Like
How did
Did you have any reason to suspect this is how Coleman was going to ask so maybe could have
Prepared to
Field him being a dick
You got a mute button
Anyway Alex
Instead of really celebrating stelter
He decides he's going to play
Some old clips he's reminiscing about his enemy
Kind of but also about
How much you yelled at smelter
Navel gazing reminiscing
Check
Brian stelter there it is oh my
Movie cover
You're looking at it the clown I mean would you let your children
Anywhere near that it
Right there
Stranger danger
I am your enemy
I would literally
Spirit
Tried to jump photos like sistalook disingenuous
Pull it off
Oh my gosh
Hell on Earth
He wants to run your life he wants to control every aspect of your life
Human
Crash
Electric
Literal
Demon spawn
Okay I'll look at it
And you know what
Better than you if you keep letting it run your life
He went to school ski runs the bank
Smiling
.
Fun
I like her music
Look in the background
Alex is older
The end of the show today
Thankfully there are these old clips of him putting a little
Gaston into his stelter hate
But this actually is a curious clip to play on the day after stelter shows been canceled that he's out at Siena
That's because of anything I was saying meant anything that it shouldn't have been so simple to remove him from his perch
This filters of the globalist
Platz if you can just be fired
Honestly knowing that stelter was just asked over business considerations and it didn't cause widespread chaos
Chaos among the global
Who makes this entire presentation
Seem pretty stupid
It seems so weird to hear how works up Alex was about stelter these clips now they were on the other side because now that
Shelter is out
Just seems like a worked up baby who is so mad that someone is criticizing him that he decided to make up a bunch of stuff about
Being Central to the globalist plans
I like this isn't even the full rent it goes on
Ingenuity
You will pay
Sally's
Get yourself together gun
Suzanne illustrative moment
Alex has any connection to reality
It's just Alex trying to put
Some kind of an elevated appearance onto his
Petulant anger
He knows well enough that if he got on his show and started yelling and lashing out about how he doesn't like people being critical of him his
Elysium is the week child he is inside
I'm asking that immature insecurity with over-the-top pronouncements about
Stelter
Probably being a pedophile and how he's a betrayer
Never that means Alex is able to protect himself from being seen for what he is which is a hypersensitive loser
The issue is that the audience doesn't really realize that they're just watching Ali
Let's play out-of-cycle drama about his own hurt
Feelings
They form opinions
Postings on social media and even harassed Elder over things that Alex says
As if there was anything behind it other than Alex being a baby with a boo-boo
Anyway I probably would have played a different clip on this episode
Symptoms for traced Elders I'm kind of a big high-level big bad guy the day after his show ended with no real pushback or fan
Victory if anything Alex was saying that anything
And this is kind of a grandiose
Here's the problem when you choose your
As you know to be
That did not demonic Realm
You know
Like you think TV is a great choice cuz it's so big and it's so you do like all its
TV but it's really not that big
As it's not as big as you might think
Cuz you can just get by
You can't
Claimed that the
If you
Didn't get the job at a Denny's you can't claim that the manager is the Antichrist
Cuz eventually he's just not going to be the manager anymore
The manager can't be the manager is like the shift
Supervisor might even
I used to work at a Dairy Queen
When I was like 15 about the burger guy
Is a Satanist
Well yeah that's great so
Counterpoint
Now you brought that piece of information to light I do retractor
Take that
So Alex just play that old stelter needs feeling good about it
You got up asking your work
No it reminded me of that time that you remember Hannibal's
Betway played his own joke
I Just Vibe with it has reminded me about quite a bit
Alex
That is shown in the newsrooms for years
As
Adult
That is required viewing at least once a week
Cold turkey
Brainwashing
I made it honestly I don't believe it
It's true but if it is
Or
They're laughing at him
Yeah I mean I think I feel like as far as like ways to end your 5 on a Friday you know instead of
Doing the whistle you just start playing that clip and you're not if you're going to leave with a bit of a smile
Alright I think I can go get drinks out really funny to you because you haven't heard
Long time
Really annoying you know I don't think you watch it every week but you play it over the PA
All of
Tucker's employees have to watch this once a week so they can
You keep their head in
The game
Sure can understand what it's like to watch me
Fake being nauseous looking at Smelter Demon
Key grip do I really need to yes
No but I mean all
Singer contract
Dammit
Hate the show
Yep
Hannity's people after watching once a month that's why they're not so hard for
Caller calls in and wants to know how Alex
The time to read so much
This is a bummer
I want to say I'm very excited when your new book comes out
Out of the end of the month now I admit
But I normally read
Candlebox
Hylian
Addicted to the internet
How many of us are
I can't wait to read
Have an epiphany that
Informational admit I'm in a trance
Ovolo attention
Now you read so much
How much information I would love
If you could share with me and the audience
Are you fine so much time to read
Suggestions on how we can use the internet
That use our self
In a way that promotes enlightenment
Also way to promote
What's a long-term
Do you get Siri or however you recommend
Take the time to read entire books
Do we have a
Free Sunday
Get away from the internet how do you recommend kids
Strong party information War
Manage information
Have the same programs over and over again so once you know their operation
You just see the same permutation of it over and over again so that's not hard
Only a few dozen things.
There's only a few dozen plays
So this reminds me of a conversation I had with a comic years ago who was really proud of their ability to do crowd work
Didn't respond to hecklers
In reality they weren't that good but they were very confident
A few possible types of responses you need to be ready to hatch
You can respond to something with an angry / meme retort a nice retort or a confused
As long as you had one of each of these in your pocket ready to go you could respond to just about anything an audience
Can proactively rock-paper-scissors theory of stand-up comedy
Is taking the act of responding in the moment on stage and reducing it to a parlor trick
You're creating the illusion of being in the moment and fast on your feet
You're faking being clever because you know that you weren't clever enough to be it for real and you're terrified of being seen
You guys not clever
And getting caught in the moment of being like
This is kind of what Alex is doing with his globalist Playbook idea
He's constructed a couple of stock responses to world events
That he's decided
Call The globalist Playbook and it's basically just his crotch so he never asked to appear like he doesn't know what's going on
Think of a tragic event has the equivalent of someone heckling
In terms of how to interpret Alex's show and the narrative
He needs to be able to respond to it quickly or else he'll risk showing week
Cast of the audience
Comic I knew Alex's pre-loaded response
Has to stop
Instead of angry nicer confused retort
Alex has things like
False flag it was secretly antifa or
Elaborate
State Plata
These are go to responses he can whip out to apply to any situation
Play Mika then rationalize based on
Some detailed be like oh this is part of that Global display
Means nothing
Alex has nothing to say she hasn't read anything
It's pretty telling that this guy asked this question and now it's his first response isn't that he reads all day everyday because
He would know that that silly
His response is just that he knows everything already so we can see things happening in the world then make stories up about them
Considering his track record of being super wrong about almost everything he's ever called
Play From The globalist Playbook this should really worried the caller in the audience
But they're not paying attention
Alex satisfies their emotional needs with ramps like the one about stelter and their need to feel like
A part of something important
With the nonsense about
Fighting close Schwab's digital Army by posting info
As long as those needs are met and as long as that's the case
The reality of it is just making
Shut up all the time it doesn't really matter at all
The audience will never care or
Yeah that
That caller
Scares me
A lot
Because
He sounded so rational and so sane
And had a
Clear thought process
But if you listen to that
That's the most
Insane thing anybody's ever said
That's the most insane Alex reads A Lot Alex reads a lot like a thing to say to a
Alex strauts insane then
I swear to you I would rather
I believe more that Raptors would eat
Chocolate then I do that Alex reads When You Believe
Chicken fried steak believe the second one more than Alex reads the second one is possible
Yeah because Alex is a passive
Participate
Speak their chicken fried steak chicken fried steak Alex would work out a deal with
Company
For advertise
Really good
Love message
Goddamn
So Alex goes on to explain his work process to this caller
Really
Legislation
I go and look at 1
Paul's
Address quickly
Reading their bugs reading class Schwab statement in knowing what they're doing
Books
Written by the population controllers
Henry Kissinger
Program
Wallace
Collapse of society
Seems to be a huge red flags anybody was listening Galaxy
I mean like he has basically these old Tech
But I don't know if he's even read or not or is he's just like
Taking them in by way of like John Birch Society literature the demon eyes those but I think that's more likely
Part of the Lord actually read yes
He talks about like ecoscience by John Beholder never read that f****** textbook
Out of here
His work clothes just like I skinned my own website
Dim some other websites
And then I go check the Twitter accounts of s*** heads like pasovic
I mean
That's not great
In the context of the rationality of the question that he is responding to which I do I mean
Idea Lego should we have a Cyber Sunday where we get rid of all of our things and actually just hungry butt face
Really fun with that
To respond to that with
Here's what I do
Ice Kim s***
And then I just kind of get the vibe of how people are talking about it and then
Putting out talking
Double down on the finger-post remix
And that's my job
And I started the day by looking at my own website to pay people to write
Headlines for responding to people who are paid to write things that will tickle me
Yeah that's a bizarre Circle
I did is I created is like okay
Do you remember Elvis
This group of Yes man that always said yes around Elvis
Yeah yeah
Exactly
So I turned that into a job
Add job to say yes to everything I have to say
Alex gets to thinking about so like what he needs
To do
And there's one thing that he needs
Read
Pray with us.
Appreciate what you doing
Jesus and I just want to remind people
Really is an answer
Operate
You got to do what you can
Salida prepare your house
Personal story right now
Valleyfair wants me to
Went to see my dad
Where we pray
Literally
Ours is a wrote you a check
But also men and women comedy
My father this weekend
Awakening
Because
I don't know all the ways of God but it's just
After did so much before us
Was your father or your mother
Connect to the people for you
My father
This this weekend
Adult
Confirm
Rrr
Particularly
All confirmed
Spiritual
About that
He's gone
Must have better service.
That place
Properly under attack
I was out with my dad
Backyard by pool
Remember he just put his hands in mine
Fujinaka flip songs.
.
We have to do that now
We made the circuit
Present
Power using that
New Jersey housing
What a ride
What a f****** rise fits the past present and future
Like your son have also been involved in the prayer he doesn't give a s*** about
Oh my God
This is
Okay I like to see the the idea that eventually
I mean I don't look
I don't wish this upon him or anything.
Then Alex will put put out a Luther Vandross Style
Pray with my father could dance with my father
Some prayers are on an album
I could pray with my father one more time man
That's what you do that's what Alex does deathbed prayers
Record them with his dad that'll give everybody the magical energy of a father ensured the closed-circuit absolu
Lutely with that with that closed-circuit energy
You got the money to be made my friend
Alex Wassabi
I will not be the past
Closed circuit
I will eat your soul you will not steal my Vitality of Youth
I just wanted to say like that
Coburg
Family that you talked about
They are an rh-negative bloodline
Ashley from you
Fallen angels
Falling
Right
They took over this
Saxons of Germany
The direction is right I think
Ukraine to Germany took over this
1 angels
Into
The actual
The true humans are the true Humanity
Bradford themselves into it
That's what I like
West Indian
Company in Fremont
The evil side of the America
Anderson Cooper
Dothan the Vanderbilts
Extension of the West Indies
That's why they needed
Get your product you know
Everything like that
And not smooth
Into a plug a that was pretty good
I mean here's why here's my take on this
Sir
That's too much
You know what
Normally I'm cool with
Conspiracy people
Imallexx
But that's too much You Got To Go's talk
Talk to somebody about the
Yeah
The saxe-coburg-gotha are fallen angels
Took over the anglos
Real human pictures of nephelym types.
And they had to go to the Netherlands
Right
And then
Maybe the West Indies company
The Dutch East India
Company I guess it's related to the
Vanderbilt's because they're both of Dutch.
Okay
I see I think we I think we nailed it no actually sir that's too much
Let's go talk to somebody East India Company dissolved
Around the time
Cornelius Vanderbilt
Founder of that family's great Fortune
Was a child
In the US
Right but didn't
The babe
Defeat the Anglo-Saxons
And then absorb them into their powers that's gaining
Angel and saxo Powers
I'm afraid you are much
I was bi wombat aliens
Yeah the wombat Is
So
Alex gets another call is a little spiritual
I enjoy your car so I look forward to receiving your product
Alice this is a message for all the infiltrators.
Bitia order
Carlos
Right now
Disposable Outlet
Sexualizing
In control
Alex Jones you have been chosen by our Lord
You are the milk
Of the body
You represent
Manipulate
They have been
Using tomato
Control
George Washington warned us against the
The power
Political parties
Nationality
We Are you standing up against movie happy
The majority of the Mastiff support Infowars
Who are against you
I stand against the Masters
Because we are using
The Powerball
Communication
Do you make a plow swab the information Warfare against us
He's going to launch info Warriors
Yeah they off minute totally
Pegasus guy doesn't know that it's two years old
All of the Lord of pet did you ever notice how the Lord is
Exactly as dumb as the person talking about him the deity has the information that the individual
Potter County
Only knows what
The Lord wants him to know cuz download The Departed upon him
Yeah good call Lord you got me on this one so apparently Alex has chosen as a leader by God
The majority of the United States supports Infowars
That's
Absolutely. Seems like a lot
For the message to see if my experience obviously
Professionally
You can't really judge
The temperature of Alex
Cuz I run in circles that are pretty a Infowars
Naturally
And so I ain't I put that to the side
Number of people that I interact with just you know whether it's
Somebody in a in a service capacity or
You know
Just a random person and generally
Anybody asked me
And sometimes Lyft drivers
I've been there like what I do
And I'll explain it and usually it's
Alex Jones who
Like most of the guy in Austin who is
The masses have really not
Just a low level of support for Alex so much
Because they have no idea who that motherfuker is in Austin
Sticks out in the memory because he was the one person that I've encountered in the wild
Really that's a has-been what who is a supporter
I think generally it's people who have no idea
M-maybe wood
Black guy
Is that guy who likes
Big Trump guy
Yeah it was a January 6th through something you don't like
This is not Star-Lord he is a character actor in the show.
Yeah yeah
Appointed leader to his fans right
F****** child with a boo-boo
YouTube most people who
Buy pay attention
I thought it's not a gas
I thought I guess
Caesar employee
He's a guy who works at
Does Alex know that
With the rotating cast of people that he knows for sure because Greg Reese
People Alex places reports all the time on the show
Each one is the best
That's ever been made
And if you go to video you'll find that his videos get
Significantly more traffic then
Even like Owen or
Harrison Smith
Soleil
Alex is somebody who is
Nothing if not motivated by traction true
Greg gets a firebox
Videos are pretty slick Lee done
Pacey shows competence
In certain aspects
I went to that
I wouldn't say that
Maybe in terms of editing
Like there's some kompa
Since they are
Jarring to listen to
Is just stupid
He has an idea
I want to see if you can come up with some ways this idea might go bad
I think everyone in the world is starting to wake up to that fact right now
That the Federal Reserve fiat currency system is with responsible
All the problems in the world right now
People talking about
Silver and gold mines
Going into private business as Bank since they have the vault already and they
Tire crypto card to
Gold and silver
And then
The private Market
Free private Market can just compete for people's trust and
Serviceability and
Start creating a parallel banking system
Z12
Call Susan idea of some type of
Digital
Fiat currency is if
I mean only
Take after all of the death and destruction they've caused four decades and decades
That's obviously the plan
How to get 8 million in Bitcoin
Look
Did this is a dumb idea
You don't understand
He just invented mining town
It makes perfect sense
Alright
Here's what we do all right we go all the way to the West
Okay we get a covered wagon together we get all buds
Together we build a little tent
We open up our own
General Store around the mind and people will pay us with the gold that they recently banned
Out of the river
The only people could really afford to run that store anyway are the people around the vibe so you know
So I think that's a great idea they should
Actually
Give their own currency out
That is a big guarantee using their money so you can
Can only buy the stuff I think that's
Yeah this is my booth
This is wild I mean also
Just
Logistically
I think the people who have a lot of resources
Right now are going to be able to buy those mines
I think you'll end up with
Probably oligarch
Mine back
Yeah
Who will be able to babysit
Unregulated by the way this is that's also
Definitely an implied part of the system Arizona
There's so many opportunities for abuse of the system
It's just it's almost
Parody of itself
Tech Bros
And all those stupid people invent things that we already invented a long time ago and then I put a new name on it
I really don't appreciate it whenever we do have like a history
Where people did the
Step-by-step
Sing that you're recommending
And you can go back and you can read about how it turned out
You can just read about it it happened before
Stop doing it that bad thing we did that led to everybody dying in the Great
Depression and all that s***
Hahaha but what
But if we did it again
So Greg's at another dumb thing to say chair
Big picture your smart guy
Lies
I think the test is clear I think that they were being offered
It's offering except
They've been doing this for years they're offering us
Slavery
They actually started offer a slavery
Years ago I think I started at 6019 right after the Revolutionary run there
Broke his back into it
And
Ultimately it's our choice ultimately we don't we don't have to be slaves we could actually
Become independent become responsible
The offering you slavery that's not really slavery and back at the Revolutionary War
Not offer flavors
Generations
Talking about these people
It's just so amazing being offered slaver
You get to see
How is that allowed
Infowars
Pedo Island
People who like the same preferred good not going to college I swear to God you should
Ashamed for not
Reading comprehension in 4th grade
That's what should be happy
I think that they can read and there's some reading comprehension there's just
I don't know what you're reading
Yeah maybe you're just reading s*** wingdings
Read a real book it's just a bunch of it's like who
It's like what
Bork
You're just suspicious of everything you read until like when you read a line that says X you like
Trick me into thinking and actually saying is why
Why is it that nobody believes in the Double Bluff of book
So you know they're like they think you're tricking you
But they're actually telling the truth it's a double blah blah blah
Researcher
Great minds
Gregory's
We're going to win this because you can see it at the way they've had this thing whole plan
They weren't expecting this much
Push back expecting this much
Define
Expecting more people to take the vaccine
Which tells me that
2000 Infowars
Right right
I mean it
Just going along with Alex's bulshit story about a two-year-old podcast that he's now saying Klaus Schwab said
He had all about himself which wasn't
The case
Solely with
The idea of misinformation
And yeah Gregory's so just going along to get along
Yeah
Yeah that is such a weird
Example of
Total capture
Just like
Hey the sky is orange
Disguise
Just Orange
Green and orange striped Lycra
The flag
Wow there is no bottom
None
Fox capture
So
These people love
So into individualism
They think that you
You are the greatest thing and God is like
Working through you
And that's why they do whatever Alex tells them
To do individuality
And also maybe some people are so dumb that we need leaders
You know 34 years ago that we need leadership I might have argued that
But after seeing covid
And realizing that a large amount of the population is
Sheep-like
We need fruit
How to respect and love for our fellow man we do need leadership
Is there going to be
Not control them but leave the Good Shepherd
That's what we have to
2B we want people to be independent believe themselves but if they believe things that are different to what rise
We must for their own good leave
Them
That's a good shepherd
Yeah no I don't understand why people don't understand that religion is great
If people don't believe what you have to say you torture them until they do benevolence Orchard
It's the way that God meant things to run
The lord gave me a message
And to be fair I mean I do think that we need to leadership as well not because I think
People are too dumb to leave themselves or anything share I think that there are other benefits
Put Wii game
Through leadership
Things like Morales
Things like feeling
Connected to each other
Sure they're all kinds of
Benefits but the way they're looking at it has a real
Patronizing
U of A
Just the public
Makes sense
I don't care about people it'll think people are great
So they don't want somebody who's the leader who's going to listen to the people who's going to synthesize it for
Probation and then ultimately is going to take responsibility for that
Decision
They make
No that's called leader
Providing a message that people can rally behind other form of leadership you could
Consider would be something along the lines of
A iron fist
The dictatorship
Now is that leadership
That's a good shepherd well it's a shepherd of sorts ineffective Shepherd
So you like beef
Not if it's shepherded wrong well Alex Lowe's beef
Is actually one of the most nutritious
It's the sacred cow it's a life-sustaining
Because it's consumed
Bible Genesis
Along with whatever just whatever
So I think
Greg is trying to point to the idea that cows are sacred in Hindu culture which is dumb because there's
Specifically
Like your day they don't
Slaughter and eat cows because they're
Sacred cow because beef is delicious
Good love it
This is mistaken
Not start by talking about beef
It's what's for dinner saith the Lord it starts with God existing an ovoid formless nothingness
Creating the Earth in light and all that stuff
It's not until Genesis 1:24 that land animals are created after vegetable
Fulshear
But humans are said to be Lords over the natural world
Interesting Lee though God does say quote I give you every seed-bearing plant on the face of the whole earth and every tree that
Has fruit with
Seed in it
They will be yours for food
The Bible doesn't start with passage about beef and that's really embarrassing
A great just yes and that s***
Who cares I mean Max captures irony is that the first real discussion regarding beef
Ends with a murder
Better than
Facebook the first big like what's beef about
Murder
She's pretty obvious from
The sacred cow idea
And Drake a strong idea
Kind of but he actually even has a
Worst Rock
I'm doing the report
Has like vegetarianism is sort of connected to yoga
And there's a bunch of the popular and there's always be into that
Because if you actually look at the
That was based on the caste system
Vegetarians were just a lower caste
Please explain Street Glide
Save the meat for the opportunity
System where we're all these lower peasants eating bugs and then they can fly Ronnie Jets and have all the good
Stuff you know
Definitely some connections between the caste system and rates
Vegetarianism in traditional Indian culture but what Greg is doing is oversimplifying things in a way that is specifically designed
Took a one-to-one with modern-day Infowars talking points like how close Schwab wants you to eat bugs
Many of the lower classes in the caste system we're not
Practicing Hindu
So they wouldn't have been concerned with the dietary restrictions that largely sound
From Hindu beliefs and non-violence
Conversely many of the brahmins were actually you know their priests and members of the scholarly class
As you might expect they're what they were more observant people in terms of
The phenomenon you see when you look at historical Trends related to the caste system in vegetarianism
Is actually that the hire someone is in cash
The more likely they are to be vegetarian
So what Greg is saying but if this doesn't work for The Tile Shop
Schwab wants you to eat bugs being so
He's pretending that there is no Hindu belief in this
Do no harm thing that just trying to trick poor people into eating plan so they could save the cows for themselves
I do recall reading be apologizing thinking man this is all about how the Richmond
That's what it is
The argument that Greg is making his absurd
But the reality of this Dynamic is actually far more complicated than even the picture that I've described and I'm not doing Justice to the new
Nuances of
Of how this plays out in
Tradition
It's there's a lot of it has a history that is almost impossible to unravel
Credible
Very very complex notion that it's like
Tricking the
The poor people into eating vegetables
Vaccaro's for themselves for me
Wow write it on the board that sounds trophy scriptures in it
Scriptures
Greg Vader
Greg
Back to his time but
Getting it in for right
What he does here is he isolates
A real serious problem
When I first came here
You know 4 years ago
Very open-minded very skeptical of us suspicious suspicious person
Are you
Stories about
You know controlled opposition everything so who knows but I got here I was just basically
Call Dad
Story that I think is important and
And do my best to get right and stick to the truth and
That was it
Remember asking Robin told me that I was like
Should I show it to anyone first to make sure that it's proved and you just looked at me
Almost witness customs
We don't have time for that you know and it's true everyone out here we're working
Oh my God
My God you have no time for quality control
To see if it's full of s***
Wow
Spell process
Or can I at least trained with somebody
Boilerplate
Reliable sources
Control app for reliable sources of Infowars
Yeah I would think that one of the things
The code Aid Infowars the most actually
I take that back
Cuz it would completely destroy the process
You're misunderstanding their business would get on air
What are you
They would quit
I mean that's the thing that they really are you know we talked about how they're lying and they don't give a s*** and they're making everything up
But we're really not talking about is if they did it
Is any Challenge on the way to
To publishing one of those stories
They would give up and then do a
That's probably true and I think not only lie and make all this s*** up
They've also can
Instructed a system
Like
AIDs that system that is
Complicit and complementary to making s*** up
No no it is 8
It is a little bit like when you see Apes
Put a stick in in a tree and then ants come up and you're like
You guys figured that out all on your own that's buck
You figured out that no quality control meme
Exactly
So
Big dumb
This is the most
Divine inspired job I've ever had my life I've never felt
Name your other job
Was very aware that I was lacking
Feel like I've been doing
God's work and it's been extremely humbling
And
We believe you believe it
Fighting for our survival
We think anybody should just join us
Would you not join us
Almost everything you say
That's why I would
Join him so I don't take much stock in that either
Yeah yeah Lottery
Seems not to join the Alex
A lot of talk
About divine ordainment
Surrounding
Various Infowars stuff
On this episode that I find
Real trouble and you know you know what that that
Alright
Maybe Infowars doesn't have a handbook
But there is a handbook that they're supposed to follow
True
What is the Bible and those m************ haven't read that
Because cleaner on
The story isn't just
Stick to the truth as close as you can. We don't have time to work out the Kinks
Well I think
They have not gotten past the beef part yet
That is a good part
It really sets the stage hurts so much to get the risk
Right
We haven't even got a later on did you know that the Pope
Classified beavers
The fish what
Yeah you know why
Friday's couldn't eat fish
Beaver fish
So
The devil
What about unloyal
Don't take it they're going to be left with the bill
That's a thing you know
Powell oil the devil is cuz all these people are these people
The Pelosi's annoy people
Dedicated their lives
To this evil
Force and what are they going to return it they're just getting put out to pasture and and used one last time for the guy
There's no loyalty all these people are going to do
Award
Get it
Where's David Knight
Where's Millie Weaver any of your old there is his loyalty
Loyal and they were disloyal so they must be
Tossed it to the Sun
One-way ride
It's loyalty does not go both ways loyalty is not a two-way street my friend I would
Not a good example of
Loyalty loyalty
Loyalty think about all the names that he
Can't get away Kenosha
Jakari calls him up every weekend
I'm so loyal I want to try and help you find a new gig jhacari
Very loyal
I mean
He couldn't even remember Jason bermas
He's talking about his early career as early as broadcast
Metaphorically speaking gun to his head
He could not remember birth
Sad
Disloyal some might say
Devil's looking pretty nice
In comparison honestly
100 million dollars Dakari didn't get s***
So Alex
Is it
I think
Some of this
Define ordained
Business is going to his head a little bit
Yeah
This is really f***** up
You know just where it where it really at the
The peak of all this right now and victory is going to be
To wear Infowars
Can
Appropriately
To the point where we're no longer needed and we can borrow out that's mine
Company man
We need to mow support so that
Because it did the
VCR defeated
This is the defeated
The populist
Very symbolic
And so that's how I see victories to work
I'm actually know that repeating
Exactly
Just going to create a
Allegiant
Looking for warriors
Pushing the truth
Because you can't stop the truth
Yeah it repeats has
F***** up repeat
I'm not compare myself to Christ
I'm just saying that the cycle of Christ
Repeat that
Suggested that it repeats
Does whatever sentiment you're trying
Convey with Idol
Close the gates the previous now I don't think of myself the same as Jesus
But
Now we're talking. But really changes things to Alex
Views himself as
Somebody who will be sacrificed
For the sins of the left
Sacrifice will bring about
The cleansing
That the Patriots need to rise or something
You know who's really really unsettling s***
If that's the case just f***
Can get it over with man sacrifice yourself
No because I don't think he actually thinks
If you want the audience to think he looks at things this way because it's so Noble in
And selfless
We need to do is find a way to land This Plane without a crash
You all need to give us a bunch of money so Alex
Text can have millions of dollars that he can disappear with
Or something
That's the great ending for this story
It's really more with that I'm sure they all want for this story is a sequel to that McAfee documentary
Alex's on the lam
That's where this goes
Well
McAfee documentary
Life as a documentary didn't
Six more calls of Gregory's
And this call is awesome
Which comment about the delusions of
Beautiful Warriors
I'm thinking that
Maybe
That would be something
A response to
Clash Royale
Info
Checkers
So to speak
And that
It might also be awake
Nobody to the
Today checking account it enforces if you had just
Stryver just a base
Membership
For now we get a little decal that I can probably put in them
That's a great idea
I think people are more inclined to
Take action
This is just going back to what he did originally
He used to have memberships
This is
This is going
Full circle back to
What you did when
It is much smaller
He took sponsors when he could
Success sponsors
Oh that's it went away
He sold gold
Is weirdo friend
Until he lost his life
Since to sell price
Just metals
Sold a bunch of supplements
Maybe now that's too expensive
Pensive
Alex
Alex I've invented this new idea it's called
Lower your overhead and taking donations
Asus brand new it's going to revolutionize the industry
Small Studio at Bedwell
Alex likes this idea
Of course he does he always has to make sure the scholar knows that he had it
Launch it we should make it very clear now
WhatsApp
Your lovely Larry we love you
Lovely Larry
Okay
20 years ago we created this Army we call them info Warriors and then two years ago
Somebody did a podcast and then yesterday I found out about it so they called themselves 110,000 into
Warriors so we need to announce that we're 100 that's you already were
Also Jason bermas didn't do a show called info Warrior
Yeah
This is
Is dumb but I do love ours is impulse to be like
I thought
Not only not only am I glad you called in I had this idea this morning so I'm not
Even dumber because it's are as I called have used a new ID
Have you thought about this thing that got four wheels and you put a motor on it and propels you forward what
Yeah
No I mean it's a car you should really look into car
Okay tell you this is a great idea and I loved it I thought of this this morning
You already thought of the car so to do that
Something really weird
Too I just got the message
It's it's pretty remarkable
Let me just go ahead and say this now
Copper power for any of those
Not ready to talk about
Because it's such a big
Really in touch with Army intelligence
Pentagon leadership
Obelisk
I can tell you that
In fact
Always listen to 4
But but
Military
Look for us lyrics
Powerball
You did this
Infowars
Call Schwab didn't do this and that podcast
2 years ago but
There is a
Really f***** up delusions of grandeur going on here
Like obviously whether or not Alex believes it one thing
What he's expressing to his audience
Yeah it's f***** up enough on its own
Did the
Divinely ordained leadership nonsense that's going on throughout the
The show is f***** up
And now Alex is saying
He's been
Selected by the good
People within the CIA and the FBI to be the leader
Of whatever their nonsense
This is
I mean I don't know how else to put it.
Basically
Appointed himself a revolutionary General
Was it
Last week
That that David Garris were on
Yeah it was one week ago
Yep exactly from today okay now
I recall last week we learned
That Glenn Beck was the FBI
And in fact was
The entire United States government's true but he got overthrown at some point we have to assume
So that was that was treated as a bad thing
And yet now in this time.
Alex is the FBI of the CIA
I am CIA in charge of that
Right
Okay that's all right everybody is always in charge of everything here's the fun part
It's all imagine
That is the fun part that is the only thing that is fun
I guess
The consequences really are just in what effect it has on his body
Right
What kind of emboldening or or radicalizing effect
You could have on people like
He is essentially the George Washington mean I think everybody
Infowars
Start matchmaking
Demons Alec
FBI badges
Why not they're in the CIA kind of like
New Bill Cooper thing is everybody
Is citizen Corps
Investigative yes
Arms
Yeah it's Greg swearing Allegiance
Do Alex has the know that's awesome
We need leadership we need a president
See you more as a leader
Off of this movement and Trump
Oh my God
It's
I said I'm not the leader they said
This is why you can't have a show without continuity
Okay well this is not okay
Cuz I know we're in the future this is even in the past this is the 19th
The last time we talked
He wasn't
The head of the CIA
It didn't come up
No honestly the last episode
Seems like he was pretty excited about Elon Musk tweeted something sad that this is an issue for me
He's the head of the CIA or something
Part of the CIA
Days like this is the most important wheat Elon Musk has ever had
It's great to eat
Great to hear you wanted to run so I got a mess
Message from God
Also Elon Musk
Straight from the good people in the FBI and CIA
Iboats
To be the leader of this Patriot movement
Right go against vaccines
Steps of Alex is the leader of all this
I mean he get
Statues
President right you would assume
I mean if he's now the leader of the deep
State the Deep state is who is chosen
Stop
Stop L the Deep state
People in the FBI and CIA
You can't you can call each other the Deep state but you're still both of the
Oh no
So this is dumb
Maybe we'll see what it where this ends up going
Dumb and scary places I assumed I would have to have proof that it's really really fun
To know
That there were people in the world
Like Alex Lee Boyer
Glenn Greenwald
Glenn Beck
Yeah we going back in sporting Alex now
Joe Rogan
Approval on that
Yep this is
This what you got this is a picture that was
Missing from that documentary I'll tell you what more about how Alex was ordained by God at a
Young age or also whenever he eats something delicious.
That's right you know like he was the Satanist for a little while
Calico Christian coronavirus hours
Indeed.com are also
We are inserted that knowledge underscore fight back but until then
Bzx Clark I'm Wilford
Snapple Snapple of the crippled pebble
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color