It's time to pray.
Andy and James, I love your room.
Knowledge fight.
Knowledgefight.com, I love you.
Hey, everybody, welcome back.
Knowledge Fight.
I'm Dan.
I'm Jorge.
We're a couple of dudes like to sit around worship at the altar of Celine and talk a little bit about Alex Jones.
Oh, indeed we are.
Dan Jordan.
Dan Jordan, quick question for you.
What's your bright spot today, buddy? My bright spot today? It's been a little while since we've checked in on the Dreamy creamy summer sure.
And talked about some of the ice cream treats naturally have been going in my mouth.
Yes.
It hasn't slowed down since I've been gone.
It has not, no.
And it's been going at full speed.
I think I'm up around, like, maybe 60, 60 ice cream? I think so, yeah.
But this is I mean, part of the problem is it can be tough to find enough variety, I mean, of easily accessible things.
You don't have, like, special order, get dry ice delivery.
Listen, most of the best ice creams I've had have been in San Francisco, and you're going to have to go a long way for that.
And a couple of times I've tried to order, like, ice cream cakes.
No, we need to stop you from ordering ice cream cakes.
But I think there's obviously still a good couple of weeks left of the dream.
Anything could happen.
But right now, I am feeling like I'm pretty close to giving the title to Cool House.
H-A-U-S? Well, yes, I assumed that I think that their consistency is pretty solid, like, across the different flavors of ice cream sandwiches and novelties.
We're talking as a whole, not like best ice cream, but best producer of ice cream.
I think so.
And if I had to choose the Standout All Star from them, it would probably be the Street Churro Cone.
That sounds amazing.
Yeah, it's quite good.
I enjoyed it.
But today what I want to talk about is a little head to head challenge versus any other, because churros are incredible.
Yeah.
They're too big.
They're almost a king of desserts.
They're almost enough to get me to buy a box of that Cinnamon Toast Crunch treat.
Absolutely.
But I didn't, because I assume it's just Cinnamon Toast Crunch at a different garbage.
They have some ice cream treats that are like poppable.
Yes.
They're little ice cream balls.
Popcorn.
Yeah.
There's one that's, like, low class.
I'm sorry, is there a box of wine version of the poppable ice cream deck or the Nestle's Crunch poppable? Yes.
Now, of course, actually, the problem is, the moment you said it, I was like, yes, you're right.
Those are the pedestrian as well.
Yes, that's what they are.
And then there's a classier version that is, like I think it's called Dream Pops or something like that.
Yeah, whatever they are, maybe a nondairy situation.
Disgusting.
Look, they're both bad.
That's the end result of this interesting head to head.
Yeah.
Each one was slightly lesser spade.
Right? They both sucked.
Okay.
It can't all be street church cones, man.
In situations where you're dealing with a subpart snack, usually the snack that really goes for being the most subpar winds up tasting better.
Also, that reminds me that also I got in under the Wire and got a Choco Taco before.
Where? Before they shut down operations.
Before they were victims of cancel culture.
The ultimate cancel culture seasons.
Good.
It was good.
Yeah.
I will say that I remember being better, but I think that's how almost everything your taste buds were newer.
The rose colored glasses of history.
Look back on these ice cream novelties of yours and you think like, oh, God, it was so perfect.
The ice cream was just the right consistency.
True.
But yeah, almost every time you're going to get one of those, the taco itself, the shell is going to be a little bit the consistency isn't great.
Sure, tacos are kind of a bad thing to have, like, too squishy, middle crunch.
But the insides, if you bite down on it, ice cream is going to spell out.
That's almost inevitable.
That is true.
But, yeah, still pretty good.
Better than either of the poppables.
That's not hard to do.
So what about you? What's your brain? My bright spot is yakuza.
Like a dragon.
I enjoyed it.
We talked earlier about how difficult we've been having finding a video game.
We thought we'd play something simultaneously, so we tried Yakuza Zero because it was on sale for, like, $45.
Yeah, it was a good start.
It was fun.
But I think both of us found the combat a little bit monotonous.
I'm just not a punching punch guy, which is weird because it's essentially the same game.
Like, all the sense of humor is there.
All of the story beats are very similar and stuff, but there's something about turn based JRPGs being dropped into modern day Tokyo that is hilarious.
It's just very funny.
And it's a good game.
I like it.
Well, good.
Yeah.
Maybe I'll give it a try.
Okay.
Maybe I won't.
We'll see.
You're not really a turn based RPG guy too often, are you? I think I was the person who told you to try three houses.
No, for sure.
But, I mean, this is more like I have not historically been too much of that.
Sure.
But I think that maybe it's something that I enjoy more than I know.
Yeah.
So I don't know.
I think I enjoy that.
You might appreciate it.
I don't know.
I like three houses.
There we go.
Hey, so, Jordan, today we got an episode to go over.
I don't know if it's unprecedented, but it's rare, certainly, and that is that we're actually going to go back to the past, but only, like, a couple of days before our last episode because I realized that we missed something in terms of the catching up to the presentation.
Sure.
So we're going to be talking about August 19, 2022 today.
Interesting.
And that is because this is the day after Brian Stelter got oh, that's right.
After we got Brian Stelter canceled.
Look, I don't think there's a direct correlation.
I don't know.
You don't know.
Well, certainly no causation.
There is correlation.
That's true.
They let us on.
They should never have done that.
Next week is his last episode.
Understand the consequences cosmically.
I understand that maybe it wasn't us who got Stelter specifically fired, but by us going on CNN, it unlocks Pandora's boss.
Absolutely.
And I do think that it had something to do with your Chicago Teachers Union shirt.
Maybe that got Stelter in hot water.
Yes.
Worth it.
Yeah.
I was looking at some of the stuff that had happened over the course of the time that we'd missed.
Sure.
And obviously there is the fake turning on Trump and Jugan's daughter's death that they seemed like actually important things.
And in that I kind of just forgot that Stelter, his show had been canceled.
And I don't know, maybe there was a part of it that was blocked me, that was blocking it out of my mind since we were on it.
Right.
Also, we don't really pay attention to TV, honestly.
No.
But this is important for Alex.
Yes.
That's the thing.
Yeah.
This is way more important for Alex than anyone other than Brian Stelter.
Right.
I think it's probably more important to him than Stelter.
Yeah.
Stelter is going to get another job somewhere.
So we'll get into this and see how Alex takes the news.
But before we do, Jordan, let's say hello to somebody wonk.
That's a great idea.
So first, this shout out goes to Emily from Laura Alice.
She's sorry she fall asleep to this every night.
Thank you so much.
You're now policy walk.
I'm a policy walk.
Thank you very much.
Next, the foundation to finally take Alex Jones's daughter fishing.
Thank you so much.
You're now a policy walk.
I'm a policy walk.
Thank you very much.
Check out next the worst druid ever.
Thank you so much.
You're now a policy walk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much.
Next, the dreamy creamy supremie.
Thank you so much.
You're now policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
And Devonstone, the legal eagle is a beautiful man and I now know that Mark Bankston is a handsome beast as well.
Thank you so much.
You're now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
And finally we got a technical cry in the mix, Jordan.
And I'm going to go with the old sound bite for this.
So thank you so much.
To Stephen, the bachelor squash of Ireland.
You're now a technicrat.
I'm a policy walk.
Your mother, tell her you're brilliant.
Someone sodomite sent me a bucket of poop daddy sharp.
Jar Jar Binks has a Caribbean black accent.
He's a loser.
Little Teddy baby.
I don't want to hate black people.
I renounce.
Jesus Christ.
Thank you, Stephen.
Yes, thank you very much.
Bachelor squat but of Ireland, which has fallen out of favor to Scotland in the Knowledge Flight International Listener ranking stepping up Ireland.
The celts are going to come for us, man.
So here we go.
We're starting off the show here.
This is how Alex comes m it's live, August 19, 2022, friday edition of the Vaunting.
The attacked the embattled infowars transmission.
There's too much confusion.
If you thought the news was intense a year ago, do you think it's intense now? You ain't seen nothing yet.
Thank you so much for joining us on this live, uncensored, unfiltered, teleprompter free transmission of we the People.
It's interesting, man.
Essentially nothing Alex says about his own show is accurate there at all.
I guess embattled just means consequences are mounting for things I've done.
Sure, yeah.
You can make an argument that he's teleprompter free, but that doesn't mean anything.
And he has a screen in front of him the producers put messages on.
He has a board that shows him the callers, and he has an earpiece that the producers are talking to him throughout the show on.
But he doesn't have a teleprompter.
That's true.
See, but it's not as freewheeling of a show as Alex wants it to appear.
Yeah, the show is not uncensored because he can't swear on the radio.
So by definition, he's operating under censorship.
And I couldn't imagine a show that's more filtered than this one.
Just recently, with the acknowledgement of Trump taking money from Pfizer, we saw a crystal clear example of the sort of filtering Alex does to the information that's acceptable to be on his show.
This is a common thing, too.
Like, Alex will conveniently pretend to not be aware of certain things about figures he's trying to support, but when they fall slightly out of his good graces, he magically knows about all the things that should have been a big problem for him before.
We saw another glaring example of this with Bill Barr, who Alex loved, but then when he wouldn't back Trump's nonsense at the end of his presidency, alex suddenly had information about Barr's family's ties to Epstein that never had come up before.
This is an intensely censored filtered and produced show.
It just appears to not be any of those things because Alex is too lazy to prepare, so he has to fill his show with pointless rants and his imagination is disgusting.
So he ends up rambling about grotesque topics for long stretches.
Glad to see him rocking out to a little All Along Watchtower.
I was thinking about that song and it is kind of interesting to really go back in time and think about how much of that type of music blew people's minds.
Sure.
Right? Yeah.
Now that is fucking nothing to me.
Like, music has moved way beyond that back then.
That must have blown people's heads off.
Yeah, I used to think about that quite a bit.
Like the idea of this being played on the radio.
Yeah, the first times you heard it on the what the fuck? Yeah.
How could you get you were listening to fucking Clog dancing before that.
And then all of a sudden this happens.
Of course you lost your welcome over to Baba O'Reilly.
Oh, my God.
Everybody was talking about the latest fiddle player before this happened.
And now you're like, holy shit, what am I doing in the small town? I get it.
It's oversimplifying things a little bit.
But yeah, that wonder is kind of like maybe it's just because it's something that is inaccessible to us and something outside of our life experience.
Sure.
But imagining you know what it is too? It's a desire and urge to go back to a monoculture.
I can see that.
It's like everybody was connected by hearing these songs on the radio.
Sure.
There was this thing that everybody was experiencing, or at least everybody within your sort of your cohort I get what you're saying.
I'm going to throw it more towards like I'm longing for the days whenever a discovery was more like Pythagoras discovered A squared plus B squared.
And it's like, holy shit, nobody's going to discover anything for like 1000 years after that.
So All Along the Watchtower, nobody had heard shit like that before.
But whenever Kanye comes out with, Jesus walks.
That's great.
That's awesome.
And it's epoch changing, but it's not like back then because we already had All Along the Watchtower, if I didn't have Jesus Walks, I could still listen to that shit.
They didn't have anything.
They had nothing.
They had those four bastards in the past.
They were wasted.
It was all just nothing.
And then Jimmy Hendrix came along and then one day, and I believe that's a cover of a Bob Dylan saw too.
So they actually had another version of this song already.
Great time.
Your point makes sense.
And one of the problems is Alex is so dumb and boring that we end up being very interested in going down that road.
So Alex has a big news story that I think will probably be his main focus for today.
Let me just do this.
Let me just give you the main stack headlines.
We're going to plow through them all, take calls and have special guests in studio.
They put out a press release yesterday.
They put out a podcast with Claude Schwab and others and they have declared their number one enemy infowars and have said that they've hired 110,000 operatives.
But they called information warriors.
Where have we heard that term before? The Info Warriors.
The counter.
man.
I keep trying to explain to the listeners they're really scared of us.
Not just me, but the fact that we've got the Death Star plans big, if true.
Yesterday they put out this press release.
A lot of agents for one press release.
That's true.
So I was able to find the story that Alex is talking about, and it's an article in News Punch about the World Economic Forum hiring 110,000 people to combat misinformation on social media.
This was a post that was published on August 17, 2022, and it's based on a video published by a channel called The People's Voice.
This is just like a junior varsity ass infowars channel on YouTube, and their main source is a podcast the World Economic Forum put out featuring the UN communications director Melissa Fleming.
She never mentions Infowars being Class Schwab's number one enemy, though she does discuss efforts they were taking to push back against misinformation.
The first one she mentions is called Verified, which is done with the help of a communications firm.
And it was an effort to take solid information and put it into formats that would be easy to share on social media.
The concern was that so much of the actual information that you could have was buried in inaccessible PDFs and large documents.
Whereas misinformation is packaged so slickly and it's optimized for engagement.
That's the entire business model for misinformation.
So it's a primary concern for them.
Whereas the folks at the UN were a bit behind on making the information that was provided good for posting.
Well, I mean, the fundamental issue is that they're running up against learning is hard and chocolate is delicious.
Yeah.
Essentially, another initiative they were launching is called Pause, where they were trying to spread the message that you should stop and think before reposting something that seems too good to be true.
It excites you, so you want to post it, but maybe it's bullshit.
Take a second to think about it, and if you still want to share it once that adrenaline wears off, go ahead.
Apparently, the belief is that encouraging the sort of behavior would cut down drastically on nonsense posting.
I'm skeptical, but maybe it couldn't hurt.
She also does say that they have recruited 110,000 information volunteers who are applying these kinds of practices and introducing good information into misinformation spaces.
I guess Alex could consider that information warfare, and maybe he's right, but I also think it is defensive in nature.
All that being said, this podcast was released in November 2020.
This is not news.
It was yesterday.
So close.
It's being presented in this newspaper article as if it is.
And because Alex has no idea what he's talking about or covering, he thinks it's news, too.
If only he'd listened to Fleming's advice about thinking before you repost something ironically, maybe he would have gotten this story a little closer to accurate.
It's possible.
Doubtful.
Yeah.
I mean, I was wondering here's my problem there, okay, with the new Sponge thing.
Can the World Economic Forum just hire 1000 people? They're volunteers.
No, that's what I'm saying.
That's what I'm saying.
That's my big issue with that is like, what are you talking about? Nobody has just the kind of cash to toss around at 110,000 new employees, let alone the World Economic Forum.
Yeah.
And I'm willing to bet that a lot of this is fairly unofficial.
I'm willing to bet that some of this is just like people signed some kind of a pledge, some sort of a symbolic pledge.
No, the Nielsen ratings are 100% accurate.
Thank God for that.
Yeah.
But Alex is getting a lot of mileage out of this two year old podcast and things happened yesterday.
Ouch.
Two years old.
Oh, boy.
Not good.
So we get to Stelter here and Alex is in a mood.
We have some celebratory things here to make fun of, but I don't know if I can laugh because I'm going to cry.
Brian Stelter, who already had no viewers, so he already hit show, was already canceled if no one's watching, like 100,000 viewers, I mean, small local radio shows have that.
We have millions and millions and millions of listeners an hour.
So if you already didn't have any viewers, it's a fact that you had a zombie broadcast like CNN.
It's dead, it's not alive.
No one's watching.
It's a joke.
I think this is sad.
You can't even really muster the energy to dance on Stelter's grave.
Yeah, but you know what should be his greatest day ever? No.
When you have a nemesis, all right, you can't be happy when your nemesis is gone because your nemesis is what pushed you to the heights that you couldn't have reached without said nemesis.
That's true.
It's not a formal enemy, an enemy you defeat.
But Stelter was a man among men.
We are about to play I'm going to play a clip a little bit later.
Alex is repeatedly yelling that Stelter is his enemy.
Okay, well, maybe I did my best.
Yeah, I get what you're saying, though.
You have more of a bond with the only people you have a bond with.
And I think that there is a like, well, I won't have him to punch around anymore.
There's probably a disappointment, like when Alex doesn't have a Democrat in office or whatever, he doesn't have that easy tool.
And for Stelter to be gone, it's going to be a little bit harder for him to, I don't know, deal with Wolf Blitzer.
Yeah.
It must be bittersweet.
It must be a bittersweet feeling to know that you've perhaps outlived your oldest enemy, but you're still an old wasting man yourself.
True.
Deep.
So we're going to get into a little bit of coverage that Alex has about monkey pox.
And I'm just going to give a little bit of a warning.
This is pretty intensely homophobic.
And why would I expect otherwise? Yeah, pretty bad.
By the way, 99.9% of the monkey pops cases with no deaths in the US are gay men having hundreds of sexual partners a month.
And the media is defending it, saying, we want you to go under lockdown, we want you to wear masks, but we want to continue actually have articles, the gay orgies.
So you got to wear a mask, you got to go under lockdown.
They're say, Coming soon, but these men can get together and give each other a bunch of diseases.
Disgusting.
See, that's not good.
Wow, man.
I hope all those people like Alex Lee Moyer and Glenn Greenwald and Joe Rogan, who loved to carry water for Alex, like the kind of messages they're steering people towards, because that's pretty cool.
Yeah, no, it's great.
So while it is true that the available information does indicate that men who have sex with men are disproportionately represented in the cases of monkeypox that have been identified at this point, the way Alex is covering this is unacceptable and is essentially no different than the rhetoric you would have heard him spout in the early days of AIDS.
He has an intense disdain for the LGBTQ community, but he knows it's unfashionable to just be honest about that, so he finds other stories he can use as cover to express his hate.
An important point about this whole dynamic comes up in a CNBC article about 98% of patients who provided demographic information to clinics identified as men who have sex with men.
According to the CDC, that's not necessarily saying that 98% of people who have contracted monkey pox are men who have sex with men.
There may be a percentage of people who saw treatment who did not provide that demographic information.
That said, it would be slightly dishonest to say that there's not something statistically relevant here.
There do appear to be increased rates in the community of gay and bisexual men, but it's dangerous to create this association and even more dangerous to pretend that it's just an STD.
It's a complicated situation.
People like Alex acting like this are going to get innocent people hurt, and I think that's what he wants.
Incidentally, there's no call for monkey pox lockdowns.
And in fact, the reality is just the opposite of what Alex is saying.
Tedros, the head of the World Health Organization said this at the end of last month.
Quote, for men who have sex with men, this includes, for the moment, you're talking about, like, mitigating actions.
This includes, for the moment, reducing your number of sexual partners, reconsidering sex with new partners, and exchanging contact details with any new partners to enable follow up if needed.
Alex hates the LGBTQ community, so he makes up shit to attack them with things that paint him as the victim and them as a privileged class who the system wouldn't dare even suggest inconveniencing.
He's pretending that the government is going to force good people like himself to lock down over monkey pox, but they won't even think of suggesting behavioral advice to gay men.
This is complete bullshit.
Because the World Health Organization has a goal of dealing with the outbreak by serving the people who are affected by it while working to minimize any stigma that's going to lead to discrimination.
Conversely, Alex's goal is that discrimination itself.
So furthering, that goal is not best served by dealing with what the World Health Organization is actually doing, but rather by creating a fake storyline that conforms to your persecution complex.
And it's complete shit.
Yeah.
Great.
Yeah, it sucks.
Yeah.
First off, only Wilt Chamberlain has had hundreds of partners in a month.
Right.
Let's start right there.
And even if you want to take that and ground it a little bit sure.
The close contact that can spread monkey pox is not something you need 100 partners.
You could have one partner.
Absolutely.
You could go on a date with somebody and have a great time and even use condoms conceivably and still contracted from skin to skin contact.
And also, all we're really seeing is what happens whenever you have a community that is isolated due to shit and a disease breaks out in an isolated community, it is going to break out of that community eventually.
But as it stands right now, the only reason that it's stuck there is because of discrimination that's already inherent in the fucking system.
True.
Like, this is a self made creation again, always.
Yeah.
Very frustrating.
And there's also a self fulfillingness that Alex is kind of working towards.
I think it was fairly similar with Covet, and that is that his actions and a lot of the rhetoric that he's putting out is exactly what you would do if you wanted the disease to spread more.
We said it at the beginning.
He must have been paid for by Covet, that's the only explanation, is that he was working for ladies and gentlemen, we are subsidized by Cove.
Is it possible for a virus to congeal together a personality long enough to pay Alex $50 million in order to spread itself? I don't think so.
But if it is possible, that's what's happening.
That is what happens.
And Alex gets worse, even let's say that's great.
Yeah, that's great.
Absolutely disgusting to spread disease like that.
I don't care if you're heterosexual or homosexual.
Men and women were having hundreds of sexual partners a month and spreading disease.
That's disgusting.
That's dangerous.
It's like saying you're going to go lit toilet bowls at the airport or you're going to go to a grocery store without a mask and spit on it.
It's okay that Tim Cook runs death camps in China because he's gay.
He wears a little turtleneck.
It's like, well, he's not threatening.
He's gay.
It's all right.
He runs death camps with suicide nets around him.
The same thing here.
Well, it's all right.
We got to lock down society because of what you're doing.
Just keep doing it.
We're going to make little kids though, wear mask over their faces.
It's like, well, so what if they rape dogs, be Seality, and give them monkey pox, and they got to be euthanized liberal.
It's all about they can do whatever they want, and we got to just stand down and put up with this crap.
So, yeah.
Rogan, how do you feel about Alex suggesting that there's a connection between being gay and raping dogs? These motherfuckers, for years, multiple years, bitched and whined about having to wear a mask to stop spreading disease, and now they're going to wring their hands and, oh, my God, someone spreading disease, doing something I don't like, instead of going into random strangers home and spitting all over their shit, coughing in front of somebody at an abortion clinic.
Like, all of this shit, they are diseaseridden horror monsters, and they're going to come at me with this bullshit.
That's very frustrating.
It is.
It's very frustrating.
I understand your frustration.
I think I'm more frustrated by the aggressively anti gay mentality that he's expressing.
Right.
Everything that he says is it's absurd.
It's awful.
It's fucking awful.
It is.
So, look, Alex wants you to post his shit online.
Yeah.
Because you have to.
You'd fight back against Schwab, but, man, let that sink in and put this full show headline up.
World Economic Forum publicly declares an Information Warfare operation with information warriors to counter Infowars and other disinformation outlets.
How honored are you as the army of Infowars to know that you're in direct conflict and information warfare with Claus Schwab and the New Order? Now do you understand why I say share the articles? Now do you understand why I say, magnify what we're doing? Because I don't want to be the best in the fight, because I'm not that good.
I want to stop these people.
I want to see other leaders like Tucker Carlson, Balsan, Ro, Joe Rogan, and other stand up, and they're starting to but you know what? The enemy recognizes us and me as the number one enemy in their new world order.
I told you 20 years ago, I was eating a chicken fried steak and drinking an iced tea.
27 years ago, not again at Waterloo Ice House after I done a two hour TV show that I literally talked about a vision.
It was like a download.
And God showed me the future, what was going to happen, and also how dangerous would be, and said, Are you ready to sign on for this? I remember sitting there alone in that restaurant and going, yes, I accept this.
Like, I was floating.
I go? Yes, I accept the mission.
And it went, here's the rest of the download.
And I got slammed with the imprint of data.
And it was like, all right, soldier, you joined.
Get ready.
I literally was commissioned by God for this war.
Wow.
Yeah.
This seems like somebody who's so much more reliable than the mainstream media.
This is.
A guy who you go to to cut through the bullshit, right? I mean, Jake and Elwood Blues were busy, so God had to commission a different asshole for this job.
Honestly, their mission from God was saving a bunch of children.
It was lower stakes than this mission saving an orphanage by doing a concert.
That, I think, is fine.
I mean, if you're going to have delusions of grandeur, at least that's a good one.
Yeah, this is a little bit different.
Maybe a little bit wrong.
So look, Claus Schwab put out this podcast that he didn't yesterday.
Two years ago.
Yeah.
And Alex wants to explain to you why.
Here we are inside the New World Order.
Well, the World Economic Forum, which is the mouth of the New World Order, the mouth of the UN, the mouth of the megacorporations, the mouth of slave masters, the spokesperson for evil has come out and said that their attempted world continual, never ending lockdown and forced injection failed.
It was still devastating.
And now there's a total rejection happening of them across the board and billions of rotting poison mRNA gene therapies that no one will take.
And their answer is a declaration of war.
Next level censorship.
With 110,000 volunteers inside media and big tech, an army of Brian Stelter Humpty Dumpty Pennywise's.
Well, Brian Stelter got fired.
Brian Stelter, humpty dumpty.
Pennywise is a barrage of imagery.
Yeah.
So that clip brings up something that I want to stress for a second here.
So a lot is made of how Alex just makes stuff up all the time, and rightfully so.
However, it's key to recognize that he does more than just makeup details and lie about concrete facts.
He also writes stories out of these fake facts that are necessary to explain them within the context of his made up world.
For instance, here Alex has this headline that he's done zero investigation into that he's presenting as the World Economic Forum, declaring war on infowars by hiring 110,000 information volunteers to counter misinformation.
In order to bolster this story, he needs to connect it to some of his larger storylines in order to embellish the story.
Alex says that the World Economic Forum is doing this because there are so many shots that no one wants to take and all the antivax people are winning the war of ideas.
So they enlisted an army to crush antivaxx voices like Alex.
This is Tana Mont to him running a disinformation campaign against a campaign meant to fight misinformation.
Which makes sense.
Liars really don't like fact checkers.
Yeah, I mean, why would you not go after them? Yeah, but what's critical here is that Alex is making up the why for this story out of thin air.
He's got a piece of information, this 110,000 volunteers thing, but he has literally no other details about this story.
So he's just making it up.
He doesn't realize this was a story from November 2020 before any of the vaccines were even available, which is kind of sad.
In order to make sense of why the World Economic Forum would be doing this in the present day, as Alex thinks they are, he just falls back on what version of this story would be most emotionally satisfying for himself and the audience.
That's why the rationale for their alleged action is that Alex's side is too successful and they have all these expiring vaccines that no one wants.
This explanation is a fiction that creates a sense of victory for the listeners and more importantly, it frames their online activity as a critical part of the fight against the World Economic Forums information volunteers.
Promoting Alex's content isn't just about getting new people into his revenue streams and selling his dumb pills.
It's actually fighting back against claus, schwab's cyber army who are only even being enlisted because you all were too powerful with your previous posting of Alex's content to begin with.
Right.
This narrative works really well for Alex on a couple of fronts.
But it's completely made up the simple detail that the podcast.
That this is the basis.
That the basis for this entire story came out in November 2020 reveals it all to just be shit that Alex is making up to stroke his own ego and convince the listeners to continue working as his unpaid social media team.
Yeah, it's wild.
Yeah.
I mean, it is a little bit like somebody took a rent fare too far and it's just now his full life, just every day is the rent fare and whatever.
Like, if somebody brings a phone in there, they got to retcon the entire rent fare to make sense of the phone being inside.
And then every time you add a new thing, now we're in a cyberpunk rentfair, and so now we've got God over there.
Like, it's just a bigger and bigger rent fare.
I was not listening to you because I started to think about Renfield Renfare.
What would that look like? Or a renfare.
Renfield renfare.
Yeah, he's got a gallon of mead.
A flagging.
No, I see that.
Yeah.
Sorry, I know you were making a point, but I got distracted by word point.
I think I just started talking about rent fares.
Yeah.
So here Alex plays a clip of that podcast that, again is two years old.
We have announces a recruitment of 110,000 information warriors close quote to counter info wars.
We specifically in.
Their documents are named and the American people and others resisting their design planetary collapse.
Let's play a short clip of the podcast that the WEF spokesperson just put out.
A part of this verified and pause campaign entails also recruiting people around the world.
And so far we've recruited 110,000 information volunteers.
It's just an elaborate fiction based on Alex not looking into the story that he's telling.
Yes.
Do we have any follow up on these volunteers? Like, whenever she announces, we've got 110,000.
That's 110,000 people signed up.
Did anybody actually do fuck off.
No.
I know we didn't solve this information in the past two years.
But I did see a recent thread on the conspiracy subreddit.
Okay.
And the people were like, oh, that explains all the shills commenting recently.
Recently.
Because they didn't look into it either.
Of course not.
Yes, they just saw this News Punch article.
The date on the article is recent.
Oh, all the shills? Yeah.
When will the chills stop shilling, dad? It really also brings into sharp focus the idea what a joke, this notion of critical thinking in conspiracy and Alex Jonesy communities are, did any of these folks and their great leader Alex stop to ask themselves what's the context of this? Is there an actual story here? No, it's convenient.
It's saying what you want it to say.
Right.
And so you will not only accept it as real and true and current, you'll embellish and make up details about it to make it even more perfect for your ego.
I do appreciate anybody who gets a piece of information and then instantly is like, well, that explains this other thing that it doesn't have anything to do with.
I enjoy that because there's nothing in between.
You'd think there would be something in between, but no, you're just like, that explains that.
My world makes sense again.
Hooray.
So Alex is mad at Sam Harris, and I don't care.
I want to hit business.
Because if you want to talk about a Rosetta Stone, if you want to talk about a skeleton key, if you want to talk about something that really illustrates who we're up against and their hubris, their smugness, their bravada, it's this clip.
You are wasting time, dude.
Come on.
Sam Harris is a supposed deep, dark web intellectual leftist, and he's doing an interview a few days ago and he goes, well, of course we censor conservatives and there's a conspiracy to do it.
Trump is too dangerous.
Sam Harris is in charge of all media.
Yeah, obviously, whatever.
I don't really care.
But one of the things that Sam Harris was talking about was that the corruption that you can find with Biden and Hunter biden, sure.
It doesn't come anywhere close to what Trump is involved in.
So these kinds of arguments about the corruption and the concerns about it are kind of weird and dumb.
Right? One of the things that he brings up is Trump University, and Alex is going to latch onto that.
Sure.
But I want to clarify one thing really quick.
According to Alex's worldview, the crimes of the Biden's are much greater than Trump.
Yeah, of course.
But in the real world, well, not really so much.
So if Alex is comparing Trump's University, let's say, for instance, to the fake imaginary version of Biden, right? Then yes.
Trump University not that bad.
Sure.
But if we're in the real world, trump looks pretty shitty he does.
And that's kind of the tension that's at play in this clip.
And that's even if you want to add in all of Biden's shitty, shady Delaware shit that he's been doing for the whole time, like, oh, credit card companies don't have to pay, blah, blah, blah.
That's corrupt.
I get it.
But that still isn't I got nuclear secrets in my house.
Yes, it's a little different.
I'm not saying anything to let Biden off the hook for any corrupt dealings.
I'm just saying that he didn't kill kids in a basement.
He didn't kill kids in a basement, which Alex is going to a legend.
And then Alex loses the thread and gets really defensive about how he didn't go to college.
That sounds about right.
That's not an issue according to Sam Harris.
No, he goes, Just look at nothing Biden can do, including dead bodies in a basement of children.
Wait, the basement is of children? I mean, compromised by foreign powers can compare to Trump University, which I think was a great deal.
Weekends with Trump and top experts and brainstorming and networking.
I mean, I can tell you people ask, why did you go to college, you pathetic creature? Well, I mean, I got out of high school and I went and got a job selling memberships at a spa, at a gym.
And I was making $100,000 a year when I was 19.
What? I was driving a sports car.
I was in a nice two bedroom apartment.
I was having the time of my life.
$100,000.30 years ago was like a million dollars today.
I was 19 years old making 100 plus $1,000 a year working 4 hours a day because I became a salesman.
And I sold a good product and I looked good and people bought the memberships, especially the women.
But the point is and a few times we're on a date, I love that salesman job.
The point is that I'm red, but I don't lie about it.
What is happening? The point is that that was a real value.
That experience was real.
I should have paid to be a salesman at that hot club.
I mean, one of the hottest gyms in US of the time.
They said, hey, you want to be a salesman? I said, sure.
Boom.
Salesman.
First weekend sold like ten memberships.
This is about Sam Harris.
Remember they say I don't have a college degree because I'm a loser.
No, I don't have a college degree because I went on the fast track to success.
But that doesn't even matter.
That's not what I'm getting at here.
What are you getting at? All these educated idiots like Sam Harris that talk really slow and act real smug and sit there in their chair and say, yeah, the number one evil of Trump is his trump University is your problem.
That he's sitting in a chair talking about what is happening.
I think that it's fairly important to recognize that not everybody does need to go to college.
I think higher education is fantastic.
I'm a big proponent of it.
But I don't think that people should be shamed for not going to college.
I didn't graduate.
Yeah, it's not the most important thing in the world.
The people learning a trade is pretty fantastic.
A lot of people find a great deal of happiness.
You can learn whatever you want.
Just find some books.
Sure.
Be great.
I just want to put that to the side just because I don't want to be like, shitting on Alex for not going to college or anything.
But he really is insecure about it.
Oh, yeah.
What's being expressed here is very much a feeling of why does everyone think he's so smart? Right? Maybe because he doesn't go into shit like his monkey pocket nonsense.
Before we go any further all right, let's start with the easy smart thing to do.
Don't defend Trump University.
It lost the lawsuit.
You don't even have to just say, oh, that sucks.
I have another smart thing he could do.
What's that? Not talk constantly about visions from God.
I mean, honestly, that would bite into his bottom line.
Not defending.
Trump University is free.
That's true.
There's no downside to not defending university, but there is a downside to defending Trump University, which is where you go on to this weird tangent about how you fuck good when you worked at a club.
Right.
That's it.
I also think that one of the things that maybe could use some examining on Alex's part is how he never stopped being a salesman.
Yeah, I don't think that's something he can really he is not a researcher or a journalist or anything like that.
He is still just a salesman.
He's selling his dumb pills.
He's selling his worldview.
More importantly, that's really his primary product.
He sells you the worldview, you internalize that worldview, and it creates needs that he can fill for you.
Yeah, there is culture in there's.
Nothing that somebody would find unfamiliar if they just listened to the whole Rich Dad, Poor dad series and then watched Alex Jones sell set.
And they'd be like, oh yeah, I guess you'd gone to Trump University.
Actually, I think you don't get sales skills at Trump University.
You get sold.
True.
You get conned.
So Stelter got canceled.
But it wasn't he just got canceled.
Now let's spend some time on Brian Stelter.
Yeah, we can celebrate all day that he's been cancelled.
He's a joke.
But he had 1000 viewers for cable news.
That's not even a pulse.
Okay? He was good because he was way to be black.
He was a laughingstock, he was a clown.
Now a jester.
He was an officious, self serving, arrogant booby.
He was the most schmug person you could imagine.
That's the armor they wear, this fake pomposity.
And so now he's been canceled.
Canceled itself.
CNN spent 400 and something million dollars on CNN Plus, and it failed in a month and a half or less than I was, like, 40 days.
So there's a lot of theories about exactly why Stelter and Reliable Sources got canceled, and it's unclear what the precise reasons are, but I think everyone is pretty comfortable with the idea that it's part of the aftermath of the Warner Brothers Discovery merger that was finalized back in April.
Yeah, there have been all sorts of cuts made throughout their properties, like HBO Max, and this is actually part of a larger story about big corporate media consolidation.
But Alex is completely missing the forest for the trees.
He hates Brian Stelter, and the story he wants to tell about this is that Stelter is a failure who got fired because nobody liked him and his show had no viewers.
That's a story that's emotionally satisfying for Alex, and it's what the listeners want to hear.
There's more to the story, though, but it doesn't matter because he's the tip of the spear.
He's the king of big tech and media watch doggery.
And just missing this entirely.
What a great time for somebody like Alex to really dig into what happens whenever media is monopolized and how the powers that be whenever they become a smaller group and a smaller number.
All of them with control over the media.
Like a number of companies.
Let's say smaller than ten.
And those companies have CEOs and they all meet in back rooms and they control the media.
Literally.
It would be a great time for somebody who is a conspiracy theorist to talk about that.
Well, I think you're sounding a little bit I'm just saying, I think that there is a wonderful opportunity for Alex here to rise above his enemies, as it were.
It would be a great idea.
And he could, instead of talking shit about Stelter, put that aside because everyone knows he already doesn't like him.
And all this, that'd be redundant for him just to do a little dance and instead be like, look, sure, we can all be happy about that, but there's a bigger picture here.
And also, it's actually a bad sign Brian Stelter got his show axed.
It's a bad sign that HBO Max is streamlining and laying off all these people.
It's part of a I know.
Consolidation coming together.
The story plays, though.
You know, that, like, I would die to defend your I don't agree with what you say, Mr.
Stelter, but I would die for your right to not be owned by one conglomerate.
I demand that this man, my mortal enemy, be freed from his prison of corporate lockstep.
That's there that message plays.
Everybody loves that shit.
And it would be an impressive thing for Alex.
Totally.
It would be amazing.
And Dee just doesn't have it.
Doesn't have the guts.
No.
Mr.
Stelter, tear down that roll.
Yes.
Come on.
The spirit got in me while you were fixing going to china, man.
You got to do it.
So Alex plays some clips here.
Here's an old clip of Stelter that Brian Alex we're doing this is your life.
Not really.
I was just think there's a few that are like these are great clips of Stelter.
So here's one.
Okay? Okay, so let's play the late, great founder of the Weather Channel, a meteorologist schooling Brian Stelter years ago.
Here it is.
First, let me bring in John Coleman.
He's in San Diego this morning.
Thank you for being here.
Nice to be on CNN.
Hello to all your viewers.
I resent you calling me a denier.
That is a word meant to put me down.
I'm a skeptic about climate change and I want to make it darn clear mr.
Kenny is not a scientist.
I am.
He's the CEO of the Weather Channel.
Now I was the founder of the Weather Channel, not the co founder.
And I'm glad you did because I am addicted to the Weather Channel.
I lost a lot of cable.
Now hold on just a minute.
I'm not done.
And CNN has taken a very strong position on global warming that it is a consensus.
Well, there is no consensus in science.
Science isn't a vote.
Science is about facts.
And if you get down to the hard, cold facts, there's no question about it.
Climate change is not happening.
There is no significant man made global warming now.
There hasn't been any in the past and there's no reason to expect any in the future.
There's a whole lot of baloney.
And yes, it has become a big political point of the Democratic party and part of their platform.
And I regret it's become political instead of scientific.
But the science is on my side.
I don't think we're going to come to conclusion about the topic right here what I do want to use because you wouldn't allow it to happen on CNN, but I'm happy when I got on the air and got transferred to your viewers.
Hello, everybody.
So the sea levels haven't risen half inch in 100 years.
So doesn't that clip actually kind of refute a lot of Alex's points about mainstream media? No, they never put voices that dissent with them on the air.
Dan right.
I mean, it's actually one of the worst clips Alex could have chosen to play.
I know it's fun to hear someone be rude to spell.
Sure.
No, I guess that appeals to Alex in some way, but it's actually so counter to the perception of media that is essential to sell infowars as the alternative to it.
I mean, he's literally saying, thank you for letting me get my message across on the mainstream media.
Right.
And Stelter is being polite to this guy who's being incredibly polite.
Yeah.
Can you imagine the reverse? Like Stelter coming on Alex's show and being addict to him and Alex being polite? It doesn't happen.
No, I can't imagine that.
Right.
No, alex would need to be more famous.
Alex would offer nothing but a hostile platform to somebody who disagrees with him.
And the media, for better or for worse, often does have a deferential platform for dissenting voices.
Maybe not as vigorous debate as Alex would like, which is I mean, it translates to people screaming at each other and saying disgusting shit, sure.
Calling each other pedophiles and what have you.
That's a good TV day.
But, yeah, I would have maybe told them, choose a different clip.
I think this hurts your argument.
Yeah, I mean, it doesn't help Stelter either.
I think that's a fairly good clip to play for everybody to look at the media and just go like, we're not doing a good job.
Whatever it is that is, that's not good.
Well, I mean, there are certainly questions.
Did you have any reason to suspect this is how Coleman was going to act? That's on you.
Maybe you could have prepared to field him being a dick.
Mute.
You got a mute button.
Anyway, Alex, instead of really celebrating Stelter, he decides he's just going to play some old clips.
He's reminiscing about his enemy, kind of, but also reminiscing about how much he yelled at Stelter.
He's kind of navel gazing reminiscing.
Sure.
It's Brian Stelter.
There it is.
Oh, my God.
That is a horror movie cover.
Seriously, he is scarier looking than at the clown.
I mean, would you let your children anywhere near that psychopath? That is a psychopath right there.
I mean, look at him.
God, it cries out, danger.
Danger.
Alert.
I am a scumbag.
I am filth.
I am your enemy.
I would literally not be able to finish my dinner if somebody walked over and talked to me that looked like these two guys.
And I'm sorry, they're not just lying anti American scumbags that want to run us all on the ground, okay? That's what it's about.
It's the spirit of evil.
Good point.
I've tried to do joke photos like this to look disingenuous and I can make any face I want to.
I can't pull it off because the eyes, she's gone.
Oh, my gosh.
Oh, hell on Earth.
He wants to run your life.
He wants to control every aspect of your life because he knows he is a cowardly, degenerate sack of anti human trash.
I pledge before my heavenly father that's right, I will resist them every way I can.
These people are the literal demon spawn of the pit of hell.
Look at him.
And you know what? He is better than you if you keep letting him run your life.
He runs your kids, he runs the schools, he runs the banks.
This guy, this spirit, this smiling leering devil that thinks you can't see what he is.
He is your enemy, period.
So fun.
I like the music in the background.
Yeah, that is fun.
This is one of Alex's old rants about Stelter that he just had to replay, probably because he can't be bothered to put any energy into the show today.
I was going to say he knows what people want.
Thankfully, there are these old clips of him putting a little gusto into his Stelter hate, but this actually is a curious clip to play on the day after Stelter's show has been canceled and he's out at CNN.
That's because if anything Alex was saying meant anything, then it shouldn't have been so simple to remove him from his perch.
How important is Stelter to the globalist plots if he can just be fired? Honestly, knowing that Stelter was just axed over business considerations and it didn't cause widespread chaos among the globalists kind of makes this entire presentation that Alex is putting on seem pretty stupid.
It seems so weird to hear how worked up Alex was about Stelter in these clips now that we're on the other side.
Because now that Stelter is out, alex just seems like a worked up baby who is so mad that someone was criticizing him that he decided to make up a bunch of stuff about them being central to the globalist plans.
And this isn't even the full rant.
It goes on.
Disingenuous, fake, false, broke, back twisting, a defiler, a betrayer, a back stabber, a devil.
You will pay.
Yeah, you think I don't see your face? Come.
Is he still praying? Did he end the prayer? You understand I forgot.
I know what you think of me and my family.
God is going to destroy you.
Get them offscreen.
Come on.
We're drunk on our children's blood.
For God's sake.
Get your shit together, guy.
So this is an illustrative moment when Alex is saying all this shit about Stelter.
None of it has any connection to reality.
It's just Alex trying to put some kind of an elevated appearance onto his petulant anger.
He knows well enough that if he got on his show and started yelling and lashing out about how he doesn't like people being critical of him, his audience would rightly see him as the weak child he is inside.
By masking that immature insecurity with over the top pronouncements about Stelter probably being a pedophile and how he's a betrayer, whatever that means, alex is able to protect himself from being seen for what he is, which is a hypersensitive loser.
Now the issue is that the audience doesn't really realize that they're just watching Alex play out a psycho drama on air and may think that he's actually saying something about Stelter as opposed to just yelling about his own hurt feelings.
They form opinions, post things on social media, and even harass stealther over things that Alex says, as if there was anything behind it other than Alex being a baby with a boo boo.
Anyway, I probably would have played a different clip on this episode if I were him.
It seems dumb to portray Stelter as some kind of a big high level big bad guy the day after his show ended with no real pushback or fanfare.
Seems like that should have been a much harder fought victory if anything Alex was saying meant anything.
And this is kind of a grandiose thing because he got fired.
Yeah, no got canceled.
I mean here's the problem.
Here's the problem.
It's just a show.
When you choose your enemies to be of the demonic realm, you think TV is a great choice because it's so big and it's like, oh, it's TV.
But it's really not that big.
It's not as big as you might think because you can just get fired.
Like you can't claim that if you didn't get the job at a Denny's, you can't claim that the manager is the antichrist because eventually he's just not going to be the manager anymore.
The manager can't be the shift supervisor.
He's a fry cook.
He's not the antichrist.
I used to work at a dairy Queen when I was like 15 and the guy who was the burger guy, he was a satanist.
Well, yeah, that's great counterpoint.
Now you've brought that piece of information to light.
I do retract take that.
So Alex just played that old stelter rant and he's feeling good about it.
You got to bask in your work.
No, it reminded me of that time that you remember Hannibal's bit where he played his own joke and just vibed with it.
Reminded me of that quite a bit.
So here Alex lets us in on a little media secret.
And I can tell you that little ranch is not my best brown silver rant, but I'm told that that is shown in the newsrooms for years every week as the resistance back to little Tucker Carlson inside dope that is required viewing at least once a week.
So that's a little gift to old Tucky.
Even that's brainwashing.
Honestly, I don't believe it's true.
But if it is true, that's brainwashing that they're doing a Tucker show or they're laughing at him yeah, I feel like as far as ways to end your 05:00 on a Friday, instead of doing the whistle, you just start playing that clip and you're going to leave with a bit of a smile.
All right, I think I can go get drinks now.
That's happy.
But that's only like really funny to you because you haven't heard that in a long time.
It has been a while.
If you watch that every week it would get really annoying.
I don't think you watch it every week but you play it over the PA.
I love this though.
Like all of Tucker's employees have to watch this once a week so they can keep their head in the game.
They can understand what it's like to resist.
They can watch me fake being nauseous, looking at stelter.
Okay, I understand.
Yell about demons.
I'm the key grip.
Do I really need to work? Yes.
No, But I mean all it's in your contract.
God damn it, I hate this show.
Yes, Hannity's, people have to watch it once a month.
That's why they're not so hardcore.
So a caller calls in and he wants to know how Alex finds the time to read so much.
This is a bummer.
I want to say I'm very excited when your new book comes out at the end of the month.
Now, I admit that I normally read Kindle books and am highly addicted to the Internet, and my cell phone is always amazing, like so many of us are, by ordering your hard book.
And I can't wait to read the physical book.
It made me have an epiphany that I'm so bombarded with information.
I'll admit I'm in a trance of a low attention span.
Now, you read so much, sir, you digest so much information.
I would love if you could share with me and the audience how you find so much time to read.
Suggestions on how we can use the Internet, use our cell phones in a way that promotes enlightenment, but also a way that promotes a long term attention span.
Do you speed read or what would you recommend to focus our attention span so we can take the time to read entire books? Do we have a cyber free Sunday? Get away from the Internet.
How do you recommend because it's a strong part of the information war to manage information, sir? Well, when you study the global it's a really good question.
We talk for days about it.
A whole college course on it or a whole degree in it.
They have the same programs over and over again, so once you know their operations, you just see the same permutation of it over and over again.
That's not hard.
Like, oh, I've seen this press release before.
I've seen that before.
There's only a few dozen things they do.
There's only a few dozen plays.
So they have so this reminds me of a conversation I had with a comic years ago who was really proud of their ability to do crowd work and respond to hecklers.
Sure, in reality, they weren't that good, but they were very confident.
And they explained to me that there are only a few possible types of responses you need to be ready to have.
You can respond to something with an angry, mean retort, a nice retort, or a confused retort.
As long as you had one of each of these in your pocket, ready to go, you could respond to just about anything an audience can throw at you.
The rock paper, scissors theory of stand up comedy.
Yeah, that's all good and well, but what it's actually doing is taking the act of responding in the moment on stage and reducing it to a parlor trick.
You're creating the illusion of being in the moment and fast on your feet.
You're faking being clever because you know that you aren't clever enough to be it for real, and you're terrified of being seen as not clever and getting caught in the moment of being like, oh, I don't know what to say.
This is kind of what Alex is doing with this globalist playbook idea.
He's constructed a couple of stock responses to world events that he's decided to call the globalist playbook, and it's basically just his crutch, so he never has to appear like he doesn't know what's going on.
Think of a tragic event as the equivalent of someone heckling.
In terms of how to interpret Alex's show and the narrative, he needs to be able to respond to it quickly or else he'll risk showing weakness to the audience.
So just like that comic I knew, alex has preloaded responses to stuff.
Instead of angry, nice, or confused retorts, alex has things like false flag it was secretly antifa, or elaborate deep state plotting.
These are go to responses he can whip out to apply to any situation, and he can then rationalize based on some detail and be like, oh, this is part of that globalist play means nothing.
Alex has nothing to say and he hasn't read anything.
It's pretty telling that this guy asks this question and Alex's first response isn't that he reads all day, every day, because I think even he would know that that's silly.
His response is just that he knows everything already, so he can see things happening in the world and then make stories up about them.
Considering Alex's track record of being super wrong about almost everything he's ever called to play from the globalist playbook, this should really worry the caller and the audience.
But they're not paying attention.
Alex satisfies their emotional needs with rants like the one about Stelter and their need to feel like a part of something important with the nonsense about fighting Klaus Schwab's digital army by posting infowars links.
As long as those needs are met, and as long as that's the case, the reality that he's just making shit up all the time, it doesn't really matter at all.
The audience will never care or notice.
Yeah, that caller scares me a lot because he sounded so rational and so sane and had a clear thought process.
But if you listen to that, that's the most insane thing anybody has ever said.
That's the most insane.
How do you do it? That's an insane thing to say to Alex Jones.
That's more insane than I swear to you, I believe more that Raptors would eat chocolate than I do that Alex reads.
Well, what do you believe more Alex reads a lot, or Alex had a vision from God over chicken fried steak? I believe the second one more than Alex reads.
At least the second one is possible.
Yeah, because Alex is a passive participant.
Exactly.
It requires no effort on his part.
Yeah, fair enough.
I can't prove that God doesn't speak through chicken fried steak.
I can't prove he doesn't have been great.
Alex should work out a deal with that company for advertising because this is making a steak and ice cream.
It'll give you a message from God.
Yeah.
So Alex goes on to explain his work process to this call.
Oh, my God.
No, but really, what I do is I scan him for I scan a bunch of mainline sites.
I scan legislation.
I go and look at what Jacksolvic is saying.
I look at what Mike Sternvich is saying, I look at Ron Paul saying what Senator Paul is saying, I look at what the Santa's saying, and I just quickly scan through all of that.
But I already know the globalist agenda from reading their books, reading clock swap statements and knowing what they're doing.
And I really go back to the key books written by the population controllers and the statements put out by Brzinsky and the books written by Brzinsky and Henry Kissinger and the program.
And so once you know that, it's pretty much reading the same thing over and over again.
And so that's where we are.
Lawlessness collapse of society.
This should be a huge red flag to anybody who's listening to Alex's show.
I mean, he has basically these old texts that I don't know if he's even read or not or if he's just taking them in by way of John Birch society literature that demonize those.
Right.
I think that's more likely they're more part of the lore than they are actually read.
Yes.
And he talks about like Ecoscience by John B.
Holder, and you haven't read that? Fucking get the folk out of here.
Get out.
Yeah, and then his workflow is just like, I skim my own website.
Isn't that what he's saying? I skim some other websites, and then I go check the Twitter accounts of shitheads like Pobik and Cernovich.
I mean, that's not great in the context of the rationality of the question that he's responding to, of which I do that idea.
Like, oh, should we have a Cyber Sunday where we get rid of all of our things and actually just fucking read books? Hey, that's not a terrible idea.
Not really.
I'm fine with that.
To respond to that with, here's what I do.
I skim shit.
And then I just kind of get the vibe of how people are talking about it.
Kramovich and Ron Paul and DeSantis are putting out talking points.
Yeah.
And then I just double down on the thing that those extremist shit heads are doing.
I grab what they say, and then I go plus one on the crazy.
And that's my job.
And I start the day by looking at my own website that I pay people to write headlines for sure.
So I'm responding to people who are paid to write things that will tickle me, I guess.
Yeah.
That's a bizarre circle.
That's an oraboros of bullshit.
Right? So what I did is I created okay.
Do you remember Elvis group of yes men that always said yes around Elvis? Yes.
Yeah, exactly.
So I turned that into a job.
Now it's their job to say yes to everything I have to say.
So Alex gets to thinking about what he needs to do, and there's one thing that he needs to do.
Read? No.
Pray with his dad.
Again, I appreciate what you do, and I know that you speak about Jesus, and I just want to remind people to not give up hope that there really is an answer out there.
But we have to keep fighting.
We must operate in determine.
I believe in these days, we must prepare our house.
That's what I'm telling my friends.
You got to do what you can, naturally, to prepare your house, but also spiritually, you've got to prepare your house.
No, I totally agree.
And I'm going to tell a personal story right now I never told because the Holy Spirit wants me to.
There's been three times in my life where I was under incredible attack and I went to see my dad and where we prayed, and literally within hours, I wrote you a check.
And there's something really special about believers coming together, but also men and women coming together and family members.
I'm going to pray with my father this weekend for awakening and victory.
And I don't know all the ways of God, but it's just powerful because our ancestors did so much before us.
And by praying with your father or your mother, it connects to the people before you.
And it's incredible.
In fact, I'm going to pray with my father and my mother this weekend.
Let's all confirm we have fathers and mothers left with us.
What are our family members? There's something particularly electromagnetic.
Let's all confirm that.
Just spiritual about that.
Do you hear what I'm saying? He's gone.
Must have been a spirit taking back to that place.
I was really under attack.
Like, eight years ago.
I was out with my dad's backyard by his pool.
I said, dad, I want you to pray with me.
put his hands in mind, and we made the circuit of the past, present and the future.
And that's why these Satanists hate us, because we have that power, and we're not using that power.
Oh, man.
Howie in New Jersey.
Howie.
Wow.
What a ride.
What a fucking ride.
Also, if it's the past, present and future, shouldn't, like your son have also been involved in the prayer? No, he doesn't give a shit about it.
I think it's the present and the future.
Oh, my God.
This is okay.
I like to though the idea that eventually I don't wish this upon him or anything, but eventually Alex's dad is going to pass away.
Yeah, that's how it works.
And then Alex will put out a Luther Van draws style pray with my father.
I think that dance with my father.
Yeah, I can see that.
I can see that.
Put some prayers on an album.
If I could pray with my father one more time oh, man, that's what you do.
That's what Alex does.
Deathbed prayers.
Records them with his dad.
That'll give everybody the magical energy of a father.
Insured the closed circuit.
Absolutely.
With that closed circuit energy, you got some money to be made, my friend.
Alex's son is like, dad, let me hold your hand and pray.
No, I will not be the past with this closed circuit.
I am the present and the future.
I will eat your soul, son.
You will not steal my vitality and youth.
Yeah, so Alex gets another call.
Hey, Alex.
I just wanted to say, like, the Saxco burga family that you talk about, they are an RH negative bloodline.
They're actually from Ukraine.
They're sorry, what people call fallen angels, or, like you say, fallen.
Sure, and that's what I say, that they believe they're their own species, right? Yeah.
I mean, they took over the stacksons of Germany.
The direction is right.
I think they went from Ukraine to Germany, took over the Saxons and the Anglos, or the angels, fallen angels.
The demons that have merged into the actual, the true humans or the true humanity, they've grafted themselves into it.
And they took over the Netherlands, too.
And that's where the West India Company is pretty much the basis for the evil side of the American colonization.
Really? Like you said, Anderson Cooper is the extension of the Vanderbilts, and the Vanderbilts are just an extension of the West India Company.
And I know parasites just live in colonies, even in your body.
That's why they need to get your products, get your parasite cleanse and everything like that smooth into a plug right there.
That is pretty good.
I mean, here's my take on this.
Sir, that's too much.
That's too much.
You know what? Normally, I'm cool with conspiracy people, I'm Alex Jones, but that's too much.
You got to go talk to somebody about that.
That's too much.
Yeah, the saxcobar got fallen.
Too much.
Too much already.
Who took over the Anglos.
Sarah? Angels.
See, that's already another too much.
Mixing with the real human.
Why did they do that? Giants.
And they had to go to the Netherlands, right? And then maybe the West Indy.
That's the one that you don't know about.
That's the one that's underground.
The Dutch East India Company, I guess, is related to the Vanderbilts because they're both of Dutch descent.
Okay, yeah, see, I think we nailed it.
No, actually, sir, that's too much.
Go talk to somebody.
Well, the Dutch East India Company dissolved around the time that Cornelius Vanderbilt, the sort of the founder of that family's great fortune, was a child in the US.
Right, but didn't they defeat the Anglosaxons and then absorb them into their powers, thus gaining angel and Saxophowers? I'm afraid you are much mistaken.
Have I mistaken? That was the wombat.
Alien oh, God damn.
Wombat.
Yeah, the Wombat alien.
How about the Mighty Ducks? Are they still doing okay? The Mighty Duck.
Aliens are okay.
Good.
Yeah.
So Alex gets another call who's a little spiritual.
I enjoy your products and I look forward to receiving your product, Alex.
This is a message for all the infiltrators.
The FBI, the CIA, the New World Order, carlos and his economics, who are listening right now.
I love you.
First of all, Alex, first of all, we are decentralizing the Infowars.
It's decentralizing their power, your power and control.
Alex Jones, you have been chosen by our Lord to be the leader in the front.
You are the member of the body.
You represent body of the left and the right wing who are taking us or manipulating us in the direction that they have been using to maintain control.
George Washington warned us against the power of political parties and replacing our nationality.
You are standing up against what we have been chosen.
The majority of the masses support Infowars.
Obviously, they are those who are against you, but they cannot stand against the masses of us because we are using the power of our lawyer, which is through quantum communication you talked about.
Totally.
I want you to continue, but what do you make of cloud schwab declaring information warfare against us and saying he's going to launch info warriors? I mean, they are scared.
Yeah, they are.
Yeah, totally.
I guess this guy doesn't know that it's two years old too.
Did you ever notice how the Lord is exactly as dumb as the person talking about him? Yeah, the deity has the information that the individual so weird.
You think they would have more on accounting.
Well, but Alex only knows what the Lord wants him to know.
Sure, that's data download.
Yeah.
Good call, Lord.
You got me on this one.
So apparently Alex is chosen as a leader by God, and the majority of the United States supports Infowars, the masses.
That's absolutely not true.
Yeah, that seems like a lot for the masses to have changed in just a short period of time.
In my experience, obviously professionally, sure.
You can't really judge the temperature of Alex because I run in circles that are pretty antiinflors, naturally.
And so I put that to the side.
And there are a number of people that I interact with just whether it's somebody in a service capacity or just a random person.
And generally, if anybody asks me sometimes lyft drivers, for instance, sure, I've been there.
They'll ask me what I do and I'll explain it.
And usually it's Alex Jones who yes, like most of the time.
There was that one guy in Austin who was a fan.
Yeah, but other than that, the masses have really not just a low level of support for Alex, so much as they have no idea who that motherfucker is.
Yes.
And that guy in Austin sticks out in the memory because he was so unusual.
Yes, absolutely.
I have encountered in the wild really, that has been somebody who is an Infowars supporter.
I think generally it's people who have no idea and maybe would be like, oh, he's that guy.
Yes.
He's that guy who like Big Trump guy.
Yeah.
That guy was a january 6 is not starlord.
He is a character actor in this show.
He's extra to most people.
Yeah.
He's the deity appointed leader to his fans.
Right.
And a fucking child with a boo boo to most people who pay attention.
Yeah.
Anyway, Alex said he was going to have a guest, and he does.
Sure.
But it's not a guest.
Oh, no.
Well, my old friend Greg Reese, great researcher, is in studio with us.
I saw him yesterday, gave him a hug.
I was busy.
He was busy.
Only talked about a minute.
It's not a guest.
He's your employee.
He's a guy who works in Infowars.
Does Alex know that? But I mean, with the rotating cast of people now he knows for sure because Greg Reese, alex plays his reports all the time on the show.
Talks about how each one is the best that's ever been made.
Right.
And if you go to band video, you'll find that his videos get significantly more traffic than even, like, Owen or Harrison Smith's stuff.
Alex is somebody who is nothing if not motivated by traction.
True.
Greg gets a fair bit because his videos are pretty slickly done.
He shows competence in certain aspects.
I winced at that.
I did see that.
Yeah.
I wouldn't say that.
Maybe in terms of editing, like there's some competence there.
Sure.
His voiceover I find incredibly boring jarring to listen to.
And the stuff that he says is just stupid like this.
He has an idea.
I want to see if you can come up with some ways this idea might go bad.
I think everyone in the world is starting to wake up to that fact right now.
That the Federal Reserve fiat currency system is what's responsible for all the problems in the world right now.
Sounds right.
And people are talking about silver and gold mines going into private business as banks since they have the vaults already.
And they tie a crypto card to gold and silver.
And then the private market, the free private market can just compete for people's trust and serviceability to start creating a parallel banking system.
So the end of their systems here, they're trying to rope us into.
Instead of them going to prison, they get more power.
What they want is they want to toss us an idea of some type of digital fiat currency.
Only a fool is going to accept anything that they take after all of the death and destruction that they've caused for decades and decades.
But that's obviously the plan.
We just get 8 million in bitcoin.
Look, this is a dumb idea.
No, you don't understand.
He just invented mining town.
It makes perfect sense.
All right, here's what we do.
We go all the way to the west.
We get a covered wagon together.
We get all buds together.
We build a little tent.
We open up our own general store around the Mind, and people will pay us with the gold that they recently banned out of the river.
The only people who could really afford to run that store anyway are the people who run the mine.
I think that's a great idea.
They should actually give their own currency out.
They guarantee using their money so you can only buy the stuff.
I think that's implied.
Yeah, that's a smart move.
This is wild.
I mean, also, just logistically, I think that people who have a lot of resources right now are going to be able to buy those mines.
But I think you'll end up with probably oligarchs of mind banks who will be able to maybe set unregulated.
By the way, that's also definitely an implied part of the system.
No, absolutely not.
There's so many opportunities for abuse of this system.
It's almost parody of itself.
I appreciate it when Tech Bros.
And all those stupid people invent things that we already invented a long time ago, and then they put a new name on it and you're like, oh, you're a genius, like that kind of thing.
I really don't appreciate it.
Whenever we do have, like, a history where people did the step by step thing that you're recommending, and you can go back and you can read about how it turned out.
You can just read about it.
It's there.
It happened before.
Yeah, and it was bad.
It was so bad.
That's why we had to not do it.
We had to stop doing it.
Why are you going like, oh, no, I've got an idea.
That bad thing we did that led to everybody dying in the Great Depression and all that shit, but what if what if we did it again? So Greg's got another dumb thing to say.
Sure, big picture.
You're a smart guy.
I really respect your opinion reports every week.
People love you.
Why are you optimistic? Where do you think we are historically? I think the test is clear.
I think we're being offered it's offering acceptance.
And they've been doing this for years.
They're offering us slavery.
They've actually started to offer us slavery years ago.
I think they started up 1619 right after the Revolutionary War, try to rope us back into it.
And ultimately, it's our choice.
Ultimately, we don't have to be slaves.
We could actually become independent, become responsible.
They're offering you slavery.
That's not really how it works.
And back at the Revolutionary War, guess what? Some people were not offering slavery so much as they were forced into it.
Yeah, generations talking about these people are so stupid.
It's just so amazing.
We're being offered slavery.
How do you get to say these things? How is that allowed? Man.
You work at Infowars.
People are like, shamed for not going to college.
I swear to God, you should be shamed for not reading comprehension in fourth grade.
That's what should be happening here.
Well, I think that they can read, and there's some reading comprehension there's just like, I don't know what you're reading.
Yeah, maybe you're just reading shit.
Wingdings I think when they read a real book, it's just a bunch of bork or you're just suspicious of everything you read.
And so when you read a line that says X, you're like, trying to trick me into thinking X.
Maybe what this book is actually saying is why? Why is it that nobody believes in the double bluff of books? They're like, they think you're tricking you, but they're actually telling the truth.
It's a double bluff.
What about the triple bluff? Oh, you can't trust the triple bluff.
So anyway, researcher, great mind.
Greg Reese the reason I believe that we're going to win is because you can see that the way they've had this thing hold planned, they weren't expecting this much pushback.
They weren't expecting this much they were definitely expecting more people to take the vaccine.
Which tells me that Susan comes out and says, today we've hired 110,000 Info warriors.
They use our term to counter the disinfo.
Right? I mean, they're desperate.
Yes.
Just going along with Alex's bullshit story about a two year old podcast that he's now saying klaus Schwab said, sure.
And making it all about himself, which wasn't the case unless you identify solely with the idea of misinformation.
Yes and yes.
Greg greece just going along to get along.
Yeah.
That is such a weird example of just total capture.
Just like, hey, the sky is orange.
The sky is not just orange.
You bet it is.
It's green and orange.
Yeah.
Now it's striped like the flag.
It's nuts.
It's so crazy.
And you're like, oh, wow.
There's just no bottom.
None.
Facts, capture.
Look, these people love the individual.
They're so into individualism.
They think that you are the greatest thing, and God is, like, working through you.
And that's why they do whatever Alex tells them to do.
Individuality.
And also, maybe some people are so dumb that we need leaders.
If you were to tell me three or four years ago that we need leadership, I might have argued that.
But after seeing covet and realizing that a large amount of the population is sheep, like, out of respect and love for our fellow man, we do need leadership.
That's right.
As leaders, we don't want to lead people.
We want them to be leaders.
But if they're going to be under the control of people, we've got to not control them, but lead by example.
Be the good shepherd.
That's what we have to be.
We want people to be independent.
And lead themselves.
But if they believe things that are different to what we believe, we must for their own good.
Or lead them as a good shepherd.
Yeah.
No, I don't understand why people don't understand that religion is great.
If people don't believe what you have to say, you torture them until they do.
It's benevolent.
Why isn't this obvious? It's the way that God meant things to run.
The Lord gave me a message.
And to be fair, I mean, I do think that we need leadership as well.
Not because I think people are too dumb to lead themselves or anything.
I think that there are other benefits that we gain through leadership.
Things like morale, things like feeling connected to each other.
Sure, there are all kinds of benefits, but the way that they're looking at it has a real patronizing view of just the public, which makes sense.
They don't care about people.
They don't think people are great.
Nonsense.
No.
They don't want somebody who's a leader, who's going to listen to the people, who are going to synthesize information and then ultimately is going to take responsibility for the decision that they make.
No, that's called leadership.
Yeah.
And another thing that's great leadership is providing hope.
Providing a message that people can rally behind.
Now, one other form of leadership you could consider would be something along the lines of an iron fisted dictatorship.
Now, is that leadership? It's a good shepherd.
Well, it's a shepherd of sorts.
It's an effective shepherd.
I don't think that's true.
So you like beef? Not if it's shepherded.
Wrong.
Well, Alex loves beef.
Okay.
Beef is actually one of the most nutritious I mean, it's the sacred cow.
It's a life sustaining what? Do you not know what the sacred cow things alive is only alive because it's consumed.
And a cow eats grass and it's self fulfilling.
It feeds you beef.
The Bible.
Genesis starts talking about beef.
Yeah.
So Greg is just going along with whatever.
Just whatever.
So I think that Greg is trying to point to the idea that cows are sacred in Hindu culture, which is dumb because they're specifically like they don't slaughter and eat cows because they're consistent.
They are sacred cows.
Yes.
They aren't sacred because beef is delicious.
Because they fucking love it.
Yeah.
This is the steak of steaks.
Also, Genesis does not start by talking about beef.
Beef, it's what's for dinner.
Say it the Lord.
It starts with God existing in a void of formless, nothingness in creating the earth and light and all that stuff.
It's not until Genesis 124 that land animals are created, and that's after birds and quite a bit after vegetables.
Sure, there's no mention of beef, but humans are said to be lords over the natural world.
Interestingly, though, God does say, quote, I give you every seed bearing plant on the face of the whole earth and every tree that has fruit with seed.
In it, they will be yours for food.
Anyway, the Bible doesn't start with a passage about beef, and it's really embarrassing for Greg to just yes, and that shit facts capture.
The irony is that the first real discussion regarding beef ends with a murder.
That's in the next book, though.
Or next chapter.
Yeah, the first big like, what's beef about murder? Yeah.
Seems pretty obvious from the get go.
It's also it's for dinner.
You already said that.
Catchphrase marketing.
Anyway, we get back to the sacred cow idea, and Greg the wrong idea about the sacred cow, kind of.
But he actually even has a worse wrong.
Okay, I'm doing the report on that now.
And one of the interesting things there's a myth of vegetarianism is sort of connected to yoga, and there's a bunch of yoga so popular, and there's all these vegans into that.
But that's a whole myth, because if you actually look at that, that was based on the caste system.
Vegetarians were just a lower caste class.
Indian culture class were given meat.
And the only reason the lower caste were given vegetarian meals was so that they could save the meat for the upper class.
Exactly.
That's what the vet description, and that's all they're trying to do.
I'm sorry, what did you just say? System where we're all these lower peasants eating bugs, and then they can fly around the jets and have all the good stuff.
So there are definitely some connections between the caste system and rates of vegetarianism and traditional Indian culture.
But what Greg is doing is oversimplifying things in a way that is specifically designed to compare one to one with modern day infowars talking points like how kawab wants you to eat bugs.
Many of the lower classes in the caste system were not practicing Hindus, so they wouldn't have been concerned with the dietary restrictions that largely stemmed from Hindu beliefs and nonviolence.
Conversely, many of the Brahmans were actually their priests and members of the scholarly class, and as you might expect, they were more observant people in terms of Hinduism.
The phenomenon you see when you look at historical trends related to the caste system and vegetarianism is actually that the higher someone is in caste, the more likely they are to be vegetarian.
It's actually the reverse of what Greg is saying, but this doesn't work for the Kaosha squad wants you to eat bugs thing.
So he's pretending that there's no Hindu belief in this do no harm thing.
They're just trying to trick poor people into eating plants so they could save the cows for themselves.
I do recall reading the Upon USAds and thinking, man, this is all about how the rich need jets.
Yeah, that's what it is.
The argument that Greg is making is absurd, but the reality of this dynamic is actually far more complicated than even the picture that I've described.
And I'm not doing justice to the nuances of how this plays out in tradition day in India.
There's a lot of the Indian subcontinent has a history that is almost impossible to unravel.
It's incredible.
It's very complex.
But the notion that it's like, oh, they were just tricking the poor people into eating vegetables so they could keep the cows for themselves works for me.
Wow.
Write it on the board.
That sounds trophy.
It's in the vedic scriptures? Come on.
You don't know it's in the Vedic scriptures.
Yeah.
So Greg thinks back to his time beginning at Infowars.
Right.
Okay.
And honestly, I think that what he does here is he isolates a real serious problem.
When I first came here four years ago, I'm a very open minded, very skeptical, suspicious person.
And I've heard all the stories about controlled opposition and everything, so who knows? But when I got here, I was just basically told to try to pick a story that I think is important and do my best to get it right and stick to the truth.
And that was it.
And I remember asking Rob when he told me that, I was like, shouldn't I show it to anyone first to make sure that it's approved? And he just looked at me almost with disgust and said, we don't have time for that.
And that's true.
Everyone out here, we're working.
Oh, my God.
We saw your work.
We chose you, believe me.
Oh, my God.
We have no time for quality control.
You have no time to check anything to see if it's full of shit.
Wow.
That's a bad process.
Is there an employee handbook or can I at least train with somebody? No.
Find a story, put it out.
Well, technically, there's an employee handbook, but it's just boilerplate.
We just copied it.
We stole it from reliable sources.
We did control F for reliable sources and put infowars in.
Yeah.
I would think that one of the things that could aid Infowars the most.
Actually, I take that back, because it would completely destroy them.
I was going to say, you're misunderstanding their business.
Nothing would get on air if someone said, hey, hold on.
They would quit.
Yeah, definitely.
I mean, that's the thing that they really are.
We talk about how they're lying and they don't give a shit, and they're making everything up.
But what we're really not talking about is if they did face any challenge on the way to publishing one of those stories, they would give up and they would do a different story.
That's probably true.
And I think that they not only lie and make all this shit up, they've also constructed a system that AIDS that.
They constructed a system that is complicit and complementary to making shit up.
Yeah.
No, it is a little bit like when you see apes put a stick in a tree and then ants come off it, and you're like, you guys figured that out all on your own? That's fucking amazing.
You figured out that no quality control means you get ants from your stick.
Exactly.
So greg's Dumb, I believe that this is the most divine inspired job I've ever had in my life.
I've never felt name your other job so purposeful in my life.
And it's interesting because the majority of my life, I was very aware that I was lacking a sense of purpose.
And for the past four years, I feel like I've been doing God's work.
And it's been extremely humbling.
We believe in humanity, so we believe you believe in humanity? We're fighting for our survival.
We think anybody should just join us.
Why would you not join us? Right? Almost everything you say, that's why I wouldn't join them.
Wow.
Also, I think you're full of shit about caring about humanity, so I don't take much stock in that either.
Yeah, a lot of reasons not to join you, Alex.
Lot of talk about divine ordainment surrounding various Infowars stuff on this episode that I find real troubling.
You know what? The thought occurs, all right, maybe Infowars doesn't have a handbook, all right? But there is a handbook that they're supposed to follow.
True.
And that book is the Bible.
And those motherfuckers haven't read that because the Bible with beef.
It's very clear on the story, isn't just stick to the truth as close as you can.
And we don't have time to work out the kinks.
Well, I think they have not gotten past the beef part yet.
That is a good part.
Yeah.
It really sets the stage.
There's so much to get through brisket, right? We haven't even gotten it.
Hey, later on, did you know that the Pope classified beaver is a fish? What? Yeah.
You know why Fridays couldn't eat fish? Had their fish.
So the devil.
What about them on loyal don't they get they're going to be left with the bill.
Well, that's the thing that shows you how loyal the devil is.
Because all these people, a lot of these people, the pelosi and all these people, they've dedicated their lives to this evil force, and what are they getting returned? They're just getting put out to pasture and used.
One last thing.
They're having a great time.
There's no loyalty of $100 million and all there is is loyalty.
They don't even get it.
No.
Where's David Knight? Where's Millie Weaver? Any of your old all there is is loyalty.
And they were disloyal, so they must be tossed into the sud.
I see.
Yeah, you see, loyalty only flows one way, right? Loyalty does not go both ways.
Loyalty is not a two way street, my friend.
I think that Alex is not a good example of loyalty.
Loyalty? Yeah, loyalty.
Think about all the names that he can't get away.
Jakari calls him up every weekend.
Yeah, I'm so loyal.
I want to try and help you find a new gig.
Jakari? Yeah.
Very loyal.
I mean, he couldn't even remember Jason Burmas on the sand.
Or when he's talking about his early career, his early broadcasting, metaphorically speaking, gun to his head, he could not remember Burman.
Yeah, sad, disloyal, somewhat safe.
Yes.
Devil's looking pretty nice in comparison, honestly.
Sure.
He gave Pelosi $100 million.
Jakari didn't get shit.
So, Alex, I think some of this divine ordained business is going to his head a little bit.
You think? Yeah, this is really fucked up.
We're really at the peak of all this right now.
And the way I see it, total victory is going to be to where Infowars can exit appropriately to the point where we're no longer needed and we can bow out.
That's my vision, company man.
So at this point is when we need the most support because they see our defeat as the defeat of the populist movement.
And so it's very symbolic.
And so that's how I see victories to work.
And I actually see us pushing all the way and being destroyed publicly as Christ side.
That compare myself to Christ, but it repeats.
I'm actually in exactly because that will repeat like the heads of the Hydra if they can cut us off, it's just going to create a legion of Info warriors pushing the truth because you can't stop the truth.
Yeah, it repeats.
Is fucked up.
It repeats.
It I'm not comparing myself to Christ, I'm just saying that the cycle of christness, it repeats.
Now, I would suggest that the it repeats, undoes whatever sentiment you're trying to convey with I don't think of myself like Christ.
Oh, yes, you think that that clause then negates the previous part of the Son.
Now I don't think of myself the same as Jesus, but yeah, now we're talking that, but really changes things.
Yeah.
So Alex views himself as somebody who will be sacrificed for the sins of the left or something, I guess, and through his sacrifice will bring about the cleansing that the Patriots need to rise or something.
This is really unsettling shit.
If that's the case, just fucking get it over with, man.
Sacrifice yourself, jump into a volcano.
No, because I don't think he actually thinks this.
He wants the audience to think he looks at things this way because it's so noble and selfless right.
In reality, what Greg Reese is talking about is far more accurate.
It's like what we need to do is find a way to land this plane without a crash.
And so you all need to give us a bunch of money so Alex can have millions of dollars that he can disappear with or something.
That's the great ending for this story.
Yeah, that's really more what I'm sure they all want.
The ending for this story is a sequel to that McAfee documentary.
Alex is on the lamb.
That's where this goes.
Well, the McAfee documentary.
Well, I mean, his life as a documentary did send well, I guess Alex thinks he got Epstein or whatever.
Yeah, I don't fucking know.
Anyway, Alex takes more calls with Greg Reese, and this call is awesome.
Craig's comment about the lesions of the info lawyers.
I'm thinking that maybe that would be something that is a response to Clash Schwab's 100,000 info checkers, so to speak, and that it might also be a way to add a little money to the checking account.
And infowars is if you had just a real not subscriber, just the basic membership.
$10 for that, we get a little decal that I can probably put in a little short class on our ethics.
That's a great idea.
That's a great idea, brother.
That is a great idea.
Because I think people are more inclined to take action if they invest in it.
This is just going back to what he did originally.
Yeah.
He used to have memberships.
This is going full circle.
Back to what he did when it was much smaller.
Yes.
He took sponsors when he could when he was too toxic to have sponsors that went away.
He sold gold with his weirdo friend until he lost his license to sell precious metals.
Right.
Sold a bunch of supplements.
Maybe now that's too expensive, too much overhead.
Alex, I've invented this new idea.
It's called lowering your overhead and taking donations.
This is brand new.
It's going to revolutionize the industry.
Pretty sweet.
Yeah.
But get a smaller studio and then oh, no.
So Alex likes this idea.
Of course he does.
But he also has to make sure that this caller knows that he had it first.
That's right.
I saw that this morning.
It's just crazy.
You called most of it.
I was thinking we should launch an army to counter swab.
We've already launched it.
We should make it very clear.
Now, basic directives are code of conduct.
They can't misrepresent it and then launch it.
Greg, help me do it.
Yeah.
You're lovely Larry.
We love you lovely Larry.
Here's the thing, okay? 20 years ago, we created this army.
We called him info warriors.
And then two years ago, somebody did a podcast, and then yesterday I found out about it, so they called themselves 110,000 Info Warriors.
So we need to announce that we're 100, and you already were.
Also, Jason Bermans didn't do a show called Info Warrior.
No.
Yeah, this is dumb, but I do love Alex's impulse to be like, I thought no this morning.
Not only am I glad you called in, I had this idea this morning.
So if I do it, I'm not stealing it from it is even dumber, because it's like, oh, no, it's a really new idea.
Have you thought about this thing that's got four wheels and you put a motor on it and propels you forward? What? Yes.
I mean, it's a car.
You should really look into cars.
Okay.
I got to tell you, this is a great idea, and I love it.
Yeah, I thought of this this morning.
Oh shit.
You already thought of the car? Yes, I would do that.
Damn it.
You're a genius.
So Alex says something really weird to discuss and this is just grandiosity.
It's pretty remarkable.
Let me just go ahead and say this now and I don't make this announcement to try to act tough or powerful or any of this.
In fact, it's so big I can't talk about it.
I'm not being dramatic there.
I'm not ready to talk about this yet because it's such a big deal.
It's actually quite frightening.
Everybody thought the cub movement was secretly in touch with army intelligence and the resistance movement and all the rest of that.
Most the Pentagon leadership are globalist, most our military control, the grassroots are great people.
But I can tell you that over the years and here currently I don't get orders from these people.
In fact I was always listening to for over 20 years.
But now it's been recognized that I'm the leader.
And I don't say that to act powerful.
It's actually great responsibility.
It's not recognized on the leader.
And so whatever's left of the CIA and the military actually looks for us, for leadership and have asked us to be the leader.
And I don't say that again that powerful.
It says a big deal.
The enemy already knows it.
That's why Clashwa was doing all this.
But God did this.
You did this.
Info wars is now seen as a leader.
Claushwab didn't do this and that podcast was from two years ago.
But look, there is a really fucked up delusions of grant are going on here.
Obviously, whether or not Alex believes it, one thing when he's expressing to his audience is fucked up enough on its own.
Yeah, the divinely ordained leadership nonsense that's going on throughout this show is fucked up.
And now Alex is saying that he has been selected by the good people within the CIA and the FBI to be the leader of whatever their insurgent nonsense is.
I mean I don't know, Alice.
To put it he's basically appointed himself a revolutionary general or something.
Yeah.
Can I ask you a question? Was it last week that Dave and Gareth were on yeah, it was one week ago.
Yeah, exactly.
From today.
Okay.
Now I recall last week we learned that Glenn Beck was the FBI and in fact was the entire United States government.
That's true.
But he got overthrown at some point we have to assume.
We have to assume that.
So that was treated as a bad thing.
And yet now in this time period, alex is the FBI and the CIA.
No, there are good people within the FBI and CIA and Alex is in charge of that.
Right, okay, that's totally different.
Everybody is always in charge of everything.
Well, here's the fun part.
It's all imaginary.
That is the fun part.
That is the only part that is fun.
I guess the consequences really are just in what effect it has on his audience.
Right.
What kind of emboldening or radicalizing effect it could have on people like Alex.
He is essentially George Washington.
Yeah.
I think the info should just start making themselves FBI badges.
Why not? Yeah, they're in the CIA.
It would be kind of like just a new Bill Cooper thing with his deputies, everybody as an FBI agent, his citizen corps of researchers or whatever.
Investigating.
Yes.
Arms.
We have one last clip here, and it's Greg swearing allegiance to Alex as the leader.
Sure.
Great.
That's awesome.
Trump is good.
We need leadership.
We need a president.
But I see you more as a leader for this movement than Trump.
Well, actually scares me to think that the best we can oh, my God.
That's what I said.
I said I'm not the leader.
They said, you're all we got.
That's how bad this is, folks.
We're right back with your phone calls on them before stay with us.
This is why you can't have a show without continuity.
Okay, well, this is not okay, because I know we're in the future.
This is even in the past.
This is the 19th.
Yeah.
The last time we talked, he wasn't the head of the CIA.
It didn't come up.
It should come up.
No, that should be a daily come up.
I mean, honestly, the last episode seemed like he was pretty excited about Elon Musk tweeted something.
I understand that this is an issue for me.
Yeah, he's the head of the CIA or something.
Part of the CIA.
Part of the people.
The real CIA people are pledging fealty to him, and then the next day, he's like, this is the most important tweet Elon Musk has ever had.
It's a great tweet.
He wanted to run surge.
I got a message from God.
Also Elon Musk tweet.
I got a message from God, from the good people in the FBI, CIA.
I am ordained by both to be the leader of this patriot movement.
Because Trump won't go against vaccines, I guess.
So if Alex is the leader of all this, he gets to choose the president, right? You would assume, right? I mean, if he's now the leader of the deep state the deep state is who has chosen the stuff.
It's not the leader of the deep state.
It seems like he's the leader of the deep state.
Deep state.
Or the other people in the FBI and CIA.
Well, yeah, but I'm assuming that the other people in the FBI and the CIA will call them the deep state.
You can call each other the deep state, but you're still both the deep state.
Are you double bluffing again? I've always unless I'm triple bluffing.
Oh, no.
Yeah.
So this is dumb but scary.
And we'll see where this ends up going.
It's dumb in scary places, I assume.
I would have to bet it would be that.
But it's really fun to know that there are those people in the world like Alex lee Moyer, Glenn Greenwald, Glenn Beck.
Yeah.
I mean, Glenn Beck is supporting Alex now, but Joe Rogan put a big stamp of approval on that.
Yes.
This is what you got.
This is a picture that was missing from that documentary.
I'll tell you what, he should have really been way more about how Alex was ordained by God at a young age or also whenever he eats something to be re upped in his ordainment.
That's right.
He's a Satanist for a little while.
You get baptized again when you're an evangelical Christian.
Yeah.
So we'll be back, Jordan, but until then, we have a website.
Indeed we do.
It's Knowledgeright.com.
We are also on Twitter.
We are on Twitter.
It's at knowledge underscore fight.
Yeah.
We'll be back.
But until then, I'm Leo.
I'm Leo.
I'm dzx Clark.
I'm Wilford Sniffle, snapper of the Gribble PIBBLE.
And now here comes a sex robot.
Andy and Kansas, you're on the air.
Thanks for holding, Alex.
I'm a first time caller.
I'm a huge fan.
I love your work.
I love you.