Alexandra First Time coloring with huge fan I love your work
Generally and my friend Jordan sit down
Have a little bit of novelty
Jordan is currently on vacation in Iceland
I'm so filling in as replacement Jordan one of my dear friends
Hilarious metrics
Welcome you've brought us a novelty beverage
Yes we got
Yes got Orange
Crush powder singles to go as you mention soda and I gave him so two years ago
And I was like what I wanted this shity
I meant to say it could be a soda or a juice or something like that
Send a text message
I live right next to a CVS
I don't give a
Too much information
CVS and I just
Too lazy to leave
My lady friend went
Do the juul
Firehouse
Chicago nearest CVS and agile
Not narrow it down at all
Beverage thing
Never had a powdered beverage on the show and its
Although
We have to stir it with the powder thing within the powder cumin and I've noticed they don't tell the people out there that I don't
I have spoons at the ready
That's fair
It starts to like
Come back into Lake
Pizza
Is it the end
I'm excited to do something
Cinepolis
What's going on
Thank you for joining up
You can do so
By going
To knowledge
And you will be a policy wonk
Also send me
Poach my donator
Chris Archer
Today we're going to be talking about the August 9th
Episode that was Wednesday
The Alex Jones Show
Except
Before we started recording you told me you don't know pretty much anything about our
No I mean I
Wow
Amazing by where I live
CVS
The Infowars sticker there was a guy at my job
Was a big fan of Alex Jones
Okay
He's adding a longer with us but not related
I don't think I hope not
Done got him
Mental Illness but
Avengers
Pop culture related
It's a man through you
Sure
I spout a lot
Samsung
10 minutes of your podcast about all anyone ever really needs military
Listen
The two hours of this
Shirts general rule of thumb
Fill you in let's get to experience
The rocky road that is Alex Jones
This August 9th episode is pretty
I think that we've chosen a good one to throw you in the deep end of a kitty pool
What is a lie I feel pretty
Sure
No no no I thought maybe he was part of the span of all the other stuff around the present
Knowing the reality is not going to help you here
Alright for sure on the news that is broken
In terms of the situation
North Korea
Paul manafort's house
Those are two things are going to come up but
Knowing the facts
Isn't going to give you context for what Alex
Yeah I know that
Let's Jump Right In
Is in a weird mood
On this side is August
Episode
Because of the situation with North Korea
The idea of
Threatening a nuclear war or nuclear Brinks
Obviously he's going to put any parent in a weird head
Exploration
Merkel order Trump speech
It's Donald Trump's fault
How old is Donald Trump
Warzone
And a little smidgen
North Korea
So he's not an apology
I don't know how he has the rights to Lottery song
But there's a lot of artists
Clearly wood
F****** hate
People like Moby
The Beatles on their butt
Carpenters website
Package contract with a
I have no idea what it is but it seems very weird.
What's that weird Leaf it's although it does
Yeah yeah
So I like this
Because it's a nice basic
It sort of
It's just Alex being like
Why can't Trump do with Kim Jeong Hoon does it all the time
Because we're not petulant children were supposed to be the adults
Reasonable perspective on it
And because
Of course
They always do
And the reason that there's a status quo is because
We don't
How things get out of control is
You can have a really stable
But once
The disaster not want there to be War
If they do shoot at Guam I'm excited to learn more about Guam
Is it convenient
I would say read up now
So this
Is going to this this idea of the potential nuclear war
Is going to kick Alex Jones off into
8 incredibly f***** up rant
That takes up about 10 minutes of the first hour of his
I want to see this this next clip is about 12 minutes
Into the show
And when he's
Going into this sort of stuff this early on the show
You know
We're get worrying for a
So here is the Alex Jones talking about
Humanity I think
Not entirely sure how to set this up but you'll see
I should probably just walk over the world map
Section-by-section here of the continents in the country
He could have been
PowerPoint
And show people in jail
He's been saying he's going to build a new TV studio for about the last
2 years
And it is not materialized
Making a million-dollar Studio
And this whole idea if I can go with laser
Are Pointers and point out that
Do you want a rainbow board nonsense but it be a physical perform
That is not that certainly not as much by volume
I like Shep Smith from Fox
Lucas seems like the only sane person
Maybe Mike walls okay
They have these giant iPads
Yet it just looks like an iPad and I'm like what
You just like f****** Minority Report
No it's the technological like a bull s*** that they're doing
Wolf Blitzer had a f****** hologram on it
Go back to Cronkite days
Alex Jones
Has not gotten to explain about Humanity Justice
Properly.
Because on screen
That are pedophiles
Like that
Bike shop
Speciesism
Information
Understanding epigenetics
We know where is an
We all know we can build
Now we're sitting here
On the face of this whole thing
Subspace colonies
Unlimited
Charge
So this is what I would like
To say this is the beginning of a meltdown that's about to happen live on
I'd like to
Open the floor for Quest
Could you look confused
It's because I don't have the background of him before he kind of jumped into politics
Text bright
Talking about
The crazy in my PIN
Easy stuff like that he was into years ago was like a lot of
New World Order stuff there's a lot of 911 stuff
Sure I don't
Sandy Hook sure
Even political
Conspiracy
Blue Boy
Essentially like
Real
Bulshit
Pseudoscience
Its bordering on ancient alien
That's what he's getting into here
Humans have a memory of being off
Planet
Stuff like that like
We used to be in the Stars we used to be like
Traveling through space but all that memories been erased
By the global
Do they want us to think that were a fallen people
It's basically that whole thing
Yeah
Ice cream
You'll see a lot of stuff that is from pop culture pop-up and his rhetoric
Don't worry about that references movies all the f***
Time cool
I wish you would have been
Cuz it couldn't have been more clear
So
Like I said this is the beginning of a breakdown
Is a little bit of a meltdown on air
Just tell you it's a
It's a bizarre
Rant
Cut-out nothing
From it
But I've cut it in
Two segments
So I sort of switches in the rain
I've I've made a cut that I've got nothing else
Out I've not
Context of this at all
Earlier that you think
Because he has children
No I think that the
He would like to present it as like the nuclear threat is scarier for him because he has children
He does bring that up, father I don't want it I don't want nuclear war that's
He's based out of Texas Austin
Show me right now just with North Korea
Define latex
If you listen to Alex if I'm not sure if that's
But
Kim Jeong Hoon hate sxsw
Comedy
I don't know what the truth
And what the rumors are about
They're actually
DNR range
But Alex thinks that they can hit Austin they can in Chicago
He basically thinks they can hit the entire United
So he's pretty scared
And it leads
Pretty strongly into this ramp
So let's let's jump into this
Kill
Whatever it is charged
Sing in charge wants to take microchip
Define shall Domino's
Is building worldwide AI system of computers
It's three-dimensional image
In tube
The seats of power into the
Malls
End of the Town squares
What's up
Being in control of everything certainly
You're coming from me and Jordan have realized is that like arguments
Sort of hinge on hypocrisy
Are a little bit useless
Just because
Especially Alex's version the right don't give a
Push it
Like spoiler alert
He's going to Advocate later in this episode for regime-change
North Korea
Meanwhile he complains about how do you know the globalist
Committed
I'm taking over and stuff like that
What do you do
Where is your base where's your moral base in terms of
Oh it's fine as long as the globalists aren't doing it
People that went to my church at
Lynn Layton 80's and 90's
Is about like
The chips in your hands and all that
Tucker Rida new song
The fear that is the the Antichrist it's just that
Interpreting
Revelation
Bring the mark of the beast
It's need for buying a
Selling
Jack Van Impe
Rexel
We would watch it late night Christmas
The guy who looks like Ricardo Montalban
That's right rexella
Guys if you've never received Jack Van Impe
JV Pizza
Social social network
Alright
We're going to order something from Amazon before we do
But it won't be
With five Daddy's R5 mommies
Cuz you can have a human
Innocence system can only be humanoid
The crime will be being male female
The crime will be male and female in Union
Revolution
In the free love of men and women and then once they had you there by successive approximation
They walk you into the gates of hell
Bastard
I've been having free love my whole life
But that's just a fear of people put into slightly different language
And there was someone else there was a lady
In no way affect
That's crazy you are so you are so deep globalist rabbit-hole
Sears
Great things going to come is unlimited cloning
I'd like the limited clothing we have now
He's up on this idea that like the globalist want to
Make
May 11th
Female bad
And that's why they're creating like
He believes that they're making people
Want to be
Friends by tricking them when their children
And stuff like that okay
He's off on some
The wild shape
Just rhetoric from someone
Who's constantly on
Like
Live a real life
Just like think
What's rhetoric
From someone who gets most of their information from like Reddit I think that a lot of his
His scoops
And his Anonymous sources
Are Reddit posts
10-4 chance Duffin
Just like that
So I think it does
I think it informs him a lot but then at the same time I think he is aware that that's who is Audie
So you know people who are
Caught up in
Okay if you will
Because I
I'm not a huge fan I don't donate money but I tend to watch
The clips of The Young Turks
And my fear was coming in with like that
Dusty Jake fella
Was going to be like the
Progressive version of Alex Jones
Progressive Fox News
But now that I've heard the first 10 minutes of it
I'm fine
I like the idea of like
Is there a less version of Alex
Yeah and the closest we can come is kind of Keith Olbermann
Okay not as crazy
But he is unhinged
Who's performing
Yeah scream zabaneh
He has sources
And the way he talks is very similar to episodes of Ancient Aliens
Play Zayn
Yeah
Is I've noticed that molasse
Yeah yeah
It's not great but it's no like
There's no one like
Like this anywhere
Alex Jones
Except for
Possibly in like a snake charming Church
In Appalachia
Those people that would come into the Hardee's I worked at at
9:30 on a Sunday night in Knox
Clean up after those
Fairyloot
Business
His rent goes on
It's not
Just about
The sexual Revolution
Leaving us from
How about
How about we
You know
Trick you into it
Saxers
But
I mean
Bears
Bigger thing of foot
Cuz there is there are binary there's not just
Two genders and you switch
Spell someone
Switches to
The one that's how they feel they are
I mean I guess that is the case
Sometimes
Intersex
Spoke those
There's a whole range that are available to people
Alex
I was just like there was some days where I'm at
BJ's and there's some days where I'm at
Wants to watch Predator like I just
Figured that's how much
I'm having fun
Open free Society
They can successfully
Waukesha
Cultural and species
Wizard
Or just the humans
Everything will be defiled
Everything
Everything will be deformed every single be made
For Destruction
Before the force is allowed to finally kill everything on the planet
Because of free will the life must be turned upside down and must
It's delivery
But it will never get that far
Because God will spare flesh but if God didn't intervene there would be no flesh there
What you look very confused
Stories very religious
Yeah
What's the other globalist
From the New World Order
I feel like it's about to start a heavy metal band
Heavy metal bands
I would put clips of him talk
Skin before my songs
Good it's just f****** nonsense
Crazy
It's like listening to Rush Limbaugh I don't agree with them
As much as I do you start to get setup with the tricks
To make the show
Our first episode that was one of the two things you wanted to make clear off the bat
One is that
We don't want Alex Jones kicked off the air that's not our agenda
We are just trying to document how much of
A bigot and a liar
And then the other thing
Say what you want about him
Have a lot of
Yeah the ability
To just freestyle rap this s***
For like 20 minutes
It's unbelievable
Why
Spirit
Basically and now he's revealed
In the middle of this rant
But God's got a spare some of that
We take a turn towards
Old Walmarts
Tension cabs now hold on
It's complicated
Because Alex
About that
Stop
I'm back in back in 2015
That he thought it was a government takeover
And I can find
No real evidence that he's lying about that he said it was just trying to
Just like the public out and get them ready for the eventual military takeover
It's like
Basically
Fight on what episode some guy did call and say that he saw saw
People
In Walmart and
That's how you got a cell phone taken away for taking a picture
I'm flying out tomorrow
Half bear half knot
Yeah but you definitely said Sandy Hook was fake
He definitely thinks
That almost all mass shooting
That the victims aren't White
Sardar fake
Yeah it's that he's a very big
Boise Idaho
Guy
What happens now that there's literally
Like each side or whatever you believe on
There's enough
You mean these photos like denial of Truth
Follow the path that you want to believe in
Instead of having
To be faced with
The truth or
With other
Currently leads to confrontation confrontation
Be peaceful and fact-based
Like conversation
I know that's laughable
It's going to end up with malicious
Okay
I don't see any way that the
It don't matter what happens
Is Trump really
Let me get Dawes on the world stage
F****** nuke somebody
That's the problem
But in terms of our country's stability
I mean he doesn't matter in the sense that even if he's impeached
We still got a big problem on our
All right white nationalist
Fringe
There's been empowered and
Emboldened
Is not going to just go away
I'm just glad I'm a white male that didn't graduate college
You're right in their demo
I can't imagine it will be difficult the very very easy headspace
To get into
Chips Trucking people who aren't straight white
Just find a way to make
All right here's the next part of the
You're going to look back on these days as happy day
Halcyon
You're going to look back on this time
Screwing around playing video games
Your destiny not feeling fulfilled
I'll look back and you are going to beg on your knees God
But you never would have done the things you did those give it serve this but you're going to realize you don't
Deception in the end because you went too far and you spit the face life
Everything good
And you're going to turn and go
The direction you meant you were
Destin to go
Because it's what you chose
That is
Spiritual
Cultural
Oblivion
The force of Oblivion
Willing itself to death
William shelter suicide broadcast
Tornado
Rally's
Stop at Trump's perfect
Idea of magic
Albumin Majesty
Image of God that's Majesty
That's wild stuff
That's very
Because it's
It's such a f*****-up thing
Because
Ever
Since United States existed
We've had multiple political parties
Yeah people have a great and they've Disick
Yep going to happen forever
But now it's
Being Twisted into these waves
More than just political problem it's just now it's now it's
God that was all this stuff
And people that listen to this
I accepted Jesus into my heart
Late night
My family and I would have no food because
I'm about to get my head cut off of the guillotine
Movie when I was 13
But if you're
Like they're just going to that's their normal
Yeah it's hot.
Feel so horrible
Yeah
Obviously don't
Teaching
Well I mean I think you bring up a good point though that is important
And that is better
The idea that political arguments have happened for hundreds
The years and it's been
Rarely
Alex's conception of the world is that there are globalist
Who want to create a one world government that will bring about the antique
Andy's globalists are
Suspiciously always
The Democrat
But also the Republican
He doesn't like
Who are Libertarians are working for the globalist also
Like he was
Republican before that he was a weird libertarian
Conservative Republican
Head to his credit he hated George Bush
George h.w. Bush
As it were
He was very very critical of George W bush
And you know
Sort of gives him the appearance of
Impartiality
But the reality is he just decided the George W bush work for
The globalist
I am so f******
And then that makes it impossible to have a real argument politically
Is that
If you're arguing against
Alex Jones's worldview
That you are
By default arguing in favor of the globalist
Who want to create a government and bring about the
Who may or may not be Brock
Hussein Obama
What's it going to do
Well Larry Nichols
This guy who's on Alex's show a bunch
In the lead-up to the election was saying that
What they were going to do Obama was going to
Screw over Hillary Clinton
Obama leaks all the stuff about the server
In order to
Destroy her is a candidate
So that Joe Biden could win
And then I think what he was saying
Is it Obama would become the Secretary General of the UN
And turn the us into a Muslim caliphate
So Obama could be the president of Muslims worldwide
The country that Muslim we're just going to get the
Yeah so that was that's the fear that they have about it
It's all
If me saying these things sounds like nonsense
And they preach it to however million
The millions of people listen
Let everyone know
Probably that you're probably
Preaching to the choir with field Elizabeth I
I guess I don't know I don't know what you listen
What I mean is I don't know how many people might actually like houses or believe what he says or how many
People are just like those guys
Diagram of people who like us and people who like Alex Jones are two circles
Hangover
I just want to tell you I almost want a t-shirt
Obama
Happy president
Like he's just going to be a dude
That's just comes around the room
Cuz I was drunk believe that you set up a command bunker a block away from the White House
My name is George Soros are creating shock troops
President-trump
The greatest American president of all time low
Was that been sad
Oh my God
I don't think George Washington would want to say that political rhetoric
But
Yeah I do
How high do you have to
To be like where does it talk about
I think
It's one part brain damage
We've documented a couple incidents
Cosmo
Brain damage
If he's telling the truth about the
A couple of traumatic bashing his head into concrete when he was a child
I'm horrible but
How to go to the other side
Dial
But then also you got stuck under house inhaling fumes
In the future
Imma kill you I don't know I guess you would take that I'm a Jewish sympathizer so
And I'm across I do so I'm not perfect
No I'm not part of the master race
Anyway
But we're not nearly done with this
Asthma thing goes a lot
I'm the primary by people if they've just started like I'm the voice of the guy that does not
Short sentences what the f*** is going on
I enjoy that
So please feel free
To let your questions
GameFly
And there's just a
Tell right there
The horns of the Earth
Don't wanna reprieve
We want
What Jonah
What
Don't want Moses
We don't want any other
Is the weather
Because we're
Annexed
Goodness and the beauty
Because once they get you to be selfish wants you to feel like you're ugly
Embrace your evil side
And as falling relation for why anyone just likes Trump and his followers
Because they've been globalist
Listen to being selfish and immature
Tasty honorable people
I do a lot of people that did not vote for Donald Trump
93% of them would be
Be totally cool
With a guy who got swallowed by a whale
Still lived afterwards
I think he was pulling for names and that was an
I have to assume that he has like just cover
This is kind of like Jesus of the old test
David I mean there's a couple of
Does people out of a desert
Out of Egypt
We've documented a good amount of him really misunderstanding scripture over the course of this
Frequently cites
The Prodigal Son story
And get the ink
Incredibly wrong message from it
His version of the takeaway is that the dad really loves the older son
Who doesn't leave
Oh no you're welcome back we forgive
The basketball score
Close
This is where the rant wraps up
This is him
One minute to break
I realized
I got to wrap this baby up
So he pulls it in and he says
A couple things at the end
But I think our soup
Supremely disturbing
And then you wait
The globalist
Send you
Desecrate you
Before you into 1,000
Monster truck
I'll tell you one thing
I like the devil
Every night when I go to sleep
Little biscuits
Devil's real he wants to kill you
We could probably do an hour on that
Yeah he comes once a year first of all
Really having a gen.
No favorites that has never going to push you down and meet you
It's not like the Krampus
Smell
So
If I had to make a power ranking of the things that I find most disturbing
About the last
10 seconds of eclipse
I would say
Number one
Is it being like
Seen enough of the devil
Bobolike
The devil what the f***
Does that mean number one
Number two
Every night
In my dreams
That's f***** up
I know it's probably exaggeration
What the f*** are you expressing
I think you put the patch
That could be although we has talked about his relation
Smokey smoke as a child
What does the younger man voice
But no longer
I don't think he is a tobacco
At this point butts
He might just be you know what
You say
Like
Tobacco Patch
Super male vitality
How do you say always product
They'll probably what
Creating negative dream
He has a pill called knockout
That
That might be doing
Side effects
Talking to the decal at 3
Nightly thing
Spirit guide
Yeah I don't know I don't know enough about his
I saw that John Oliver
Where they bought a bunch
Because product on Santa
Come to a lab
To analyze them and they
Let me the basic conclusion they had was that they have what they say on the label in it
They don't have any like heavy metals or anything like that
So he thinks that that is like I've been cleared they tried to do a hatchet piece on me
But also in the in the breakdown if they have it
There's no science
The shows if it does anything
Yeah that's all just basically
Placebo
Depth
So there's that
Three device things have vitamin
Secret 12 is just vitamin B12
Okay great
Okay it's not a secret
There's
It's just more expensive
Did the one that you really sells meal
Life-changer
Is it colloidal iodine
Supplement
This is just normal
This is not special at all is iodine
No that's true it's true
I mean if I were to make a
T-shirt I probably mark up the price a little bit
Plaistow
I guess why not Market
The price of onion
You're not going around telling people that the globalists don't want you to have shirts
Another trying to kill you in the shirt will save your life
And that is the end of the ranch
But that's the first 10-15 minutes of the show
He's on for how long is 4 hours
He's on four for the four years on
Fourth hour today is Rodger Stone
Diu doesn't work
I heard that Paul manafort
What's that tabloid
Any just country
Yeah but all the details with us.
Will Rodger Stones response
Do it was
Haywire they
I had a hole
Like
Responsible
He knew that they
It came from Trump yeah super sucks out
The idea that if you like always, knowledge of the Trump plan stories in there
That's not good at all it's the type of thing where it's like
Give us dude that means
He's going to flip on me
Well there's that and they know he knows
Yeah
That's trouble
We are
Some fun guests on this episode
That I'm going to get you ready for we got Rodger Stone
He's going to show up for a little bit
We have
Steve pieczenik
We are going to really deal with
He is a former CIA psychiatrist
Ghost wrote books
Was Tom Clancy apparently
Spend
He'd actually the doctor
I don't I think he's legit I've never looked into the Tom Clancy
Happy stop but he is actually a psychiatrist
A psychologist
But
The other guests
There used to be most
Excited for
Is
The podfather
Adam Curry
The creator of podcast
Why Adam Curry comes in and I got bad news you're not going to like Adam Curry when this is
Iuc uses website
The message
Honestly I think we got to quit podcast
Adam Curry
Sincerely
Two steps away from
He'll show up soon
I'm going around and pit beer
O'Reilly's
That's fine
God bless
Target sell those books
Sure but
After that ramp
Going to dive into the
Going to go into the actual news of the day
Going to start by trying to really shine up that s***
That is the Paul manafort situation
Now before we get into it
It's important for me to point out to you
Closest associate
On Infowars is Rodger Stone
Rodger stone is on almost every day
He hosts the fourth hour like once a week
He's apparently getting his own show
On Infowars
Tattoo of Nixon face on his bed
F*** him
But
The thing that the reason I needed to bring that up is because
Rodger stone is also a close associate of Paul manafort
Specifically
I used to own a business
These two have like a
Consulting firm
Doesn't know
Until the news breaks publicly
Means to me
That Rodger Stone didn't know
Or Rodger didn't know and didn't tell Alec
And either of those possibilities
Is pretty f***** up
In terms of spheres of
Information
To try and
Spin this in positive life
Do you think there's a way and I know you're building of that I apologize
The djia
You're you're just about to start Bohemian Rhapsody and I started talking writer
As Freddy's
Do you think there's a chance that Jones could ever flip on
We could ever just go again
We've tried to WarGames this a couple times
I think he's in too deep now
But there's got to be a way
I think you could figure it out it would just require a perceived betrayal
Just him awkwardly
Eating crow for like 2 days ago
I think it would take more than two days
He's done
So much
Dick-sucking
He's he's been his biggest cheerleader
For over a year-and-a-half
So I think if you was going to flip it would take
He needs to decide what it is he was going to flip about
Start to build it up prepare his audience for it and then
Executed over the course of like a week
Can't do it now I think
I think you
Is it in trouble
But
Here is a how he wants to spend
The man-of-war
FBI raid
Ladies and gentlemen we get to hear that Paul manafort
He got raided
Ago
Isn't that just cute
FBI conducted
Campaign
Chairman
Manafort's home
Trump's former campaign chairman late last month
What's the special counsel investigation into Russian meddling
From what I heard
Just send them all the documents
Russian meddling
Ukrainian government
Pro us capacity
So that's the first
Part of spin there from The New York Times
Paul manafort he was forced out as President Trump's campaign chairman last summer after 5 months
Criticism about his business dealings with
Pro-russian interest
Disclosed Tuesday that his consulting firm received more than 17 billion dollars over 2 years
From Ukrainian political party with links to the Kremlin
The following serves as a retroactive admission
But Mr manafort performed in the United States and Power
Ukraine's party of Reba
Without disclosing it at the time
Time as is required by law
The party of regions
Is the political
Former president Viktor Yanukovych
Who fled to Russia during a popular Uprising in 2014
This is not pro us in
Sure of course
This is very much
Russian interests
Send Ukraine
And the reason that he had to flee
Was because
Job Ukraine's Got really pissed off in Russian
Intervention
And they're in their business
And that's why
Can't go to Ukraine now
Shorty will be killed
So that's bulshit
That's a load of bull s***
Also the idea that he's like oh yeah
Turn over everything
That's why they raided him
He didn't
You have probable cause
Like there's a whole thing
What they do right but if you're in Alex Jones's head you like
Now the globalists are just pulling strings is all for show
See some people being like
Even though it's f******
Dumbest s*** like
They're upset
Their candidate didn't win
So they're coming after
It's a witch and some people thinking that might be a pop
Haha
It's the 8th
Team thousand meanings addresses that they don't disclose
And it's just keep happening or you like
Probable cause
You're dumb
Because
Fake
Stories about lies about Russia
Meetings and what have you and then with your doing is they're moving the field like the field goal
Removing the post
Would you describe in this neck
Text clip
It's not about it's not about Russia
Little bit about Russia
And now.
Just showing their cards
Your check this out
Presidential
Russian now we're looking at
We're looking at the garage
Oh
Cross board
That's not that's not what I know
With the idea of looking at finances
Important as you can see
Where there is foreign money coming into places
100 different things Florida
That's why you got to go and look at all this money and stuff.
It's not a tax Dragnet but Alex knows his audience
This is Dominic be like
You know cheap moving the field goal
This is about Russia even though the country
Is Ukraine
B paid 17 million dollars to Mana for it
That's still very deeply connected to Russia
So
Rodger Stone comes on
And
Into some
Fairly paranoid
Rambling
Which is not uncommon
On for him
Then in this next clip
I don't know if
Let me be clear
I wrote this clip is very excited
But talks about how he is in a death battle
Basically
I don't believe him
Google
Publicly
Augusta back often.
We got hold on their territory
Facebook
Okay
I don't like that he's been talking about I meant it.
Divulge
It just developed
Right I don't mind
Site
I agree with you if that were what's happening
That's not what's happened
He got kicked off of Google ads
Because
He has a
Implied
Incredibly Close
Connection with
A president
And my clinical figures
Google ads
Okay so they refused
To put him in
They're advertised
Secondarily
He claims the Google is trying
To delist him
I make it so you can't search for Infowars length
Based on something that Mike cernovich found
That lately
These subcontractors were hired by Google to Mark Infowars articles
Is like
Bad
Mark every Infowars thing is bad
If you actually get into it it look into
To the case what happened was
This manual was created
In terms of like
Yu-Gi-Oh
It's very complicated how Google search
Work
Perform searches
Judge
How accurate
The things that come up are
Quality result
Thousand thousand
The People concert
Searching for things
And in their manual they use Infowars as an example of an unreliable source
Oh God has consistently things that they say are proven to not be true
And all that
I'm so they used as an example of something that would be deemed a low-quality result
Google
It was like well
General that was made by
Company that we hired and we agree that's not incredibly fair that we use that they use that as an example
So they corrected it
We're not
The d-list anybody
The truth constantly proven wrong
They didn't say that that's my editorializing
He's not fighting for
Free Speech if he was
I would be on his side in as much as that
If if people were like legitimately trying to crack down on him
Then we can have it Ark
Does people don't want to be involved with them
And
People are make
And he keeps breaking terms of service
Anyway
You would think that like if
He really had an issue the first thing
Like if someone really wanted to crack down and like right
Stop using this music
No
Good luck
Just coming in every break with Ted Nugent
Did you join this organization
Access all these clips
No God no
I wouldn't pay for this s*** okay
To pay for this
The show is over I'm not giving him any money ever
Giving money
Come to be a bigot
I believe him to be a very problematic racist man
Is a roller coaster
He doesn't understand all this race-baiting
Most of cases trappy false flag
Cultural Warfare
I'll get back to this as a shot is a genital wart
Shot that can be given
AR
One of the
UVA that's one of the biggest causes a server
Purple Panther
And if you don't
If you're not able to get hbv odds are you won't get cervical cancer
Temecula
So many women
And Alex Jones has this belief
That if any vaccine
It says
Like something is a potential side effects
Then that's actually why they're giving a
About how like autism or
Diabetes
Are like they're giving it to you in the vaccine
He pulls up the inserts of the vaccine
Humans biology isn't
Incredibly complicated 2nd medication
And he doesn't accept
You think so
Call the vaccine
That they're giving all these
Hispanic women
Gardasil shot
In the third world
In order to
Decrease their birth rate
And what have you because it leads to
Infertility problems
Beauty like
Give him all the
Instead of looking at it
There are unfortunate side-effects they're going to happen to a certain amount of people but compared to the amount of death it's caused by
People demon
Net positive
Like
He would talk about that more
Is like the same version of Ayo I have a black friend say stackable that I said
And also the idea that
White people attack black people is false Flags
A silly
The idea that
From time to time that like
It's 15
People attacking white people
And what does never really unpacked especially by Alex
Does the idea of the reporting of crimes
Police believe in the crime
People just wipe
Washington's way like I'm not going to deal with it
There's a systemic racism
Inside Police Department
Sharai Prime's against black people are often not report
So
Anyway
Like I said this is a roller
Cuban
He's been real white identity white nationalist be up to this point this clip ends
Cuz it's
Known to man
Fertility
Gardasil
It doesn't mean we don't expose
We need financial support
Water filtration
Why people trying to kill white people
Weird racer children
We've got toothbrushes that are impregnated with silver
Werewolf
How ridiculous
The pretty like we're saying though in terms of his skills it's pretty impressive to be able to make that kind of a pivot
Go from like
Weird race
Conspiracies into
Give us money
Was that
Dietary coverage
Does manafort's stuff for now
You know it's just a big toe
Text Dragnet
It's all trying to cover up for probably the crimes of Hillary Clinton
He doesn't really ever cover news
Kind of
If it was you alone
And you are a bigot
The boy
Clip
Finally heard
The audio of what Trump
Said to North Korea
From his vacation
I hope his quote about fire and fury
Why am I surprised
Play like bothered by but I like why
Yeah of course it's going to be the exact opposite of what
His immediate reaction
Are you bored
Cuz there been a couple times
The big ones
These were
Long ways back
He went on a rant about how marijuana should be legalized
I totally agree with that
Pump that he's on that
Okay and then also few super again
Police being able to commit to the last
The forfeiture
So whenever you're like
Roll around a bunch of money images
That's what I think I'm super against that too
Eminent domain issues like that use on the right side
Yeah totally
He doesn't square that up at all but I'm
I'm not
I'm not worried when we agree
Some about vaccines
If there was
Even if you're crazy there's some things you believe that aren't crazy
Stop
Layaway
Here is that yours Alex
Doing a little bit of nice analysis of the Trump comment
Seen before
Nevada
Fascinated by that split
He looks evil the real Donald Trump
If that's like
That's your man propagandists losing
Baptized
So I talked a little bit more about North Korea and what's probably going to have to
To be done
With them and
Is off
Knox
I have four children I don't want one
Butt slapping
Quickly
Get involved in this when we do this
They got million plus man
Rockets
Not Justa control but high-powered Atomic weapon
Hydrogen bomb
Radiation weapons
Direct energy weapons
North Korea
Butthead
We are still at war with North Korea
Surprised
To hear that he does not go over all of it at the top of the hour do just now.
That's a bummer
That's where the clip is not great
No
But I was having a conversation
About how I feel like
Either someone in Japan or
South Korea
Going to have no idle
You think it's all just a petulant child
I hate
To be a naysayer just in case
Stopping really bad does happen
But I don't call
So I can rub in your face but all those people.
I don't believe that that is in
North Korea strategic in
What is interest
To have a nuclear weapon
So they have like
Basically
Look at be f*****
Using it is
In any way helpful
Like I don't think even under the sea
Threat of their own destruct
Cuz I mean
They teach the population that the United
Destroy them
But I don't think that Kim Jeong Hoon
I don't think that the higher-ups
Actually think that
They think that
People would
If they could take them out but they know that
Yeah they know that the rest of the world understands that there's way too many Rams
If they were to attack
Because
Soul is such an easy target
From from
Beyond the DMZ North Korea could hit them
So easily and that's Millions
MZ
Play my God
Can I get a few more workers there I like this B
I've had nothing but wonderful experiences with the Chicago DMV
But
Yeah
I want
I hope more than anything
I don't want
You know what a tablet
There is one Past
What's that
We could have a
The new series
That's true
Not worth it
People do
I would say that
Short of us attacking them
This is going to watch it
But don't you look at a
President who's 38
Nothing else is going down
Hey wait what's the way to get popular I think even he he
I know that
That's the wrong way to do that
You would want to go and run out of non-nuclear countries to invade
McCabe
Trouble
The news
Flexing on r-and-r not in line with the agreement
He was saying already like a week ago
Even if they're found to be in compliance I think they're not
Which is bad fat
Here's the f******
Something about this rain
If Trump
Now invalidates the agreement
Or tries to pull out
The only people that really win
Because they got all their money back
And
Positive thing for us to do
Stay in it
Yeah but a black guy
Bright
I always forget about that
We are here what their job is it
To try to get rid of everything that happened over the last
Release people in Congress
Literally
What they wanted to do today barackobama
Zebra
I called that s*** two years ago also shout out to Jeffrey Lord finally getting fired from CNN
You're gone
It's very difficult to keep track of all this
I don't know how you do this
Are you
You brought by at like
And I'm just so beat down by this
Just for one day I would say that me and Jordan are both
Crazy some sort of
I can't explain it cuz it's not healthy but there's some sort of fun
And exploring Alex's crazy
Because
You're just jumping and you haven't listened to a lot of or old episodes
But a lot of ways that
He does not make anything he says okay
Get
By my estimation
From what I've learned over
We're studying him
Solidly for the last 8 months
Is
That he is
A child
He has arrest
The development
The probably stems out of
Childhood drug use
Childhood brain damage
Under parenting
For some sort of abuse as a child or combination
Vera
The world
Infantile way
That is
Inform his philosophy about these globalist
He started reading books that he couldn't
And when he was a child
And now
He's gotten to a point where he's very successful
Got a paranoid Army of races
Just behind him
And
There are a lot of people like Rodger Stone
Like these other gas that he has on
Gorgeous using
I'm just getting tricked by guess
Over and over and over again
It's very sad
But the consequences of it are they real
But
Sent Brogan die anyway
Kind of fun to laugh at the
Stupidity
Sure
It's like the reality
Soaked into
Some more fun stuff
Rodger stone is about to appear
He is he is not
Audible
In this clip
This is Alex Jones talking to Rodger Stone
This makes Scorpio predictions on death
But he does so in a really weird way
With with with with comedy shows
He's super mad at like Colbert and John Oliver because they've done jokes about him
Believe the comedy shows are part of the globalist apparatus
It's a it's fun
Yeah absolutely
Cutting off our sponsors
You expect
I respect you
I wonder why
Because she was a criminal
This is the kind of crap
I'm a winner
Move forward
We are going to defeat these people we are the winners
We are the free market we are the American
Hello hello
It's right around the corner they're going to kill me
Rodger Stone
Twice Donna death hoax
Yeah like he's pretended that he got poisoned with polonium like 9 months ago
Have a couple months after that he was in a
Bizarre
Witness list car
T-boned by a guy who's trying to kill him
Present the idea he had the flu
He said he got polonium
His doctors told him not to tell anybody I said don't talk about it
Polonium poison
No you said all that crazy
Zip.
Shabadaba
Could just do the s*** out of
They came to the came to an agreement because he apologized
Then retracted
The story that he did
But ever since then he's played it like
They couldn't wait to get out of that lawsuit they're lucky they got out without paying me
Do you reported lies
Besto Trump
Entire episode about the Chobani situation
That's really interesting episode
That really highlights
How f*****-up Alex's
Ciabatta bread it's really good I love it
Sure know a lot of that
Oh my God
Shirt
So Rodger stone is on
And his next clip
He reveals that he's part of a secret
Society
But talks about what they do
Which makes it no longer really a secret society
I heard something about him being a swinger I think you might be but you know I don't like to get into people's personal lives
I don't know if that was what I was
No this is
Very Trump debate
We have pledged
For a government raid for harassment
So you're in good company
Because you're the tip of the spear because you are
So
You see there the it ends with some nice
You're the best
That's a Hallmark of Alex guest sort of manipulating him
You're so important you're the you're the greatest
Rodger Stone got this group of three hangs out with
What are you do you just sit around with like brandy
Sit around and talk about this is going to be targeted
Jared Kushner
Clearly doesn't indicate that he had any foreknowledge of
Manafort's raid before the news broke
Zion Wednesday
What is he now
What kind of inside information does he have
It's just him and his a****** friend sitting around and commiserating
That's
Crazy also if you're really a secret organization don't f****** bring that up on the Alex Jones Show no
That makes me think that you just
Maybe it isn't
Girls Club
So weird
He doesn't have a lot to say it's mostly just up
Yeah that's it
But now we got to get to Adam
Got it to the podfather
Oh my gosh
Should I throw to a video
He doesn't
No but he
He does have a podcast apparently called the No Agenda show
Which
He
Every podcast
I got an agenda do you have one I feel like you're one of like 6 people to have a
Agenda
Some agenda
Everything's like the no Spin Zone is like the worst name show ever
Like what you mentioned he is a former MTV VJ
Basically I don't know exactly she invented podcasting but everyone being like
The first
Yeah to do podcast
But also what you don't know
Is that his uncle was a
CIA
Dawn
Don Greg
This is named parallel
And so he has a lot of information about North Korea that you don't have
Because
He wants to give you a little bit of analysis
About the North Korea situation
And I actually do agree with a tiny bit of
In terms of
Did this is probably not going
Flare up
But his take on
Is very interested
The people are still in
Once you see them leave
That's probably that's probably
Industrial complex
What region
That we've been trying to sell the
We of course want missile-defense there to keep our eye on China
North Korea is not suicidal
I also don't think the president's words meant nuclear war
Fury and Fire
And really hot
In another remove in his negotiations
Kim Jeong Hoon
One way or the other
What's trying to sell them at what time
Well
I don't I don't think that's what
Primarily motivated
But then beyond that with the end
You got to give
Kim Jeong Hoon
The chance to save face
What they're getting at what they get into is the idea that Trump will be like
All right look
You get rid of your nuke
And then 50 years down the line will reunify Korea
And it'll be you who did it
Be the one responsible for reunifying
North and South Korea
Like what that's what
That's what's going on
You think that's what's going on
That's not what's going on
No
But that's what they think of
Because
That's what North Korea would want but if it
If they're in charge
Right
That's a big problem with this
Because neither side would copper
Yeah and that's why they
Our two countries
Michelle Renee
Okay
I will do that
Adam Curry is
A bit of a ray
Realize
The guy who brought us podcasting
Is a difficult big
But let's listen to this next clip
Explains that desert
Cultures are not compatible
Well obviously there are problems and to my original premise
The problem is we want to have stuff in that area to keep on Shining
Interested
There's stuff going on that we really don't understand don't know much about
And man do we have
Cultural differences
Incredible cultural differences with the Chinese
Chinese tourist I was in in Florence
We are very incompatible from everything that I've seen and I'm just talking about the people that come to
Sisters
But she's completely
WhatsApp
Push you out of the way
So this is one of the big
Nationalist narrative
Is that other cultures are not compatible with ours
Yeah because of I don't know
Intrinsic problems that they have
Put on the street for people homeless
Sure in every culture
Chicago
It happens in every city
With homeless
So it's f*** off with the
Trying to paint Chinese
Evil Street shitters
Yeah
But
I work in tourism
Where
You know you get sort of stereotypical Lake
Well you know what I don't normally get tips from
People from this cut like that often
European
Who don't give a
Go to parts of Europe tipping is rude
So like you giving a tip
Is
Out of line so what we think is generous is actually not appropriate
So they're not being rude
Feels bad cuz he want their money
People love me so much I only made $4 I'm not sure if I like you so much but it would be rude of them to give you
Money because
Oh poor person here too
That's the motivation behind
Anyway
I drove last night for the
Cheap trick for sale yeah
I made $285 in
Everyone's on Polk
Is great earth coked-out going to be Cheap Trick
Brother man somebody
Very strongly
Dislike The Narrative of
Incompatibility
Proven
By people
Being unwilling
To be compatible with
People who come in
That's how the evidence is incompatible
Because we bully people
I&i Uno other them
Until they insulate completely into their own
Cloisters
And then one crazy person of that group attack
Awesome then we see it is
Compatible
What sister
Look at the whole Rihanna. Whatever
She's not that way cuz you Rose
Eraser the United States you raised her culturally different yeah that's how
Confused on point though
No because
Those cultures are bad
And we don't want
People from those cultures coming into our culture
But I just don't understand
The end
Serta result of that mentality
Because
At a certain point
It has to be eradication of those bad cultures
It's all gravy baby
I think he's dumb and
I really really really really really get worried when people start
Disgust
The possibility of
Integrate
And stuff like that because it really smacked
Of
It's not cultural if that's not what it's about
People who are different
Course
One more quick left before we before we end this adventure
Well you know
You know there's only so much
To discuss
He only yells about North Korea couple times
Paul manafort narrative is stupid
It is
I expected honestly that's a rant you did it
Beginnings take us much longer to get through
Yeah
You wanted me to not talk as much
Cuz you're allowed to get there
Size for a pulled back
Apologizing
Spiritually we have a lot to
Lot of lot of bulshit
Yeah
Describe his balls
Alright this is Adam Curry
Saying
Some stuff
That
I don't know how to put two
Too fine a point on this
She might
Be a literal name
I don't know and I'll explain my case after the create
Okay so what if he had a podcast early that's
We can still keep podcast
Next week Leo Laporte thought I was Chuck
So here is a
And then what's the cultural deal with
Running around like pirate ships
Further in the European Union are recently
The idea is to create a uniform
People who look like in Amsterdam
And I saw the transition
First it was a Turkish Inn in Moroccan
Second third generation
The culture kind of float
Is to have a big massive people
Bringing people who can do the work that the
The old people the whitest people
And slowly create a big
Beautiful buildings injuries
Yes
S***
Yeah
So
Do you want to learn a little bit about what he just said there
So he's talking about white
People race mixing
And stuff like that and how that's really negative
Yeah he brings up the color
You not making it up it's not a conspiracy theory
Now
If you're out there listening
Please feel free to do
Google the kalergi plan
It's kalergi
You can go as far as you want down the Google results
Almost every single website
You will find
Is white
Supremacist
Neo-Nazi
F******
Crazy anti-semitic New World Order
Yeah hundred percent
There is no such thing called the kalergi plan
It is something that is
Meetup
Buy these
Dudes who think that whiteness
Is somehow being under attack
It's a white genocide narrative
And here's how it began
There's a guy named Richard Vaughn
Cove color
You're the gentleman back in the 20s
He came to prominence
He was the son of an Austrian and a Japanese wife
Multicultural in his in his life
And he understood that
Another bad thing to have different cultures
I in your family
Who is Big Life
Create something called Deep and European Union
Back in the in the
Twenties
His philosophy he believed that
Race would eventually disappear
Hey societies evolved
And
That all these white nationalist white supremacist sites take out of context
Is this quote
The man of the future will be of mixed race
Today's races and classes will gradually
Appear
To the vanishing of space-time and
The Eurasian negroid race of the future appearances
Egyptian
Will replace the diversity of peoples with a diversity of individual
I find nothing scary about that
Everyone all these f****** people are
Scared about their whiteness
That they're like
Did the plant that's what they want that they're going to make that happen
All he's saying is
That's probably what's going to happen as people get rid of their hatred overtime and become more acquainted
Did with other cultures Bowl outcome of of people
Not being assholes
We have planes
We have ways to be around the people of different things.
So it's going to happen
People got to be falling in love or f******
And that's probably a radical
In the twenties of this is probably what's going to happen in the future
Not at all
A crazy idea
That is there were to be some sort of thing where he actually said
I'm going to
To make different races
Is Buck
I'm going to make him interbreed
In order to create these
People who look like ancient Egyptians
Then
It's f***** up
Cuz I don't think you can do that
The problem store
It's forced
Crossbow
Problem problem
Secret of a bigger problem implementing
That plants
They believe that like
These these migrated melted
Do that
These migrants that are coming into they believe that it is like
A force
Wave minorities,
2D white place
Bucked up
That is straight-up white supremacist
Thinking whites
Supremacist
Good plan
I took it was like they're bringing these people in
To do jobs that old white people don't want
What to do anymore
Which
Still happen
We can kind of agree is
Disparity
There is like
Immigrant labor issues but that's not what the color
Really fun
Compare to Alex Jones
And Adam Curry talking about the kalergi plan it being globalist
Wanting to d-white society by bringing in
Brown and black people
In order to breed with them
Hitler opposed
The clergy
Because he felt that this pan-european Union idea would be a pacifist country
They wouldn't be able to
Defend itself against the inevitable
Attack from the United States
Okay so that's one problem
He also believed that the the planning for the pan-european Union
Was full of Mason
Which if you want to translate to Alex Jones vernacular
Global
Don't forget it
There's a problem
Because Richard Vaughn I could have colored
Was roundly post anti-Semitism in defend
And the Jews
Vociferous
So Hitler hated this guy
And thought that his organization was full of globalist
Yeah basically
There's an analog here
Alex Jones
Kind of undecided.
That's where I'd like to leave things
Terms of italic
There is no kalergi plan
Adam Curry
It's f****** straight-up spouting Neo-Nazi white supremacist bulshit on Alex's show
I don't give a s***
Grew up on MTV
He did
Wake me up
Alex Jones one of his biggest problems he doesn't f******
Have anywhere to save the world release
So you just allows people
Ideas like this
I'm going to guess that he doesn't know all that much about this kalergi
Plan idea
For that the only place
Are f****** hate
Stairs
Scares me the idea of him f***
Screaming at me about demons
Gunship
An hour behind
What do you think that would sear Xperience of your first Adventure into Alex Jones lamb
It is not Paul's as I would have guessed
Once I put in the
The practice of people actually watching it for real
Once you start to think about that it becomes less funny
And also
I appreciate that you take the time to do all this
Can watch the video of him also doing that
Like some of those
Like
It's not bad but I would have like to seen what he was doing
It's not as visually appealing as you might think.
Screaming once you seen it all the time
This is very rarely
Aesthetically pleasing
Ready to do that but never will
But you have to listen to the whole show
Do I ever
Yeah
And they're still after 8 months
There's not a point where you're kind of like
Parkside
No
Because I know enough about him know that I'm not going to be led down to The Darkside by a f****** idiot
There are moments
When
Maybe I
A couple times I've gotten high in the last
Few months
Those are the times that I'm like
I can't handle this
Because I Am Naturally skeptical of rich
I don't think
Vetta corporate interest
Are really they don't want to
I do have a distrust
Of
5 super powerful
Really confident and on a rant
And I'm a little high
I can't defend myself severely I'm like
You're really confident about your ideas you must be right
But that passes
I realize oh no no no no no
This is a monster is dude
Angel Robles.
I don't understand
And maybe it's cuz they're older they're getting older they're scared what might happen
The world after they're no longer around
You mean Alex
Korean
Does Clipson
Play they want to keep the white race
Like I said it's mostly with
The last moments at my heart
It's tops
And that it's all done
Right
You know heaven
But
I don't know
Maybe it's cuz I don't care
I don't know I just don't care I think I think one of the pieces of it is that for you and I
The fact that were white doesn't matter that much to us
Yeah a lot of people who it is a very important piece
To them
And then I also almost a little not a flip of that but in the same vein
Is that we are white
And we are
So we have to
To be conscious of notches
Taking that for
Cuz I think we do is easy
These that you take for granted that's just your life that's the life that you've always known
No matter what
You are or whatever
So but I get reminded by like my fiance when she's like
Yeah I had to I ran into
Do the courtyard and like make sure the door was locked
Because I was afraid of some
Get me
That makes no sense
Because I'm 6 ft 2 in gigantic
Is never a fear of
Sure you know black people dealing with
So it's
Wright's I'm trying a new Baseline for a lot of other people's existence
Yeah
And I'm trying to be more aware of
Okay I want to erase pen
So if people want to send you some Ray spent money they can do it at Riggs for you yahoo.com
And I work a lot of tourists
Stuff we just had 200 congratulations
And it's a fun time
I'd rather plugged
If you live in Chicago
Add at North bar
Credits
3 show
It's super fun
Jokes if by chance you're listening to before this Sunday we have
A guest of the show Friends the show Marty DeRosa 100sq hop
They're all going to be doing
Stand-up for sketch the heck of a show
Jeff Hernandez
At North 8th
Very weird to have something
The plug that isn't their website
Got that today, it didn't dawn
But you know what's
What about talking trash. Com
But everyone out there that is
Play podcast me and Matt Riggs about short
Arab
The stupid ass on Twitter at knowledge underscore fight and we are on iTunes
Knowledge fight
Apple Park
Book
We are out there on the streets I really appreciate all the messages
Super awesome to engage with fans
Brandon
Also
I forgot
What do you think about this Crush
It's a little sweet
Whole bunch
Good facsimile of a soda but it's pretty sweet
So now I don't care anyway
Who's been fun
Anytime Jordans out of it
Thank you for joining me and keep your resume on file
No
But I can tell you
Formulate
This is business guy
Is old dude
He's kind of an a******
Got a big bushy beard
Yeah
Written about stuff
But I wait IV
Kids and stuff
He's a real weird dude
Comes on Alex Jones
The show a lot
Mental illnesses
Breland
Medication is
Trying to kill you
John Rappaport
Gofucker
Thanks for holding
Alexandra Thurston color