Damn
I have great respect for knowledge by knowledge I'm sick of them posing as if through the good guy
College fight
Nick.com
Worship at the altar of Selena
Alex Jones
Sup today is
Coca-Cola
Coca-Cola classic or newco
Podcast noted Lee famous
Critical
Of their space flight
They came out with that space flavor no concept of a Coca-Cola Space Universe
Supposed to taste like
I got only way I could find that was in like a six-pack of minicamp
Wright still in my fridge
No interest in drinking down there
They're garbage
Coke put out another flavor called Dreamworld
Which is supposed to be the flavor of Dreams
I'm sorry whatever the f*** they're doing I guess it's some kind of viral marketing campaign it must get enough attention
Like based on how these ideas
You know people talk about eikyou with
The flavor of space saver 3
You know I think that's
I think they're dissecting Travis Scott's AstroWorld you know cuz that's a mixture of
Yeah well I mean you got a you got space and you got Dreamworld
Put them together you got AstroWorld
I think that dream world was much more of us
Success
Pretty good
Kind of a passion fruit kind of vibe to it
Coca-Cola mixed with a certain
Do there's maybe a couple of fruit
Kind of feeling better let me ask you the ultimate question those did they itchy you a taste
That would remind you of a dream
I guess
World do you dream of passion fruit
Right on the nose all right if not then maybe not I don't know I have no interest
Assessing the accuracy of flavors
I will just say that it's pretty alright
Who is the taste tester for Dreamworld
Did active the rapper dream date
Anyway I appreciate the salvaged what was the last of that shattered reputation
The Dreamworld
Yes what about you
For me it's a new album out by jid
Tastic album okay
Excellent album
It's one of those things
Kingswear
Maybe only an outside critic
Can kind of look at Subway on
And then accelerated to a high extent so this is like jid
Looked at Kendrick's last album I was like
What if I did the most tender
You know in like Kendrick can do the most Kendrick kids would say hold my beer right
Something that it's almost also a little bit of an omage
Combined with a little bit of a parity in a way
You know it's just like
Taking out a lot of Kendrick
I'm really hammering it home like he's changing time signatures every 5 Seconds changes voices
You got characters going on
This is Kendrick is s***
You know that's what he's doing
Right but it's really good
I'll check it out that's Matt we can't check it out I've started to exercise
I'm listening to a bit of music and I will save it
Stuck
L2
I don't think that would have helped me up and I got deep into a
I don't know
Too late copy of Mamma Mia no 2010's pop
Okay alright take Fall Out Boy some of those hits are better than we remember
No they're not
I'm going to leave this here
Snakes on a Plane by Cobra Starship was alright
Alright
Workout
Alright I does that does sound like a strikes strikes recorded
Today we have an episode to go over haha
And take a little break
For Dam
I wanted self-care comes in all sorts of shapes
Sizes and varieties haven't just decided today
I was going to back 2000
Because I wanted to
Substance
Did deal with middle of the week was going on
Is just like
Is b*******
I don't know spinning wheels rambling about others going to be
Call swags before the midterm share share share all the f****** time still can't believe he cares about the
The midterms right now it's pretty it's pretty fun
I guess
Something to talk
Talk about so many times and promoted book somebody to
Is out
I'm going to be getting that book
Okay we're going to do that episode of
Again the self-care I needed was something with meat on the bone
Yes I am so we're back to August
6 2003 that's where we are in our progression through 2003
Scroll back through the the episode
Yeah I'd say more my baby
Well I mean the trial got in the way and what have you
Excited to go over this and discuss some of the b******* that Alex was doing on this day back in 2000
Let's say hello to some news
So first Conrad Zimmerman isn't the cult leader but he does have novelty Beverages and snacks
Thank you so much you're my apology Wong
Very very much laundry in the canals of Amsterdam
Terrifying to in a certain way
Journal policy walk
Thank you very much I know that I just said the Fall Out Boys
I'm good song so now you not want to talk I don't have no credibility in this week but I disagree
Nobody's going to argue
Next
This one
Late sorry about that
Thank you very much everything right monkeys
For turtles
Stone
The mechromancer thank you so much you are now attacking
Democrat
Miami
And then we're going
To come back
And I'm going to
Start the show over
F*** you
I got plenty of words for you
At the end of the day
F*** you and your new world order
She rode in on
And all your s***
Maybe today
Maybe I'll
Got to hear tomorrow
And you never see me again
Back here again
I apologized
Start yesterday
Was legitimately
Thank you
Mount Jordan
Yes we have an out-of-context drop
Population
The basic yes yeah yes
This is great
If Alex has very frequently talked about how big is audience
10% of the world
Yeah
This this was a new level of brag
What the heck
6%
Of the of the web traffic and then there's Infowars MMA
Banking information
One out of every 10 paid hits
Wow wow I've ever you know when you think about that do you think those Google search results and they bring back
A billion
Results you know in like a second or whatever
That means it's roughly
10% of those are Infowars articles of some sort
He has a lot of tentacles
Until maybe all of these websites
Every p******* part of Infowars
These Diversified
And that does seem like a back door
Some enterprising reporter language
So let's jump into today's contact
Go with a major world news story
Alia Bhatt
Was another global
So for some perspective
This episode is from August 6th
And the bombing of the Marriott in Jakarta happened on August
East 5th
Well there is no preponderance of any evidence
Completing Alex to say it's looking like a globalist plot you just literally says that about every
I was wondering what the globalist plot in this regard
Well I mean okay if the globalist plot but what is their plot Beyond just they decided to blow up this
Oh okay
So it goes like this
The globalist
Are attacking
Sort of Western etarget
Indonesia hotel chains
Write in order to force the hand of the Indonesian government
To playing along with their globalist takeover and crack down on the public install a martial law
Indonesia so goes the work
Classic cig the Sun never fell on the Indonesian Marriott chain
Yeah I believe is what it says yet essentially the plot the plot is
To try and force the hand of the government
To go along with her blow up all your McDonald's
Basically
Okay so incidentally these two bombings that Alex is talking about working
As they were both carried out by members of the terrorist group Jamal
Islamia
Members of the group or were convicted of doing
String of bombings in Bali
There were a couple that in that in that attack
Sure and it's pretty clearly established that they were behind the Jakarta bombing as well
What are the more persuasive pieces of evidence that was found was the head
Love the suicide bomber which was identified by multiple sources as being a man
Sunny
Who was a member of j i
I'm guessing Alex good to say that that was planted there or something because he's smart and he loves back
Ivy
Did you just say what I heard you say and that's
Like we're going to be fine with that
I'm so the suicide bomber went into a hotel and blew himself up
Well I believe it was a car bomb
Okay
Still
But
Of all the things that were intact
His head was identifiable
Yeah yeah yeah
Crazy
Intex is a is a way to put it
Ikea
We're not talkin dental records
Like it literally sounds like somebody walked by there like holyshit it's him
How have you been
Yeah it was other members of the the group who had been arrested identified him
I don't want to be
Morbid right
It is wild
Aridity
No I don't I don't disagree
That's wild
And that's probably why Alex would say it's fake
Probably wouldn't do something like that
Because
Your response is what people how people would respond to it yeah it was something a little bit
I would be very suspicious yes
Yeah so jamaat-e-islami I was a terrorist organization that operated in Indonesia
Mostly inspired by opposition to the more moderate forms of Islam that were practiced there
This was
Seen as a form of Western degradation so they targeted things associated with the Marriott Hotel in Jakarta
That largely tourist area
In Bali where the bombings have
Right the group
I had received funds from an organization called all haramein which is a charity that had clear ties to Al-Qaeda
But I remain did engaging a bunch of legitimate charity work some of the funds were dispersed
The terrorist groups like jamaat-e-islami ah
Which led to the charity being shut down in 2004
Yeah yeah
Is a charity organization that is based in Riyadh Saudi Arabia
The point is that Alex is legitimately just talkin
He hasn't had time to come up with any conclusions or way the preponderance of evidence
But he can't resist the opportunity to blame this tragedy on his imagined enemies
And incorporate that made-up story Into His larger conspiracy worldview and so keys
Saying that there's a preponderance of evidence
Right
Just saying
I mean I think this is interesting
Insofar as
It feels like this is one of the few times where the plan in real life has been in
Exactly as bad as Alex
This is fake globalist
How do you mean I mean
It's just
Tactically I don't think that's going to achieve what it is but they think they're trying to achieve you know what I'm saying
No one no one
No one is going to care if you blow up a Marriott I'm sorry
I think people did
Haha
Like it's a low-level Target
You're not going to get what you want out of the Marriott
Conceivably
One of the reasons
Statues that is that it
Frequent it by tourists
And foreign Nationals
And it would cause
A
A reduction of Western tourism to the Western influence possibly business
This is would be scared of
Coming in Europe there are ripple effect that you could
Could think
Might be
Be achieved by attacking these Western Target
I don't know if I think the idea is as bad as you are thinking it is
I respect is a terrible idea I can understand the thought process
Gets there
Is a lot
So we are I think see it I see it I'm just it this is just one of those
It plots
Ultimately that has been
Tried before
And it doesn't really
You know it doesn't really do it
That's just not how you you got to get you got to get a good one
Well Hope Springs Eternal
Zoe
Trying to nail down exactly like where this conspiracy
He comes from or what Alex is
Basing this on
We get 21
Fairly
Relevant
Peace
Good morning
4 Hour
Before
Not
Warren
The Belize government I think it's Alex thinking the Bali is its own country if I remember
Tunisia
Alex Simpson
I don't know what he's doing
So infused with Alex is going to do to try and make this conspiracy steak is work with the idea that there was some kind of advanced
Warning of the bombings
They were feds on the ground
Immediately
As always this stuff is
Partially true
There were federal agents there but not USA
There were two groups from the Australian federal police who were working with the Indonesian law in for
One on a Narcotics operation and one on an anti-human trafficking task force
They were able to respond to the bombing
Mbali considering that they were already there in the country
But this isn't suspicious and it doesn't prove anything close to a conspiracy or false flag
And again
This is related to the 2002 Raleigh bombings I posted the Jakarta bombing that just had
Happened that Alex's
Discover a different situation playing fast and loose
These details a little bit and I think it's intentional
So there was some Advance warning but that's not not necessarily a thing where it was specific enough to guarantee the
Ability to stop either the Bali bombings or the Jakarta bombing before they happen
In the case of the Bali attacks the US
Captured Omar Al Farooq who was understood to be a high-level Al-Qaeda operative in the region
His contact information has been found in the possession of number of senior members of the group and after the US forces in
Irrigated hemenway's it almost certainly bordered on torture
He talked and explain his role in the Southeast Asian sell of al-Qaeda
The US attempted to pass this intelligence onto the Indonesian government because part of it involved a reasonable suspicion that they
They were planning an attack somewhere near the anniversary of 9/11
What are the recommendations that the u.s. made was that the government should arrest
The prominent cleric named Abu bakar Bashir
Who al-farooq had named as being someone who was involved
In the organization and planning of attack
The political situation in Indonesia the time was
Was very tense
What's with a secular president of megawati
Sukarno putri who's vice president
Hamza has said to have close ties with many of the radicals of the US wanted to focus on including
Beshear
Do you have this vice president
President who was on the other side Erica Ware
Like it would just be the top to voters get in so it'd be piano
This guy and then the guy who hates him the most on the planet is the vice
It's a tough situation to navigate
The country is majority Muslim and megawati didn't want to make any arrests
Particularly of religion
Just figures about evidence of their haven't committed a crime
Switch bus
Couldn't provide
The warning that the US had was too vague to be actionable in the Indonesian government was somewhat in a bind
Ultimately the Bali bombing
Could not be stopped but afterwards the megawati government began to act
Be arrested but she ran with a string of church bombing
He said he'd been involved in that occurred on Christmas Eve
You're 2000
Scaccia in the lead-up to the
Jakarta bombing Australian federal police were still in the country because the government had asked for their assistants investigating
Volleyball
In the course of that investigation many members of jamaat-e-islami oh were arrested and questioned
And a picture began to take shape
That another bombing was being planned but no one provided
The specific Target they were planning to hit
Just that it was likely that the group would attack a soft
Target
If that's all you have to go on
You can be on guard somewhat be
You can't possibly deploy the resources necessary
Attack every soft target in the country
Or even
All of them just in Jakarta
Well I mean yeah it is it is a warning that says bombing is coming
But without where or what or whom you or how to stop it
So you're like
Well yeah but what do I do with
Right now
The notion that like a soft target would be chosen
Isn't really that much
The new information of revelatory because
The original bombing
Was of a bar
You know
It's okay
Then you kind of get the sense that that's
In the
The mo I mean even then that's not really good in
Intelligence there because like oh well
You could just be assuming that they're going after a soft target or you don't even really know what is
Soft target
Too damn quiet house off this song
Stuff Tactical
Nothing you saying means anything and he refuses to take responsibility for the things that he says
He just throws it at the wall and then moves on to another room for anyone can make
Can clean up his mess
None of this is
It has any connection to
The reality of the situation
He's blurring details
Intentionally or because he doesn't know any better about
Two different incident
I mean you don't even understand
He's a he's got people on the ground with the bali's as we speak you know like he's he's there
He overthrew the ball leaves government
Country album
Steve is notably part of the body of sovereignty movement
Make sense
So Alex has some other news stories he wants to hit on
This wasn't a story that was in the guardian the day prior
This is an article from September 6th
2002 in the aftermath of the Bali bombing
Right whenever they did know stuff
About a thing
The basic gist of the story is this
In November 2002 British citizen named Christopher rodway was killed in a car bombing
He was an engineer employed at the military Hospital in Riyadh
And in the immediate aftermath of the Saudi government said that this was not terrorism but was actually more likely a personal matter
At the time Saudi Arabia had a public stance that it was very insistent that they did not have any terrorist elements
Existing in the country
And this would contradict that narrative so there was an attempt to find another explanation
When personal reasons didn't stick a bunch of employees at the British Embassy were accused of carrying out that bombing with the goal of blaming
The Saudi Arabian government
Seven people were held in prison for long stretches treated quite poorly and a couple of them were actually sentenced to death
Before ultimately being released
This is a story that Alex is completely wrong about and if you just go a little bit further down the story he's using it
The credibility of these accusations being made by the government of Saudi Arabia might seem a little shot
Quote
A guardian investigation this you're discredited the case against the men and uncovered evidence of systematic torture by the Menace
History of internal
According to Defence papers submitted by way of appeal
Do the Saudi Supreme Court last month
And seen by The Guardian
The men were systematically tortured until they confess
They were subjected to sleep deprivation for up to 10 days at a time suspended from chains hanging from hooks
Above their cell doors and repeatedly beat
They were told their relatives would be harmed if they did not cooperate and we're offered early release in exchange for concessions
At this point I want to make totally clear that I'm opposed to this treatment of detainees in the same way that I'm against how the US treated Omar
Al-farooq
In the latter case it was interrogation tactics
Like sleep deprivation
The allegations in this case are far more
Abusive incruse
The fact remains that these are abusive and unacceptable on both counts
And I'm not trying to minimize one compared to the other or anything they're both unacceptable
Beyond the moral issues putting someone into distress is not a reliable way to gather information
You may end up getting until this accurate but you also might not so it's often B best practice to not
View the fruits of tortured interrogations is being Trust
The reason that I gave this
Much more of a pass in the case of al-farooq
Then then in the case of the
Play with the Saudi government blaming the British
Citizen
Is because there were other corroborating details and pieces of supporting evidence
In that case but didn't come from al-farouq himself
And it appears of the things that he told the US forces were accurate Dave did their best to verify that information as opposed to
To just going
Oh we tortured him enough that we've got the correct
Information
Terrible
Awful
In early 2004 the British Embassy workers who were tortured and forced to admit to crimes they didn't commit on video buganda
The process of trying to sue the Saudi government
The rules at that point in the UK where that you couldn't
Sue a sovereign government but their case sucked a challenge that law
Actually want a case on this in 2004 but it was
Ultimately overturned by a higher Court in 2000
Answer the
Did not
What a what a weird
World that we live in where you can just get swept up into
Something that has nothing to do with you and then your tortured for like
That's absurd
It is very very dumb that that
Just exist
Don't we all
Dissipate in this system
Yes very silly
Reading
Some of the folks
Experience. Not so much
I mean obviously
Tails of being beaten in
The experience of having your government not have your back
Feeling like that
Yeah
Interesting
Expressions of the trauma that lingers
Bev B added
Did to bye-bye like well there's no recourse really have
Hurricane just went through your house and
That's it
Hurricane just went through your house
Now you have to live with it
Bye-bye
Yeah yeah
It's f***** up
Undoubtedly
So
There wasn't something that Alex
Touchstone
A little bit he said that they pulled them out
They pulled.
Yeah it's some of that was not not entirely clear based on
The peace
Pieces of information and the sources that he was citing
I am so you gets back to that and there's a little more clarity
And Other Stories
Security
Connected
So this story actually makes total sense if you understand the larger context of what's going on
It's only suspicious if you're only given access to the sparse details that Alex covers on his show
The sparseness of the details actually a strategic aspect of Alex's broadcast because he's not interested in giving his audience a better grass
Facebook news events
He's just trying to find tiny slivers of information that he can use to make every of that conform to his pre
Predetermined storyline
Everything fits neatly into the the globalist there behind everything box
This article that Alex is talking about it's from late 2000
The context of this is that the US intelligence
Community have gotten information from al-farouq
And other sources that there was a plan in motion to carry out a bombing in Indonesia
Areas or buildings that were seen as western or prime targets for groups like Jamia islamia
So they had every reason to suspect that a c's or government buildings could be under threat
Do you want to try to relay this information to the megawati government who found themselves unable to act in it
Moana in a way that satisfied us
Concerned a few options on the table for how to proceed
Evacuating South temporarily is a completely Justified and rational
Decision to make in this situation
And it's definitely not cause for any kind of Suspicion
Alex is trying to use this sliver of information that the USA considered evacuating Embassy staff prior to the bomb
Going to insinuate
That they had specific for knowledge of the attack but this doesn't stand up to scrutiny
It's also kind of dumb considering that if they did have foreknowledge of the attacks Target
They wouldn't have had to worry about
Officials at their office
The primary target of that
Attack in Bali was Patty's Pub
A bar that was frequent by tourist
Though there was a smaller bomb that was detonated at the US Consulate office as well share share
One person sustained minor injuries
Is and it happened around 11 p.m. so most people probably weren't even at that office
According to the Australian police report the consulate bomb in Bali was packed with s***
So the
The thinking was that this was less aimed at killing people or causing destruction as much as it was a statement bombing
You know yeah you fella bum with s*** whenever you're trying to cover everybody with s*** I feel like that makes a perfect
Yeah
Yeah it's so this
Doesn't
Work the analysis again trying to
Apply it
More broadly to the
The bombing that he's covering that is not appropriate
Right
All right it is he sounds places that are geographically close
I bet it's been like well obviously all vomiting
Things happen in this geographical area happen for the
The exact same reason every time every detail about circumstances are exactly the same
Pose things and it's fine
You know Daddy's that is a really interesting failing that kind of goes under the radar with
It's a lot of his conspiracies like
It is impossible
To pull off the same job the same way over and over and over and over
Daddy's is it that was too suspicious that they never f****** and Ina in like unique and interesting
Ways they're always able to pull it off
Yep that's crazy
It's it's
Anime is perfect
Theory of good is perfect you're just you're making up your enemy
Of course the power that you need them to have at any given point
It's
Narrative
Convenience character Shield
Shield
So Alex goes on to make up more details about this article that I think it's just the way he does this is
Is just fascinating
On Muslim
Across the archipelago
For you at
Speaker
Bar
Ordered it
Of the Marriott four hours
The complete picture
Alex is creating out of this article that he's reading
This article was written long before the Jakarta bombing at the Marriott and had to do with the US threat to remove m
Embassy employees in 2000
2 prior to the Bali bombing
Do you ask didn't end up evacuating staff and it had nothing to do with that Marriott which is the hotel.
Spell Target in
Start up
The reason that Indonesian have speaker tenjune was expressing regret with the US
Decision to threaten to remove was because he was worried about the message that would send to the rest of the world
Did Indonesia wasn't the safe place to be
He was concerned with the country's reputation which
Make sense
How does no idea what he's talk
He's reporting that the US plan to evacuate staff hours before the bombing that happened in August 2000
Brief and his sources an article from October 2002 that is an issue
Or at least that's how it appears
Well I mean because he's actually
Conflating sources he's making a stew
Okay
I mean
The whole here is
What
Amount of us
Officials were at the Marriott
Like why are they why is the United States government like specifically like listen
We obviously would be like they know that the embassy is going to be bombed
But who all was staying at the Marriott that needed to be evacuate
The Marriott did host
Like some of them
Like they had
Sure head
No I mean yeah
Pass
It is it is a little bit like the United States
Government is like hey
Listen
Eric
You got to get out of that Mariah I know you I know you could stay there for a week until we find you a place closer to
To the office
We'll see here here is where this this to aspect comes coming
Is this story
From 2002
About the threat to remove Embassy
Employee
He's bringing in there saying that they were told to get out of the Marriott
Be involved with this
No article cuz it's wrong about the US Embassy
So he brings in another article
Not even Bridge
He just jams them together is if they're the same thing
Again
Because Alex up to this point has been relying on this October 2002 article to argue that the embassy was
Threatening to withdraw
That was true but he was lying about the context of it and pretending it was a recent article related to the Jakarta bomb it right
Now he's using me completely different source to make a completely different client while acting like it's the same story
Apparently what happened was that the US Embassy
She canceled reservations at the Marriott
Four and a half hours
Before the bombing
Alex's sole-source on this is a translation of an Indian Indonesian website that makes this claim
And their only source is an alleged employee of the Marriott who is inanna
There's no evidence of this that this is the case
If I were the embassy in Iraq
Castrating elaborate
Fake terrorist plots in order to force the Indonesian government of the cracking down on terrorists and going along with my larger Global agenda
I don't think I would cancel those reservations
Keep them in just not sure why it doesn't make any sense
Or even better
Some of the Expendable people who worked at the office could show up for the reservations at the embassy to reply even
More pressure on the Indonesian government when was the book
What's up I mean they said they canceled a booking break
Didn't say there was an event at the hotel that day
They could have been a booking for Anytime implication is that it was like
They were supposed to check in
Four and a half hours after this or that day or something
And Alex will play with that a little bit later
It is a little bit like if I'm planning a false flag
I'm not at Minas you said you don't like I'm going to leave those there
What are you going to say if we let it go too long there non-refundable okay
We got
Are the reservations are supposed to start the next day they have a 24-hour cancellation policy
The US Embassy for the United States globalists in Indonesia
In Spanish
Is there supposed to be there like that that day
Or whatever like
A bombing takes a while to plan it didn't come together exactly four hours
Last minute
So there's literally only once
Scenario where this makes sense as proof of a can
Conspiracy
And that's the world where
Evil globalist behind this plot
Cancel the reservation so they could leave behind a calling card for the conspiracy theorists
Define
This is basically Alex pretending the information is taunting
Which
You have to realize is a part of his the way he
Give you the world course it is it is difficult to keep in mind that he
He does feel as though he
He's fighting the Mad Hatter leaving Clues behind at the scene everywhere he goes
The globalist of the Riddler
Feather using puzzles and
Exacto
Read all these clothes then I'll find the treasure underneath the United States Constitution it makes perfect sense
I'm
You know you and I are pointing out these problems with the idea of them cancelling reservations as being
Even accepting
The framing that they did in fact cancel these reservations
Which on that day which I do not know to be true
Thursday a solid piece of information about that it doesn't work
If they were there
They left
Maybe
But even then I don't know
That's what Alex says
Alex doesn't have another source
This is just embellishing and making up details about the idea that the embassy
Cancel reservations at the Marriott before the bombing
The flimsy article that he's basing this on doesn't say any of this but he can't help himself from escalating
Now they didn't just cancel reservations they're actually there and checked in but they went through all the trouble to check out
Hours early before the bombing
Alex is making this up because if it were true it sure would seem pretty suspicious eyes like view you even real
That's like
Flimsy ass s*** you know certainly would raise more of an eyebrow then
Then
The other details they call in and
Early check-in because we got to we got to the Marriott too soon and they go again okay fine
We got a room available so they go through the whole rigmarole they've left a credit card and an ID they've done all this s***
They go up to the room and then lie all f*** I forgot
We got the Palm today then run down there they have to make a fake
Being there for make a big scene my room wasn't as clean as it nater to me
Reminder refunded and then they leave
It's
Conceivably the dumbest
Track of events
I actually believed happened through this
Alex can't make compelling arguments based on the information that's available
Upshift that makes his case look stronger he's doing this because he's a liar
Once you establish the idea that you had these Embassy
See people there
Who checked out
And you add it to believing the Saudi Arabian government about the British
Who are carrying out bombings to destabilize the Saudi Arabian government bright can combine this all together
And now
You have a hit
It was at the Marriott
More more
Victory victory
How do you know that
You can see hero Alex's building out the story
You're the flimsy Source the claims of US Embassy canceled reservations hours before the bombing took place at the Marriott which he is now
Now reporting as the US sending in a team of about 20 people who are pulled out early
This is solely from his own imagination and it's nothing more than him writing his own little story about this tragic event so we can you
Use it to further his own goals
One thing I want to draw special attention to is the part where he says that they were pulled out of the hotel because of threat
This is important because it's a synthesis of this flimsy Source about the cancel hotel reservation
And that article from 2002 about the lead-up to the Bali bomb
Alex is taking the hotel detail from one story and mash it up with the embassy being concerned about threats
That.
Detail from the other story I meant serving it up for the audience as if it's something meaningful and it's the same thing
If anything this is an abusive information and it's kind of silly to pretend that what he's doing is
Questioning world event
So the question is just lying about shitzo mass-casualty events can be incorporated into your world do you more easily
And you can profit off the
The bright bright
It is it is funny that I I
Throughout this entire time I find myself trying to
To give advice to the globalist
And then realizing again but what I'm really doing is Justina writers room with Alex trying to punch up his narrative
Is too big
That's too big it's too obvious
And then I realize I'm not I'm not talking about this I'm with Alex being like okay listen
What we got to do
From the article about the canceled reservations that allege they were 10 to 20 rooms
So that's just a number that he's coming up with
It's all I didn't specify which
3 days
Either that or he's getting the two more days
But he's just he's just cracking those details into his own form
Whatever shape you want them to take
In order to make his story makes sense
Now what I think is more interesting
With your writerly instinct is the way that you have been one step ahead of Alex's narrative
What do you like
Hotel
Well it isn't that is interesting about going back to the past he does have those abilities it does feel like he's busy
There is a little bit of an A to B to C with the wave that the
The layers of the
Conspiracy are added on as he makes stuff up about like
The little colonel that that is at the edge of the base
Feels like he's trying
Yeah it's not good but it is an effort which were not used to seeing in the
Holyshit
It's transparent
If you take the time to pay attention to it
But if you don't
Or if you just operate off headlines
The Optics of seeing a headline that says
U.s. Embassy
Canceled reservation right four and a half hours before bombing accept whatever Alex says
About it like if you just
Except the story that he tells about that headline chair
The escalation of it does make sense
Or if you believe
The Saudi government about the British Embassy
That they tortured have got 12 skins
There is a
Conspiracy that is crafted
It's a little bit like a
Good kid improving a book report
Where you're like okay
I know you didn't read that book
But I'm actually kind of respecting your level of creativity in faking that you read that book you're making up some fun s*** shirt
It's like if a kid
Improvised a book report that was super disrespectful to a bunch of people died in a bomb
Yeah
That would be gross
Is actually the Civil War
Burial grounds
Yeah that's a really worse book
Sounds doesn't just stay on this topic all all episode he also just
Yells about stuff
Never rest
So that's a little severe
Yeah I think
That you could make an interesting argument that in some ways
The police are
Acting as
But sometimes they do operate as a death squad
I think that's not what Alex is talking about police brutality
Kind of the issue little Hollow
I mean if you were putting together an Alex Jones was right clip
I don't understand why that's not on there
Unless well because Alex it doesn't work in the present for him
It's not it's not worth while for him to
To really hang his hat on go back to Talladega
Go to Lakeview
Defend the too many people on the left
He can't do that no
Nope he has to literally be above the left-right Paradigm in order
To do that and he's absolutely not
Yep yep
In this next clip Alex
Calls
Checked and unfortunately
Question that Alex was not prepared for
Arp
Military research
Research
Forgot the p
I was really interesting about the first of all that was not a got your question
Know that
The big thing as my mind was it like on the stand
Alex
This case when Dario was
But
Testifying
That's her with DARPA stand Sorrentino that is true
That is funny 2003 Alex Wood
Fumble around with what does DARPA stand for
Yeah that's
We're if that way if that was script
See what I've heard that Ding real fast
I understand
Twisted Fork
Advance
I understand if you would have trouble with like harp
That much
I don't know what her,
And he's in the middle of
Like this
It's been awhile since we've done 2003 episode that whole thing about how they were trying to gamble on terrorist
Attacks and stuff
Set up a stock market on deaths
It's B
Pretty front and center of his narrative
You should not be talk conspiracy theorist you should have DARPA on the reading
Math teacher you have to be able to do long division in your head like you have
You can't stumble around with that s*** otherwise going respect
Call
And this is the level of discourse
What's going on on the show man eats
Heady stuff
I want schedule
Minion on a cup
Sweden
Bad
On August 27th
Marczyk
Going to be
Closest
We know
Globaltranz
We do know that
Valve
Believe in
Carter
Bush Clinton
Exactly
Very
And you think that they would
Celebrate
That date with another
Attack and
Is that
Reading about it
Here
We've been worried about
When is
That is amazing
But I mean
Look that's amazing
Not knowing a thing to suddenly just being like this thing is Central's real worried about it
Verify this is that true the numbers a man that there's a preponderance of evidence that
Mars is going to be still playlist Mars is the God of War
It happens
Right I just appreciate that instantaneous
Absolutely
Absolutely you bet brother you've just fill in the blank
If there is something you're asking if Alex if you should be worried about it
Absolutely brother is a reason to be operate
You are not crazy for having this fear of something that nobody is literally ever thought before
You are right my friend let's kill minute
It's a valuable time on my show talking about being worried about Mars being too close
I don't know boys celebrating
Mars being close
How to build a problem here you didn't explain how this is related to an occult
Situation
Oh I bet because Mars is Mars is close this time they can be like this important
I'm hearing the words you're saying
But you sound dumb it makes so much sense
Really really
Umart you reveal yourself to be a mark what do you ask questions like that if she just it's just
Understood that the globalists
Bomb things
When planets are close
How much closer
I felt like a million miles closer on this one day
I think it was quite a bit closer
What's closer
I don't know I don't remember I looked it up but I don't remember the exact
Right right I did look up if there was any bombing on
Little League World Series
Maybe somebody videos
Cabela's right over the the Raptors but some
Yeah this is just dumb
It's interesting
That you have that response of like why do you even would that even be something at the globalists
Arranged it this to me I mean I'm joking around
Scolding you or like making fun of you would like to me it is like
McDonald's app
Shuffle little bit closer
Yeah
Banana Breeze
There's magical powers that come from
Blue Xbox further away
Something else changes that makes you
Let's likely to celebrate
Write it being further away than
Venus gets closer
Is it just a day
Is it just like all this is It's like a solar eclipse they all go outside they look up and then I got like that
And then they go back to their lives
Solar eclipse
You got it that's right
It is
So much
Your caveman just like anything is a side just like all there's a shoot except that's a side
Decide
Such that it is just caveman thought
Alex takes like
The date
Kind of simplistic understanding of symbolism occultism
Supplies it sort of
Universally
Seems like it could be
Like
An equinox or somebody's got bombs
Anytime there's a like
A date that has like
Every Lego it's doubles
March 6th 2009 369
The magical powers on this date
I like B one thing that's never really addressed is
How many holidays occult people have
To have
Every day there is a holiday there's something
We should all live like that
Everyday is special and we're celebrating
Everyday but not everyday Mars is the closest it's going to be in 60,000 years
Now that's true it heavy
And something years before we get that again
Someday
And look at it cuz there will be a thousand years so
So Alex
We know that his dad was a big baby ask I have planned a bad influence on him
Uncle wasn't better
5 years ago
I like that image goblin teeth
Demon face
Dehumanizing
A responsive that is interested I would like to
To know what that is like is a gentleman I regret to inform you we are in this dating thing
Fall into the dehumanizing
What is dehumanizing specifically inside the
I don't I don't know
I'm trying to visualize this
I appreciate first
My favorite visual is lifting up the curtain to reveal a pet that's just great that's good show with chip
Okay if you reveal if you open a curtain to a pit
It's good stuff
Yeah alright
It could be anything man
I mean it would have to be is it is it there's got to be more than one Satan in the pit
First off they need to be multiple Satan's in this
That possible
I assume he can split himself up he's got classic Marvel Powers these days
Sorry right
That's not my son
This is like the argument that Alex in his uncle had yeah probably
I think that's the cousin Buckley's dad
My guess is he has brought up before
Lyra talks about uncle's with the information
So
Fun
There's nothing new story that Alex touches on here
President Bush
Real real nice
And all the things where people talk about how accurate Alex's they seem to just forget his
Constant obsession with how a universal draft was right around the corner and other Global estate
Set up for the next time there was a terrorist attack
That was a
And all your sons and daughters were going to be
Conscripted
Big white van that
And he was pretty tore up all the time
One wonders if Alex made a big stink when Trump nominated Donald Benton to this position in April 2017
That was evident
Trump trying to reinstate the draft
I would imagine it wasn't
I don't think you probably even notice
This is a small government office that has existed since World War 1
Probably the
Just be abolished
Even though it's not a pool for a draft
The names and information gathered from Selective Service registration are used by The Joint advertising marketing research
Studies program out
Department of Defense
Which uses that information to recruit volunteers into the armed services
Anyway
It's up it's not cool
Right right there isn't a draft
And there wasn't wanted 2003
Get rid of that that's that's bad
I mean
It's obvious there won't be a dress we can barely afford the military we have now can you imagine if we just had an
An influx of
I don't know 10 million people
Just to walk in there how much would it cost to outfit them do we got to spend a trillion dollars on one plane
Kind of understand the thing
Or something like that
In
Past days
Although I
I think that there is a social contract
Is coming to place that is we will never have a draft again
Ever
Is not something that
Is going
BECU in as appropriate
On any level
And
Because of that
I think it'll be a show of good faith
I might just get rid of this office because there's this premise of it is like in case we need
Write this registration break glass
Get rid of that because you're not going to need it cuz we're not doing the draft again I mean you know
It is it is always a a pretty
Universal step towards fascism whenever you have a standing army it at the call you know
What part of it's that idea of a rapid medical Army
Part of that hypothetical draft is you're not really supposed to have an army
That's ghetto
So everybody has their own skin in the game so to speak and now it is kind of an impunity
And that's kind of part of our agreement you know we don't have a draft and then we'll look the other way whenever you start warzone
All the time
We can go and get rid of that part of it too
Give me the most of these office
So
Look
Alexandra present-day talk a lot about being broke
And being in debt
And
You know he needs money
I
Who found the
Time
Ever said that
Okay
Honor the very first time well I mean if you believe
What he's about to say
I'm about
Very important
People in Japan
You know Alex baby
I'm not going to
Infomercial
Wow
Yeah that's kind of a bummer
That to here
Someone else say back to him
In the past
Bad news Jim yeah yeah gym
The show
Deteriorate
Largely
Hey marketing infomercial
Water filters
Introduction of an infomercial
With this
Hey I'm behind on my shortwave bill
Right cuz we pay for airtime
On the shortwave State share and my water filter guy helps pay that bill so here he is by his
Is water filter
Very difficult to square someone saying
You know what
I like that you don't do infomercials and you've got the Integrity to not turn your show into
Anyways my water filters
I agree with you bear mentioning that it is not as intrusive at this
Not the whole show they're doing
Pretty transparent
This guy selling his sales pitch for his water filter
Fluoride
And so like there is still like content is being used as marketing
So still that look blurry distinction but it is
A far cry from the
Deterioration into infomercial City
I am leaving behind the information
Yeah that Alex
Becomes later it isn't like I appreciate most of all that 15,000
Dollar number
You know
That I feel like now
He's got shell companies he's got to have accountants will
Going to lie for him and then he's got to have accountants that his account
Why do in order to launder their lies right
Bullshittin a legal situation
Barnes all you've got to do is pay your shortwave bill you stay there stay there
A good sweet spot yeah absolutely
Poor Alex
There's a lot of folks who
Dinner
What are the things that they say I think you would agree with that is
That he tells it like
Like it is
Order
Tell him like it is
Telling it
Like it
Is no one who has
No one who says I tell it like it is
Ever actually
One does
R2 has anything good
D'usse people who calls them like they see them
As long as you add the plural
Cousin like I sees them that's that's good stuff
Okay so that's a little bit straight shooter
Straight shooter
No no no other people describe you as that makes me think that you are a liar
Silex takes more call
Here and he gets a call from a guy who I believe in laws
I appreciate this man it's kind of difficult to tell exactly where he's coming from but he believes
I think
Maybe in a Godzilla kind of situation it got that
It's self-evident law
Yeah natural law perhaps to specific enough for me to really nail down but he does believe that just because
Laws are signed into law that doesn't mean their laws
He's not in the jurisdiction
Score of the law of the Jungle kind of guy
I think
Based on his voice
I don't think Elias demijohns probably true but maybe spiritual in anyway
Here's a request
Alex
Run all over you
Just want to know if I can
Time to call you
2 minutes
What
Working
Good excuse
Phone call
Like dude I'm behind the 8-ball
I like it when trying to let him down easy getaway out of had big trouble
Listen I'm on the run from the cops right now I can't be taking phone calls
Doing the radio show honestly I had to get rid of my phone I've got burner phones
I throw them into the ocean after I use them one time in a bunker that is sealed with lead and
They'll never find me
I'm by the 8-ball
I'm working for the next 6 hours
I'm being chased by the cops
I've got to take my daughter fishing at some point
So I can't call you it's really obvious
The way you could just handle this it is unsafe for me to talk to you off the air
I don't know what you're up to there's a lot of ways that this could have
Expose me
It's just
If you're Alex is the simplest thing in the world
But you don't want to give that message
Because it's
Too likely to make the audience think that you think that they're crazy
Or something
Where is
Public figure
There is a very
Acceptable boundary to be like I'm not talking
Sing to you on my like
Affair with each other
Email or something
But it's not we're not going to do that
When you Court when you actively Court people who blur the line between reality and fiction
It's going to be a little bit more of a tighter walk
To let him down easy
On account of you don't know what part of the fiction that's going to
Add you into that's true that through a lot of interactions and Alex has a
This man's over the course of
There is an unwillingness to
Be honest about what the boundary is because of that
And we just need to keep this separate
The only thing I know about you is you believe what I say
It's you do the Groucho Marx thing I don't to be a member of any club that would have me as a number
No self-esteem but with Alex
Completely different I made this club and I don't ever want to visit this club
Close I lock the door with them inside it want to be around anybody who would be a member of my
All the double deuce and I'm not step
Open foot and not f****** place
Something like this color
Here's what he wants to discuss with Alex off of hair
Well
Interpretation
The Bible
Oh boy
It's a long story
Doughboy
Alright order
Well
Pervert
Description
Some places
Bill Reese
Figure out what
If not
Perverted word
Yeah I think
Open hour
Probably probably longer than
Sir sir you have just explained
Why I do not want to talk to you
People have been studying the Bible for quite a while now
You didn't you have cracked the code
Get there you're telling me
And it'll take you half an hour to explain it
It's out I'm sure you're going to stop in a half hour I'm going to start the watch you don't get on with things
31 last year and I know that another thing that was making the rounds on social media was
Recently was a clip
Of Alex saying there was going to be
False flag globalist terror attacks
You know before the midterm
Call Ron filipkowski
But Alex says that all the f****** time. Everyday
It is not worthwhile or meaningful
To post at all
To make people think this is like
I'll look at him
Look at him he's making a
Desperate weird prediction know this is what he does every day
Since 2003
Records without a cord
Kent State
Is recording a special Authority
Today's New York Daily News
If you want you can get
Get the Daily News
Boom boom
I mean let's say we've had explosions before the midterm we've had nukes
Before
Presidential election
We've had there were going dark before
Haitian me up
I mean they were obviously the polonium poisoning was rampant for a while
There were two incidents now
The same person
Also didn't happen right yes there was
Yeah
Constant
Can feature of his career
Anybody who
Doesn't understand that it's window dressing
It's again just like we were
Laughing and joking about this before it just like if you ask Alex is there a reason to be scared about something
One of the things
Always uses to scare people is that
Specter of
The coming false flag attack
That is justified by some
Piece of his
His narrative
There is
Obviously
Democrats are scared that they're going to lose the midterms and so they must do bombings in order to make sure they
Win the midterm
Sprite
Ashcroft wants to get Patriot Act in but there's opposition to it from the Patriots
He's better do some boom boom
In order to
Make sure that this goes through
Always it's always this and I don't understand how it's been
20 years
I know it's yours and it's still an effective thing it's still something that people can
It's because people dip in and out
It's because people like Ron filipowski get to dip in and out
A f****** youth baseball coach
I turned by the media into some f****** alt-right hero
Just being a f****** idiot
I hate him so much
But
I mean it is it is that like if you dip it in
Every 3 or 4 months
That you have in your head this idea well he can't do this everyday
Because you assume that
Because there's no way he could do this every day even if you have an awareness of who Alex is and you don't
Pay much attention
Bronson even was like
Does he repeated exhaust is a awareness of what
By watching a bunch of it
And unfortunately I don't
I think that most people should do that cuz
Well I mean the problem is our own assumptions based on how everything else work
It is to us
Unsustainable to do the same thing everyday will you imagine that you watched
Clip every few months and you go wow this must be an unusual thing it wouldn't
Newsworthy
He's on one it wouldn't be newsworthy if it's everyday
It's newsworthy because it's manufactured
For you
It created for you I think there's that
The dipping in and out for sure is a is a
Piece of it
You know there is just
Hanging in the world
Like negative
Traumatic events
Do happen
Jo-Ann's
Those are things that Alex will then attach these ideas to
And that people
I guess people will just
Experience that as being the confirmation
And they'll forget about all the
Countless times that he's been
Making up
Vague
Warnings about boom boom
I mean that the thing that's most
Suspicious is I like
In 20 years the globalist would have to have taken a break for a
No way I've never stopped
Not once there's no
Despite the fact that they celebrate a million holidays every year
It is always a work holiday they never even take a vacation like Alex that way
Read that he's not working ever know
Just gave me an idea for a movie Pitch
Globalist vacationing finally take no no no
Mario 2 movie pictures
The globalist
Are on vacation
But they're still need to be false flag
Naturally they bring in the junior varsity globalist
Right
Somebody gets somebody gets promoted this is their big shot right but it turns out the eager young person this is
This is a if they were younger or movie like 15 years ago
To be a Vince Vaughn Owen Wilson vehicle are the guys who come in and they
Have you paid the screw everything up but at the end they come together and really the cab old school
The closest Maaco
I got to call him something like the the the nation Squad
You know they're not Global na
That sucks
Back for you in about
Six months to get a treatment going
So I'm glad to have gone back to the past because at least there is something
Concrete going on to be.
That is
Refresher appreciate the path
A great deal
And so I will check back in on the present-day keep people posted on
I'm bulshit outages up to as the
Terror of the mid-term approaches midterms
But until then Jordans
We doing website.com
We're also on Twitter
But until then I'm Neo I'm Leo I'm dzx Clark
Gerald Smith
No savage
I was wondering where Gerald Wilfred cousin
The Gribble Pitbull
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work