Knowledge Fights.
Damn important.
I am sweating Knowledgebuy.com.
It's time to pray.
I have great respect for Knowledge.
I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys.
Shang.
We are the bad guys.
Knowledge.
Knowledgefight.com.
I love you.
Hey, everybody.
Welcome back Knowledge Fight.
I'm Dan.
I'm George we're dude.
Takes sit around, worship at the altar of Celine, and talk a little bit about Alex Joe.
Indeed we are.
Dan.
Jordan, quick question for you.
What's your bright spot today? My bright spot today is Coca Cola.
Coca Cola Classic or New Coke? Look, they have great taste in podcasts, so they decided to sponsor.
Of course, I was noted famously critical of their space flavor.
They came out with that space flavor.
I have no concept of a Coca Cola space.
You tasted it.
Wait, was it supposed to taste like space? Yeah.
Okay.
That's right.
Now I remember.
It's not memorable.
No.
And not good.
The only way I could find that was in, like, a six pack of mini cans.
Right.
And they're still in my fridge.
I have no interest in drinking them.
Fair.
They're garbage.
But Coke put out another flavor called Dream World, which is supposed to be the flavor of dreams.
What? I'm sorry.
What the fuck they're doing? I guess it's some kind of viral marketing campaign.
It must get enough attention based on how dumb these ideas.
Yeah.
Or just, like, people talk about, like, hey, what's the flavor of space? Right.
What's the flavor of a dream? I think they're dissecting Travis Scott's Astro World because that's a mixture of flavor.
Yeah.
Well, you've got space and you've got Dream World.
If you put them together, you got Astro World.
That makes sense.
I think that Dream World was much more of a success.
Okay.
It's pretty good.
It's got a kind of a passion fruit kind of vibe to it.
Sure.
It has, like, a Coca Cola mixed with a sort of there's maybe a couple of fruits.
Let me ask you the ultimate question, though, is did they achieve a taste that would remind you of a dream? I guess.
World.
Do you dream of passion fruit? If so, right on the nose.
Okay.
All right.
If not, then maybe not.
I have no interest in assessing the accuracy of these flavors.
I will just say that it's pretty.
All right.
Who is the taste tester for Dream World? I don't know.
The Dream.
He rewrites it anyway.
I appreciate that they salvaged what was left of a shattered reputation with the Dream World.
Yes.
What about you? For me, it's a new album out by JID.
Fantastic album.
Okay.
Excellent album.
It's one of those things where maybe only an outside critic can kind of look at someone and then accelerate it to a high extent.
So this is like JID looked at Kendrick's last album and was like, what if I did the most Kendrick? And, like, Kendrick can do the most kendrick kids would say, hold my beer.
It's a little bit something that it's almost also a little bit of an homage combined with a little bit of a parody in a way.
He's taking out a lot of Kendrick and really hammering at home like he's changing time signatures every 5 seconds.
He's changing his voices.
He's got characters going on.
This is Kendrick as shit.
That's what he's doing.
And he's doing a lot of it right.
But it's really good.
Okay.
So it's a great album.
All right.
That's how it works.
I'll check it out.
That's math.
I actually can't check it out.
Oh, yeah.
I've started to exercise again.
So I'm listening to a bit of music and I will say that I'm stuck squarely show tunes.
I don't think that would have pumped me up enough.
Okay.
Although I got deep into a bootleg copy of mama mia.
No.
Okay.
All right.
I think fall out boy, some of those hits are better than we remember.
No, they're not.
I'm going to leave.
This is a fallout boy ambassador song from snakes on a plane by cobra starship was all right.
Okay.
All right.
That does sound like it strikes a chord, so to speak.
It'll pump you up.
Yeah.
Anyway, Jordan, today we have an episode to go over and we're going to be talking.
I had to take a little breakie for dams.
Self care comes in all sorts of shapes and sizes and varieties.
I decided today I was going to go back to 2003 because I wanted something of substance to deal with as the middle of the week was going on.
It's just like sick of this bullshit.
I don't know, spinning wheels, rambling about other is going to be false flags before the midterms.
Sure.
She says all the fucking time.
Still can't believe he cares about the midterms right now.
It's pretty fun.
I guess.
It's something to talk about.
Sure.
That is a good point.
He can only say Claude Schwab so many times and promote his book so many times, which, by the way, is out.
I'm going to be getting that book and we're going to do that episode eventually, but that'll be fun.
Again, the self care I needed was something with meat on the bones, right? Yes.
And so we're back to August 6, 2003.
That's where we are in our progression through 2003.
It's been a while since we've done 2003 episode.
It's been a long time.
Yeah.
I scrolled back through the episode.
I'd say more, maybe.
Well, I mean, the trial got in the way, what have you.
But I'm very excited to go over this and discuss some of the bullshit that Alex was doing on this day back in 2003.
But before we do that, let's say hello to somebody who wants Jordan.
So first, Conrad Zimmerman isn't a cult leader, but he does have novelty beverages and snacks.
Thank you so much.
Jordan.
Policy wonk I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much.
Thank you, Nick.
Getting stoned while wandering the canals of Amsterdam while listening to knowledge fight.
Thank you so much.
You're an I apology wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much.
That sounds great.
That sounds terrifying, too, in a certain way, yeah.
Next.
I don't know why Alex hates Brian Stelter.
The stray cat said some great tunes.
Thank you so much, you're an IP policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much.
I know that I just said that Fallout Boy had some good songs, so I'm not one to talk.
I know, no credibility in this, but I disagree.
Okay.
The stray cats did not nobody is going to argue.
Next.
This one late.
Sorry about that.
Happy birthday, monkeyskate.
Love Pumpkin.
Thank you so much.
You are now a policywomp I'm a policy walk.
Thank you very much.
Pumpkin did everything right.
Monkeyskate.
The one's on me.
Yeah.
And that poor turtle that Dan jumped on.
Thank you so much.
Jordan.
How a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much.
We got a couple of technocrates in the mix.
Sure.
So, first, rock and stone.
Thank you so much, you are now a technocrat.
And the macromancer.
I'm a policy wonk.
I have risen above my enemies.
I might quit tomorrow, actually.
I'm just going to take a little break.
A little breaky for me.
And then we're going to come back and I'm going to start the show over.
I'm the devil.
I got to be taking on this.
Fuck you.
I got plenty of words for you, but at the end of the day, fuck you in your new world order and fuck the horse you rode in on and all your shit.
Maybe today should be my last broadcast.
Maybe I'll just be gone a month, maybe five years.
Maybe I'll walk out of here tomorrow and you never see me again.
That's really what I want to do.
I never want to come back here again.
I apologize to the crew and the listeners yesterday that I was legitimately having breakdowns on air.
I'll be better tomorrow.
Thank you.
Now, jordan? Yes, Dan.
We have an out of context drop from today's show.
That's been a little while on this one, too.
It's good news.
We're getting back to basic.
Yes.
Finding our route.
I like it.
This is great.
Alex has very frequently talked about how big his audience is.
We know, conservatively, 10% of the world.
At least.
Yeah.
This was a new level of brag.
Okay.
Infowars.com now gets 6% of the web's traffic.
What 6%? So there's porn and then there's infowars and then there's, I don't know, banking information.
Almost one out of every ten page hip is in force.
Wow.
When you think about that, you think of those Google search results and they bring back a billion results in like, half a second, or whatever.
That means that roughly 10% of those are infowars articles of some sort, something along those lines.
I know that Alex says he has a lot of tentacles, and so maybe all of these websites, every porn site, is just a part of infowars on infowars.
Yeah, he's diversified.
Man, that does seem like a back door for some enterprise.
Come on, now.
So let's jump into today's context here.
Alex starts off the show with a major world news story.
And I don't say that facetiously.
I usually do.
Yeah, I think that there's actually a news story.
The evidence is coming out that the bombing in Jakarta was another globalist operation.
Again, the Saudis are saying the British are carrying out the bombings in Saudi Arabia to destabilize the country so they can create a crisis to offer their new World order solution.
The evidence shows that that is indeed a fact.
The preponderance of the evidence, new information is coming out about the original Bali bombing last year and the fact that the British and US.
Government were there carrying the bombings out.
So for some perspective, this episode is from August 6, and the bombing of the Marriott in Jakarta happened on August 5.
There is no preponderance of any evidence that's leading Alex to say it's looking like a globalist plot.
He just literally says that about everything.
Well, I was wondering what a globalist plot is in disregard, huh? Well, I mean, okay, it's a globalist plot, but what is their plot beyond just they decided to blow up this okay, what is the plot? So it goes like this.
Okay.
The globalists are attacking sort of Western targets within Indonesia hotel chains, right.
In order to force the hand of the Indonesian government to playing along with their globalist takeover and crack down on the public, install a martial law station Indonesia, because as goes Indonesia, so goes the world.
Well, I mean, yeah, that is the classic SAG.
The sun never fell on the Indonesian Marriott chain, I believe is what it is.
So that is essentially the plot.
Yeah, the plot is to try and force the hand of the government to go along with fascism will blow up all your McDonald's, basically.
Got you.
Okay, so incidentally, these two bombings that Alex is talking about were connected as they were both carried out by members of the terrorist group Jamal Islamia.
Members of the group were convicted of doing a string of bombings in Bali.
There were a couple in that attack, sure.
And it's been pretty clearly established that they were behind the Jakarta bombing as well.
One of the more persuasive pieces of evidence that was found was the head of the suicide bomber, which was identified by multiple sources as being a man named Esmar Latinsani, who was a member of Ji.
I'm guessing Alex could just say that that was planted there or something, because he's smart and he loves facts.
Did you just say what I heard you say? We're going to be fine with that.
So the suicide bomber went into a hotel and blew himself up? Well, I believe it was a car bomb.
Okay.
Still.
Yeah, but of all the things that were intact, his head was identifiable? Yeah.
That's crazy.
Intact is a way to put it.
That's insane.
We're not talking dental records.
It literally sounds like somebody walked by and they were like, holy shit, it's him.
How have you been? Oh, no.
The rest of you is gone.
Yeah, it was other members of the group who had been arrested and identified.
Listen, I don't want to be morbid.
Right.
No, it is wild.
Yeah.
I mean, it is wild.
Okay.
No, I don't disagree.
That's wild.
Yeah.
And that's probably why Alex would say it's fake.
I mean, that is ripe for fake ending.
Right.
Guess what? If you were going to do something fake, you probably wouldn't do something like that because your response is how people would respond to it.
Sorry, what? Yeah, something a little bit more I would be very suspicious.
Yeah.
So, JAMA Islamiyah was a terrorist organization that operated in Indonesia and surrounding countries, mostly inspired by opposition to the more moderate forms of Islam that were practiced there.
This was seen as a form of Western degradation, so they targeted things associated with the west, like the Marriott Hotel in Jakarta and that largely tourist area in Bali where the bombings happened.
Right.
The group had received funds from an organization called Alharaman, which is a charity that had clear ties to Al Qaeda.
Though Alharmaine did engage in a bunch of legitimate charity work, some of the funds were dispersed to terrorist groups like JAMA Islamia, which led to the charity being shut down in 2004.
Yes.
Al Haramin is a charity organization that is based in Riyadh, Saudi Arabia.
The point is that Alex is legitimately just talking shit.
He hasn't had time to come up with any conclusions or weigh the preponderance of evidence, but he can't resist the opportunity to blame this tragedy on his imagined enemies and incorporate that made up story into his larger conspiracy worldview.
Right.
And so he's saying that there's a preponderance of evidence.
Just saying shit.
I mean, I think this is interesting insofar as it feels like this is one of the few times where the plan in real life has been exactly as bad as Alex's fake globalist plan.
What do you mean? Tactically, I don't think that's going to achieve what it is that they think they're trying to achieve.
You know what I'm saying? Like, no one is going to care if you blow up a Marriott.
I'm sorry.
I think people did.
I think they did.
But, I mean, at the end of the day, a Marriott is like, it's a low level target.
You're not going to get what you want out of a Marriott? Well, conceivably one of the reasons to choose that is that it's frequented by tourists sure.
And foreign nationals.
Right.
And it would cause a reduction of western tourism to the country.
Possible western influence.
Possibly businesses would be scared of coming in.
There are ripple effects that you could think might be achieved by attacking these western targets.
Right.
I don't know if I think that the idea is as bad as you are thinking it is.
No, I respect it's a terrible idea.
I can understand the thought process that gets there whereas no, actually it's as globalist plot is a lot sillier.
I think I see it.
This is just one of those plots ultimately that has been tried before and it doesn't really do it.
It's just not how you got to get a good one.
Well, hope springs eternal.
Yeah, that's fair.
They say that's fair.
So trying to nail down exactly like where this conspiracy comes from or what Alex is basing this on we get to one fairly relevant piece and we had calls yesterday from listeners.
Several on air.
Several off air and a bunch of emails of folks that were watching CNN and Fox yesterday early in the morning after there had been a bombing in Jakarta.
The capital of Indonesia and they talked about how the US diplomats and US employees have been told to pull out 4 hours before.
Well, I have no way of confirming this.
I was getting emails, I believe it's true about it, but here it is now in Reuters and Sky News and in other Asian papers.
And of course the feds were on the ground within minutes just like the Bali bombing but with the Bali bombing two weeks before they had specifics of the attack and our government told the Bali's government and told the Taiwanese government.
This has been in the mainstream papers like the Straight Times not to warn anyone, not to tell the American people or the Australians or anybody else.
The Bali's government I think is Alex thinking that Bali is a I don't think it is a city state if I remember, province of Indonesia.
But Alex seems to I don't know what he's doing.
So it appears that what Alex is going to do to try and make this conspiracy stick is work with the idea that there was some kind of advanced warning of the bombings and that there were feds on the ground immediately.
Sure.
As always this stuff is partially true.
There were federal agents there, but not US agents.
There were two groups from the Australian Federal police who were working with the Indonesian law enforcement, one on a narcotics operation and one on an anti human trafficking task force.
They were able to respond to the bombings in Bali considering that they were already there in the country.
But this isn't suspicious and it doesn't prove anything close to a conspiracy or a false flag and again, this is related to the 2002 Bali bombings as opposed to the Jakarta bombing that just happened, that Alex is covering.
It is a different situation.
He's playing fast and loose with these details a little bit, and I think it's intentional.
Yeah.
So there was some advanced warning, but that's not necessarily a thing where it was specific enough to guarantee the ability to stop either the Bali bombings or the Jakarta bombings before they happened.
In the case of the Bali attacks, the US.
Had captured Omar Alfaruk, who was understood to be a high level al Qaeda operative in the region.
His contact information had been found in the possession of a number of senior members of the group.
And after the US.
Forces interrogated him in ways that almost certainly bordered on torture, he talked and explained his role in the Southeast Asian cell of Al Qaeda.
The US.
Attempted to pass this intelligence on to the Indonesian government because part of it involved a reasonable suspicion that they were planning an attack somewhere near the anniversary of 911.
One of the recommendations that the US.
Made was that the government should arrest a prominent cleric named Abu Bakar Bashir, who Alfarok had named as being someone who was involved in the organization and planning of attacks.
The political situation in Indonesia at the time was very tense, with a secular president.
Megawati Sukarnoputri, who is vice President hamzahas was said to have close ties with many of the radicals who the US.
Wanted to focus on, including Bashir.
So you had this vice president on sort of one side of things and a president who was on the other side.
It was like early America, where it would just be the top two voters get in.
So it'd be this guy, and then the guy who hates him the most on the planet is the vice president.
And it's a tough situation to navigate.
Right.
The country is majority Muslim, and Megawatti didn't want to make any arrests, particularly of religious figures without evidence of their having committed a crime, which the US.
Couldn't provide.
The warning.
That the US.
Had was too vague to be actionable, and the Indonesian government was somewhat in a bind.
Ultimately, the Bali bombings could not be stopped.
But afterwards, the Megawatti government began to act.
She arrested Bashir and charged him with a string of church bombings that he had been involved in.
That occurred on Christmas Eve, year 2000.
Got you.
In the lead up to the Jakarta bombing, australian federal police were still in the country because the government had asked for their assistance investigating the Bali bombings.
In the course of that investigation, many members of JAMA Islamia were arrested and questioned, and a picture began to take shape that another bombing was being planned, but no one provided a specific target that they were planning to hit, just that it was likely that the group would attack a soft target.
Right.
If that's all you have to go on.
You can be on guard somewhat, but you can't possibly deploy the resources necessary to protect every soft target in the country, or even all of them, just in Jakarta.
Well, I mean, yeah, it is a warning that says bombing is coming, but without where or what or how to stop it.
So you're like, well, yeah, but what do I do with that? Right.
Yeah.
And the notion that a soft target would be chosen isn't really that much new information or revelatory because the original bombing was of a bar.
And even then you kind of get the sense that that's in the Mo.
Sure.
But I mean, even then, that's not really good intelligence there because, like, oh, well, you could just be assuming that they're going after a soft target or you don't even really know what a soft target to them quite.
Is.
How soft is soft exactly? It's tough to call.
Tough to call.
The point here is that Alex just saying shit.
Nothing he's saying means anything.
And he refuses to take responsibility for the things that he says.
He just throws shit at the wall and then moves on to another room for anyone.
Can make him clean up his mess.
None of this has any connection to the reality of the situation.
He's blurring details intentionally or because he doesn't know any better about two different incidents.
I mean, you don't even understand.
He's got people on the ground with the Bali's as we speak.
government.
He declared Bali its own country.
Obviously, Steve is notably part of the Bali sovereignty movement.
That would make sense.
So Alex has some other news stories he wants to hit on.
So remember that article from yesterday, the London Guardian? Saudis accused British staff of destabilization campaign.
British Embassy staff and Riyadh have been accused by the Saudi Arabian authorities of coordinating a campaign of anti Western terrorist bombings in the kingdom.
The Guardian has learned the accusations of the British Embassy in Riyadh, according to the bombings to stabilize the Saudi regime is the latest and most bizarre piece of information to escape the hall of Secrecy behind which the Saudis have been conducting legal proceedings against seven Westerners who they say have been tortured into making false confessions.
So I said day one, before the story ever broke, that the evidence is it was the British doing this.
Wow.
So this wasn't a story that was in The Guardian the day prior.
This is an article from September 6, 2002, in the aftermath of the Bali bombing.
Right.
Whenever they did know stuff about a thing.
Yes.
The basic gist of the story is this.
In November 2000, a British citizen named Christopher Rodway was killed in a car bombing.
He was an engineer employed at the military hospital in Riyadh.
And in the immediate aftermath, the Saudi government said that this was not terrorism, but was actually more likely a personal matter.
At the time, Saudi Arabia had a public stance that it was very insistent that they did not have any terrorist elements existing in the country, and this would contradict that narrative.
So there was an attempt to find another explanation when personal reasons didn't stick.
A bunch of employees at the British Embassy were accused of carrying out that bombing with the goal of blaming the Saudi Arabian government.
Seven people were held in prison for long stretches, treated quite poorly, and a couple of them were actually sentenced to death before ultimately being released.
This is a story that Alex is completely wrong about, and if you would just go a little bit further down the story he's using as a source, the credibility of these accusations being made by the government of Saudi Arabia might seem a little shoddier.
Quote a Guardian investigation this year discredited the case against the men and uncovered evidence of systematic torture by the Ministry of Internal Interior officials.
According to defense papers submitted by way of appeal to the Saudi Supreme Court last month and seen by the Guardian, the men were systematically tortured until they confessed.
They were subjected to sleep deprivation for up to ten days at a time, suspended from chains, hanging from hooks above their cell doors, and repeatedly beaten.
They were told their relatives would be harmed if they did not cooperate and were offered early release in exchange for confessions.
At this point, I want to make totally clear that I'm opposed to this treatment of detainees in the same way that I'm against how the US treated Omar Alfaruk.
In the latter case, it was interrogation tactics like sleep deprivation, whereas the allegations in this case are far more abusive and gruesome.
The fact remains that these are abusive and unacceptable on both accounts.
And I'm not trying to minimize one compared to the other or anything.
They're both unacceptable.
Yeah.
Beyond the moral issues, putting someone into distress is not a reliable way to gather information.
You may end up getting intel if it's accurate, but you also might not.
So it's often it's best practice to not view the fruits of tortured interrogations as being trustworthy.
So the reason that I gave this much more of a pass in the case of Alfaruk than in the case of the Saudi government blaming these British citizens is because there were other corroborating details and pieces of supporting evidence in that case that didn't come from Alfaruk himself.
Right.
And it appears that the things that he told the US forces were accurate.
They did their best to verify that information, as opposed to just going, oh, we tortured him enough that we've got the correct information.
All that being said, this is all terrible and awful.
Yeah.
In early 2004, the British Embassy workers who were tortured and forced to admit to crimes they didn't commit on video began the process of trying to sue the Saudi government.
The rules at that point in the UK were that you couldn't sue a sovereign government.
But their case sought to challenge that law.
They actually won a case on this in 2004, but it was ultimately overturned by a higher court in 2006.
And so they did not get to what a weird world that we live in where you can just get swept up into something that has nothing to do with you and then you're tortured for like that's absurd.
It is very dumb.
That just exists and we all participate in this system.
Very silly reading.
Some of the folks experience, not so much.
I mean, obviously tales of being beaten and the experience of having your government not have your back or feeling like that.
I mean, how could you affect yeah, there's some interesting expressions of the trauma that lingers that's added to by like, well, there's no recourse.
No, there's not really have.
It is like a hurricane just swept through your house and that's it.
A hurricane just swept through your house.
Now you have to live with it by it's fucked up.
Undoubtedly.
Yeah.
So there was something that Alex touched on a little bit.
He said that they pulled them out.
They pulled people out hours before.
Yeah.
And some of that was not entirely clear based on the pieces of information and the sources that he was citing.
He gets back to that and there's a little more clarity.
There's another one.
US planned withdrawal of Indonesian staff hours before blast.
And this is out of the Jakarta news.
Hours before the powerful blast in Bali Island went off, the US had reportedly announced a plan to withdraw its administrative staff from Indonesia for security reasons.
Do you have these two stories interconnected with Bali and with Indonesia? It's the same story over and over again.
So this story actually makes total sense if you understand the larger context of what's going on.
It's only suspicious if you're only given access to the sparse details that Alex covers on his show.
The sparse list of the details is actually a strategic aspect of Alex's broadcast because he's not interested in giving his audience a better grasp of news events.
He's just trying to find tiny slivers of information that he can use to make every event conformed to his predetermined storyline.
So everything fits neatly into the globalists are behind everything box.
This article that Alex is talking about is from late 2002.
The context of this is that the US intelligence community had gotten information from Alfarouk and other sources that there was a plan in motion to carry out a bombing in Indonesia.
Areas or buildings that were seen as Western are prime targets for groups like JAMA Islamia.
So they had every reason to suspect that embassies or government buildings could be under threat.
The US had tried to relay this information to the Megawatti government, who found themselves unable to act on it in a way that satisfied.
US concerns, which left few options on the table for how to proceed.
Evacuating staff temporarily is a completely justified and rational decision to make in this situation and it's definitely not caused for any kind of suspicion.
Alex is trying to use this sliver of information that the US had considered evacuating embassy staff prior to the bombing to insinuate that they had specific foreign knowledge of the attack, but this doesn't stand up to scrutiny.
It's also kind of dumb considering that if they did have foreign knowledge of the attacks targets, they wouldn't have had to worry about officials at their offices.
The primary target of that attack in Bali was Patty's Pub, a bar that was frequented by tourists.
Though there was a smaller bomb that was detonated at the US consulate office as well.
Sure.
One person there sustained minor injuries and it happened around 11:00 p.m., so most people probably weren't even at that office.
According to the Australian police report, the consulate bomb in Bali was packed with shit.
So the thinking was that this was less aimed at killing people or causing destruction as much as it was a statement bombing.
Yeah.
You fill a bomb with shit whenever you're trying to cover everybody with shit.
I feel like that makes a perfect yeah, that makes sense.
Yeah.
So this doesn't work.
Alex is again trying to apply it more broadly to the bombing that he's covering that day.
Sure.
And it's not appropriate.
Right.
He's found places that are geographically close and then it's been like, well, obviously all boundings happen in this geographical area, happen for the exact same reason every time and every detail about circumstances are exactly the same.
Just sort of transpose things and it's fine.
That is a really interesting failing.
That kind of goes under the radar with a lot of his conspiracies.
Like it is impossible to pull off the same job the same way over and over and over again like that unless you're the globalist.
But I mean, that was too suspicious that they never fuck up in unique and interesting ways, they're always able to pull it off.
Yeah.
That's crazy.
Your enemy is perfect.
Whatever.
The enemy of good is perfect.
You're making up your enemies.
Of course.
Right.
Your enemy has the power that you need them to have at any given point in time.
It's narrative convenience.
Right.
It's like having a main character shield, like that kind of thing.
Yeah.
Main enemy shield.
So Alex goes on to make up more details about this article that I think is just the way he does this is just fascinating.
And it goes on to say yesterday's blast, however, may prove to be just the evidence Washington needed to force Jakarta to come down hard on Muslim civilian groups.
In the past analysis did not rule out the occurrence of deliberate violence across the archipelago to provide a pretext for US intervention.
Meanwhile, Indonesian House of Representatives Speaker Akbar Tongjun said that he regrets the US.
Government's decision.
And again, it says the US.
Government ordered its employees and embassy staff pull out of the Marriott 4 hours before the blast.
Very astute timing.
So this is a complete fiction that Alex is creating out of this article that he's reading.
This article was written long before the Jakarta bombing at the Marriott and had to do with the US.
Threat to remove embassy employees in 2002.
Prior to the Bali bombings.
The US.
Didn't end up evacuating staff, and it had nothing to do with that Marriott, which is the hotel that was targeted in Chicago.
Right.
The reason that Indonesian House Speaker 10 June was expressing regret with the US.
Decision to threaten to remove staff was because he was worried about the message that would send to the rest of the world that Indonesia wasn't a safe place to be.
He was concerned with the country's reputation, which makes sense.
Right.
Alex has no idea what he's talking about.
He's reporting that the US.
Plan to evacuate staff hours before the bombing that happened in August 2003.
And his sources, an article from October 2002 that is an issue.
This is the level of work that he does, or at least that's how it appears.
Well, I mean, because he's actually conflating sources together.
Right.
He's making a stew.
The whole here is, what amount of US.
Officials were at the Marriott.
Why is the United States government specifically listen? Obviously, it would be like they know that the embassy isn't going to be bombed, but who else was staying at the Marriott that needed to be evacuated? Well, the Marriott did host some events sure, in the past.
It is a little bit like the United States government is like, hey, listen, Eric, you got to get out of that Marriott.
I know you've been staying there for a week until we find you a place closer to the office, but you got to get out of there, Eric.
Well, see, here is where this stew aspect comes from.
Sure.
Right.
So Alex has this story from 2002 about the threat to remove embassy employees.
And now he's bringing in they're saying that they were told to get out of the Marriott naturally, which can't be involved with this article because it's from about the US.
Embassy.
Right.
So he brings in another article that's a good idea to bridge the gap.
Not even bridge the gap.
He just jams them together into the same thing.
Okay, very astute timing again.
US.
Embassy canceled the booking of Marriott Hotel four and a half hours before the explosion.
Embassy canceled the booking of the Marriott Hotel before the explosion.
There was something interesting happening just hours before the explosion shot the JW Marriott Hotel.
So this is a bit of a pivot point, because Alex, up to this point, has been relying on this October 2002 article to argue that the embassy was threatening to withdraw staff.
That was true, but he was lying about the context of it and pretending it was a recent article related to the Jakarta bombing.
Right now, he's using a completely different source to make a completely different claim while acting like it's the same story.
Apparently what happened was that the US.
Embassy canceled reservations at the Marriott four and a half hours before the bombing.
Alex's sole source on this is a translation of an Indonesian website that makes this claim.
And their only source is an alleged employee of the Marriott who is anonymous.
There's no evidence that this is the case.
If I were the embassy and I were orchestrating elaborate fake terrorist plots in order to force the Indonesian government into cracking down on terrorists and going along with my larger global agenda, I don't think I would cancel those reservations.
It would keep them and just not show up.
Yeah, I mean, it doesn't make any sense.
Or even better, some of the expendable people who worked at the office could show up for the reservations and then the embassy could apply even more pressure on the Indonesian government.
Hold on.
When was the booking for? What's up? I mean, they said they canceled a booking, right.
But it didn't say there was an event at the hotel that day.
They could have been a booking for any time.
The implication is that it was like they were supposed to check in four and a half hours after that.
Sure.
Or that day or something.
Right, that's a great thing.
But he doesn't say no.
That is a great point.
Yeah.
And Alex will play with that a little bit later.
Okay.
But it is a little bit like if I'm planning a false flag, as you said, I'm going to leave those there.
What are you going to say? Listen, if we let it go too long, they're non refundable.
Okay? Right.
We got them.
Exactly.
They have a million come on.
And if it's a thing where the reservations are supposed to start the next day, they have a 24 hours cancellation policy.
I'm not sure if it's different for the USM, but if they have a special deal, budget is tight for the United States globalists in Indonesia, they got to pinch pennies.
Or if they're supposed to be there like that day or whatever, a bombing takes a while to plan.
Yeah.
You should know it didn't come together exactly 4 hours before I forgot to cancel it last minute.
So there's literally only one scenario where this makes sense as proof of a conspiracy, and that's the world where the evil globalists behind this plot canceled the reservation so they could leave behind a calling card for the conspiracy theorists to find.
This is basically Alex pretending that information is taunting him, which you have to realize is a part of the way he views no, of course, it is difficult to keep in mind that he does feel as though he's fighting the Mad Hatter, leaving clues behind at the scene everywhere he goes.
Yes.
Like the globalist or the riddler.
They're using puzzles.
Yes, exactly.
If I figure out all these clues, then I'll find the treasure underneath the United States Constitution.
It makes perfect sense.
And you and I are pointing out these problems with the idea of them canceling reservations as being a silly idea.
Right.
And that's even accepting the framing that they did, in fact, cancel these reservations on that day, which I do not know to be true.
Exactly.
I don't think that there's a solid piece of information about this.
Yeah, no, it doesn't work.
If they were there and they left, maybe.
But even then, it's at the Marriott.
I don't know.
That's what Alex says.
We've got the Saudi Arabians accusing the British government of carrying out the bombings and destabilize the region.
You've got the US.
Government with its employees who checked in hours before the bombing, then check out just a few hours later.
Alex doesn't have another source.
This is just him embellishing and making up details about the idea that the embassy canceled reservations at the Marriott before the bombing.
Right.
The Flimsy article that he's basing this on doesn't say any of this, but he can't help himself from escalating things.
Now, they didn't just cancel reservations.
They were actually there and checked in, but they went through all the trouble to check out hours early before the bombing.
Alex is making this up, because if it were true, it sure would seem pretty suspicious.
I suppose you even if they were there.
But even then, that's, like, flimsy ass shit.
It certainly would raise more of an eyebrow than right.
The other details.
But now it is a little bit like they check in.
They call in, and they're like, hey, can we get an early check in? Because we got to the Marriott too soon? And they go like, yeah, okay, fine.
We've got a room available.
So they go through the whole rigmarole.
They've left a credit card and an ID.
They've done all this shit.
They go up to the room and then like, oh, fuck, I forgot we got the bomb today.
They run down there.
They have to make a fake scene.
They have to make a big scene.
Oh, my room wasn't as clean as it needed to be.
How dare you, sirs? I demand a refund.
And then they leave.
It's conceivably the dumbest track of events for you to actually believe happened.
It's not great.
No one would go through this.
It's absurd.
But here's the thing.
Basically, Alex can't make compelling arguments based on the information that's available.
So he's cheating by just making up shit that makes his case look stronger, and he's doing this because he's a liar.
Yes, it does, though, right? Because once you establish the idea that you had these embassy people there who checked out, and you added to believing the Saudi arabian government about the British folks who were carrying out bombings to destabilize the Saudi arabian government.
You can combine this all together, and now you have a hit team at the marriott.
All right, it turns out the government had inserted a team of, well, it looks like 20 people or more what? Into this marriage.
They pulled out just a few hours before the blast.
And maybe it's just a coincidence they just so happened to pull them out when they were going to be there for two more days.
How do you know that? Because of the threat that's happening.
And of course, it turns out that the bali bombing they told the Taiwanese not to warn the bali's government, bolt the bombing.
You can see here Alex is building out the story.
He has a flimsy source that claims that the US.
Embassy canceled reservations hours before the bombing took place at the marriott, which he is now reporting as the US.
Sending in a team of about 20 people who are pulled out early.
This is solely from his own imagination, and it's nothing more than him writing his own little story about this tragic event so he can use it to further his own goals.
One thing I want to draw special attention to is the part where he says that they were pulled out of the hotel because of threats.
This is important because it's a synthesis of this flimsy source about the canceled hotel reservation and that article from 2002 about the lead up to the bali bombing.
Alex is taking the hotel detail from one story and mashing it up with the embassy being concerned about threats, that detail from the other story, and then serving it up for the audience as if it's something meaningful.
And it's the same thing.
If anything, this is an abuse of information.
And it's kind of silly to pretend that what he's doing is questioning world events.
Yeah, this isn't questioning.
This is just lying about shit so mass casualty events can be incorporated into your worldview more easily and you can profit off them.
Right.
It is funny that throughout this entire time, I find myself trying to give advice to the globalists and then realizing again that what I'm really doing is just in a writer's room with Alex, trying to punch up his narrative.
Like, a team of 20 is too big, too many people are going to that's too big, it's too obvious to see.
And then I realized, I'm not talking about this.
I'm with Alex being like, okay, listen, here's what we got to do.
He took that from the article about the canceled reservations that alleged that there were ten to 20 rooms.
Right.
So that's just a number that he's coming up with.
Yeah, why not? The reservation was apparently for three days, although it doesn't specify which three days.
And so that's where he's getting the two more days thing.
Sure.
But he's just cracking those details into his own form, whatever shape he wants them to take in order to make his story make sense.
Now, what I think is more interesting with your writerly instincts is the way that you have been one step ahead about narrative right.
That is interesting about going back to the past.
He does have those abilities.
It does feel like he's building something.
There is a little bit of an A to B to C with the way that the layers of the conspiracy are added on as he make stuff up about the little kernel that is at the base of it.
It feels like he's trying yeah.
It's not good effort.
No.
But it is an effort which we're not used to seeing in the present.
Holy shit.
Right.
Yeah.
It's transparent if you take the time to pay attention to it, but if you don't, or if you just operate off headlines and the optics of seeing a headline that says, us.
Embassy canceled reservations four and a half hours before the bombing.
And then you accept whatever Alex says about it if you just accept the story that he tells about that headline.
Sure.
The escalation of it does make sense.
Or if you believe the Saudi government about the British Embassy employees right.
That they tortured and got false confessions out.
Right.
These things.
Yeah.
There is a conspiracy that is crafted.
It's a little bit like a kid improving a book report where you're like, okay, I know you didn't read that book, but I'm actually kind of respecting your level of creativity and faking that you read that book.
You're making up some fun shit.
Sure.
It's like if a kid improvised a book report that was super disrespectful to a bunch of people who died in a bomb.
Right.
Yeah.
That would be where the Redford Grows is actually the Civil War burial ground.
That's a really worse book.
So Alex doesn't just stay on this topic all episode.
He also just yells about stuff, too.
Sure.
It's death squads, folks, and that's what Homeland Security and the National Police are.
That's what the SWAT teams are.
They're setting up death squads in America.
It's in Patriot Act one and two, to be able to come and kill you and never even tell people why they killed you.
Never charge you, never indict you, never arrest you.
I mean, this is textbook classical tyranny.
We're going to take calls, and I got a bunch of other news we're going to get to toll free number to join us.
So that's a little severe.
Yeah.
I think that you could make an interesting argument that in some ways the police are acting as not always, but sometimes do operate as a death squad.
I think that's not what Alex is talking about.
No.
Alex doesn't seem to really have that much problem with police brutality these days.
Kind of the issue so it rings a little hollow.
I mean, if you are putting together an Alex Jones was right clip, I don't understand why that's not on there.
Unless well, because Alex it doesn't work in the present for his own that narrative in the past.
Exactly.
And it's not worthwhile for him to really hang his head on.
Can't go back.
At least brutality.
Not now.
Too late.
You have to defend too many people on the left.
He can't do that.
No, he has to literally be above the left right paradigm in order to do that, and he's absolutely not.
So in this next clip, Alex goes to calls.
Sure.
And unfortunately, a caller asks a question that Alex was not prepared for.
What does DARPA stand for? It's the Advanced I've got to dig it out, but it's the Advanced Military Research System.
Okay, thank you very much.
You bet.
When you hear somebody talk about DARPA, they start with Advanced.
They never put the data, but it's the Defense Advanced Research Agency.
There you go.
Forgot the P.
One of the things I thought was really interesting about that first of all, that was not a gotcha question.
The caller was not trying to stomp him.
He was just interested.
And Alex should know that.
The thing that stuck out in my mind was that, like, on the stand in Alex's case, when Daria was testifying, they asked her what DARPA stands for.
She knew.
Yeah, that is true.
In 2003, Alex would fumble around with, what does DARPA stand for? Yeah, that's weird.
If that was scripts, he would have heard that ding real fast.
I understand what does Harpa stand for? Advanced.
I understand if you would have trouble with, like, Harp.
Sure.
He doesn't talk about Harp that much.
I don't know what has come up, but DARPA is like and he's in the middle of like this.
It's been a while since we've done a 2003 episode, but he just had that whole thing about how they were trying to gamble on terrorist attacks and stuff, set up a stock market on deaths.
It's pretty front and center of his narratives.
If you're a conspiracy theorist, you should have DARPA on the ready.
He should be caught on his back foot.
Yeah.
If you're a math teacher, you have to be able to do long division in your head.
Like, you have to you can't fumble around with that shit.
Otherwise, no one respects you.
So Alex takes another call, and this is the level of discourse that's going on on this show, man.
It's heady stuff.
Okay.
I wanted to get your opinion on a couple of things.
I was reading that on August 27, mars is going to be closest to the Earth than 60,000 years.
Yeah, it's going to be the closest to Earth 60,000 years.
We know much these globalists are into the occult.
We do know that opinion about if that has any significance or not.
Absolutely.
I don't believe astrology, I don't believe in quackery.
But the globalist.
Jimmy Carter, Ronald Reagan, Bush, Clinton.
They got shamans.
They're doing Seances.
They admit they run off of astrology.
Exactly.
And I keep meaning to mention this.
I'm glad you brought it up with Mars, the closest it'll be in 60,000 years, that's in humankind's history, folks.
In 60,000 years.
These guys are totally obsessed with numerology, what that portends the astrology.
And that's why they're moving so hard.
And it is very dangerous.
Go ahead and do you think that they would celebrate that day with another attack? Is that what you need to be looking at? I don't make predictions on things like that when they don't have enough data.
But I have to admit that reading about it and then seeing over the last year, we've been worried about August 24 when it will be the closest to Earth it's been in 60,000 years.
Okay, all right.
That is amazing.
I don't make those kinds of predictions, but I mean, look, that's amazing.
To go from not knowing a thing to suddenly just being like this thing is central to reorder.
Yeah, we're terrified of this thing.
Oh, is that true? I've been crunching the numbers and then there's a preponderance of evidence that Mars is going to be mars is a god of war.
That is true.
That was an event that did happen.
Right? I just appreciate that instantaneous.
Absolutely.
Is that something we should worry about? Absolutely.
You bet, brother.
You just fill in the blank if there is something you're asking Alex, if you should be worried about it.
Absolutely, brother, you nailed it.
There is a reason to be afraid.
You are not crazy for having this fear of something that nobody has literally ever thought before.
You are right, my friend.
Let's kill minutes of valuable time on my show.
Talking about being worried about Mars being too close.
I don't know, celebrating.
Celebrating what? Mars being close.
That's another problem here.
You didn't explain how this is related to an occult situation.
You're just like, oh, I bet because Mars is close this time they're going to be like, this is important.
I'm hearing the words you're saying, but you sound dumb.
It makes so much sense.
You reveal yourself to be a mark when you ask questions like that.
It's just understood that the globalists bomb things when planets are close how much closer? How much closer? It couldn't be that much.
It's not like a million miles closer.
On this one day I think it was quite a bit closer.
Much closer.
I don't know, I don't remember.
I looked it up, but I don't remember the exact right.
I didn't look up if there was any bombing on.
Sure.
Well, you had to the Little League World Series to play that.
Maybe some boss yes.
Maybe some home runs were hit that shouldn't have necessarily made it out.
Yeah.
Gravitational pull of mars right over the rafters, running track power got a little bit stronger.
Yeah, I mean, look, this is just dumb, but yeah, it's interesting that you have that response of like, why would that even be something that the globalists are interested in? Because to me, I mean, I'm joking around, scolding you or making fun of you, but to me that makes total sense.
It's just a little bit closer.
Yeah, there's magical powers.
Okay, but if that's the case, then it suggests that as markets further away, something else changes that makes you less likely to celebrate.
Right.
It being further away than Venus gets closer or is it just a day? Is it just like, oh, this is like a solar eclipse.
They all go outside, they look up and they're like, oh, look at that.
And then they go back to their lives.
Oh, no, they can see a solar eclipse and then they got to bomb something.
You got it.
That's right.
Yeah.
It is so much your cavemen.
Just like anything is aside, just like, oh, there's a shooting star.
That's a sign Mars is a little close.
That's a sign.
It is such that it is just caveman thought, that's all it is.
Well, and Alex takes kind of a simplistic understanding of symbolism, occultism and just applies it sort of universally.
Right.
a date that has doubled.
So it's like March 6, 2009, three, six, nine sure.
Very suspicious date.
Magical powers on this date.
I like that.
One thing that's never really addressed is how many holidays occult people have to have.
It is every day there is a holiday, there's something.
Take away the bombing and we should all live like that.
Every day is special and worth celebrating, but not everyday.
Mars is the closest it's going to be in 60,000 years.
No, that's true.
It's going to be 59,900 and something years before we get that again someday.
And look at it, because there will be a bomb in 59,000 years.
We know that.
Put it on your calendars.
So, Alex, we know that his dad was a big JBS guy and bad influence on him.
Turns out his uncle wasn't better.
My uncle really is an expert on the new world order.
He's got it for years and I had an argument with him about five years ago.
I said, yeah, the new order is going to set up a B system and biometrics, but I said, It's going to take time to do that.
He said, no, they build it, they lined it all up, they get it ready and they announce it.
And boy, how true his knowledge on that is.
That's what they do.
They set the whole thing up.
We go, Gee, what's behind these curtains? They lift the curtains and it's a total dehumanizing, satan pit.
Oh, how interesting.
We're in it, ladies and gentlemen.
I like that image.
Like a goblin feast or demon feast.
It is a dehumanizing Satan pit.
And his response to that is interesting.
Yeah, well, that is interesting.
I would like to know what that is.
Ladies and gentlemen, I regret to inform you we are in the Satan pit.
Okay, so you trip and you fall into the dehumanizing Satan pit.
I don't know.
I'm trying to visualize this.
Right.
I appreciate first off, my favorite visual is lifting up the curtain to reveal a picture.
That's just great.
That's good show.
But ship.
Okay.
If you open a curtain to a pit, it's good stuff.
Yeah.
All right.
What's in the pit? It could be anything, man.
I mean, there's got to be more than one Satan in the pit.
First off, there needs to be multiple Satan's in this pit.
Is that possible? I assume he can split himself up.
He's got classic Marvel powers these days.
All right.
Right.
Sure.
Yes.
Not my favorite.
This is like, the argument that Alex and his uncle had.
Yeah, probably.
I think that's cousin Buckley's.
Dad.
Oh, yeah.
That would be my guess.
Because he's definitely someone who Alex has brought up before.
Right? He talks about uncles with information.
So fun.
Oh, yeah.
There's another news story that Alex touches on here.
Bush picks new Selective Service director Crawford, Texas.
President Bush has picked a former lobbyist, an exmarine, as a record of the Selective Service.
Bush said Tuesday intends to nominate William A.
Chatfield for the post.
The Selective Service would provide manpower for the military of an emergency force to draft.
They've got all the bills lined up now.
One more terror attack, universal Draft.
It collects young men's names through the Selective Service registration system to try to change the law for women.
Chatfield is currently a government relations consultant with Kindness and Chatfield Associates in Washington.
So that's real nice.
And all the things where people talk about how accurate Alex is, they seem to just forget his constant obsession with how a universal draft was right around the corner and how the globalist had it set up so the next time there was a terrorist attack, that was it, and all your sons and daughters were going to be conscripted.
Yeah, big whiff on that.
And he brings it up all the time.
Yeah.
One wonders if Alex made a big stink when Trump nominated Donald Benton to this position in April 2017.
If that was evidence of Trump trying to reinstate the draft, I would imagine it wasn't.
I don't think he probably even noticed.
Yeah.
This is a small government office that has existed since World War One and could probably just be abolished.
Even though it's not a pool for a draft.
The names and information gathered from Selective Service registration are used by the Joint Advertising, Marketing, Research and Studies Program out of the Department of Defense, which uses that information to recruit volunteers into the.
Armed service anyway? Is there anything not evil? It's not cool.
Right.
But there isn't a draft, and there wasn't one in 2003.
That being said, let's just access office.
Get rid of it.
Yes, get rid of that.
That's bad.
It's obvious there won't be a job.
We can barely afford the military we have now.
Can you imagine if we just had an influx of, I don't know, 10 million people just to walk in there? How much would it cost to outfit them? We've got to spend a trillion dollars on one plane.
I kind of understand the thinking of something like this in past days.
Although I think that there is a social contract that has come into place that is we will never have a draft again, ever.
No, that is not something that is going to be seen as appropriate on any level.
And because of that, I think it would be a show of good faith for the government to get rid of this office.
Yeah.
Because there's this premise of it that is like, in case we need this registration brick glass.
Right.
Go ahead and get rid of that because you're not going to need it because we're not doing a draft again.
Yeah.
Well, it is always a universal step towards fascism whenever you have a standing army at the call.
Like part of that idea of hypothetical army.
Well, no, I mean, the current standing army that we have, the part of that hypothetical draft is you're not really supposed to have an army.
So everybody has their own skin in the game, so to speak.
And now it is kind of an impunity, and that's kind of part of our agreement.
We don't have a draft, and then we'll look the other way whenever you start wars all the time.
We can go ahead and get rid of that part of it, too.
Yeah, that would be nice.
Get rid of most of these offices.
So, look, Alex in the present day, talking a lot about being broke and being in debt and he needs money.
Yeah.
I have found the first time he ever said this, okay.
On air.
The very first time.
Well, I mean, if you believe what he's about to say.
Oh, so he says, to be honest got you.
And I have to do this.
I've never done this in five years, not one year.
I am with a shortwave bill, and Jim Shepherd's been helping me.
So it's paid to the shortwave outlet.
I'm about $15,000 behind.
Folks, we need you to simply buy the videos, let you make copies of them, and buy the books and buy the products from sponsors like Jim Shepherd.
Because when I have a sponsor that covers part of the cost and I cover the other part of the expense, very important that that sponsor be supported, especially when they got a real product.
That's amazing.
I don't mean to make this a long rant.
I'm not going to start doing this all the time, but I want to keep reaching the people in that French village.
I want to keep reaching the people in hiding in Indonesia.
I want to continue to reach people in Japan and in the Highlands of Scotland.
Jim shepherd, good to have you on the show.
Always a pleasure to be with you, Alex.
And I'm sorry you had to sit there while I went to that diet ride, but Alex, I really respect the way you do things.
May not know this, but several times I've mentioned to you, alex, maybe you got to give next response on there.
And invariably what you tell me is, jim, I'm not going to turn my show into an infomercial, into a merchandise and infomercial, I'm not going to do it.
I want to get the news out, and that's my primary objective.
Wow.
Yeah.
That's kind of a bummer, that to hear someone else say back to him in the past, bad news, Jim.
Jim largely a marketing infomercial.
Yeah.
He's the water filter sponsor.
Right.
So basically it's just the introduction of an infomercial.
With this, I'm behind on my shortwave bill because we pay for airtime on the shortwave station.
Sure.
And my water filter guy helps pay that bill.
So here he is by his water filter.
It does seem very difficult to square someone saying, you know what? I like that you don't do infomercials and you've got the integrity to not turn your show into anyways, my water filters are the best.
I agree with you.
It does bear mentioning that it is not as intrusive at this.
No, of course it's not the whole show.
Right.
It's at least like, all right, here is a chunk that they're doing.
And it's pretty transparent that this guy is selling his shit right now.
At the same time, a lot of Jim's sales pitch for his water filter is about the evils of fluoride.
Sure.
And so there is still, like, content that's being used as marketing.
Right.
So there's still that blurry distinction.
Poncon.
Yeah.
But, man, it is a far cry from the deterioration into Infomercial City and leaving behind the information that Alex becomes later.
I appreciate most of all that $15,000 number.
I feel like potatoes when you look at Alex, but I feel like that's where you got to stay at.
The $15,000 is important to you, because then look at him now.
He's got shell companies.
He's got to have accountants willing to lie for him, and then he's got to have accountants that his accountants lie to in order to launder their lives.
Right.
Like, that is a web of bullshit.
Think about this.
He's just got a bill.
He's in such dicey legal situations that he has to be friends with Barnes.
Yeah.
All you've got to do is pay your short wave bill.
You stay there.
Stay there.
It's a good sweet spot.
Yeah, absolutely.
Poor Alex.
Yeah.
There's a lot of folks who defend Alex, and one of the things that they say I think you would agree with, and that is that he tells it like it is.
I tell it like it is.
I don't pull my punches.
I fight evil.
I expose the new world order.
Evidence is now coming out.
The bombing in Jakarta, Indonesia, was the work of the globalist.
They were pulling their people out hours before it took place.
From the very hotel itself, not other hotels.
They had threatened the government to submit to total Global Control or Terrace Wood strike.
Yes.
No one who says I tell it like it is ever.
Actually, one does or two has anything good to say.
What about people who calls them like they see them? Well, that's delicious.
As long as you add the plural.
Yeah, it calls them like I sees them.
That's good stuff.
Okay, so that one is all right.
That's a little bit that has reverence.
What about a straight shooter? Straight shooter? No, it's something that other people describe you as.
That makes me think that you are a liar.
Alex takes more calls here and he gets a call from a guy who I think doesn't believe in laws.
I appreciate this, man.
It's kind of difficult to tell exactly where he's coming from, but he believes, I think, maybe in a God's law kind of situation.
Trying to get that self evident law? Yeah, natural law, perhaps.
He's not specific enough for me to really nail down, but he does believe that just because laws are signed into law, that doesn't mean they're laws.
So he's not in the jurisdiction.
He's more of the law of the jungle kind of guy.
Based on his voice, I don't think he lies in the jungle.
Yeah, well, that's probably true, but maybe spiritually.
Okay.
Anyway, he has a request for Alex.
I keep running all over you, but I've had you on a couple of segments.
Anything else you wanted to add from New Mexico? I just want to know if I can get a time to call you for a few minutes off the air.
I got some things to hash over to kind of take some thought.
Unfortunately, from the time I leave here until about midnight tonight, I'm going to be working.
But good excuse.
I don't know when I can talk to you, sir.
I mean, I'm not trying to spam a big shot or anything.
I'm in deep trouble.
I have hundreds of phone calls, hundreds of emails, faxes with folks that want to talk to me, and let's talk about it here on the air.
Go ahead.
What's going on? Look, dude, I'm behind the eight ball.
I like it when trying to let them down easy.
Gets way out of hand.
I'm in big trouble.
To the point where he's like, listen, I'm on the run from the cops right now.
I can't be taking phone calls at any point in time.
I shouldn't even be doing a radio show.
Honestly.
Listen, I had to get rid of my phone.
I've got burner phones.
I throw them into the ocean after I use them.
One time I'm in a bunker that is sealed with lead and they'll never find me.
Listen, I'm behind the a ball.
I'm working for the next 6 hours.
I'm being chased by the cops.
I've got to take my daughter fishing at some point so I can't call you.
It seems really obvious the way you could just handle this and that is that it is unsafe for me to talk to you off the air.
Yeah.
I don't know what you're up to.
There's a lot of ways that this could expose me.
If you're Alex, this is the simplest thing in the world, but you don't want to give that message because it's too likely to make the audience think that you think that they're crazy or something.
Whereas Alex is a big public figure.
There is a very acceptable boundary to be like, I'm not talking to you off air.
We don't know each other.
You can send an email or something, but we're not going to do that.
When you actively court people who blur the line between reality and fiction, it's going to be a little bit more of a tighter walk to let them down easy on account of you don't know what part of the fiction that's going to add you into.
That's true.
You see that through a lot of interactions that Alex has with his fans over the course of time.
There is an unwillingness to be honest about what the boundary is because of that.
I know who you are.
Right.
I know.
And we just need to keep this separate.
The only thing I know about you is you believe what I say.
You like me and that's bad.
Yeah.
The Groucho Marx's thing.
I don't want to be a member of any club that would have me as a member.
Surely that's used to describe low self esteem.
Right.
But with Alex completely different.
I made this club and I don't ever want to visit this club close.
I lock the door with them inside it.
I don't want to be around anybody who would be a member of my club.
Listen, I own the Double Deuce and I'm not stepping foot in that fucking place.
No.
So anyway, this caller here's what he wants to discuss with Alex offair.
Let's talk about it here on the air.
Go ahead.
What's going on? Well, it concerns the interpretation of the Bible and we are not supposed to fear any has to expose the devil and he will flee from you.
Oh boy.
And it's a long story.
The pieces of this puzzle are scattered from one end of the Bible to the other and put them all together in right order.
They're going to take some serious thought because Christ said that the scribes will pervert the scriptures.
And there are some places that take Bill research to figure out what was changed.
This is not a total holy word of God, it is the perverted word of God.
And I think it would take a half an hour if you don't what I mean, probably longer than that.
Sir, you have just explained why I do not want to talk to you up there.
Sir, people have been studying the Bible for quite a while now.
You didn't you have cracked the code.
You cracked the code.
You're telling me.
And it'll take you half an hour to explain it to me? Yeah, that's I'm sure you're going to stop in a half hour.
I'm going to start the watch and that you don't get on with things.
So you have one last clip here and I know that another thing that was making the rounds on social media was recently was a clip of Alex saying that there was going to be false flag globalist terror attacks before the midterms.
This is another clip Ron Flipkowski decided to post without context, relevant context that Alex says that all the fucking time, pretty much every day.
It is not worthwhile or meaningful to post at all to make people think this is like, oh, look at him, look at him.
He's making a desperate, weird prediction.
No, this is what he does every day and has since 2003.
I've already read Patriot Act too.
It allows them to secretly grab you, blow your head off for any misdemeanor and get business records without a court order.
And Ashcroft is going to go on a ten states tour to promote this.
Well, I know he's already promoting it, I'm sorry, 20 state.
20 state tour.
But you're telling me that he's recording a special oh, man.
Recorded in today's New York Daily News.
If you want, you can get the Daily News online.
Well, the fact that they're introducing this now tells me they're getting ready to do some boom booming.
Oh, yeah, they're going to do some boom booming.
I mean, let's see, we've had explosions before the midterm.
We've had nukes before presidential election.
Sure we've had they were going ramp up helicopter intoauguration yes, obviously the polonium poisoning was rampant for a while.
There were two incidents to the same person that also didn't happen.
Right.
But yes, there was that.
It's constant.
It's a hallmark and feature of his career and anybody who doesn't understand that, it's window dressing it's again, just like we were laughing and joking about this before.
It's just like if you ask Alex, is there a reason to be scared about something, absolutely, yes.
And one of the things he always uses to scare people is that specter of the coming false flag attack that is justified by some piece of his narrative.
There is obviously Democrats are scared that they are going to lose the midterms.
And so they must do bombings in order to make sure they win the midterms.
Right.
Ashcroft wants to get Patriot Act Two in, but there's opposition to it from the Patriots.
He's better do some boom booming in order to make sure that this goes through.
It's always this.
And I don't understand how it's been 20 years.
I know.
And it's still an effective thing.
It's still something that people can it's because people dip in and out.
It's because people like Ron Philip.
Owki.
Get to dip in and out.
A fucking youth baseball coach turned by the media into some fucking alt right hero for just being a fucking idiot.
I hate him so much.
But it is that, like, oh, if you dip in every three or four months, then you have in your head this idea, well, he can't do this every day.
Because you assume that because there's no way he could do this every day.
Right.
I mean, even if you have an awareness of who Alex is and you don't pay much attention, jon Ronson even was like, does he repeat things? Absolutely.
Yeah.
There is a awareness of what Alex does that you only really get by watching a bunch of it.
And unfortunately, I don't think that most people should do that because it's obviously well, I mean, the problem is our own assumptions based on how everything else works.
It is to us unsustainable to do the same thing every day.
Will you imagine how bored you would get if a show that you watched the same thing, you see a clip every few months and you go, wow, this must be an unusual thing.
It wouldn't be newsworthy.
Yeah, he's on one.
It wouldn't be newsworthy if it's every day.
But it's newsworthy because it's manufactured for you.
It's created for you.
I think there's that the dipping in and out for sure is a piece of it.
And then I also think that one of the reasons that it stays effective is there is just pain in the world.
Like negative traumatic events do happen.
Sure.
And those are things that Alex will then attach these ideas too.
And I guess people will just experience that as being the confirmation, and they'll forget about all the countless times that he's been making up vague warnings about boom booming.
Yeah.
I mean, the thing that's most suspicious is in 20 years, the globalists would have to have taken a break for a bit, at least.
No way.
But they have never stopped, not once.
Despite the fact that they celebrate a million holidays every year.
It is always a work holiday.
They never even take a vacation.
Well, they're like Alex that way.
Except even that he's not working, ever.
No, but that just gave me an idea for a movie pitch.
Globalist vacation.
They finally take a vacation.
Now we have two movie pitches.
Okay, that's one.
That's the first 1.
Second one.
The globalists are on vacation.
Sure.
But they still need to be false flags.
Naturally.
So they bring in the junior varsity globalist hemps.
Right? Absolutely.
Somebody gets promoted.
This is their big shot.
Right.
But it turns out this is an eager young person.
If they were younger or we had made this movie, like, 15 years ago, this would be a vince Vaughn, owen Wilson.
Absolutely.
They're the guys who come in and they ragtag band of misfits.
Vacations? No.
The global intern.
Yeah.
What would we call them? I mean, you got to call them something like the Nation Squad.
They're not global.
It sucks.
We'll work on this.
Yeah.
We'll workshop this and have it back for you in about six months.
We'll get a treatment going.
So I'm glad to have gone back to the past because at least there is something concrete going on to be discussed.
Yes, that is refreshing.
I appreciate the past a great deal.
And so we'll check back in on the present day, keep people posted on dumb Bullshit, the Terror of the midterms midterms.
But until then, Jordan, we have a website.
We do have a website.
It's knowledgefight.com.
Yeah.
We're also on Twitter.
We are on Twitter.
It's a knowledge underscore fight.
We will be back.
But until then, I'm Leo.
I'm Leo.
I'm dzx Clark.
I'm Gerald Snippets.
No.
Gerald.
Yeah.
I was wondering where Gerald? That's Wilford's cousin.
I am Wilford Snipplesnabble of The Gribble Pivot.
And now here comes the sex robots.
Andy and Chamberlain, you're on the air.
Thanks for holding.
So alex.
I'm a first time color.
I'm a huge fan.
I love your work.
I loved.