Damn important
I have great respect for knowledge B I'm sick of them
Knowledge fight
Acknowledge
Dot-com
The altar of Selena
Alex Jones Jordans
Quick question for you
My bright spot today Jordan isn't actually bright spot but it's sort of all right okay
It's right here
Santa
Oh boy I saw a flavor
#what if what's the Fanta what the Fanta
What the Fanta
You can't f****** with flavor with a hashtag that is it that I call foul
?
Because it says fine
Clues hashtag what the Fanta
Oh my God one of those drawings
To these
Curious flavors as we talked about in the last episode
Dream
Bland Chevy World Coke
Also got a number of messages from people who were like egg up at space Coke
That happened not going to happen
I'm drawn to these things
You got like
Pineapple
Orange
Butter fruit flavors
Only thing I know about Fanta is be commercial from the early.
Advanta
It's fruit
Write all of them approved
Expecting fruit
Bachelorette
Candy
That big of a heel turn
My friend that was not a fruit
I can tell you that for sure
Yeah I think it's cotton candy I'm putting this on the record
Candy grapes
They taste like cotton candy and their grapes
That the fruit that would be an interesting Tech
Alright that I'll put that down
Just because that help
Okay that makes my guess a little bit more
Well done
Also it's not good
No relief done job
Get your s*** together
You know what I didn't even wanted necessarily tell you but it begins with a t and ends with an a
Serena
Well I mean that
Was
A beautiful boat because
Mentally emotionally affected Williams to retire
Not one of the greats
The Great
I think
I think that a good on iPad don't know enough about tennis to say
Fully willing to
I agree with you I just think it's
And someone who knows nothing about this portal
Definitely top players of all time
You are an expert so I'll take your word on it
So is it Pippin just have feelings
Pete Sampras
From my youth
Feelings
Memory memory actually
As a man with a substantial arm hair I imagine that you do have a lot to go on
Rob Robin Williams on the great tennis player
Started me make a biopic arm hair fat lady
Robin Williams
Mcenroe he still he still around
He narrates a TV show
Little yellow bumps
No regular duration that is John McEnroe with no like and they just
It's never even address their never like hey Felix
That's his job but whatever
You're crazy
That House of Payne
Song Jump Around
References John McEnroe
That's not crazy
John Mcenroe what's the biggest thing in the world
Forever very short. Of time
I'm saying
Time oh yeah it was a long time ago
Accu Brite Spot
I really think this is one of the best ones I've seen in a long long time like
Top-to-bottom everybody is
Is good is that young kid you like you're doing well correct yeah yeah he's headed to the quarterfinals my man
Wrath of course discretion it is
In San Francisco Around The Bay
Fedele's out dad
I already saw that coming from a mile away or if it's San Francisco
1400 miles away
Where are they at
In terms of the egg
No I mean like in terms of the final semi-finals where we at
The final how many rabbit
Before the fourth round is the quarterfinals in the semi-finals
So so the fourth round is the round of 16 okay the round right before the
16 tonight is probably we're going to be the best
Match of the entire tournament
Kyrgios vs. Medvedev
Kyrgios
Crushing it was the first time in his life in the Russia
Different carriers
Different Medvedev
But
Can be great I would love it if
The fuk with you the US Open
Was
Still at like
3 in the
Same time as the French
Ulta
To set up 8
Exactly the same number of memories of you being like I'm going to be up
Fall Nikes
I woke up at 3 a.m. so I can
I'll be up until 4 a.m. tomorrow night
Sit at a bar have to go to the airport
That's true
I just assumed that's what it's like to be satisfied that you're always watching
The 2 a.m. illegal streams help
I could I do that
I feel like a number of wrestling fans have the same sort of thing with I
Japanese
Promotion
Pay-per-views and stuff to love something I guess guess yeah
Today
What are we talkin about appraisal
Episode
Because bats
Signal weather
What speed
I heard people talking about a speech
I can't tell if you're joking
No I mean I know about the speech but it's like I just don't understand why people
Yeah okay yes okay
Okay
Nevermind
That was it
I really thought that if there was some stuff but it's just it's a look
It looks familiar I actually I mean we can get into a little bit now and will come to more episode and such but
I think this is
Speech is either going to be historically and
Incredibly relevant and guy or
Not
But in a temp
To be very historically relevant
Yeah I'm not sure exactly how the ball is going to break at this point
He gave us
Speech that was essentially like Hey look
Here's the situation
Trump
And the people who were following him these Maga folks
Are a mess
They don't care about democracy
And they are very serious threat to democracy
Proceed as we
Are experiencing it now and
Disability of the country
Normal Folk
Democrat
Independence
Publicans who aren't into that nonsense right
We have a responsibility to do what we can't
To protect democracy Now
The
Future Generations will look back
Psoriasis being in the
Fight if we do our job they will look at the
This point
As an inflection point in history
There were a number of things that are
I would say a little bit overdue in terms of
Recognition of Hey look
This s*** is nonsense
Right
Well and
You do previously had called hook 70 fashion
So you there isn't there is like a little bit of a finally
Some of this is
These words are being uttered
There is an aspect of life
Love you too little too late that is definitely present
Doesn't even really mean
Girl like
Is it going to
Push any needles
Directions
Or is this going to be something that has just a severe backlash
Who knows
In my in my humble opinion the only reason that a president should give a speech is as
Cover
Somebody to arrest like a thousand people at the same time right
And then all of a sudden in the middle of this meet you start cutting two people being arrested
Do a blocks
Like all the bankers are going
Like the whole thing that's do that's because I pathetic
Oh absolutely man that's the he's giving his speech to say that these people
Are coming for democracy
Surprise
They're all in jail right now
How about that well as we are at the speech as we are a few days after this
Unfortunately your your movie fantasy the shot happen
But yeah I'm really there's part of me that is quite
Conflicted about like
How
Exciting to think
The
Like
You know given voice
Do a lot of this stuff
Like or how meaningful it is
I would like to believe that like a
Indicative of
You know something
The broader
Honestly
There's a there's a
Another part of me that is a geyser
It's probably empathy
Dent in its direction
Directionless
Even well I mean you have to ask yourself
And I think that no I think the entire country is asking
Can you tell right now
Does anybody even listen to the president anymore
More like all of real talk
Does anybody
Care what he says
They might be one of the largest effects of trump
I know it's like someone who f****** cares with the president has to say years we had
Twitter
Even before Trump you had president to it have
Detox
No promises that I capture
The Syria Redline Seattle used to a bit of that
Just talk
Just all the time
It seems tough to like comeback for
From bad to good
I will take all this very seriously gravitas of the office
Get me and say that I should give a s*** about what the
What it says
I can if I so choose
But how dare you say I should
Yeah it's a tough
It's a tough
Walk from the past
Stuff like my fellow Americans I come to you today to like
Trump being like
They say I have a
The small dick imagine imagine FDR's Fireside
Speeches if it was just like oh you only thing we have to fear is how tiny Hitler's balls are you my right
Everybody
Gorgeous
The notion of
Thinking about
President
In history
Caring about
Memes
Send it
Does the equivalent of memes at the time
Did he get mad about memes
Holy if there was a if there was a nasty little
Comic is stripping a paper he went ape shitt maybe that's why I looks like them
I think so
Anyway we got an episode to go over valances response today
A second 220 220 22
And whose reactions about
Great speech I loved it I buy huge fan of Biden from now on vocativ in its imagery
All the things I said about Emma
Other diseases
Of
So first illegal Owen Wilson impersonator thank you so much
Lego nexo for fucksake thank you so much right now policy walk
That's my favorite one in a long time
Gets to the point love it
Classic
I will not do an impression
Next every second of knowledge
Thank you very much
As you all know for security reasons my name is changed monthly
This month you may call me tickle tickle
Poppy top thank you so much
Door knob
Thank you very much
I keep saying the walkie a little before we go outside
Thank you so much
Don't get mad and tell your brother someone
Sodomites
Jesus Christ
Thank you so much thank you very much
Sweetheart
The speech happened
And
Because of that
Alex decided like I'm not going to wait
Intro to play
I'm just getting them there I'm diving
The show start
Sink my teeth into this speech he is
Like just
In it okay
Now see America is going under total New World Order martial law
Tomorrow's news today
Timex
Nailed it
Yeah that's not bad
Professional
Larian set
Really seems to be
What are the primary things that Alex's folks
Kristen
The optic
Pics of it
The red light
Behind him. He gave a speech at
Knight Caesar
Preoccupied by
I mean I assume that the
Content of the speech is not really something
He's very
A little bit here in there
Some of that stuff that really works well for him
Yeah but
The Optics are the reasons
That
This is really sticking in his craw is it worth
We heard for
Years
During Trump's time Alex being like
You have
The bully pulpit
Do an evening speech
Get out there in a dress
The population in Primetime and get your
Your message
Do that right or you didn't
Do the thing that I Alex wants and now here you have
Doing exactly what Alex
I was wishing Trump would do
But giving a speech so you know the thing that there
Famously Furious that he
He cannot do
You know we can't speak
Clearly for a second
Do
Note that Alex doesn't
Play like
The full speech
Replace some B will get that here in a second but like
Because there is a key he makes gas all the time cuz no plan exhaust
And so
Yeah it's
I think it's sour grapes
Someone for Alex
The Trump would have done something
Something like this you wishes the Trump would have
Declared war on the globalist
He's in a situation
Kitchenware like Biden's doing the thing I wanted Trump to do
I'm not saying
That I have any kinship with Alex over this but I do believe that his idea of what
Speeches
Would happen
Is very similar to mine
You know that that
You know this speech happens
While your arrest
Sting everybody that you need
Arrested
Yeah I think he and I are very similarly alive and that means a wave it
Speeches should go well
There's a slight difference
Well you guys are both like experience
I'm wishing reality was a movie
Alex's portraying
Giving the speech
Cover for bags
Locking up of all of their political enemies
Yes I guess there's a similarity
To somebody about that
Like an expert
What's nothing
Supposed to say to that expert
I don't know there's like 700 episodes
Maybe they'll give you a honorary degree
Otso Alex
Does start the show by playing some of B
And I noticed that there were some
Some Cuts
Not a republican Embraces our extreme ideology
Cuz I've been able to work at these mainstream Republican
And here
In my view is what
True
Subway
So there's pretty obvious cut
There is very important to point out is that
Biting does go out of his way
Be very specific about like
Like what he's talkin
He's talking about folks
Do not understand the transfer of power
The folks who don't have any interest
The turtle
Governing
Rules and norms
Not just Republicans
This is not just a very partisan
Types p.m. he broke down at one point and just started screaming
In a fashion
Rita's bring it up.
Intrigued me that there was this these days
Because he has all the time
In the world on his show you can play whatever you want
Do you know
What he wants
Right
But here's what was said
Between
At the clips that was cut out
Quote
But there's no question that the Republican party today is dominated driven and intimidated by Donald Trump and the magaru
Publicans and that this is a threat
To this country
These are hard things
But I'm an American
Not the president of America or blue America but of all America
And I believe it is my duty my duty to level with
To tell you the truth no matter how difficult no matter how pain
It may be coincidence that this was cut out but it also seems like a point Alex wouldn't
Be super comfortable with
Particularly the part about
The Gob being intimidated by Trump
And his followers
The Impressions about Trump and the Maga folks is supposed to be that they're winning the Battle of ideas and that they're just smarter
More patriotic than the rest of us
Which is why they've taken over the GOP
It's not a great idea to plant seeds in the audience
Does Mida maybe they're part of something hostile that is gaining power not by being ideologically better
But by being more willing to threaten
An employee file
Alex also cuts out the part at the beginning or Biden says quote
We must never forget
We the people are the true Heirs of the American Experience
But the began more than two centuries ago
We the people burning inside each of us the flame of Liberty that was lit hear it Independence
Too tall
A flame that lit our way through abolition the Civil War suffrage the Great Depression world war Civil Rights
That sacred flame still Burns now in our time as we build an America that is more prosperous free and just
That is the work of my presidency admission
I believe in with my whole soul
That's just good business on Alex's bar cutting that out
He has a vested interest in pretending that his political enemies
I hate the country and what it stands for
So it's best not to allow someone like buying
Speak like this on Infowars
Is someone who has a passionate
I love
For the country or two.
Robidoux confused
Really terrifying if he quoted Thomas
Batman
That would be accurately
Inaccurately quoted Thomas Jefferson
They would go
Absolutely a****** at all
Day all day would
Would be a Non-Stop barrage
What we all know.
To be the truth
Of their ability to remember or even
Fantasize
Thomas Jefferson quote
Speechwriter
Slipping something about Deez Nuts or something of that quote Thomas Jefferson
PJ all
That be wonderful at the way you got to go
So I mean he plays
Enough
Of the speech
Just play
The full path
If you wanted to put there is just this is Frankenstein together everywhere
They promote authoritarian leaders and they fan the flames
Political violence
Threat
For personal rights
So the pursuit of just
The rule of law
The very soul of this
We hear you heard it
More and more talk about violence
She could hear that caught there again
Instead in the middle of that right after where it cut
The mob that stormed the United States Capitol on January 6th
Brutally attacking law enforcement not as Insurrection is to place a dagger to
The throat of our democracy
But they look at them as Patron
And they see their Maga failure to stop a peaceful transfer of power after the 2020 election
Has preparation
And for the 2020
2 + 2024
I think Alex knows well enough that most of his audience
Stussy January
Six Riders is Patriots
Which is uncomfortable
Yeah
It's hard for the
It's hard to rationalize
If you really have
Confronted on
Yeah yeah this is holding up a mirror to his audiences beliefs in a way they could be threatened
Where is Auto Parts
To the speech that are left in they really are
Brixton tea leaves in Biden saying
They promote authoritarian leaders
Because the audience
Doesn't think they do that
Trump DeSantis bolsonaro in orbit
Furthest Thing from authoritarian in the audience's eyes
So hearing Biden say that is just absurd.
That's not the
It's not something's like
I'm taking it back by then
Yeah
Another part that Alex leaves in
It's quote
Maga forces are determined to take this country back work
2 in America where there is no right to choose no right to privacy
No right to contraception no right to marry who you love
All that stuff
Stuff that is audience
Believes it is totally fine with I was going to say that's like
Yeah man that's what we are doing
In favor of banning contraception they want to get rid of marriage equality
The idea of right
The Privacy is vague enough that they can just
Slept that in Alyssa
Day I don't know what that mean we want the right to privacy but we also want to break into your home if you
Things to do with
Social media I don't care whatever
This is not threatening
For Alex to show the audience because
Is the audience the feeling divided
Is declaring war on them
For their political beliefs
The I identify with the people
The Biden is describing as a threat
Democracy which is what Alex wants
To feel
The case of the January 6th thing that's a little bit
That's a case where the audience will see their feelings mirrored by what Biden to saying but
It's not about political positions make
Can justify his rash
Opposition to abortion or believing that marriage is just
Between a man and a woman are things that are common in Many religious communities
Give you pause to look at
Put yourself in that mirror
The rights of January 6th action
And those actions are way harder for people who want
See themselves as
Respectable
To justify
That's a mirror is best not to look into partially because
Except
The group that
Tried to overrun the capital in order to stop a life electric being certified poses a threat to our Democratic process
You don't want let me want that mirror
Alex has also cut this part out
But while the threat to American Tobacco
Chrissy is real I want to say as clearly as we can
We are not powerless in the face
These threats
We are not bystanders and its ongoing attack on democracy
There are far more Americans
Barber American
From every
From every background at believe who reject
The extreme Agha ideology
Send those who accept
After that line
There was a big
This could be useful to instill fear in the audience but that's
Play as well with the Infowars version of Biden
And these ideas
A huge part of the election
Conspiracies that vine was so unpopular and then no one would come to his rally so
You don't really want these large Applause brain and the getting Applause
For the idea that there are more people who are sick of this
Stuff then Alex's
Gubiotti of that good
That's not good
There's a bunch more that's cut out and a lot of it is Biden saying things about uniting around defending our political process
Cement getting Applause
No need for stuff like that
Because it's bad
You don't want it I mean yeah
Also
For him it
Yeah you know it's not even a thing it's just like oh yeah we're not you we don't
We can't use that
So why leave it in you know and nobody's going to question us for
For cutting it it's obvious by audiences going to watch the whole speech
They're going to accept whatever interpretation I give and that's going to be real
You know I was I was wondering
You know part of why I think the
It's calling the January
Six people Patriots
It is weird to me it's
Because
It was such a huge fuk up
You know like they really we all saw that it was just a bunch of f****** assholes
Just really being pieces of s***
You know
You can't
Mythologize that the same way
You can the boss
Boston Tea Party
Do you know like that was just a bunch of assholes going on a boat and like
F****** s*** up you know Counterpoint
What
William Travis
Fair enough
Drunk assholes f****** murdering people at their house who was only there because he was running away from rats
His ex-wife
Nevermind nevermind
I should have looked at
Mormonism
We're too close to it now yeah that's all remember some of the details as opposed to that
Selling of the myth
I think you're right
For now but give it a little time
One more bit that was I noticed a
Just a massive
You've got here
Republic
Predicting
This is inflammatory
Is dangerous
It's against the rule of law
And we the people must say
This is not
Who We Are
America must be cut
Jarring
So here's was missing there
Quick look
I know politics can be fierce and mean and nasty in America
I get it
I believe in the give-and-take apology
Disagreement did debate and
We're a big complicated country but democracy and doors only if we the people
Respect the guardrails of the Republic
Only if we the people accept the results of free and fair election
Only if we the people
Politics not as Total War but mediation of our
Democracy cannot survive when one side believes there are only two outcomes to an Alexa
Either they win or they were cheated
That's where Maga Republicans are today
FairPoint
Can't argue with that
Every single
F****** election
It it's getting
To the point where
You know obviously that's
To give some of
The folks
Pause
On the
Maybe some of the more aware self aware
Listeners Alex's
Church be like all right
Sarah Palin lost
Those cheating
Laura Loomer lost
Cheating man who has the time
To cheap that many election
When the globalists are stretched
Binman they don't have time for Alaskan election
Sarah Palin can lose on her own baby and with the case of Laura Loomer it's got a
You got to look at this house
Glass is half-full
Absolutely
Dab
You lost
Aw away from getting a double you know what I'm saying like that was a very short
Short walk
I also in this portion by Melissa phone number visit
Accomplishment
Helped
Make possible in the past two years all of which are things that Alex is pretending aren't real
So it's best not to confuse the audience
This also
I also cut out the part where there's a protest
Yelling stuff
To disrupt the speech and
Notwithstanding those folks you here on the other side there
They're entitled to be outrageous
This is a democracy
But history and Common Sense
Good manners is nothing they've suffered from
Pretty Far Cry from all those times Trump
Interrupted his own speeches to demand protesters be kicked out or times he responded with
Libra tattoos
Bobbing
Assaulted at his rallies that 11
It's kind of hard
The patients that Biden is exhibiting
Intolerance of somebody who disagrees
Tyrannic
Right especially juxtaposed with
I'm out really have to
To cut out a lot
Hayden speech in order to make him look like
Like a tyrant
I mean but
There's red lights and he's doing this at night
So that's pretty good I mean
He is part about it is like
You know
I suppose you could go with the bailout in like the ACA 2
Portray Obama is a
The Tyrant you know at least there's that
But was biting it really does feel like he's half acid
You know like
Is he a tyrant if he's willing to be like a 10K in student loans
Forgiveness
I'm not going to go after these hard right people and say we got to get 20
Is negotiation all right you're literally
Your own power
Sure
I think it's 12
But it's a challenge that I open up to the plate
Another thing that's weird here is that the part where this
Picks up
After the
We're Biden says quote and now America must choose
That's actually from earlier in the speech
This is edited out of order to create the impression that Alex is wanting
Convey right I promise I can make Alex's show looks
So much worse if I just gave up on the idea of a linear time
That's not fair because this is
Definition of Taken
Things out of
Out of context in
Temporal space
Yeah I know if you take it out of one
Time and then put it into a different time
And make it appear that thoughts are flowing into each other that aren't you might as well edit in each individual word to make
IMO Tyrunt
Yeah might as well be a magazine cutout of a letter
I understand that maybe four-time reasons Alex would want to play the whole speech
But the wave is being presented is irresponsible and it's
Intentionally deceptive
So a clip comes to an end
Are the part of
Give the speech
An Alex
I have some more
Abyss
Is it
Like this is the entire show
We can choose a better path
Forward to the
The future
Future of possibility if
Pictures of build
This country
He is on the
But they're planning to Stage violence
Move on us
Godwin
Only miss was the porches
Torches
Isn't that traditionally pitchforks and torches
She's coming from the other
Directions
Yeah and I think
The torch is certainly in
Present parlance
Evokes ideas of the United right rally
Which would be the buddies that he's around yeah
I don't know I don't understand exactly
I'm sure there's some images trying
It's not that but
I strongly suspect that Alex has the time that he has there because
Cuz he knows that his followers are prime
To hear something like this as the go-ahead to start shooting
Preparing out violence against
The government
He desperately needs to create a pre-emptive narrative that anything that may happen
Is not real and will be a false flag
Incidentally what Biden said the public Figures were calling for violence and we were talking about that talking about Alex
This was almost certainly in response to Senator Lindsey Graham going on Fox News and saying that if Trump was charged for having all that class
Syj tomorrow logout then there would be riots in the
Nothing is not always about out
Everything is always
You could argue that most things are not
Typically
That's a dead giveaway that they're probably
I do appreciate
The discourse in America you know like
You think back to those
Those conservative commentators like William F Buckley
Play Junior
And you think about him now saying you know
What amounts to I'm Rubber and you're glue neener neener
Give me sticks to you
I mean I think a win
I didn't get evolution chart
You know ask not what the government could do for you and what you could do for the government
Because the government
Can do everything but not for you for you that you must do nothing
So yeah I think that
That
Obviously he knows that they're about to go to break
And so you have a limited amount of time but the Heat
The reverse of everything
A little bit late
I'm telling you the entire show is just
False flags are coming
This is
Cuz that's the only thing that's important
Alex knows
Well enough
He's plugged into Noah keys
Friends with all kinds of keeper types
Begging to
Fight a f****** War forever
Like he knows enough
To see the Opera
This to see the way people are talking about it
I know
Someone
Probably
Making a bomb as we
Yeah
So
When that happened
If that happened
I don't want to be playing
Time for it
And I don't want this
To be set back to my business
Into my ideology
It has to be fake in advance
And when he was talking about false Flags coming
Before this speech
I mean it's the same thing
It's just
Much more
Important
When there was
Then I went to text on this before but like
The clipse on
Social media going around him saying off also I can come before the midterms Jeff that's just his normal every
3 days
Type
This is far more pic
Didn't know that the reason is because
He knows there's a heightened
Jantz Fridays friends are going to do some
Real f*****-up stuff
That's true I I don't know I think I would take that back
I think I would take the bet
Because the bed is
If you rest Trump and you do the the law thing
Incorrectly
There's there's they they attack
Or
Nothing happen
Said we
I think I'd take the bet
I think if we get Trump and they don't attack
The wind drops
Out of their sails
Completely
Like if they
Actually healthy to look at it this way
Because
Anything
That
The legal system or whatever
Should play out how it plays out
And if there is
Cause and it's
Appropriate to arrest them
Talkin arrest him
There should not be a consideration of what the backlash will be because that
I understand that
But you understand that is the consideration that be is being taken place
I understand
Certainly that's a big part of
The conversation hopefully not within law enforcement
Why didn't why do you think Billy didn't charge him in the first place it
The doj
Maybe it's not appropriate to a sitting president be charged I don't know look
Fair enough so maybe other considerations
Yeah I get I get where you're coming from
But also I think that's a naive
Because I think the
To Sumit immediate backlash is the backlash
Might be
Might be short-sighted
So like if
You know Tumblr arrest
Nothing happens it doesn't mean like
6 months
I love planning later something wouldn't happen jailbreak
Right but I mean
If you do understand we're dealing drugs out of his Resort prison escape
Planned planned by the dumbest people on the f****** planet you know like I'm not afraid of their plans
I'm afraid of a flash mob
Do you know what I mean
Yeah I feel like their plans would be spoiled
Very very easy
Right yeah
Right
It's it's
Stop
Sing to
Think about
But I hope that the
Decision-making isn't being Guided by
The potential for
People to
Cause
Rampant
And random
Political damage
Because I did again
Not a great way to guide decision
Right right right
There you go
Cancerous
So this got me really excited but don't worry it's a
Deflation
This is an emergency broadcast
Ladies and gentlemen and I'll be up here tomorrow
Taping another emergency 3-hour broadcast
Special guest
Storms across the country
What
Big guests as well as
Psychological warfare
Expert
Now you can't tell me that it's going to be a deflation
I wanted you to see how I felt I thought it was going to be pechanec
He was going to be making his return
Now's the Time yeah so somebody's playing was not able to get
Texas
Whatever I'll just leave it at that
Alex didn't
Record
Or at least it's not up on Van. Video or
Any anywhere I can find a v
What normal place
Things are posted
So I don't think it's happened but
Thinking about it like
It's probably just Rodger
Righttime dealers in Florida
Yeah that would be
Said if it is Rodger then of course you'd have to save some
Something Hollywood
I'll just leave it at that
Oh I mean there was a weather of
Yeah I know I do. I didn't check the weather report
Ecstasy where there were
Who could
Possibly even
Be a Metrology
Joel skousen is not coming in no shape with you at fast
Oh man
Barnes
Just a hickey
What if he got Bannon
What if he got the band
Promote
Maybe he's got a
Family
Is it a bunker the War Room bunker
Not mad about now
I don't know
Trump
He's got to get out of the state
Yeah extradition from Texas is tougher than you might think
Alex's ass of analysis and its really superficial
This is like if you go to the zoo
You know that's an elephant hunt
Chair
Are you sure
The leader of the country gets up
And declares half the nation terrorist
Says they're about to engage in terrorism
And they do it with troops behind them with a red background
There's a dark cross in every Hollywood movie
Every dystopian system they show that exactly
Iconography
All the scripted
Vendetta
Also incidentally
Filming at 3 hour special so honey I can't take you to the store
Pazuzu
Listen we were going to go fishing but that fell through so we're like let's go to the zoo and now
That's why I don't mind
Sorry
Playing got delayed everything is movies have everything is based on the surface level at appear in
Isn't it kind of troubling
It's really doesn't mean much more than him saying that the he looked at the speech and it reminded him of movies
Yeah
Didn't say that s***
Just a mischaracterization of his
It would be interesting if he threw that one out there though
Hey listen
Listen assholes
50% of this country is coming to kill you
If the president said that
That would be a statement of War
Straight Talk Express coming at chess
50% of America's Got a Gun and it's coming for you
50% of America are bad boys bad boys
Alright okay
Dear
It's it would have been I think
I think our conversation about
Probably be different if that was what he said.
That's it
Undiplomatic
Unproductive way to The Last Jedi background
Looking at look at it Raves right now those people yeah I get it I get it that would be evil
I honestly would even have a pretty different take on it if it was what you fantasize about
Whatever different they got it if they pulled that one off
So Alex's
Talking about this
Sony's like
And this seems like
I can work with this guy
I'm going to I'm going to create
Some Brandy
Blood red light
We're coming for you and what it is
Operational name
Oh God have a name
What is called operation
Matador
I bet
Bullfight
Long
Skinny razor sharp sword
When the bull lunges forward
Into the Heart
And step aside with Escape
As The Bull
Razer self into the Dust
This is operator
Matador
Operation matador
T-shirts coming soon okay no no no no no no
Names of Ben documents in the past you've been like we got operation lockstep and that's not real either
Thing though
At least there was a wordlock step that could
Another document
Pitch your old name
Everyone I bet it's called admin
And then just give it a name but he getting they call it the name they came pretty as option which is bullfighting
And the camera I got matador's batter
Call Jack
Evan and then he has his own
F****** analogy in order to explain the name that he pets
They made up for it
They have the metaphorical will wherewithal to make that up there it's a pain.
Valic likes with those he's going to keep going there
He's just sitting there like
And for this and I'm going to
Spit ball of the name of myself
Yeah
So we goes along with this bull analogy
Why you get a bull
Big giant razor-sharp
Orange
I think Sharp
The pissy moth
Power supplies
Remote control
Running down our families and
NFL
I'm sorry what
Throwing a little Spears
Now the red cakes
67 days out from the midterm
I know they're set to lose
Open
Behind it
Is the FBI
We're Not Gonna
Jump on the sword
Populous Christian conservative
Operation matador
What is happening
An understanding for language that you know that most of the stuff Alex talk about is b*******
Spears being poked
Just buzzwords he throws around to prompt an emotional reaction
From the audience
This list is an airing of grievances
And the complaint is basically that Alex doesn't like technological advance
Whores a society that Embraces immigrants
And lgbtq Community folks
He yells about Free Speech all day but wants to live in a country where athletes aren't allowed to take a knee during the national anthem
Women protest of racial discrimination in policing
These are things that Alex conceptualizes as the spears being used to poke the metaphorical Bull and it really just sound
Sounds to me like Alex's
Expressing a profoundly white identity view of the country
He doesn't believe that people who are not straight white
Christians are entitled to rights or power in this country
I don't sublevel anytime he hears a conversation by people who fit this description
Acting in a way that he doesn't like
His reaction is basically like you should be glad us white folks even let you be here
Yeah I mean
It does seem like
The more
Apps metaphorical stand-in for Alex in this scenario is in fact
Back to the bullet self
Constantly being in Rage
Did you buy any number of different things
Alex's
Yeah
He's angry
Annoy time he sees these things
These things
Like
People living
Experience is that at
Spear being poked into his white Christian tolerance
Colin Kaepernick taking a knee instead of just accepting police violence that the
Reading at a library instead of being shamed into never living in public
That's the spirit
Immigrants being allowed into the country instead of having a hardened militarized border they're killed for cross
Sing status
Here's the thing
What a bull charges after being poked by a bunch of beers
It's a natural reaction
The Matador waving that flag is something of a bull can't really be fault
Supercharging
It's the expected result of all the poker
If we understand Alex's metaphor his padria buddies are the bull and there they would be well within their rights
To charge the Matador
In this
Case bomb thing
Because they went poop so much
Write the only problem is that the matador's cape has the FBI behind it
That doesn't really make sense because in the metaphorical Matador situation did this whole thing
Really no way to make it a false flag
You would need like a fake ball or some s***
How this works
Hibiscus
Yeah this isn't Alex warning about a false flag this
Zim warning his buddies about following their
He's trying to tell the bull not to
To charge because it's
The Trap because I was understands that his buddies want
The charge that Matador really badly
They want to bomb s*** and Alex is smart enough to recognize that the way the people are talking about Biden
Speech is exactly the kind of thing that will lead
Lob as much of a stimulus for that as a matador waves
This isn't a false flag
Situation he's talking about
More of a Honeypot
Kind of idea
Yeah I was I was
Comparing them to the bulletin board in the Sun
It's that they lose at the end
Is the bulldozer
When
True
The bull can't like
Overcome the whole thing and be like I
Listen
I've chosen the way of peace
Like the bull is going to do the thing because they have no ability to stop them
I think a better way to make as metaphor work
I guess
Is
The bowl is the audience
Alex is the Spears
Poking them
Yeah a man
Getting arrested
Is the Matador
That work
That's something that he was ever a spear or anyting
Things to do with this incitement that is being done by Alex
Yeah
No Volkswagen
Trickery really even then Alex could be the Matador trying to
Navigate the bull but really
Not having any control over where the bull goes
And so the bull constantly comes at him and then you know runs forward in his there's all kinds of
Collateral damage
I think the point though is that has metaphors in
Some good know that is the point
Alex
Talking about this being like
Steve Volkswagen Terror attacks that they're going
The globalist are going to do and s***
Work within this
Like the framework
Talking about the only way for the bull metaphor to work
Is
Alex understanding
That is audience
He's going to carry out bombing
Right it's just that they're being provoked into doing it right
Because they think that it's the right thing
To do
I would also accept that it might work if adding actual bullfight
When the Matador pull the
Dacapo side
FBI what
It's still on.
Nobody would Wake Forest
But I think that maybe Alex and thinking of the cape
Is a flag
I don't know.
I don't have
Of that many clips
From this whole episode of the reasons is because it's in
Volkswagen
That's really
80% of content okay
Why you make an announcement this folding crazy
Because they're going to pull stuff so damn horrible
Assassinate
Trump
They'll come kill me
Sure
Making their move
I will be dead by the midterm
I mean but but what are you
Are you talking about then
You're just didn't say you call for violence
You're saying he's saying that they're coming they're literally coming to kill you and there's no stopping it because
Just announced
He is an ounce
That the war has started
The war has started haha
But the war is a trick
What
You can't stage false Flags if the war has already started
Do you understand
There's no reason to have faults
Flags
Cuz you want to look like you're only
Fighting defensively it's the same thing that you can just do the thing and
Then you have people lie for you
True
I mean
That's an option
Kohl's
Part of the fun banter here is
Missing your ideas adopting Alex's ability
To patch over thing
Yeah there's too many holes here for me even to really do work on this too high
Butts
Alex's tummy hurts
Told you last month
My gut-level also intellectual analysis is
10 times worse than it's ever been
More concerned
Aaron
Unless we see massive just Department whistleblowers now unless we see people even in corporate media that know their Mercenaries
Know what they're doing wrong a lot of them
Unless we just see everybody start coming out and saying I'm not with this it's over
We don't want to have a war with these
What are the process
Pyrrhic victory
No you lose
That's why you don't you don't want
Yeah nobody's actually going to
Fight a civil war
It would be absurd
I mean frankly just be expense
Heather will be here
More and greater right-wing terrorism
Dunno what happened really because
As much as
Some of that is galvanizing for his community
No denying
Oklahoma City bombing
Certainly something there
They've made a lot of mileage on
It's also a lot of work
It's a hassle
And you rather not do that
Weather
Play in this this space
This Schrodinger's bombing
Space that Alex is in now is much easier to
To live in
Well and I mean not
Just that bud
If you're going to have a civil war you then you have to have a
The concept of your endgame
And
If you're the terrorist side then
Ostensibly your endgame is
Defensive
Maintaining your territory
What is your territory
Occupied Texas
I mean that's what I'm saying so if you win the civil war do you get all of America or do you get
A certain subset
Open of America and you don't want a subsection of America
Right everybody who's
How would you get all
They can't there's no infrastructure that they can handle
There's no way to get water
Win win the civil war they're like ours all the Wild West
They can't govern
True
You know how like
Alex believes the Trump is the rightful president of the u.s.
I'm sure he thinks the Confederacy is the rightful government of the US
Mid-South didn't just not lose the Civil War they wanted all the way right
To get back to that
Byron Scott
Inconceivable
That's fair it's on me
So
Workday
Baguette
Trucks
Fuel oil bomb
But if we put enough
Cheat on them
Learn about this
Neutralize
So we are bombs and trucks
Ready to go
Right today
This is Extreme
Yeah
If I believe any of this I'd be pretty scared
Real struggle to get her
Sure and I mean if you believe all this like OKC was a false flag
Fuel bomb truck
Ready to go
You kind of have to
To think that
The target would be a civilian Target
Yeah
If you're somebody you just
Lives and bike listen to Alex
I don't know how you could not think like well maybe the building that I work in
Could be a Target or Thursday
Got2b cripplingly scary
Weather is
The conscious fear or not like he's got to be
Something that
Doleful benefits of volcano Casey it's not like
It's not like all this only happens in the major cities
It's like that is
I mean it's not not a hurry but it is like
That is more of the well it could happen in my supper
Mid-range
Insidious
Nah. Not a metropolis right
Yeah
And I pick up the feeling that he wants.
So Alex is Alexa
But he's talked
Did they say who
I can agree with him
High-level current CIA
High level
Army
Special operation
And I concur with my analysis
But I'ma see those people
Obviously
People that have
Agreed
Martial law that's f****** Steve
A bestiary is 100% of Stevie way2go
Oh yeah
Guys who have run regime-change
Beazer epithets that Alex uses to describe Steve pieczenik
And he's
Not saying the word
He's backsliding into this
Abusive relation
I have a matter of time
It is God and get it back already
Now
I do think
That it would make
Sense that these high-level people
Agree with Alex
Because we heard
Not too long ago that the f****** leader
Yeah but he doesn't even remember that
He does not remember that he is not
Calling people right you are until I brought it up you forgot I completely forgot
Is the day today
It's a day-to-day you're not at all of the Patriots in the
They look to him as leader of course they're not
Geico intersect
What are they doing with analysis shouldn't they know s***
Deborah
It's there
The things they know from The Things They Know shouldn't be calling them to confirm his analysis and not have them
Be like we were thinking the same thing bro
We don't have any explanation or why
He's just talking s*** with people
You don't actually have any
Brother's Day
They're not like high-level
Talkingshit with
Basically
I'm not fun
This clip
I was really where I am
If I were
Involved in towel throwing
This is maybe where I would throw the towel on this
So they are getting ready to
Bye
Attacker whatever
Poisoning
There's a plethora
Things they can do within the
Call flag
Realm
Because
I want a few weeks to maximizer
RhymeZone
Tober first
Going to start stuff up
Is that all part of operation matador
The truck bombs are loaded
You better believe the mentally ill schizophrenic Mass shooters
Drugged up
Government cecia New World Order
Programming centers for operation
Right now
They are rolling out
Guaranteed you can bet your bottom dollar
Zoning out a little bit because it's just repetitive yelling nonsense about false
Flags that I kind of got brought back down to the ground by this clip
Like what
What are we doing
What Alex is conspiracy in this Grand false-flag that's coming and Biden
Speech is a Harbinger for it
It all centers around the
F****** midterm I mean
The plot for the
Volkswagen by creating the public perception that it makes
Sentence for Democrats to win midterm elections
What is going on
And it's not just that but
Please listing
Everything is a sign
Like every you know it's not just false Flags where it's like oh there's an explosion or something
No it's like
Hey the power went out for 8 hours
For you anything
Could be explained as the jump off
Yeah he's lifting random ass s***
You know anybody
Is everything any of anyone's on Rises and the rooster is silent
Looks Shifty at you in the grocery store that
You know like there's no Escape if you see a rainbow in the colors are inverted weight
Back they've been beaten back we have neutralized
Powerball
It's insane abs
The notion that it's about the midterms is just pathetic
I can't
There was
Lisa self seriousness that Alex had
In earlier times in his career
Where that would this would look embarrassed
For him
To be like going
So far out of his way to
To create these elaborate
Conspiracy theories
About
Something like a mid
Midterm election
Yeah
It's
Howell Howell
Best is he with like
Breeding
Like politics
Like sports
Yeah, like a pop-culture kind of thing
He's doing
This about a midterm
So sad
Yeah man supposed to be about
Now you're at the mid
911 is coming in order for Democrats to win
Sad
It's
Hey
It's the most important election
I mean I think that a lot of people very rightly critique that kind of rhetoric all over
The place that night I think that's fine
I just I think that Alex is doing a
Substantially worse version of it more extreme version
What a bummer yeah
Calls
To talk to people who are like
You know in the military
Are you going to bomb something
Because it should be a false flag
Negril at people about that
Okay I'm taking calls my first question to everyone
Have you or are you about to build a bomb
I think
In the past I have heard people say like how it's going to talk to you all fair
Maybe not on the radio
He says he wants to take calls from military Folk
Uno thing
I would suggest
It is a bad
Strategy because they didn't send devices people to lie about being in the military
I'm only taking calls from military people that go
Hey guess what now I'm military
Yeah
I don't know if you recall that story of The Bundys and all those dudes sitting around
I'm talking about their f****** military experience doubt all their wartime s*** none of them had ever been in the Army at all
Yeah
They brought that up on here for
Alex takes a call from somebody who is allegedly movie National Security or made
Maybe ice could be anybody resumes dubious
And I have some news about a bomb
Tony is a 15-year Homeland Security
And he wants
Washington d.c.
Johnny
Hey how you doing a mistake God bless you
15 former federal employee
Protection work for ice
Regard
To the
Everything is coming about
They wanted us to
Do the vaccine man
Gmail
There will be there will be
I still work there
It's going to be a nuclear bomb
Plutonium or uranium
-
Anymore
Set a lock down so not a nuclear bomb
Power outage but without the
-2 radiation
14 / 8
Beer people some people can be also
Clear plastic explosive
It's going to be a neutron bomb
We got
Supplies
I figured we got
As you know about the body bags
Myself my
Bodybag Culver
Tire spot
Which is Kissinger
A skier obsessed with Neutron bombs and populate America
This guy sounds a little speedy
I mean
He's more chatty than any CBP officer I've ever anymore
Because he left over vaccine mandate
6 months ago
Sure vaccine mandates
Neutron bomb is not just a nuke minus the radiation there's still tons of radiation but the
Concept is to minimize the long
Longevity that the radiation is the affected areas
Inhabited more quick
Get people back in
But I guess
We should be on the lookout for nuclear bombs that have no radiation involved cuz this
High-level ice Insider has warned of a tan Alex
Disagree this is a serious concerns
We should probably be really worried about
This is busy
Is definitely worth your mind
Yeah yeah yeah guy dubiously associated with federal government programs
Ostensibly. On speed right now telling me that
Nuclear bombs without plutonium are going to hit people
I'm going to go with a pass on this one you passed I passed cuz Alex said I agree
The difference with this business
The difference between you and Alex
I'll drink another color he's got an idea
Talk to you
My personal opinion is that
Maurice White
And if you notice there's a lot of
Ukrainian
I'm through there I haven't noticed
Are you going to use these
Ukrainian
His body has
Mesa Falls
And they're going to dress him up and Trump
Trump gear
And have them do so
Some stuff
And
Martial law
So look out for ukrainians dress up as Trump supporters carry a neutron bomb
Martial law also trucks
Swiss fuel bombs already
Gassed up and ready to go
A boy we got a lot of things to worry about this is a concern.
A buckshot of
Concern if the
Did he say that he's seen
He hasn't seen ukrainians coming through the Border
Soma care
Mexico
What does the zoo ukrainians are going through Mexico they fly into El Salvador
If you created the coming through the portal
Well there's a tunnel from Ukraine to Brazil
And then
North Korea
From North Korea you know the channel connect France and the UK
Okay you know I have that but Ukraine in Brazil
And they're like listen we could go to the United States
But those m************ UK my way
We're going to take the land
Route through Arizona or whatever you might be thinking about this wrong
Did you know there's an Odessa in Texas
Did not know that is there a teleportation device
Okay Dallas support portal territory
So
Lot easier to get a suitcase nuke through I would think so
Anyway and has connections with
Quote those
The whole country or country
So we'll see who disagrees
This is a good example of pointless to disagree without
Michelle
Kohl's right now let's go to
John in Vegas
Yeah I'm looking at
At the Biden transcript
Right now and
Little thing that you're talking about in this I tell you what
What you're doing
Edging your audience
Is embarrassing
A shame your seminar caller
You said you were calling on up
Air Force
The club right now while you're gaslighting
Even the Washington Post said it was basically a declaration of war
Everywhere
Unprecedented
Denying that
Two-player games
Controlling your thermostat
Everybody Talks
Flashlight
Food color is a good example of why you can't really inject disagreement on Alex's own show Even if you have a valid point like how
None of the things I like to say about Biden
Streator Acura
So it's good is hang up on you talk over you call you with seminar collar and create fake reasons
Not engaged anymore
Your points
He can list off weird unrelated talking points
Distracted listener
I was like what exactly does your Therma
Girls that have to do with whether or not
Play Alex's discussing
Speeches accurate
I believe
I believe he was actually speaking
Literally nuts Apex
If you if you
Scan the sentence
Since then he's actually the stacks of Articles them
Selves
That are controlling our
Thermostat
So that was just letting everybody know that the stacks of Arden
Cuz it's taking over
The amount of printing
And wasting of paper and non recycling that Alex does
Does taking a shower with state governments have had to control your thermostat
Thermostats because we can't stop printing second-story will reflect
That's that is a theory
Soundscan also dislike move the goalposts and pretend
Only you've been honest about why you called in he would have engaged with your points total
He cannot play any of the clips and present his unwillingness to present his own evidence
As an unwillingness to engage with your games that you're playing
Pulling into screams Alex is pointless and even though the prime directive of our show you know to not interfere with info
Kind of destroyed
Because of our presence at the trial and might work with the plaintiff
I still think that it's important to point out that this just is
Something it's going to go anywhere. I would not incentivize
That behavior
Although I do kind of wrestle this cuz I think that person probably is a listener varsho cuz he's the edging Chrome
I'm not saying that
Weave
Popularized edging but I didn't realize I don't think I've heard anywhere else
Specifically ours yeah
Or at least they give the
Suspicion
Strongly
And I kind of considered not
Playing even because I might be some of the f****** with Alex about
Creating like
Trying to mess with him it was just giving a disagreement about
The point that he was making using the edging doesn't necessarily mean he listen
Could be it could be one of those words that just starts to get popularized through the
He's not even bring it up
Is
Played in the past times or like that's
Somebody wasn't
Incentivize that right I don't want
People to think like
If they listen get on our show through if I don't want anyone to think of that is like
Something that
What is or or is it will
Like
Behave good job
Soccer with Alex
Or a thing that they compete with that people compete with each other on it like oh if it's funny enough it'll get on the show
That's not going to happen
This is just a good teachable moment where this person had a point
That's a Alex
Could not respond to
Can you see the all of the methods and he deploys immediately in order to get out of this
Just call
Delegitimize the person as a seminar caller
Accuse them of gaslighting
Say I would play the clip
But you don't deserve it because you lied I wouldn't gave with your points but you lied
Yell over them before they better go you disagree with
I disagree with the way your
Exactly just cut it off.
It's not
There's no win
0 Oz is the psych Warfare
Gaston
I will.
No I'm bored
We're not going to listen to much of it
I found it to be a little bit
Like
I don't know boring
But we have one clip you and I don't think that this is exactly
The beginning that Alex wanted
I to this interview
Studio weather for the next hour plus he is recognized
Formation psychology
Psychology department of psychology
Educational Sciences
They said University Belgium
Joe Rogan
A show as well
You want to get right into Biden speech professor
And just how
Nighttime with troops behind him with red lights
It's right out of
Germany's right out of
Stalin's Russia North Korea
Our enemies are going to be
We've got to have a war with him what did you make of that
Vices
People who are
Represent by Nas
The mega extremists
These people
And that's why
What should be avoided
It will be
The people act
Because the system
Control aggression
Crucial importance
Resistance and realized
Foremost
You have to watch
I would sell its name to this aggression
This is not really what Alex wanted
The professor isn't describing a false flag he's saying that Biden speech with possibly a bad idea because it'll be you
Used as justification for people who want to do violent things when they do violent things
This isn't good with that Alex's concept
Because it basically is admitting it out of community real largely incline
Towards violence
They don't have a good handle on that internal enemy that is aggression and are begging for someone to give them a reason to act on
Understood appropriately this episode as base
Sleeping I was tripping over himself
The frame Biden
Speech in a way that in
Inflames that aggression is Audia
Basil lip-service to not wanting any violence so we can evade any accusations
Goody's causes
Calling for terrorist
Put simply I don't respect anybody who except
What's a booking on Infowars but this guy is coming out to the conversation to Biden speech
Completely different perspective
But Alex
And I think that their views are actually at all.
Each other
I disagree with the professors Point mostly because if taken to its logical
Two conclusion you end up in a place where criticizing
Any potentially violent segment of the population is bad
Because it will trigger their aggression
But I do accept
Pointers at least
Connected to reality and it's something that can be debated
Position is more less just rooted in his feeling
Wings and it's not something you can
Deborah few
At all it would be pointless to argue with
I'm about a conversation
Is
Alex saying
When
The people that I've riled up to
Violence
April
And his conversation is
Actually
They shouldn't
Do violet
Because that is
Is the the thing
But if Alex
But if you say that to Alex's listeners
Then they won't do violin
And then there will be a false flag because they won't actually be an actual attack
So those
To those two conversation
Are in direct opposition in terms of gold
Call Alex kind of wing
Viva like violence
This is an attempt to
Do you know what this metaphor with the Matador
Like it is
If you
Metaphor it is what this doctor this
This is an attempt to lure you into doing
Something
I'm as opposed to it being fake
That's not a larger possibility
Is false flag
The term
Includes
People doing things they shouldn't do because Biden made them angry
Flag loses any meaning
As a term
So if Alex is describing that as something to qualify for the phone then I would say we have
Past the point where anything
Has any
Definition yeah yeah cuz the idea false flag
It has to include I planned this
To achieve the opposite of what
Theoretically I want something on somebody else
To frame a person
Which implies
Intent
Whereas this is if you include
They
Photo quotes
Nothing
Then I wanted to do already right
That's just responsibility
Just called responsible for your action trapperman because I didn't like Biden speech
I don't know really like
I mean it is a little bit like every like okay hey
Here's a good speech
People shouldn't steal from
The grocery store cuz the people need food
I know like that makes me want to steal from grocery stores
But when I did
It was cuz he tricked me
That makes sense
I like it
Yeah
One of the things you should take away from this
Is that
Regardless of whether
Alex
Is talking
Incoherently with this metaphor in stuff
Or
If you really does believe that if you bomb something
Because you're mad if I did
Speech that's a false flag whatever the case
The term false flag is meaningless to him
What is a signifier of something
That is just like
Don't take
Take this seriously
Where is audio
Stu like not
Accept any kind of like
Idea that
The information space
But they live in and the stuff that Alex is emanate
Is part of the viola
What's right is part of inflaming that aggression right that that's what false flag
It means don't
Include this
In your balance
Of
Consequences of this world
Ironically to return to an earlier metaphor than Alex himself made
If you are taking
Taking your three-year-old daughter to the zoo
And you're looking an elephant
And you go
That's not f****** elephant
Fake elephants
Then that's more like what Alex
Again the trip at the zoo has
Cancel cuz Alex needs to report this 3-hour video that he ended up not recorded
Maybe next time little lucy
Yeah this interview this guy found very boring
I mean he's talking about this idea of like a mass formation
Chess video the idea that
Part of the population has been tricked into thinking covid is
Real and it because of
What is fate
We need to do all this stuff in order to battle covid invariant
Hypnotic state moreless
If you listen to it if you want to
Go ahead but if you do
You'll notice that
A lot of
Maybe all love
The things that he is describing as being indicative of this
They sort of hypnotic right that people are in
Kind of
Describe
People who
Support Trump
And I just
I found it to be an uncompelling interview and
This
Phoenix get his verbal patterns
Prairie
Boring
I hate it
I really don't like that guy's using terms that I think Alex
Kind of not understanding and dancing around yeah
It's just
Ida Ida
This is very little to do with what I think is important which is Alex's response
To Biden speech
Rite Aid so
We will leave it off there
But yeah so be worried about ukrainians dressed as Trump supporters who have forgotten that already
Suitcase nukes
Anytime
Portals
Keep an eye out about
Possibility of fuel
And also the midterms coming up
Also you noticed Alex is like doing other stuff but he's not saying go vote
Talking about the
Get out and vote
There's no real like a there's a
It is much like a invoice
Who's going to sponsor registration Drive
Borgess baby scared of
Even play whenever he's like all Hey listen Laurel over
DJ you guys
You need to be in the office you need to be there he's never like I hope people vote for you that's never
That's my strong arm
Occasionally
If you wanted to go out
Support Laura Loomer
I think more it's like
Donate turkey exactly
It's all money yet
Will be back Jordan I with another episode ending
But until then
We have a website we sure do its knowledge right. Com
Because we have a busy
No it's a bit it
Two letter for midterms.
We don't actually have that website this is
This is me
Also we're on Twitter
Will be back but until then I'm Neo I'm Leo I'm dzx Clark I'm
Darrell Gribble gravel of the sniffles novel it's another relative
And now here comes
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work