Knowledge fight.
I am sweating knowledgebite.com.
It's time to pray.
I have great respect for knowledge.
Bite Knowledge.
I'm sick of them posing as if there's the good guys.
Chang.
We are the bad guys.
I love you.
Hey, everybody.
Welcome back.
Knowledge, right? I'm Dan.
I'm Jordan.
We're a couple of dudes.
I like to sit around worship with the altar of Celine and talk a little bit about Alex Jones.
Oh, indeed we are, Dan.
Jordan.
Jordan, quick question for you.
Yeah.
What's your bright spot today, buddy? My bright spot today, Jordan, isn't actually a bright spot, but it's sort of a all right.
Okay.
Boy, it's changing the rules of the game.
It's right here it is fanta.
Oh, boy.
I saw that.
They have a flavor called hashtag what's the fanta? What the fanta? What the Fanta? You can't name a flavor with a hashtag.
I call foul.
I just call foul.
That might not actually be the name of it might be question mark, because it says find clues.
Hashtag.
What the fantasy? Oh, my God.
I'm drawn to these curious flavors, as we talked about on the last episode, dreamland dream world Coke.
Yeah.
Also got a number of messages for people who are like, hey, you got that space Coke? It's got to be at the store, right? I don't understand how you are dealer.
When did that happen? Not going to happen.
But, yeah, I'm drawn to these things.
Sure.
And Fanta, you got, like, pineapple, orange, a lot of fruit flavors.
Only thing I know about Fanta is the commercial from the early winter.
That's the only thing.
Yeah.
I don't think I've ever had a Fanta despite the commercial asking me if I want one.
Apparently.
No, I do not.
It's fruit.
Yes.
Right.
All of them are fruit.
Sure.
So you're expecting fruit here? I think it's cotton candy.
You think it's cotton candy? I don't know.
You can't have that big of a heel turn.
My fruit candy.
That was not a fruit, I can tell you that for sure.
I think it's cotton candy.
What if it's cotton candy grapes? They taste like cotton candy and they're grapes.
That's a fruit.
That would be an interesting technicality.
All right.
I'll put that down just because that helps.
Okay.
That makes my guess a little bit more sensible.
Yeah.
I liked grapes.
Candy grapes.
Well done.
Also, it's not good.
Well, poorly done job.
Get your shit together.
What's your bright spot? I didn't even want to necessarily tell you, but it begins with the T and ends with Serena.
Well, I mean, that was a beautiful moment.
I was going to give you a pass because of a monumental it was emotionally effective for Serena Williams to retire such a good match.
One of the greats.
Not one of the greats.
The greatest.
I don't know enough about tenants to say, and I'm fully willing to agree with you.
Yeah.
I just think it's as someone who knows nothing about the sport.
Definitely saves one of the top players of all time.
Yes, for sure.
You are an expert.
You do not need to wait into the end game argument of like, oh, is it Pippin? Or yes, I get you.
I just have feelings about Pete Sappers from my youth.
What feelings? Memories.
I have memories, actually.
As a man with substantial arm hair, I imagine that you do have a lot to go on.
Sure.
Robin Williams, one of the great tennis cherries.
Absolutely.
Why didn't he make a biopic? All it takes to be good at tennis is arm hair.
Patley.
Robin Williams.
Sampras Adams.
I like that McEnroe.
Yeah, he's still around.
You know what he narrates a TV show.
Does he yell a bunch? No, it's just like a regular narration.
That is John McEnroe with no, it's never even addressed.
They're never like, hey, by the way, it's John McEnroe.
That is narrating.
Supposed to be a guy who yells things that he's known for.
Exactly.
That's his job.
But whatever, you know, it's crazy.
What that House of Pain song? Jump around.
It references John McEnroe.
Wow.
That's not crazy.
John Mcenrow.
What's the biggest thing in the world for a very short period of time? I'm saying that time.
Oh, yeah.
That was a long time ago.
Anyway, I'm sorry, I've hijacked your bright spot.
No, my bright spot is the US Open.
It's great.
Oh, yeah.
Fantastic.
How's it going? I really think this is one of the best ones I've seen in a long, long time.
Like top to bottom.
Everybody is good.
Is that young kid you like doing well? Caress? Yeah.
He's headed to the quarterfinals.
My man.
He's crushing it.
Rafa, of course, is crushing it.
Is the US Open taking place in San Francisco? Around the Bay.
It is not.
Alcarez isn't going down the trail.
No, he's not dead.
I already saw that coming from a mile away.
Yeah.
Or if it's San Francisco from 1400 miles away.
Where are they at in terms of the no, I mean, like in terms of the final.
So before the fourth round is the quarter finals, and then so the fourth round is the round of 16.
Okay.
The round right before the quarterfinal tonight is probably going to be the best match of the entire tournament.
Curiosity versus Med Vedev curios crushing it for the first time of Russia.
No, different Karaos, different med badevs.
Okay.
But yeah, it's going to be a great one.
I would love it if just to fuck with you.
The US Open was still at like three in the morning.
That would be great.
Awesome.
Same time as the French.
All tennis is set up at exactly the same time.
They are the French open.
I just have a number of memories of you being like, I'm going to be up all night.
I woke up at 03:00 a.m.
So I could be up until 04:00 a.m.
Tomorrow night.
In order to watch this at a bar, I have to go to the airport.
That's true.
I just assume that that's what it's like to be satisfied.
You're always watching.
02:00 am.
Illegal streams help.
I could do that.
I feel like a number of wrestling fans have the same sort of thing with, like, Japanese promotions, pay per views and stuff.
You got to make sacrifices to love something, I guess.
I guess.
Yeah.
So, Jordan, today we're going to be talking about a present day episode.
Okay.
We're checking back in because the bat signal went up.
Something very important happened that Biden gave that speech.
What speech? I heard people talking about a speech that Biden gave.
I can't tell if you're joking.
No, I mean, I know about the speech, but it's like I just don't understand.
Okay, never mind.
Yeah, that was it.
I really thought that there was a box.
It looks no, actually, we can get into a little bit now and we'll get into more during the episode and such, but I think that the speech is either going to be historically incredibly relevant or not, but an attempt to be very historically relevant, that's tough.
Yeah.
I'm not sure exactly how the ball is going to break at this point, but he gave a speech that was essentially like, hey, look, here's the situation.
Trump and the people who are following him, these MAGA folks are a mess.
They don't care about democracy.
Right.
And they're a very serious threat to democracy as we are experiencing it now, and the stability of the country.
US normal folk, Democrats, Independents, Republicans who aren't into that nonsense.
Right.
We have a responsibility to do what we can to protect democracy now.
The future generations will look back at us being in the fight.
If we do our job, they will look at this point as an inflection point in history.
Yeah.
There were a number of things that are, I would say, a little bit overdue in terms of recognition of, hey, look, this shit is nonsense.
Fascism is bad.
Right.
Previously, he had called semi fascist.
Yeah.
So there is like, a little bit of a finally, some of these words are being uttered, right? At least out in the air.
Right.
There is an aspect of, like, this might be too little, too late that is definitely present.
And there's also an element of, like, what does this even really mean? Is this going to push any needles in any direction, or is this going to be something that has just a severe backlash? Who knows? In my humble opinion, the only reason that a president should give a speech is as cover for somebody to arrest, like, a thousand people at the same time.
Right? Yeah.
The meters all paying attention and then all of a sudden, in the middle of the speech.
You start cutting to people being arrested, doing perp walks, like all the bankers are going.
The whole thing needs to be that speed.
Does the hypothetical president in this circumstance know that they're just a distraction? Oh, absolutely.
That's the whole game, man.
He's given a speech to say that these people are coming for democracy.
Surprise, they're all in jail right now.
How about that? Well, as we are that's a speech.
As we are a few days after this.
That didn't happen.
Unfortunately, your movie fantasy did not happen.
There's a part of me that is quite conflicted about how exciting to think giving voice to a lot of this stuff is, or how meaningful it is.
I would like to believe that this is indicative of something broader.
But honestly, there's another part of me that is, like, this is probably impotent in its direction.
Lists, even.
Well, I mean, you have to ask yourself no, I think the entire country is asking itself right now, does anybody even listen to the president anymore? Like, all real talk? Does anybody care what he says? It might be one of the large effects of Trump, I think.
So who fucking cares what the president has to say? For four years, we had a president who's like, oh, he's talking shit.
He's just talking shit.
Yes.
Oh, I'm going to do this thing.
No, you're not.
You're just talking shit on Twitter.
Right? And I think that even before Trump, you had presidents who would have sort of empty talk and promises.
Sure, Syria, red lines, you get used to a bit of that.
And then you have a president who's just talking just all the time.
It seems tough to come back from that, to be like, we'll take all this very seriously.
Think about the gravitas of the office.
How dare you look at me and say that I should give a shit about what the president says? I can if I so choose, but how dare you say I should? Yeah, it's a tough walk from the past of, like, my fellow Americans.
I come to you today to Trump being like, they say I have a small dick.
Imagine FDR's fireside speeches if it was just like, oh, the only thing we have to fear is how tiny Hitler's balls are.
Am I right? Yeah.
High fives from everybody.
Yeah.
Or just the notion of thinking about presidents in history caring about memes, the equivalent of memes at the time.
Did he get mad about memes? Oh, totally.
If there was a nasty little comic strip in a paper, he went apeshit.
Maybe that's why Alex likes him.
I think so.
Anyway, we got an episode to go over alex's response to this, September 2, 2022.
And yes, his reactions about what you'd expect.
It was a great speech.
I loved it.
I'm a huge fan of Biden from now on.
Evocative in its imagery all those things I said about him having other diseases to see where this goes.
Alex loved it.
Yeah, we'll get into all that.
Before we do, Jordan, let's say hello to some new walk.
Oh, that's a great idea.
So first illegal Owen Wilson.
Impersonator.
Thank you so much.
You're now policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Next.
Oh, for fuck's sake.
Thank you so much.
You're now Policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much.
That's my favorite one in a long time.
Concise gets to the point of it.
Yeah.
Next.
Classic charles, thank you so much.
You're now policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much.
I will not do an impression.
Next.
I've listened to every second of knowledge fight jacob, thank you so much.
You're now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much.
And as you all know, for security reasons, my name has changed monthly this month.
You may call me Tickle Tickle Poppy Top.
Thank you so much.
You're now Policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
And we got a couple of technocrats here in the mix.
Jordan.
So first my dog wants to know why I keep saying a little walkie.
A little walkie for Tanny before we go outside.
Thank you so much.
You are now a technocrat.
And Cora, thank you so much.
I'm a policy wonk four star.
Someone sodomite sent me a bucket of poop.
Daddy Sharp.
Jar Jar Binks has a Caribbean black accent.
He's a loser.
Little kitty baby.
I don't want to hate black people.
I renounce.
Jesus Christ.
Thank you so much.
Thank you very much.
So, yeah, the speech happened, and because of that, Alex decided, like, I'm not even going to wait for my intro to play.
I'm just getting in there, right? I'm diving in.
The second the show starts, I'm going to sink my teeth into this speech.
He is, like, just in it.
Okay.
As you can now see, America is going under total new, older martial law.
Biden has literally given a speech declaring war on the people in a Hilarian set.
timing.
Nailed it.
Yeah, that's not bad.
That's professional.
Sure.
The Larian set really seems to be one of the primary things that Alex is focused on.
The optics of it, the red light behind him, the fact that he gave a speech at night.
Sure.
These are things that Alex seems almost preoccupied by.
I assume that the content of the speech is not really something he's very interested in.
Well, some of it.
A little bit here and there.
Sure.
Some of the stuff that really works well for him.
Yeah.
But the optics are and I think one of the reasons that this is really sticking in his craw, as it were, is we heard for years during Trump's time, Alex being like, you have the bully pulpit, do an evening speech, get out there and address the population in prime time and get your message across.
Trump wouldn't do that.
Right.
Or he didn't do the thing that Alex wants.
And now here you have Biden doing exactly what Alex was wishing Trump would do.
And not just that, but giving a speech, the thing that they're famously furious that he cannot do.
He can't speak clearly for a second.
Right.
Which is kind of thing.
And you do note that Alex doesn't play, like the full speech.
Of course not.
He plays some bit and we'll get to that here in a second.
But yeah, because he makes gas all the time.
There's no plan.
I think it's sour grapes somewhat for Alex.
He wishes that Trump would have done something like this.
He wishes that Trump would have declared war on the globalist I mean, yeah, I was going to say and he's mad that he's in a situation where, like, Biden is doing the thing I wanted Trump to do.
I'm not saying that I have any kinship with Alex over this, but I do believe that his idea of what speeches would happen is very similar to mine.
The speech happen while you're arresting everybody that you need arrested? Yes, I think he and I are very similarly aligned in that being the way that speeches should go.
Well, there's a slight difference because you guys are both like experiencing reality as a movie, but no, I'm wishing reality was a movie.
Right.
That's the difference.
That is the difference where Alex is portraying Biden giving the speech as cover for as what I think would be inevitable, locking up of all of his political enemies.
Yeah.
So I guess there is a similarity.
You should talk to somebody about that.
Like see an expert.
About what? Nothing.
What am I supposed to say to that expert? I don't know.
There's like 700 episodes of our shows they can check in on.
What if it's a world historian expert? They'll be like, oh yeah, maybe they'll give you an honorary degree.
Yes.
So Alex does start the show by playing some of Biden's speech.
And I noticed that there were some cuts.
Okay.
Not every Republican embraces their extreme ideology.
I know because I've been able to work with these mainstream Republicans and here, in my view, is what is true.
Oh, boy.
So there's a pretty obvious cut there.
And one of the things that is very important to point out is that Biden does go out of his way to be very specific about what he's talking about.
Yeah, he's talking about folks who do not understand the transfer of power.
Right.
The folks who don't have any interest in the governing rules and norms of government.
Not just Republicans.
This is not just a partisan type speech.
So I assume he broke down at one point and just started screaming january 6.
It wasn't that long ago.
January 6.
I mean, in a fashion.
Yeah.
You just bring it up.
Okay.
So close.
So it intrigued me that there was these cuts, because, as all the time in the world on his show, he can play whatever he wants.
Sure.
And you know what he wants to play.
Right.
So here's what was said in between the clips that was cut out.
Quote but there's no question that the Republican Party today is dominated, driven, and intimidated by Donald Trump and the MAGA Republicans, and that this is a threat to this country.
These are hard things.
But I'm an American president.
Not the president of red America or blue America, but of all America.
And I believe it is my duty, my duty to level with you, to tell you the truth, no matter how difficult, no matter how painful.
It may be a coincidence that this was cut out, but it also seems like a point Alex wouldn't be super comfortable with, particularly the part about the GOP being intimidated by Trump and his followers.
Yeah, the impression about Trump and the MAGA folks is supposed to be that they're winning the battle of ideas and that they're just smarter and more patriotic than the rest of us, which is why they've taken over the GOP.
It's not a great idea to plant seeds in the audience's mind that maybe they're a part of something hostile that has gained power not by being ideologically better, but by being more willing to threaten and employ violence.
Alex also cuts out the part at the beginning where Biden says, quote, we must never forget, we the people are the true heirs of the American experiment that began more than two centuries ago.
We the people have burning inside each of us the flame of liberty that was lit here at Independence Hall, a flame that lit our way through abolition, the Civil War, suffrage, the Great Depression, world wars, civil rights.
That sacred flame still burns now in our time as we build an America that is more prosperous, free, and just, that is the work of my presidency, a mission I believe in with my whole soul.
That's just good business.
On Alex's part, cutting that out? Yeah.
He has a vested interest in pretending that his political enemies hate the country and what it stands for.
So it's best not to allow someone like Biden to speak like this on Infowars.
As someone who has a passionate love for the country, it would be too confusing to me.
It would be really terrifying if he quoted Thomas Jefferson.
That would fuck them up.
That would be especially if he did it accurately.
Now, if he inaccurately quoted Thomas Jefferson, they would go absolutely apeshit all day.
Right? All day would be a non stop barrage of, this guy doesn't know shit about Thomas Jefferson, despite what we all know to be the truth of their ability to remember or even fantasize thomas Jefferson's.
Quote yeah.
If any Biden speech writers are listening, slip in something about something, and then quote, Thomas Jefferson, call TJ all day.
That would be wonderful.
That's the way you got to go.
So he plays enough of the speech that you just play the full passage if you wanted to.
Sure.
But this is Frankenstein.
Together, there are just cuts everywhere.
They promote authoritarian leaders and they fan the flames of political violence that are a threat to our personal rights, to the pursuit of justice, to the rule of law, to the very soul of this country.
We hear you've heard it more and more talk about violence.
So you could hear that cut there again.
Yeah.
Here's what Biden said in the middle of that, right after where it cut.
Quote, they look at the mob that stormed the United States Capitol on January 6, brutally attacking law enforcement not as insurrectionists who placed a dagger to the throat of our democracy, but they look at them as patriots, and they see their MAGA failure to stop a peaceful transfer of power after the 2020 election as preparation for the 2022 and 2024 elections.
I think Alex knows well enough that most of his audience does see January 6 writers as patriots, which is uncomfortable.
Yeah.
It's hard to rationalize if you really have to get confronted on it.
This is holding up a mirror to his audience's beliefs in a way that could be threatening, whereas other parts of the speech that are left in, they really aren't.
For instance, he leaves in Biden saying, quote, they promote authoritarian leaders because the audience doesn't think they do that.
Trump DeSantis Bolsonaro and Orban.
They're the furthest things from authoritarian in the audience's eyes.
So hearing Biden say that is just absurd to them.
That's not something like, I'm taking aback by this.
Yeah.
Another part that Alex leaves in is, quote, maja forces are determined to take this country backwards.
Backwards to an America where there is no right to choose, no right to privacy, no right to contraception, no right to marry who you love, all that stuff.
That stuff that his audience believes in and is totally fine with.
Yes, I was going to say that's.
Like, yeah, man, totally.
That's what we are doing.
They're antiabortion, they lean strongly toward or outright in favor of banning contraception.
They want to get rid of marriage equality.
And the idea of right to privacy is vague enough that they can just slip that in a list that I don't know, listen, we want the right to privacy, but we also want to break into your home if you're gay.
Maybe it has to do with social media.
Whatever.
This is not threatening for Alex to show the audience because it gives the audience the feeling that Biden is declaring war on them for their political beliefs.
They identify with the people that Biden is describing as a threat to democracy, which is what Alex wants them to feel.
In the case of the January 6 thing, that's a little bit different.
That's a case where the audience will see their feelings mirrored by what Biden is saying.
But it's not about political positions they can justify as rational opposition to abortion or believing that marriage is just between a man and a woman are things that are common in many religious communities.
So it wouldn't give you pause to look at yourself in the mirror.
The riots of January 6 were actions and those actions are way harder for people who want to see themselves as respectable to justify.
That's a mere it's best not to look into partially because what Biden is saying makes sense.
Yeah.
The group that tried to overrun the capital in order to stop the last election from being certified poses a threat to our democratic processes.
That make sense.
Yeah.
You don't want to look at that mirror.
Alex has also cut this part out.
Quote but while the threat to American democracy is real, I want to say as clearly as we can we are not powerless in the face of these threats.
We are not bystanders in this ongoing attack on democracy.
There are far more Americans, far more Americans from every background and belief who reject the extreme manga ideology than those who accept it.
After that line, there was a big cheer.
This could be useful to instill fear in the audience, but that doesn't play as well with the infowars version of Biden and these ideas.
Yeah.
A huge part of the election conspiracy is that Biden was so unpopular and then no one would come to his rally.
So you don't really want these large applause break and the getting applause for the idea that there are more people who are sick of this stuff, sure, than Alex's goofy audience.
Not good.
That's not good.
Now there's a bunch more that's cut out and a lot of it is Biden saying things about uniting around, defending our political process and then getting applause.
Right.
No need for stuff like that because it's bad optics.
You don't want it.
Also, for him, it's not even a thing.
It's just like, oh, yeah, we can't use that, so why leave it in? And nobody's going to question us for cutting it.
It's obvious my audience is going to watch the whole, they don't give a shit, please.
Yeah.
They're going to accept whatever interpretation I give and that's going to be reality.
I was wondering part of why I think that calling the January 6 people patriots is weird to me.
It's because it was such a huge fuck up.
We all saw that it was just a bunch of fucking assholes just really being pieces of shit.
And it's like, you can't mythologize that the same way you can the Boston Tea Party, that was just a bunch of assholes going on a boat and like, fucking shit up.
Counterpoint what? William travis.
Travis.
Fair enough.
Yeah, fair enough.
You can build an entire American legend on a drunk asshole fucking murdering people at their house who was only there because he was running away from his ex wife.
Yeah, never mind.
My bad.
I should have looked at Mormonism.
We're too close to it now that you still remember some of the details as opposed to the selling of the myth.
Exactly.
So I think you're right for now, but give it a little track.
Sure.
No, they're the true American revolutionaries in ten years.
I get it.
So there's one more bit that was, I noticed, just a massive cut here.
There are public figures today, yesterday, and the day before predicting and all but calling for mass violence and rioting in the streets.
This is inflammatory.
It's dangerous.
It's against the rule of law, and we the people must say, this is not who we are.
And now America might jarring So here's what was missing, their quote.
Look, I know politics can be fierce and mean and nasty in America.
I get it.
I believe in the give and take of politics and disagreement and debate and dissent.
We're a big, complicated country, but democracy endures only if we the people respect the guardrails of the republic, only if we the people accept the results of free and fair elections, only if we the people see politics not as total war, but mediation of our differences.
Democracy cannot survive when one side believes they are only two outcomes to an election.
Either they win or they were cheated.
That's where MAGA republicans are today.
Fair point.
Yeah.
Can't argue with that.
Yeah, every single fucking election.
It's getting to the point where, obviously that should give some of the folks pause.
Maybe some of the more aware, self aware listeners to Alex Chit should be like, all right, Sarah Palin lost.
That was cheating.
Laura Loomer lost.
They can't all be cheating, man.
But what if they can't? I mean, who has the time to cheat that many elections? Even the globalists are stretched thin, man.
They don't have time for Alaskan elections.
Sarah Palin can lose on her own baby.
And with the case of Laura Loomer, you got to look at this.
Half glasses, half full.
A huge win.
Absolutely.
You lost, but damn upsetting.
Yeah, you lost, but you were a w away from getting a w.
You know what I'm saying? That was a very short walk.
Also in this portion, Biden lists off a number of his accomplishments that he's helped make possible in the past two years, all of which are things that Alex is pretending aren't real.
So it's best not to confuse the audience with that.
Yeah, definitely don't do that.
This also cut out the part where there's a protester yelling stuff to disrupt the speech, and Biden says, quote, notwithstanding those folks you hear on the other side there, they're entitled to be outrageous.
This is.
A democracy, but history and common sense, good manners is nothing they've suffered from.
That's a pretty far cry from all those times Trump interrupted his own speeches to demand protesters be kicked out, or times he responded with gleed protesters being assaulted at his rallies.
Yeah, that one was tough.
It's kind of hard to paint the patience that Biden is exhibiting and tolerance of somebody who disagrees as tyrannical.
Right.
Especially juxtaposed with kick that bum out.
I know.
You really have to cut out a lot of Biden's speech in order to make him look like a tyrant.
Yeah.
But there's red lights and he's doing this at night, so that's pretty good.
The funniest part about it is I suppose you could go with the bailout and like the ACA to portray Obama as a tyrant.
At least there's that.
But with Biden, it really does feel like he's half ass.
And is he a tyrant if he's willing to be like a ten K in student loan forgiveness? I'm not going to go after these hard right people and say, we got to get 20.
Come on then, jack, this is negotiation.
All right.
Jack, you can't you can't be a tyrant if you're literally low balling your own power.
Sure, I think it's tough, but it's a challenge that Alice wants to stepping up to the plate.
Yeah, sure.
Another thing that's weird here is that the part where this picks up after the cut where Biden says, quote, and now America must choose.
That's actually from earlier in the speech.
This is edited out of order to create the impression that Alex is wanting to convey.
Right.
I promise I could make Alex's show look so much worse if I just gave up on the idea of linear time.
That's not fair because this is a very definition of taking things out of context.
Out of context in temporal space.
Yeah.
No, if you take it out of one time and then put it into a different time and make it appear that thoughts are flowing into each other that aren't, you might as well edit in each individual word to make it say how much I rent.
Might as well be a magazine cut out of a hostage letter.
I understand that maybe for time reasons alex wouldn't want to play the whole speech, but the way this is being presented is irresponsible and it's intentionally deceptive.
Yeah.
You shouldn't expect anything otherwise.
So this clip comes to an end or the part of the speech and Alex has some words and this is it like this is the entire show.
We can choose a better path forward to the future, a future of possibility, a future to build a dream and hope.
And we're on that path, moving ahead.
Everything he said is an inversion of the truth.
Here we go.
For a few he'd give a speech to clearing war in America.
They are locked and loaded.
The stage massive terror attacks.
This country is on the footsteps of doom.
And everybody better get the word out that they're planning to stage violence.
They're the ones preparing violence.
They have the history of provocateurring, and you heard it with no proof, say that Republicans are calling for violence.
They had a bunch of national TV shows the last two days say I'm calling for violence when I'm calling for the opposite.
These people are making their move on us.
My God, with a fascist background.
All they missed was the torches.
Torches? Isn't that traditionally pitchforks and torches coming from the other direction? Yeah.
And I think that the torches, certainly in present parlance, evokes ideas of the Unite the Right rally.
Yes.
Right.
Which is his friend, which would be the buddies that he's around.
Yeah.
I don't understand.
Exactly.
I'm sure there's some images trying to evoke that's not bad.
But I strongly suspect that Alex has the tone that he has there because he knows that his followers are primed to hear something like this as the go ahead to start shooting or carrying out violence against the government.
He desperately needs to create the preemptive narrative that anything that may happen is not real and will be a false flag, completely fake.
Incidentally, when Biden said the public figures were calling for violence and when people are talking about that, they weren't talking about Alex.
No.
This was almost certainly in response to Senator Lindsey Graham going on Fox News and saying that if Trump was charged for having all that classified, shaded mara lago, then there would be riots in the streets.
Nothing.
It's not always about Alex.
Nothing is always except for him.
You could argue that most things are not about Alex, typically.
Especially when Alex says they're about him.
Yeah, that's a dead giveaway that they're probably not.
I do appreciate the discourse in America.
You think back to those conservative commentators like William F.
Buckley Jr.
And you think about him now saying what amounts to I'm rubber and your glue, or Nina, what bounces off me sticks to you, is essentially just, I think, a win.
I think it's evolution.
Sure.
Ask not what the government can do for you and what you can do for the government.
No, this is an inversion.
That's not what the government can do for you because the government can do everything, but not for you.
For you they must do nothing.
He's not even a Berliner.
Obviously he knows that they're about to go to break and so he has a limited amount of time.
But the argument of the reverse of everything is true.
What he said is not true.
What I say is true.
It's a little lazy, obviously.
A little bit lazy.
Yeah.
Look, I'm telling you, the entire show is just false.
Flags are coming.
Sure.
Because that's the only thing that's important.
Yeah.
Alex knows well enough.
He's plugged into friends with all kinds of Oath Keeper types who have been begging to fight a fucking war forever.
Like he knows enough to see the optics of this, to see the way people are talking about it and know someone is probably making a bomb as we speak.
So when that happens, if that happens, I don't want to be blamed for it, and I don't want this to be a setback to my business and to my ideology.
So it has to be fake in advance.
Yeah.
And when he was talking about false flags coming before this speech, it's the same thing.
It's just much more important.
Now, when there was those we touched on this before, but the clips on social media going around with him saying false flags are coming before the midterms sure.
That's just his normal, everyday type, right? Yeah.
This is far more pitched.
And I know that the reason is because he knows there's a heightened chance that his friends are going to do some real fucked up stuff.
Yeah, that's true.
I don't know.
I think I would take that bet.
I think I would take the bet, because the bet is if you arrest Trump and you do the law thing correctly, they attack or nothing happens and we get Trump.
I think I take the bet.
I think if we get Trump and they don't attack, the wind drops out of their sales completely.
I don't even think it's healthy to look at it this way, because I think that the legal system or whatever should play out how it plays out, and if there is cause and it's appropriate to arrest them, fucking arrest them, there should not be a consideration of what the backlash will be, because that's terrorism.
Right, I understand that, but you understand that is the consideration that is being taking place.
I understand.
Well, at least certainly that's a big part of the conversation.
Hopefully not within law enforcement.
Yeah, of course it is.
Why do you think Mueller didn't charge them in the first place at the DOJ? Maybe it's not appropriate for a sitting president to be charged.
I don't know.
Look, fair enough, but there's also maybe other considerations.
Sure.
But yeah, I get where you're coming from, but also, I think that's naive because I think that to assume an immediate backlash is the backlash sure.
Might be short sighted.
So, like, if Trump were arrested and nothing happens, that doesn't mean, like, six months of planning later, something wouldn't happen.
Sure, that's possible in elaborate jailbreak.
Right.
But you do understand we're raising Trump out of his resort prison again.
We're talking about an escape plan planned by the dumbest people on the fucking planet.
I'm not afraid of their plans.
I'm afraid of a flash mob.
Do you know what I mean? Yeah.
I feel like their plans would be foiled very easily.
Right.
Yeah.
It's tough.
It's a tough thing to think about.
But I hope that decision making isn't being guided by the potential for people to cause rampant and random political damage because that again is terrorism.
It's not a great way to guide decision making.
Right, but that's where we are and that's why Biden gave the fucking speech.
Exactly.
There you go.
So this got me really excited.
But don't worry, it's a deflation.
This is an emergency broadcast, ladies and gentlemen.
And I'll be up here tomorrow taping another emergency three hour broadcast with some special guests who are going to be here today.
But with the storms across the country, their plane is delayed until this evening.
I'll leave it at that special guest studio tomorrow.
We've got big guests as well in studio today.
A psychological warfare expert, one of the leading ones in the world at the bottom of the hour.
Now, you can't tell me that it's going to be a deflation.
Well, I wanted you to feel how I felt.
I know, but come on.
That's so good.
I thought it was going to be patchanic.
I thought he was going to be making his return.
Now is the time.
Yeah.
So somebody's plane was not able to get to Texas for whatever reason.
Look, I'll just leave it at that.
Alex didn't record 3 hours.
No, this did not happen.
Or at least it's not up on bandot video or anywhere I can find of the normal places things are posted.
Right.
So I don't think this happened, but I was thinking about it like it's probably just Roger, right? You lose in Florida.
Yeah, that would be the one.
That makes sense.
And if it is Roger, then of course you'd have to say something along the I'll just leave it at that.
Right.
You can't be like, oh, I mean there was a weather event.
Yeah, I didn't check the weather reports to see where there were delays, but yeah, I'm trying to think who could possibly even be in that rolodex.
Joel Scousen is not coming in.
No, he'll Skype with you at best.
Oh, man.
Barnes just I think is in Texas now.
What if he got Bannon? What if he got the bands? Bannon would come remote.
That is true.
Yes.
Maybe he's got a family vacation plan.
He's in the bunker.
The war room bunker that Alex is not mad about now.
No.
Stealing the name of all look at it.
It's no big deal.
Yeah, I don't know.
Trail could be.
Why not? He's got to get out of the state.
Yeah.
Extradition from Texas is tougher than you might think.
So Alex has some analysis and it's really superficial.
Ladies and gentlemen.
This is like if you go to the zoo and take your three year old, you go, that's an elephant, honey.
Sure.
And it's an elephant.
There's no debating.
It's an elephant.
Or that's a tiger, or that's a giraffe.
Or that's a grizzly bear.
Or that's a penguin.
Or that's a boa constrictor.
When the leader of a country gets up and declares half the nation terrorist and says they're about to engage in terrorism.
And they do it with troops behind them with a red background with a dark cross above it.
There's a dark cross in every Hollywood movie and every Dystopian system.
They show that exact iconography, all of it scripted by design in Vie for Vendetta.
It's the exact set.
Also, incidentally, filming that three hour special, so, honey, I can't take you to the zoo.
I know.
I had plans to take my daughter to the zoo.
Listen, we were going to go fishing, but that fell through, so we were like, let's go to the zoo.
And now that's why I'm sorry.
Plane got delayed.
Everything is movies.
Yeah.
Everything is based on the surface level and appearances, and it's kind of troubling.
So it really doesn't mean much more than him saying that he looked at the speech and it reminded him of movies.
Yeah.
Also, Biden didn't say that shit.
No, that's just a mischaracterization of his work.
It would be interesting if he threw that one out there, though.
Hey, listen, assholes.
50% of this country is coming to kill you.
If the President said that, that would be a statement of war.
Listen up.
Listen up, assholes.
Listen, Jack.
50% of America straight talk express coming at you.
50% of America has got a gun and it's coming for you.
50% of America are bad boys, and they run with a team of bad boys.
All right? Okay.
Yeah.
I think our conversation about it would probably be different if that was what he said.
Yeah, it would be very interesting.
That's an undiplomatic way to the last Jedi background, looking at looking at rave, fighting all those people.
Yeah, I get it.
That would be evil.
I honestly would even have a pretty different take on it if it was what you fantasized about.
I think I would have a different take on it if they pulled that one off.
Yeah, it's very queueish.
Yeah.
So Alex, he's talking about this and he's like, man, this seems like I can work with this.
Okay.
I'm going to create some branding.
Ladies and gentlemen, when they project big, blood red lights on a wall with flags and troops at the ready, they're saying, we're coming for you.
And what it is.
I wouldn't be surprised if this doesn't have an operational name.
Oh, God.
I have a name.
I bet it's called Operation Matador.
I bet.
Operation Bullfight.
They see us as the bull, and they are shaking a red flag in our face.
And the matador is the deep state with a long, skinny, razor sharp sword so that when the bull lunges forward, the mad door uses the force of its weight to drive it into the heart and step aside with his cape as the bull buries himself into the dust.
This is Operation Matador.
T shirts coming soon.
Okay.
No, you don't get to do that.
All your operation names have been documents in the past.
You've been like we got Operation Lock step.
And there was not really at least there was a thing, though.
At least there was a word lockstep that could be found somewhere.
Another document.
Exactly.
But matadors exist.
I understand that.
But you can't pitch your own name.
You workshopped it.
You can't just be like, I bet it's called, and then just give it a name and then call it the name they gave it.
But he had a second option, which is bullfight.
And he came around like, matador is better.
He did work.
Come on, man.
Come on, Jack.
And then he has his own fucking analogy in order to explain the name that he bets.
They made up for it thinking that they had the metaphorical wherewithal to make that up.
Yeah, it's a pained metaphor.
It's not good.
Alex likes it, though, so he's going to keep going.
So he's going to keep going with Operation Batador.
Yeah.
All right.
It's fun, though.
The idea that he's just sitting there is like, I bet there's a fucking name for this and I'm going to spit ball.
I'm going to name it myself.
Operation Listen Up Jack.
Yeah.
So he goes along with this bull analogy.
Sure.
So that's all this is.
And the way you get a bull that outweighs the matador 15 times and has big giant razor sharp horns to finally run into the sword is they throw little spears are they sharp in his back? Sharp to piss him off and to anger him.
That's what they've been doing with the open borders and the drag queen story time, that he valued dollars and shutting off your power supplies and remote controlling all the devices in your house.
We warned you 20 years ago they would do sure.
And running down America and running down our families and having the NFL take a knee and all the rest of this garbage.
I'm sorry, what that was throwing the little spears, the barbs in our back.
But now the red cape is out with 67 days out from the midterms, where they know they're set to lose big despite all the dead people they've got on the rolls hoping they can steal it with mailing ballots.
And so now the red tape is out being slapped in our face and right behind it is the FBI and the New World order getting ready to state terror attacks because they know we're not going to jump on the sword.
Populist Christians, conservatives are too smart.
Operation Matador.
What is happening? So if you follow this and understand info's language, then you know that most of the stuff Alex talks about is bullshit.
And a lot of these things he's listed as spears being poked to anger the audience are just buzzwords he throws around to prompt an emotional reaction from the audience.
This list is an airing of grievances and the complaint is basically that Alex doesn't like technological advancement and abhors a society that embraces immigrants and LGBTQ community folks.
Right.
He yells about free speech all day, but wants to live in a country where athletes aren't allowed to take a knee during the national anthem in protest of racial discrimination and policing.
These are things that Alex conceptualizes as the spears being used to poke the metaphorical bull.
And it really just sounds to me like Alex is expressing a profoundly white identity view of the country.
He doesn't believe that people who are not straight white Christians are entitled to right or power in this country.
And on some level, any time he hears a conversation about people who fit this description acting in a way that he doesn't like, his reaction is basically like, you should be glad us white folks even let you be here.
Yeah, I mean, it does seem like the more apt metaphorical stand in for Alex in this scenario is in fact, the bull itself, constantly being enraged by any number of different things.
Alex is the spears.
Yeah.
He's angry people anyway.
Each time he sees these things, these things like people living, he experiences it as a spear being poked into his white Christian tolerance.
Colin Kaepernick taking a knee instead of just accepting police violence, that's a spear.
Drag queens reading at a library instead of being shamed into never living in public, that's a spear.
Immigrants being allowed into the country instead of having a hardened militarized border they're killed for crossing, that's a spear.
Here's the thing.
When a bull charges after being poked by a bunch of spears, it's a natural reaction.
The matador waving that flag is something that the bull can't really be faulted for charging.
It's the expected result of all the poking.
If we understand Alex's metaphor, his patriot buddies are the bull, and they would be well within their right to charge the matador, in this case, bomb things because they've been poked so much.
Right.
The only problem is that the matador's cape has the FBI behind it.
That doesn't really make sense because in the metaphorical matador situation, this whole thing, there's really no way to make it a false flag.
You would need, like, a fake bull or some shit.
And I have no idea how this works inside this conception.
Yeah.
This isn't Alex warning about a false flag.
This is him warning his buddies about following their instincts.
He's trying to tell the bull not to charge because it's a trap, because Alex understands that his buddies want to charge that matador really badly.
They want to bomb shit.
And Alex is smart enough to recognize that the way that people are talking about Biden's speech is exactly the kind of thing that will lead, that will be as much of a stimulus for that as a matador waving a cape.
This isn't a false flag situation he's talking about.
It's more of a honeypot kind of idea.
I was comparing them to the bull more in the sense that they lose at the end.
The bull doesn't win.
True.
The bull can't overcome the whole thing and be like, hey, listen, I've chosen the way of peace.
The bull is going to do the thing because they have no ability to stop themselves.
I think a better way to make this metaphor work, I guess, is the bull is the audience, alex is the spears, poking them and then getting arrested is the matter to us.
Yeah, that works.
Yeah, that's something along the line.
And Alexander will deny that he was ever a spear or anything to do with this.
There's the incitement that is being done by Alex, and then there's no false flag or trickery really well.
And even then, Alex could be the matador trying to navigate the bull, but really not having any control over where the bull goes.
And so the bull constantly comes at him and then runs forward, and there's all kinds of collateral damage.
I think the point, though, is that this metaphor isn't good.
No, that is the point.
And Alex is talking about this being like, stage false flag terror attacks that the globalists are going to do and shit and just doesn't work within the framework that he's talking about.
The only way for the bull metaphor to work is Alex understanding that his audience is going to carry out bombing.
It's just that they're being provoked into doing it because they think that it's the right thing to do.
I would also accept that it might work if adding actual bull fights.
When the matador pulled the cape aside, the FBI was there.
It's still not a false flag.
No, but it would make more sense.
But I think that maybe Alex is thinking of the cape as a flag.
Right.
I don't know.
Trying to come up with a way to work.
We're working on it.
We'll figure it out someday.
Look, I don't have that many clips from this whole episode, and one of the reasons is because it's incessant false flag talk.
That's really 80% of the content.
Okay.
Why do you make an announcement this bold and crazy? Because they're going to pull stuff so damn horrible and they're going to go ahead and make their move on everybody.
They'll assassinate Trump, they'll come kill me.
Sure, naturally.
And then they're going to come for you.
They're making their move, and they're insane.
I will be dead by the midterms.
But what are you talking about? Then say you call for violence.
He's saying that they're literally coming to kill you and there's no stopping it because he just announced it.
So if he has announced that the war has started, then the war has started.
But the war is a trick.
What? I don't know.
You can't stage false flags if the war has already started.
Do you understand? There's no reason to have false flags.
Yes, there is.
Because you want to look like you're only fighting defensively.
It's the same thing that Alex wants.
I mean, no, Alex did the thing for Russia.
You can just do the thing and then you'll have people lie for you.
True.
I mean, that's an option.
Yeah.
Look, there's holes.
Yes, there's holes.
You're right.
My bad.
I'm sorry.
I know that part of the fun banter here is missing your ideas.
I'm putting this on you by adopting Alex's ability to patch over things.
But there's too many holes here for me even to really do work on this.
That's too hard.
But Alex's tummy hurts, so I told you the last month, my gut level also, intellectual analysis is ten times worse than it's ever been.
that unless we see massive Justice Department whistleblowers now, and unless we see people even in corporate media that know their mercenaries and know what they're doing is wrong, and a lot of them do, unless we just see everybody start coming out and saying, I'm not with this, it's over and again.
Well, we'll just have a war with these people, and we'll show them that's the plan.
We don't want to have a war with these psychos.
We'll beat them, but in the process, it'll be a Pyrrhic victory.
No, you'll lose.
Yeah.
That's why you don't want to really badly.
Nobody's actually going to fight a civil war.
No, it would be absurd.
No, I mean, frankly, it'd just be expensive.
There will be more and greater right wing terrorism, and that will be what happens.
You don't want that, really? Because some of that is galvanizing for his community.
Denying Oklahoma City bombing is certainly something that they've made a lot of mileage on.
Sure.
It's also a lot of work.
It's a hassle.
And you rather not do that.
You rather play in this space.
This Schrodinger's bombing space that Alex is in now is much easier to live in.
Well, and I mean, not just that, but if you're going to have a civil war, then you have to have a concept of your end game.
And if you're the terrorist side, then ostensibly your endgame is defensive maintaining your territory.
What is your territory? Occupied Texas.
I mean, that's what I'm saying.
So if you win the Civil War, do you get all of America, or do you get a certain subsection of America? And you don't want a subsection of America? That would be all right.
But how would you get all there's no infrastructure that they can handle.
There's no way to get water.
If they win the Civil War, they're like, oh, it's all the Wild West.
They can't govern.
True.
You know how, like, Alex believes that Trump is the rightful president of the US.
Sure.
He thinks the Confederacy is the rightful there is that government.
The south didn't just not lose this.
Of award.
They won it all the way.
Right.
So he just wants to get back to that.
That's kind of how you should conceive of that.
That's fair.
It's on me.
Yeah.
Look, I'll guarantee you they got trucks loaded with fuel oil bombs right now.
I guarantee you they're going to run the same place again.
They did 95.
But if we put enough heat on them and if enough of their minions they're trying to set up as Apaches learn about this, it will neutralize them.
Yeah.
So we got bombs and trucks sure.
Ready to go.
Right.
Today.
This is extreme.
Yeah.
If I believed any of this, I'd be pretty scared.
This would be a real struggle to get around.
Sure.
And I mean, if you believe all of this, like Oakc was a false flag.
They have fuel bomb trucks ready to go, you kind of have to think that the target would be a civilian target.
Yeah.
If you're somebody who just lives and listens to Alex, believes this stuff goes about your day, I don't know how you could not think like, well, maybe the building that I work in could be a target or something.
It's got to be cripplingly scary.
Whether it's a conscious fear or not, there's got to be something that it's awful.
And if he's evoking OKC, it's not like it's not like, oh, this only happens in the major cities.
It's not a city.
But that is more of the well, it could happen in my suburbs.
Yeah.
It's a mid range American city, not a metropolis.
Right.
Yeah.
And I think that's the feeling that he wants the audience to have.
So Alex has some experts that he's talked to.
He's not going to say who, but they fucking agree with him.
In the last few days I've talked to high level current Pentagon and high level current CIA and high level Army Special Operations Command and they concur with my analysis 100% and say it's their analysis and then America has never been in more trouble.
But obviously those people can't come on the show.
But I can tell you that people that have done this in third world countries and people that have run regime change agree there's an attempt by the leftist arm of the deep state to stage events and permanently bring America into martial law.
That's fucking Steve.
Yeah.
That is Steve.
That is 100% of Steve.
Oh, yeah.
Guys who have run regime change, these are epithets that Alex uses to describe Steve patchanic Patanic alone.
I bet he's talking to Steve.
He's not saying the words though.
He's back sliding into this past abusive relationship.
Only a matter of time.
It is.
You just can't quit.
Just rip the bandaid off and get him back already.
I know.
Now, I do think that it would make sense that these high level people agree with Alex because we heard not too long ago that Alex is the.
Fucking leader of the government.
Yeah, but he doesn't even remember that.
He does not remember that.
He is not calling people who are until I brought it up.
You forgot? I completely forgot.
It's a day to day.
It's a day to day show.
No continuity, anything.
Not at all.
Alex is in charge of the Patriots and the government.
Yeah.
They look to him as leader.
Of course, their analysis intersects.
What are they doing with analysis? Shouldn't they? No shit.
Yes, but that's what analysis is.
The things they know from the things they know.
Yeah, but shouldn't he be calling them to confirm his analysis and not have them be like, we were thinking the same thing, bro.
We don't have any explanation or why let me explain this.
He's just talking shit with people sure.
Who don't actually have any information.
Well, there's that, and they're not, like, high level he's talking shit with Steve.
Basically.
Fun.
It's more fun.
Yes.
Speaking of not fun, this clip was really where if I were involved in towel throwing sure.
This is maybe where I would throw the towel on this.
It kind of brought me back to reality.
They know they've lost politically.
They know they're about to lose the election.
So they are getting ready to stage something huge, ladies and gentlemen.
So the public will at least buy that.
Oh, because of the big terror attack or whatever or terror attacks or mass shootings or mass poisonings or power outages or whatever it is they're gearing up to do.
There's a plethora of things they can do within the ball flag realm.
And so I'm just going to be every day on this until the election because they'll want a few weeks to maximize it.
I'd say we enter the prime zone October 1.
In October after they may go ahead and just start stuff up now and then they may do a bunch of attacks.
They may do one big, giant attack.
They may do five, six big attacks.
Is that all part of Operation the truck bombs are loaded, okay? You better believe the mentally ill schizophrenic mass shooters are being programmed and drugged up and are in government CIA numerolder programming centers.
MKL for operations right now, the Manchurian candidates are ready.
They are rolling out, guaranteed.
You can bet your bottom dollar.
I've been kind of zoning out a little bit at this point because it's just repetitive yelling nonsense about false flags.
But I kind of got brought back down to the ground by this clip, and it was just like, what are we doing? Like, Alex's conspiracy and this grand false flag that's coming, and Biden's speech is the harbinger for it.
It all centers around the fucking midterm.
I mean, the plot for this giant false flag is about creating the public perception that it makes sense for Democrats to win midterm elections.
What is going on? Is this what Alex has been brought to? And it's not just that, but he's listing everything is a sign.
It's not just false flags where it's like, oh, there's an explosion or something.
No, it's like, hey, the power went out for 8 hours.
They're coming for you.
Like, oh, shit, the WiFi down.
Anything could be explained as the jump off anything.
Yeah.
And he's listing random ass shit.
Anybody? Anything rises and the rooster is silent.
The globalists are coming.
If someone looks shifty at you in the grocery store, that's the size right there's.
No escape.
Yes.
If you see a rainbow and the colors are inverted tomorrow, it's going to be fine.
I can't hang with that.
They've been beaten back.
We have neutralized the car bomb.
What are you doing to me? Yeah, it's insane.
And the notion that it's about the midterms is just pathetic.
I can't there was at least a self seriousness that Alex had in earlier times in his career where this would look embarrassing for him to be, like, going so far out of his way to create these elaborate conspiracy theories about something like a midterm election.
How obsessed is he with treating politics like sports and like a pop culture kind of thing that he's doing this about a midterm? Yeah.
So sad.
Yes, man.
He's supposed to be above this.
He used to do 911, dude, and now you're at the midterm.
Well, he's trying to pretend that 911 is coming in order for Democrats to win a midterm.
It's the most important election of our lifetime.
Stan.
I think that a lot of people very rightly.
Critique that kind of rhetoric all over the place.
And I think that's fine.
I think that Alex is doing a substantially worse version of it.
More extreme version.
What a bummer.
Yeah.
So Alex takes some calls and he wants to talk to people who are like, in the military, hey, are you going to bomb something? Because it should be a false flag.
Don't bomb something.
He doesn't grill up people about that.
I think I would if I took over Info Wars for a day.
I would be like, okay, I'm taking calls.
My first question to everyone, have you or are you about to build a bomb? Well, I think that in the past I have heard people say, like, alex, I want to talk to you off air.
Yeah, I think some of those people might say that off air.
Maybe not on the radio.
But he says he wants to take calls from military folk who know things.
Sure.
And I would suggest that this is a bad strategy because it incentivizes people to lie about being in the military.
If I'm only taking calls from military people like, oh, hey, guess what? Now I'm military.
Yeah, I don't know if you recall that story of the Bundys and all those dudes sitting around talking about their fucking military experience, all their wartime shit.
None of them had ever been in the army at all.
Yeah, Dave Anthony brought that up on alex takes a call from somebody who is allegedly maybe national security or maybe Ice.
Who knows? It could be anybody.
His resume is dubious and he has some news about a bomb.
Tony is a 15 year Homeland Security and he wants to give us his view on this from Washington, DC.
Go ahead, Tony.
Hey, how are you doing, Alan? Hey, God bless you once again.
But, hey, I'm calling because I'm 15 year former federal employee for custom Border protection work for Ice.
But I'm calling in regard to the whole entire thing about everything is coming about.
As you know, six months ago, I walked away from the federal government.
They wanted us to do the vaccine mandates.
And I told my orchest email there's about nine to 12% of us to walk away.
But there will be something coming every couple of months, of which I got numerous members when I still work there.
And more likely, it's going to be a nuclear bomb minus the plutonium or the uranium it's going to set off, and that's going to be one of the new set of lockdowns.
So not a nuclear bomb, suitcase nukes, power outages, but without the tax they blame on the Russians.
I believe all that's in the cards.
But that's what you guys are getting briefed on.
It's one of the things we're getting briefed on.
But minus the radiation still, there won't be no radiation that's going to be set off.
It's all going to be and that's going to be one of the ways that they said with the vaccine, one of the way they feared people, some people are going to be also afraid of nuclear, but it's really classic explosive.
Or are you saying it's going to be a neutron bomb? We got supplies for the last two years.
They've been planning this stuff for the last two years.
As you know about the body bags, myself, my former office, we had over 200,000 body bags all over the entire spot.
Sure, you said something.
They're saying it's a nuclear bomb minus radiation.
That's a neutron bomb, which is kissinger and Brazevski are obsessed with neutron bombs.
And he populate America.
This guy sounds a little speedy.
I mean, he's more chatty than any CBP officer I've ever not anymore.
He's not part of it because he left over vaccine mandates.
Yeah, six months ago.
Sure.
Vaccine mandates six months ago.
Also, a neutron bomb is not just a nuke minus the radiation.
There's still tons of radiation, but the concept is to minimize the longevity that the radiation is there.
So the affected areas have inhabited more quickly, and we get people back in.
But I guess that we should be on the lookout for nuclear bombs that have no radiation involved because this high level Ice insider has warned of it and Alex has agreed this is a serious concern.
So we should probably be really worried about this.
This is definitely worth your mind space.
Yeah.
A guy dubiously associated with federal government programs, ostensibly not on speed right now, telling me that nuclear bombs without plutonium are going to hit people.
I'm going to go with a pass on this one.
You pass? I pass because Alex said I agree.
I'm going to pass.
I'm going to go with a pass on this one.
So we finally serve the shark tank.
Alex is the one going with this business.
We found the difference between you and Alex.
Yeah.
So we get another caller.
He's got an idea.
Great to talk to you.
My personal opinion is that they're bringing the borders wide open.
If you notice, there's a lot of Ukrainians coming through there I haven't noticed.
And they're you going to use these Ukrainians because Biden has connections with those people.
The Russians in Florida.
Ukrainians may say false flags in Europe and America.
I agree.
That they would stand again from it.
And they're going to dress them up in Trump gear and have them do some stuff and bam.
Martial law.
So look out for Ukrainians dressed up as Trump supporters carrying neutron bombs and also trucks with fuel bombs already gassed up and ready to go.
Boy, we got a lot of things to worry about.
This is a concern.
Fuck.
Shot of concern.
Did he say that he hasn't seen Ukrainians coming through the border? Seen so many of them.
He has.
Not so many.
Where? Mexico.
Ukrainians are going through Mexico.
Yeah.
They fly to El Salvador.
What are we doing if Ukrainians are coming through the border? Well, there's a tunnel from Ukraine to Brazil and then they these are the ballots from North Korea.
Ballots from North Korea.
You know the tunnel, how it connects France and UK.
Okay.
They have that.
It's between Ukraine and Brazil.
Ukrainians are in Odessa and they're like, Listen, we could go to the United States.
But those motherfuckers, you can't trust them.
We're going to head to Mexico first.
We're going to take the land route to get through Arizona or whatever.
We might be thinking about this wrong.
Okay.
You know there's an Odessa in Texas? I did not know that.
There's an Odessa in Ukraine.
Is there a teleportation device between Odessa? Okay, now we're talking.
I think there's a portal.
You might be right.
I think we're in portal territory.
That makes it all a lot easier to get a suitcase nuke through.
I would think so, anyway.
And Biden has connections with quote, those people.
The whole country.
So we have one caller who disagrees with Alex.
Interesting.
This is a good example of why it's pointless to disagree with Alex on his show.
Let's race through your calls right now.
Let's go to John in Vegas.
John, thanks for calling.
Go ahead.
Yeah, I'm looking at the Biden transcript right now and I don't see a single thing that you're talking about in this? I tell you what.
What you're doing, edging your audience constantly is embarrassing and a shame.
You're a seminar caller.
You said you were calling on the Air Force about the Biden speech.
I can play the clips right now while you're gaslighting.
Even the Washington Post said it was basically a declaration of war.
They're saying Republicans are planning violence everywhere.
Are you denying he's up there with troops behind him? That's unprecedented.
For a president to give a speech with troops at nighttime with red light behind him, unprecedented.
I'm denying that.
I've had enough said.
You disagree and have legitimate points.
I talked to you.
I'm not going to play your games.
I got stacks of articles and controlling our thermostats.
Their child.
I'm sorry, what the border they're saying Republicans are about at the Hill.
I'm not even going to humor you and play the Cliffs everybody obviously speech last night.
So this caller is a good example of why you can't really inject disagreement on Alex's own show, even if you have a valid point.
Like how none of the things Alex is saying about buying and speech are accurate.
True.
Alex could just hang up on you, talk over you, call you a seminar caller and create fake reasons to not engage with any of your points.
He can list off weird, unrelated talking points to distract his listeners.
Like what exactly does your thermostat have to do with whether or not the way Alex is discussing Biden's speech is accurate? It has nothing to do with that.
I believe he was actually speaking literally in that because if you scan the sentence, then he's actually the stacks of articles themselves that are controlling our thermostats.
So that was just letting everybody know that the stacks of articles have taken over.
The amount of printing and wasting of paper and non recycling that Alex does taking over added impact on climate change.
You got it to the point where governments have had to control your thermostat.
Controlling our thermostats because we can't stop printing stacks.
History will reflect that our culture was brought down by stacky.
That is a theory.
Automobiles and Stackis.
So Alex can also just move the goal posts and pretend that if only you'd been honest about why you called in, he would have engaged with your points.
No, you're just playing games.
He cannot play any of the clips and present his unwillingness to present his own evidence as an unwillingness to engage with your games that you're playing.
Calling and disagreeing with Alex is pointless.
And even though the prime directive of our show to not interfere with infowars is kind of destroyed because of our presence at the trial and my work with the plaintiffs, I still think that it's important to point out that this just isn't something that's going to go anywhere.
I would not incentivize that behavior.
Although I do kind of wrestle with this because I think that person probably is a listener of our show because he used the edging.
I mean, I'm not saying that we've popularized edging, but I don't think I've heard I feel like I haven't heard terrorist edging anywhere else.
Yeah, like Pez dispenser for protocols.
Yeah, I think those are things that might be specifically ours.
Yeah.
Or at least they give the suspicion strongly.
And so I kind of considered not playing that clip even because I'm like, that might be someone who lives in the Star Show.
But it wasn't fucking with Alex.
It wasn't trying to mess with him.
It was just giving a disagreement about the point that he was making.
And it doesn't necessarily using the edging doesn't necessarily mean he listens to the show.
It could be one of those words that just starts to get popularized through the poster.
Yeah, but the only reason I'm even bringing it up is I've not played in the past times or I'm like that's someone who lives in store because I don't want to incentivize that.
I don't want people to think, like if they can't get on our show through, I don't want anyone to think of that as like something or that will be, hey, good job, fuck it with Alex, or a thing that people compete with each other on, like, oh, if it's funny enough, it'll get on the show.
That's not going to happen.
Yeah, this is just a good teachable moment where this person had a point that Alex could not respond to and you see all of the methods that he deploys immediately in order to get out of this call.
Delegitimize the person as a seminar caller, accuse them of gaslighting, say, I would play the clips, but you don't deserve it because you lied.
I would engage with your points, but you lied and yell over them before they agree with this.
Well, I disagree and obviously the point is going to be I disagree with the way you're exactly just cut it off.
It's nonsense.
It's not somebody who you can engage with.
There's no win.
So Alex is the psych warfare guest.
John.
It's not Steve, Jetty.
No, unfortunately.
And we're not going to listen to much of it because I found it to be a little bit like, I don't know, boring.
But we have one clip here and I don't think that this is exactly the beginning that Alex wanted to this interview.
Professor Matthias Desmond is in studio with us for the next hour.
Plus, he is recognized as the world's leading expert on theory of mass formation psychology and psychosis.
Applies to Covenant Pandemic, professor of Clinical Psychology, Department of Psychology, Educational Sciences at Gint University, Belgium, and practicing psychologist.
He worked in discussing widely in the media and he's here with us.
Of course, he's well known for the Joe Rogan Show as well.
He wanted to get right into Biden's speech professor and just how art typical it is with at night time with troops behind him with red light.
It's right out of V for Vendetta, it's right out of Nazi Germany, it's right out of Stalin Russia, it's right out of North Korea and saying, our enemies are going to be bad and we've got to have a war with them.
What did you make of that? And it's great to have you here with us.
Yes.
Well.
This speech definitely puts us at risk of something.
And it is that it entices the people who are targeted.
Namely those people who are referred to by President Biden as mega extremists.
That it entices these people to act upon their aggression.
And that's what should be avoided at all times because it will be counterproductive and self destructive if people act upon the regression because the system can perfectly control aggression.
I believe that it is of crucial importance that we stick to the principles of nonviolent resistance and that we realize that the first and foremost enemy we have to watch is that part of the enemy that is in ourselves, namely this aggression that might entice us to act in a violent way.
This is not really what Alex wanted.
The professor isn't describing a false flag.
He's saying that Biden speech was possibly a bad idea because it'll be used as justification for people who want to do violent things when they do violent things.
Right.
This isn't good with Alex's concepts because it basically is admitting that Alex's community are largely inclined towards violence.
They don't have a good handle on that internal enemy that is aggression and are begging for someone to give them a reason to act on.
It pretty much understood appropriately, this episode has basically been Alex tripping over himself to frame Biden's speech in a way that inflames that aggression in his audience, but pays lip service to not wanting any violence so he can evade any accusations that he's causing and calling for terrorist acts.
Right.
Put simply, I don't respect anybody who accepts a booking on Infowars, but this guy is coming at the conversation of Biden speech from a completely different perspective than Alex, and I think that their views are actually at odds with each other.
Oh, yeah.
I disagree with the professor's point mostly because if taken to its logical conclusion, you end up in a place where criticizing any potentially violent segment of the population is bad because it will trigger their aggression.
But I do accept that his point is at least connected to reality and it's something that can be debated.
Yeah.
Alex's position is more or less just rooted in his feelings, and it's not something you can refute at all.
It would be pointless to argue with him about the conversation.
Is Alex saying, when the people that I've riled up do violence a false flag? And his conversation is actually they shouldn't do violence because that is the thing.
But if you say that to Alex's listeners, then they won't do violence, and then there won't be a false flag because there won't actually be an actual attack.
So those two conversations are in direct opposition in terms of goals.
Well, Alex kind of winks at the like, don't do violence.
This is an attempt to his metaphor with the matador.
If you just have the metaphor, it is what this doctor or the professor is saying.
This is an attempt to lure you into doing something as opposed to it being fake.
But that's not the larger way that unless, and I accept this as a possibility, if false flag as a term includes people doing things they shouldn't do because Biden made them angry right.
Then false flag loses any meaning as a term.
So if Alex is describing that as something that qualifies as a false flag right.
Then I would say we have passed the point where any definition yeah.
Because the idea of false flag has to include I planned this to achieve the opposite of what theoretically, I want something on somebody else.
Exactly.
I do an illegal thing to frame a person, which implies intent.
Whereas this is, if you include the quote unquote tricked me into doing a thing that I wanted to do already.
That's just responsibility.
That's just called responsible for your entrapment because I didn't like Biden's speech.
Yeah.
I don't know.
It's not really like it is a little bit like, if you're like, okay, hey, here's a good speech.
People shouldn't steal from the grocery store because people need food, and they're like, oh, that makes me want to steal from grocery stores, but when I did, it was because he tricked me.
Yeah, that makes sense.
It doesn't.
I like it.
Yeah.
And I think that one of the things you should take away from this is that regardless of whether Alex is talking incoherently with this metaphor and stuff, or if he really does believe that if you bomb something because you're mad at Biden's speech, that's a false flag.
Whatever the case, the term false flag is meaningless to him.
It is a signifier of something that is just like, don't take this seriously.
For his audience to not accept any kind of idea that the information space that they live in and the stuff that Alex disseminates is part of the violence is part of inflaming that aggression.
Ignore that.
That's what false flag means.
Yes.
It means don't include this in your balance of consequences of this world view.
Ironically, to return to an earlier metaphor that Alex himself made, if you are taking your three year old daughter to the zoo and you're looking at an elephant and you go, that's not a fucking elephant, that's some fake elephant, then that's more like what Alex is doing.
Again, the trip to the zoo has been canceled because Alex needs to record this three hour video that he ended up not recording.
It's a real bummer.
Maybe next time a little lucy.
So this interview with this guy I found very boring.
He's talking about this idea of, like, mass formation, which is the idea that part of the population has been tricked into thinking COVID is real and that because of he's not saying Covet is fake.
Sure.
That we need to do all this stuff in order to battle Covet and they're in a hypnotic state, more or less.
But if you listen to it, if you want to, go ahead.
But if you do, you'll notice that a lot of maybe all of the things that he is describing as being indicative of this sort of hypnotic state that people are in kind of describe people who support Trump.
Right.
And I found it to be an uncompelling interview and get his verbal patterns.
It's very boring.
I hate it.
I really don't like that he's using terms that I think Alex is kind of not understanding and dancing around.
I don't care.
That makes sense.
It has very little to do with what I think is important, which is Alex's response to Biden's speech.
Right.
And so we will leave it off there.
So be worried about Ukrainians dressed as Trump supporters.
Really forgot that already.
Suitcase nukes.
Yeah.
Anytime you see portals are always be afraid of portals.
You should be worried about the possibility of fuel bombs and trucks.
Sure.
And also the midterms coming up.
Very important.
Also, you notice Alex is like, doing all this stuff, but he's not saying go vote.
He's spending hours talking about the dangers of these false flags, but not at all.
Get out and vote.
There's no real like, there isn't as much like, hey, inforge is going to sponsor registration, drive.
None of that stuff.
More just be scared of even whenever.
Listen, Laura Louver MTG, you need to be in the office.
You need to be there.
He's never like, I hope people vote for you.
I hope people strong arm.
You might say that occasionally people need to go out and support Laura Loomer, but I think more it's like donate to her campaign.
Yes, exactly.
It's all money anyway.
We'll be back, Jordan, with another episode.
Indeed.
But until then, we have a website.
We sure do.
It's knowledgeright.com and the 2024 midterms.com.
God damn it.
Which is intentional because we have it with a z.
No, but it's the 2022 midterms.com.
We don't actually have that website.
This is me.
We'll get it there.
Obviously, we're on Twitter.
We are on Twitter.
Is that now? We'll be back.
But until then, I'm neo.
I'm Leo.
I'm dzx Clark.
I'm Darrell.
Grabbed grabbel of the sniper.
Snapple.
It's another relative.
There we go.
And now here comes the sex robot.
Andy and Janzas, you're on the air.
Thanks for holding, Alex.
I'm a first time caller.
I'm a huge fan.
I love your work.
I love you.