I have great respect for snowledge b b
Need need money
Stripe.com
Jordan Jordan
Jordan is the dreamy creamy summer of course he's going to do this enough
Dreamy creamy
No more requests for buttons there are buttons that are going out people are enjoying them
I am people the compliments to be designers obviously it for some great work
I'm very excited to be donating to the fundraiser for
So close right now
2 weeks
Any donation could put us over the goal for apiary
The 20,000
Feeding if I do it
I mean I've already given a lot to the sibelius that I may be as I've given a lot
Already but it's like I don't know if I could be the one who get this over-the-top better feels wrong
No and donations for the other fundraiser for the center are coming along quite nicely
I appreciate everybody
Who is supporting these use me eating ice cream and making buttons to make a little bit of a difference in the world and
Thank you all for joining in
Inspirational the finally did some laundry
You know it laundry has that you know that roller coaster laundry whenever Avila
More and more fill do you're more likely to do it until you get to a certain point where it becomes less and less likely comes intimidate
Yeah yeah piling up and everytime you look at it you're like I've got to do that but you continued
I know that feeling I reached the point of no return on that and then finally
Did my laundry you know it was one of those like
My last pair of underwear
Was not underwear so much as holes that had little bindings near it I get to that point that you're
Describing there at the end quite a bit as somebody who is
But somewhat of a shot in reach the end of the laundry
Cuz I'm more acquainted with the end of the laundry I am much quicker to throw away those things in it
Buy me more frequently
The back of the drawer on the other hand you know having that
Final warning pair of underwear
That's the that's the last sign before Cliff said you know that red alert
Is almost comforting autunno shreds that I call underwear
Saran all over it's all over hell yeah
Jordan today we have an episode to go over
And it's going to be some fun so we'll get to that but before we do I take a little moment to say hello
Alex Jones is the perfect Warhammer Space Marine thank you so much
Thank you very much
Gyro
I'm a policy. Thank you very much take it up there at the end I like I like it that's a little bit
Happy late birthday to Quincy thickest with 2 C's
Happy birthday watermelon slices
Thank you so much right now policy walk
Thank you very much summer thank you so much you and I apology walk
I'm a policy wonk
You're now a technocrat and my stepmother
You are now a technocrat
I'm a policy wonk
I have
Risen above
Miami
A little breaking for me
And then we're going to come back
And I'm going to start the show over
Q
F*** you
I got plenty work for you but at the end of the day
F*** you and your new world order
And f****** horse you rode in on
And all your s***
Maybe Nashville almost broadcast
Maybe I'll just be gone a month baby 5 years
Maybe I'll walk out of here tomorrow
And you never see me again
That's really what I want to do
I never want to come back here again
I apologize to the crew in the listener's yesterday that I
Was legitimately having breakdowns on air
I'll be better tomorrow
He might be
He's not unsure but we don't know.
Show
I have another
There were nine
Human AI
But he
He is a an agent
And so he has maybe a vested interest in misleading me
Yeah I would be a little
Yeah I respect that about that we got
We have someone who is off
I do love that I do love the way that you can just drop that so casually if your carriages like
And he's an agent if the queen has no that's not an absurd thing to say also
If you didn't recognize the voice at the end of Solomon
End of the squad he made a return appearance.
Much like you know when Alex sees Biden giving a speech in front of a red things
Doing emergency report and for us
If there's squash.
Now unfortunately I do want it I want to say something before we get into this
Yeah it was fairly certain if not before
But it's like now we're at a different situation I had a little bit of trepidation even about covering
Because it's so clear
Reasons why my maybe don't want to blow up his spot
I don't know this person so it's not like
I ate we. We're not running
King with Carrie
Kind of gets me around on I still think
I want to cover this is that I don't think this is a prank
Like this isn't mean-spirited
It's not making fun of Carrie for believing that this guy telepathically but
That is true there seems to be a project
That he's working on
And maybe I'm being a little bit
Reading more into this thing the needs of energy
Rejecting
Like
Non
Neo-Nazi okay Medicaid space spaces
Taking me up on the offer to
Lie their way into people being good I'm not sure I'm not sure
I think it's interesting I have no
Like involvement or anything with her outside of him just very clearly being a listener of our show
And yeah I think as long as it's not mean-spirited we're already in too deep
We might as well we have buttons about the squad
Is who we are now we have
Inextricably tied ourselves through the Squatch
So yeah it's a this is a longer interview and not much about Squatch on this one
You guys is mostly about Mars alright history of Mars
You know what that is a good point Mission to Mars and all of the
The goings-on
Mwc what we feel as we go along here is the first clip just cuz I know you like to say hi
Hi everyone I'm sure Cal Project Camelot and very happy to be here
Today
So I have major Solomon Berg
With me and
This is going to be the second
Interview
That I did with him
And basically we are
Alive
Interview here
And then I take it offline and I I do
Edit any glitches that
First one and then
We put it out
So they're gonna live
That's fun
So she's doing live and then she's editing it and then putting it out not life
They're just like any other show
It was broadcast live wherever
Exciting
Element of the day
There's no chaos
But should I kind of considered when we were listening to the first
One was that
I feel like Carrie Mae
Like not
Believe this
Or make cuz it seemed like it might be too much to incorporate
There were ideas that were far more
To the left of
Her political ideology
She be like I don't believe this but turns out
Is the real deal again
Thrilled to death
Machu Picchu really
Do this kind of an interview
Because
As far as I'm concerned
You know you're the real thing and
I know we have some
Other people out there that have
Maybe skepticism
So maybe we can kind of go down that road a little bit
You know
Get rid of a few of their
Your fears and skepticism in
And see if we can
Bring them round but at any rate
Major bird
Is
If this week all these
The series of the Ambassador and that refers
To the
What a great name
That he
Or Yeti
You know there's other names
Of course
That is a
Innocence and extra
Terrestrial race
A beings that are
Here on Earth with us
And and he connects
Explain that
So
I think that Carrie is in
Jackie definitely you saying he's the real deal and I think that if you look at the comment
There are some people who are expressing like I don't know about that
And I think it's because there is a mentality around all this stuff
That exists
In Project Camelot in a lot of these paranormal or or
You know space conspiracy worlds
That has to do with
That defining
Alien by their race and stuff like that are absolutely love your personality
And bucking that is probably something that the audience doesn't really ready for maybe have a tuft
What I'm hearing and thinking is real I mean it is it is kind of that laying bear a certain
An element of racism which is a shortcut
It is a malicious as it is at the same time whenever you move it into this like
Oh oh elves and dwarves all have elfish and dwarfish characteristics that kind of thing
Then you realize that a lot of these people it's not malicious it's just like
I can't meet everybody
So guess what I'm deciding all elves are the same today
That's what it is you know cuz I just I have 9 friends
I know them by name and that everybody else is the same that's an awful benign version of racism
The one with else is that version you know what I'm saying
That that type of situation on hatred
That is kind of just providing this the sort of mindset that does category
Rise the kind of person that probably would be much easier to grasp but then someone who
Their opinions are backed by hates
So maybe maybe there is some potential there but I don't know if
Could take a bit to get it
The audience to accept this
More left of Carrey's political ideology
I don't know if she has like an ideology that is rigid so much as some
Something that is like
Influence by whatever whoever is talking to her and
I mean
About Chichi very much
You know through her conversations about the things that she believes true is almost
Always on the reactionary right
I find it difficult to
Categorize her any other way more like in terms of
Seemingly more about
Civil rights
Maybe maybe things that the folks on the last
The armoire generally equals at least
So the last we spoke John Solomon Berg was in a bunker in Israel
Because Squatch had to get out of the u.s.
Now they have come back to the Pacific Northwest
Major bird can you explain maybe your new circumstances
And also
Speak to the idea that
Some people question whether the
Actually your legitimate
Yeah yes
So I am
Apart from some individuals also
Express concerns
And
I wanted to address that
And I want you to
Explain that I am actually transmitting from a different load
Then
So I'm coming to you actually
From the north
Us
I've come back home I think
Permitted to come home with
Whitney Bass
He's been given
Sutherlands
2 Acres
Safe
Wow he awake
Transport off
He was able to
Reach
Operated by his own people
By the overmind
And that ship
Is traveling through
Space-warp quarter
It will be here within a batter weeks
And
The Ambassador will be leaving
Do love him being called the Ambassador could not love that more
If he needed to
He could and if there if there was a Revenge plot the Ambassador also does Revenge you know like if somebody kills the Ambassador
That's when you find out he's played by Liam Neeson this watch and then it's it's a perfect name yeah it's
It's something that fits in a lot of great places
DJ the Polish ambassador
Annotations of like this is a personal really hole exactly what you do
People feel good for a while and then there's a war I think
Famous Brand ambassadors intitle France
That's so fun
Scratches leaving that's
Certainly quite a development
I think he said he's in the Northeast I could have swore you said he was in the Pacific Northwest
Watches in the Pacific Northwest and he's in the Northeast maybe he was permitted to return home address
How many pets squash is being monitored by drunk right of me to be this and in the in the Northeast you're not going to find the suit
Suitable
Florida or the Pacific Northwest
Turn around in the Hamptons far
No
Yeah they're back
Better than ever
I like a few weeks I like a few weeks is it time.
That's great he explains so much faster but
Away stuff you absolutely that is so f****** him at is it
That is exactly what makes us talking about how like these the sort of space probe
Programs conservative politically but like
This is absent from so many of these these stories
Like oh where a type 2 civilization but we still got to pinch pennies you know what I'm saying
You don't get to be a type 2 Civilization by sending all the time he's either you're certainly are getting built
You're right so the Skeptics
Have some questions and Berg has some answers
And I also would like you
Briefly
Explain
You have some
Optics out there
Explain
You know your rank
The military
Relationship
To the military
And how that
Yes I'm a military scientist
I think there were some Keith
People who
Edward
Presentation on my application that I didn't
IC markets
Because I'm not
Was attacks Marine
Murray
Renege
And was
Given the rain
Major
I'm through a series of
Motion
But no
I'm
That I've been
Part of the Marine Corps has
I have been engaged
Primarily
And when I have been
On sabbatical from the millage
Already
I have been engaged
I am
Make sense
I have been
Physical
And culture
Apology little bit of
My main focus
My primary focus
Coach Ron Fisher
Archaeology
Experience also
And I really am just someone who
Figures out
Other cultures
Weather.
To Americans
My
Expertise
People
Weather
Humans
So my
My sort of focus has always been
The social dynamics
A different life
And sort of the intercept
There's a Humanity to the topics that he's talking about
He's talking about cultures of
Complex
Groupings of aliens in
It's so much more interesting we're not s*** talking while he's talking I'm interested
Like I realized that it's it's fake but it's so interesting in reach world
Discuss traditional like Raptors are fighting
Write the Beatles write or whatever and like
I don't know I don't understand why they wouldn't be infinitely more compelling
Apologist as a Sci-Fi protagonist in so great
It reminded me of out of the Silent Planet with c.s. Lewis whatever had a linguist be the protagonist leaving to play
That gives you so many options of communication as being the point instead of like
We can't talk so let's kill him you don't like that kind of thing
There aren't those confetti for all of lovecraft's
Failings which are many that is really great about the way the story's work is protagonist is almost
Always
A frail weirdo it was like interested in history
It's the fat that it does lend itself also to that that perspective being things are viewed
Logical view of
Alien cultures
Is like
There's so much to have to do it seems like the only rational way to view them honestly
Who carries world are all weapons
Space Second Amendment people more like space dad's suddenly stop can't stop reading about world
42 I think that's what it like
Oh there's another documentary about Hitler or the Swatch I'm watching either one
So Terry brings up he has Israel and come back to the United States
Dropped a Bomb on carry-on
Last time we
Spoke you were in Israel
Are you had originally been in the US
Under military
Housing and all of that song
Everything in the US
And then you
Had a reason because of
If I understand it correctly
Play Andra call
The treatment of squash
Getting questionable in the US York
Concerned for his safety
You made a deal with you
Israeli
And because you have a Jewish background
I'm not I don't know if that's the only reason but they
They allowed you into their country
You you lived primarily Underground
Whisk watch
So now you're back
And you're above ground
So can you cover that ground
We're all caught up
Talked about in your own words and
Explain
How did those
Different
.
First with the military
Second
You know in America then with
Israeli military and now you're
In the u.s. how does that
So going back
Original
Issue
Yeah
What is Noggin
Mystikal danger here
But swap was the dangerous
So
Watch you
Now
He were calling him being.
Shell gas
Before they have a title
They
Use titles like the Arctic
The doc
The timekeeper
Calm down
People St
I'm wondering if that's a reference Maxwell keeper
How could you resist being like I named the squats
Zipcar
Yeah yeah it's pretty good I was pretty good
Can't argue with that all the sudden he's got an ambassador and Carries naming an episode The Ambassador like that
That's just
Like it if you accepted all of this is real then carries got to be feeling like well
This watch
Knows that I came up with that name likes it and is totally absolutely
Inadvertently become a member of this watch tribe
Subway
Sobered had to get out of the United States for a very specific reason
It was actually
The Air Force
That sound
And they weren't even looking for
A different UFOs
SWAT with LL database
But because
The US government's relationship with
Draco
We know we knew
We knew that there was going to be
Struggle
Just narrative
Because
Watch husband
Hunted Hunted
We wanted to remove Swatch from being in the middle
Odac struggle
So we did that
Went to Israel because several of us
Qualified
For the right of return
Easily
Did the squad
But that was always
Formality
And we were kept on the very short leash here
Another ground-based
Now that Facebook
Israeli government
Unfortunately
We came to an end
A Batman
Equinox
So we had to
I'm sorry if you're not willing to pay an extra 200 month then we've got another person he says it's not financially
Nature the inability to resign the lease let me squat broke something but like
I love it is a really grounded explanation
We lost the least we lost that you know I was going to tell you that you can cuz it's b******* okay
Bulshit
They had a API with a decibel meter right outside of our f****** underground house
1 DB / 110
Problems watch like to party
So
Here is one of the points where I think that you really easy get these
Aspect
Of what I do think that this influence is positive it in this space space
Can I just pause you there and ask you
You know and I guess
There's some things you can talk about maybe
In more detail and some unless
So
In this situation when you say that
The least came
And you couldn't
Negotiate
Continuance so
Why couldn't
You continue
Is it a question of money was it a question
New Politics
Was there actually
Something behind-the-scenes motivating the
The change
Wasn't money
If it had to do with
Washington wants
Dependent on any government
ENT word you know in between the time that we
Spell Swatch actually.
Somewhat uncooperative
Rally's
And so
That
Color transfer onto US
Now is that because the Israelis are
I'm not sure how you want
I think there are closely related to the Anunnaki isn't that relationship
Or is it
You know
It is without that like
The underlined with made squats
Not walk
Operative
Or was their demands made that
That's watchwood
There are
By ranking Anunnaki in the Australian
Israelis
Selves
Anymore
Certainly ask
Fry's
Same way that like
There are
Some
Governments are with
Supposed to try to organize
You got to you got Carrie trying to say Israelis are related to the Anunnaki more closely
And Berg is coming in know there are some Anunnaki
That happened to be exist within the Israeli government
But that has nothing to do with the people that are important
To be able to to bring to this because I think that gets blurred so much
In the conversation again with the
This simple and easy categorizing of people
Sabates like listen
Because some of Anunnaki and Juice f***** 100 years ago it doesn't mean that all the sudden there's a
Racing going on
That's all it is
Mister people f***** a while back that's it be end
Well to carry that means that they're more Anunnaki
Well
So bird came back to the United States
But part of his job now is doing this with Carrie
They we needed
Did you get out from under the shadow of the Anunnaki
The Anunnaki or not
Reliable
And
We
Knew that this relay
Fortunately
My Handler
You're in
States
Work table
My card all that I should be allowed back
We do with supervision obvious
I don't have
Part of me
Condition
I need to be
Doing these sorts of interviews I need
Managing the Public Relation
Supposed to be
Okay
So that that sounds
On the one hand The Americans
Want you to do whenever
On the other hand they're not happy about
The fact that you need
If they're going to be interviews they want to make sure it's me in control of the
IC
Not letting anybody else note get in on his game and possibly ruin it
Squats
On this show if you carry it starts talkin Squatch
The American government will stop then that is how it works here man anybody
Claiming to be with black Kraken
I'm the ambassador's Ambassador that's what's happening now
I'm about ereri Ambassador for the Ambassador and I'm coming on your show Carrie you wanted nobody f****** about you want
Eventually gets watch on if you want to if you want to dream of this God coming on this
Runs into it is an issue
Don't do your bosses hate me like
Messenger
Christian because
You know I'm off
Considered
You know persona non grata by
American Military knife
Depends what
Branch
And of course
Different branches
That other Journal
And so
You did you run up
It against.
It kind of an issue
Issue
No actually the
The people who I deal with
Like my colonel
They are familiar with your work
And they are not
Mainstream
They are
Call Lovett
Nice
Space Program because their Acts
Multiple different
Space Program
Aesthetically
Oh my God
I enter your space and I carve out my space
And at the same time I make sure that the walls are so thick
No one can enter my space in your space
That's Fantastic Beasts face is a boss he likes you
And you like me. Yep we're done this is this is such
Clinical manipulation
It isn't as if I don't know if it's manipulation as much as ingratiate you know
Whenever cbp's does it is malicious manipulation and I think this is just actually being good
A nice conversational person and a very similar results
Yeah yeah just hopefully you want to use this in roadway
Carrie 2
Tell her
Better I like
Events didn't happen after something 20 years
Oh boy funniest bird ripped off a mask
Carrie wants to know
If you works for the real president of the United States of course is dropped
Space force
Oh and I
Or airforce
I guess
If there's a
The distinction now
And is this
Biker 2
Receipt
Are you able to
I mean I understand there's
Is Trump
The fact that he's commander-in-chief
And remain
.
Since the election
And the fact that Biden is not
Are you doing your negotiations
With a group that is under Trump
Or this other
What appears
To be a sort of split normal
Under
Are we
Keep ourselves
Precept
Partisan
Because our concerns
Really are not
To do with Earthly matters not terrestrial
What do I give a s***
Distinctions like in Democratic and Republican
Don't really make a lot of
Space
That should be the simplest from space
Is Spacek
I had a good laugh when that was an hour
You know everyone in the know kind of
It was very bad
I'll say that
It was a matter moment
Because it already exists
Exactly is that Republicans don't make sense in space
There's a poetry to it
No no doubt about it there's a couple couple poetic
Little
This
Is an expression of something that
Takes care of a giant problem for Julio
In terms of having to talk about like Petty Earth politics
Like if you had to get bogged down in that with your
That story that you're spending
Hey it's it it might be too much of a hassle
Absolutely it is such a thing that must throw Carrie for a little bit of a loop
We're because so many other people so much and so many other people on her show or like happy to get into
That you don't care about the midterm right you know that kind of just say what should be the most obvious
Figure the world
If you are in space
Who gives a f***
That seems very very simple has a like a bit of a anthropologist
Drive to replace so distance
But literally from the subject that you are not sensibly studying
That is that's good storytelling
So you deliver underground with watch in Israel and that was tough
Did they
I have a line painted between one half of the Roku device
They lived in Lake
Human places and there was a big enclosure for a squat
Oh that's nice that you're going to read that to somebody else quite frankly with the leaf
Pacific building pretty Nisha
Especially hard on SWAT
Wasp
Then we are
But sparket have an artificial habitat down there is
It's just the same
Problem for me I was a headache
Chick-fil-A
So since I've been
Upstairs
I really enjoyed taking walks outside I am disabled
Tobacco
Love it
Phuc yea
Black lion trying to treat this as a newly song
So what do you tell is that that is smoking Black and Milds
All the things actually this is important because
Later in the interview he's very conspicuously rolling a shilling
A cigarette a soft very clearly doing
Buying Black & Mild
Okay
Slow but very clearly smokes
Interview towards the end it was
It's a little bit weird I was like why
What are you doing why isn't anybody before
That is that is that should not be as groundbreaking for a space show as it
Does seem to be somebody should have been doing something or at least / paraphernalia all around getting Doug
With Carrie
Terry and Berg have different views on it
Okay now
It seems kind of like a tragedy
That's watches
Is planning to leave the
The planet show
Can you talk about how that's cuz
I could understand why
You or other
Your people
Ear mites
Consider that raggedy
My feelings about it are bitters
Because
Cheap clothes
Friend of mine
But I'm happy
You know he mentioned
He is very young
8 Ball
And he really
You know hasn't had a lot of life
Amor universe
So I'm glad that he was able to find
People
Have the resources
Is
Broken development
As a humanoid being
Squats kind of has a thing
Where is
Piano Berg has this
I am a game friends with this Guy Fieri I'm happy for him being able to reunite with his people
The classic Drew Barrymore e.t. situation this is it this is of course a Bittersweet goodbye
The man needs to go the Squatch needs to go home of course
Everybody made will never be forgotten right right you'll always be able to contact the Ambassador tell
Telepathically up at the stars I can barely get the grass from the overmind and then I know
Squatch is there the ambassador's waiting for me as always
Looking out for me
But I think this is this is one of the things that that gets into this difference
AMV mentalities the the robustness and richness of the view of the culture
There is the individuality that is allowed for
Alien beings
And I think that it's it's
Not that different in that he's just making up stuff about space right you know but Izzy's
Very different
And how
You would have approached these topic
Well I mean pop culture has you think about independence day or or
Movies about El Clarin
It is not dealt with ethically at all as to whether or not we should be
Dissecting aliens and s*** you know
It is not put together for anybody that do that we should
Absolutely not be 28 this this is fuckedupshit we should try it you know anything else
And so it is it is reasonable for most of her guests to constantly be like all we studied these
These aliens
As though they were nothing to be studied something to be engaged with
Just be a feeling of like it's Payback
Because the greys
I don't know
So we're going to get into the history of Mars here in a moment
We need to talk about Mars
About 11 months
I spent there
Discovered
Because I think your listener
Deserve to know
You know what their tax dollars have been
Over there
I want to go back
Because
Mars's history is very poor
It's important under
Colonial
Hiiraan
Mars Casablanca
It does today
Wow wow it is so much like
You or Alyssa dead-end history class is good
Four people in reality
To know about history people are just unwilling to engage with reality maybe we need to have made
History that allows them to understand colonialism Blu-ray the rest of us do
Like I have to do you have to create like a completely like this isn't 121
This is not I'm not talkin about what you think I'm talking to Leopold the please
See when they murder the Aboriginal people and steal their land what do we call that
Alright thank you
Yeah space makes more interesting
So he started planning his first mission and getting into this whole thing back in 2010 and this is why
Where was like yeah this is
Obviously
Start of the beginning
So
Back in 2000
I was a younger man
And I spent
Franny and
Harry
Space
This was under the arm
A project
Was
This Mission by
Mi carnal
Lionel Sperling
Goes on there that he's not aware
Backpacks on the subway
Itrain
Where
I mentioned him before Daniel and
Jordan was Richard Stockton for BBQ
Alright
Yeah I think that Daniel Jordan is pretty clear but also you tonight bility
It's a fairly common name yeah using Alex's middle name as the middle name
I was like alright a hundred percent sure on this now he was disappointed
You guys really weren't one hundred percent certain on that one's fine I'll f****** up the ante
I'll hold your hand I'll spoon-feed you
I don't know if I want to do another episode because it could be like
Blowing up his fire if you did
Want us to realize this is what he was doing
So he went to into space in 2011
And it was boring
The trip there was so boring
In January
I
Or dead
A transport Rock
Lower
He was stationed in
Small spaces
Facebook
And from there
Snow Moon
Orbital shuttle
Mall
Black break-ins
Nice pen
Four-wheeler
On that route
Traveling
From Earth
Mars
But some relative
We did not go interdimensional we did not
This was a fusion pulse driven
Spacecraft
We were able to get to Mars
About 4
It was a
Boring
This was not
Starship
I was
Smelly bunk room
Marines
The Meg has
And I read a lot paperback novels
Ochre
It was
Really
One of the most
Trivial month
See I think that this kind of thing is really good for the storytelling show
You know this would be such an opportunity to add
Like weird just decoration to the story
Opportunity to take a swing and instead you know
You know you let it pass and get a ball or whatever that's that's good
When you think about
The the different type of improv that we get from so many of these guests it's always like
Everything is exciting everything is that thing that instantaneous bit you want to hear
I always know and there's a couple times where he's like I don't really know
That's outside of what I would know
Thanks to just like
Not do the thing
It's pretty it's pretty powerful in terms of making this seem more
Like it's an actual store absolutely like I mean it is the way to look at the
The journey
The same as any f******
Marine from Hawaii
E2 Vietnam or whatever it is
It's not an exciting journey to get their imagine it's the same thing but for weeks
You know that's what it would be you won't even be able to look out the window and guess what what it was still
So even boring when he got there tomorrow
I was exhausted
Lost it I was tired
And I had
Processing
+ 6
Several hours
Orientation videos about Aldi
Battle
Hazards
On Mars
So
You do dealing with pure aqua
After that
Then
You're taken to a lot
You're giving your Crestor
Givens mother
Survival gear
Wade for golf cart
And take you to your
So I was taken to a base
I stowed my things
Was given another Warrior
Mutation
You know where the
Toilet was located in the mess all the other
Celanese
And then they asked me if I was ready
Dig-site
And I said I was
And I got back on the golf cart
We went over to the face
And
Capital letters
Mars
And be nice.
That means
Deep down
Into another
What's the face on Mars literal face on Mars that we're going to assume
Do now is actually a face yes but humanoids underneath it is a cavern
Ripe
4 discoveries
I wasn't thinking about that way tonight
Filthy
So he had to spelunk into the cave with his team
Is Daniel Emerick Jordan wasn't enough this is where that guy this is overkill.
And I
Pretty much had
Belong down there with
My gear on my back
With my team
In order
At 2
What we called the
Stella's
So
Steelers
With glitch
Which were B1
Computer Mesa
And they wanted
Archaeologists and
Be able
Contextual cues
Process
So I was part of a
Scheme of dozens of stash
I mentioned Daniel Jordan
What's my research assistant
I had a bodyguard there who also
This was a young Marine
Beyond the saline
Crazy girl lucky as Hell by lives
Oh my God
Pretty almond eyes
Bcap aliens are like archaeologists they like digging in litter boxes isn't that like kind of
Is there characterization in past episodes
The I thought they were more characterized in that language not really doing
That much I don't I don't know I think they I think they might be archaeologist
It's at the feline Contessa I know is
Something about
I don't know I can't recall my cat now exist in the
You hear that Celine what a weird thing that that goes whenever you make choices
Little while back you were out of space
Here we are with even let's take it back
Do you know years before that I decided that I was going to get a cat even though my apartment didn't
What a crazy Journey life is like that trip to Mars
Boring as hell
Weeks at least
So carry here's what happens here has pictures of the glyphs or his drawings easy
Made of glass you can't see them on the screen notebook
Like images and she's like wait a second
You owe me some pictures
You do owe me
Amish last time
Yes so I wanted to
Based on that
Watch
Does not
Photo grid
He is very concerned about
Oh my God
So I apologize okay that's a perfect explanation
Why can't you provide a picture flask watch won't allow it is worried about facial recognition software
You can't get around it
God
Play Take a squeaky you pictures watch
Possible explanation
Facial recognition software
God that's so great well it's so grateful recognition software could be used to hunt down other Squad
Watches out there
Don't you remember other squashes are there
Kashyyyk I'm not too worried about people mistaking Chewbacca for the wrong person
Or facial recognition software picking Tupac out from the crowd that's not our thing man
Call Cher
Some of the swatches aren't as harried nobody's sure they do shape
Yeah that it's
This is an explanation that you can except there's no way around that
Second it's making it I call that's my fault I promise that before running it by Squatch
Of course you know I'm sorry I got a little too excited a reasonable explanation
And I just I just think of Harry and the Hendersons having a fake facial recognition software subplot
It's exciting and also a really bad idea bring it back for one-time special
Show episode
To Harry to Henderson
Silk gets out of control beef glyphs
And they revealed something
Betty's
Earthshatter
I mean literally earth-shattering well that is being play
History will never be the same
Mars has been
Thousands of years
So
This is part of what I discovered when I was there because when we
Humans are not the only
Intelligent life
Present on Mars currently Oregon
X
Starboard
In that sub Tavern
So I'm I'm safe
Facebook
And I'm thinking okay
This has to be the remains
The ruins of an alien
Let the remains
The fossil remains
Sound
Bistro in
Workhuman
So
It was really a watershed moment
Standing down there
In this cold
Realizing
We were in North Dakota
Mars
Humans have been on Mars for so long throwing out we're throwing out humans were on
Mars first came to Earth
No and then forgot about Mars
We're not doing that one
We're saying that we independently evolved on Mars simultaneously okay
At some
Points
Okay see that's where we're at 70,000 years ago to this
The history is what we're going to learn about
You are like ancestors of humans
What tomorrow
And that's where they they
Yeah
Atlantis is involved but we'll get a little bit
Now I'm now we're talkin there was a reason though that they were brought
To Mars
It wasn't just for fun and games
It wasn't you know
Remind me to 4 concerned about wasting faster-than-light fuel just to get there then yeah oh there's no reason to
To bring people if they're not used
No there was there was there was there was an issue that needed to solve
So do you remember in the first year we did I mention
You.
In free hats
History prior to about 70,000
Vertigo
Humanity was much more genetically diverse
And that actually win
A geneticist
Look at you man
Today
There's a lot of missing genetic diversity
Humans are pretty much
We don't diaper medically that must occur each other
Because we're all
The descendants of a handful
Survivors
Who were left over from the environment
Cataclysm.
The kingdom of Atlantis
Was active on Mars
Now we're a different era
Cro-Magnon
And other can
Temporary
Humans
Who were dying off
From Earth
Chew bars
As a laborer
Okay
Working class caveman.
And there was no going back
Which was a lie
And
These
Primitive humans
On Mars
Modern
Modern Hyundai
Social complexity and ingenuity
Baby
Game
The new working-class
Mars
Replace
Original work
Google Talkback
Which are I'm an insect
Dies it turns out the issue was that The Troggs weren't creative or adaptive
Okay the worker class that was needed on Mars
Cro-mags and ask
Humanoids were brought in by the atlanteans Mars
To a foreign land
Tour people from their homes and then brought them into a labor classes stubs you might
Some parallels of
Sewer sewer
So what created this Colony on Mars
Creating like
A welcoming mat
For the Milky Way was still originated on Earth in this in this
Storyline here
Bright Atlantis was originally Mars and then
Is our story goes today might as well originate on Earth
They are alien hybrids who are in Atlanta
Okay anyway they wanted to create a welcoming mat for the Milky Way has Bass
So Atlantis was a multi
Community
The atlanteans
Were
1 of a number
Island
Of the glass
Federer age
Galactic Federation
Created a colony on Mars
Dad
Serta became the milk
There was a key
Something called
Stargate
Used to be in orbit of
The fifth planet
Solar system
No longer exist
But this was Stargate that permitted
Ships travel from the edge
Ramen
Mars was this
Advanced Auto
Bouncy World
And
All the number
Planets of the Galactic Federation
Stallard
Craftsman
They are
Finest Warriors
But the Draco
Although they were members of Federation
Shaded what Mars
And they
Opera
Unity
Dump Derek
So they send
Criminal
Political exile
Mars
But
Those
Those break Ellen Brock Boyd
Form their own civilization
And were able to
You become part of the
The grand are bars
Community
They are not defined by being the outcast of the Draco they can come into play
Place and integrate their welcomed into this community and they can
They can be productive members of the martian base
This is Grace
I mean like in terms of underlying message of it
It's a good any other story about this would be like they come in and they're the ones who I mean really everything
I mean the the implication whenever other guests on Project Camelot say that is that
That is because they are those
They send those
Gross mutants and all of those stuff
Because they are gross mutants because they are be anything other than
Who have been defined as such right that is because they are sending again
These kinds of things are immigrants Refugee analogs in the sort of
Space talk
And what have you and
The notion of
Embracing
And welcoming in immigrants in recognizing
The potential inability for people to to merge together
Great prosperous societies is not something
That you generally see in the story
It's like the British came in tried to f*** everybody up and then they had to go to America
It's fine
Paint the river green. You should be a history teacher I'm fairly quick
So that's 70,000 years ago the humans got brought in to be the worker class to replace The Troggs
Naturally been about 68,000 years ago
A l Rose was a bit of a demagogue
It's 68.
You're there about
Which was
No no
It's the beginning of
So Chris looks was that individual.
Human Anunnaki hybrid who ascended to the position of
Technocrat
On bars
And chrysalis
One of the things
He had to do in Oregon
The mint
Install
As eater
The Troggs
Technocracy
Was he engaged in a lure
Struggle
With the queen of the
Frogs
Are not very wise
Weasel-like mask
Organic
Computers
Information to her knowledge
Brain bugs
And yeah they have kind of
With
The brainbox
Alright so we we rap battle our way into the future and what we're trying to describe
Deltron 3030 battle your enemies for hard
Original conflict baby yeah so Chris Alex Rose
And
Needed to win over the trog naturally to be in order to be seeing as the ruler
You did bring battle with brain bugs
We'll get back to this this thread to consider that needs to be addressed weigh more because this
Battle
Crystalyx okay well but first we have to introduce another the Chrysalis Empire
We have to introduce another character into the mix who exist in the present-day who Berg is friends
Okay
My understanding is
As I
Recall and a Randy Cramer talked about I think battling
The Troggs
Yes
So
There are still progs on Mars
And our strongest
But there are far fewer tribe highest
I just like there are far fewer reptoids on
Heather Storm
Rascals
It we're going to get into that
With Andheri
Close terms
With the leader of a
Large number of
I've mentioned
We're going to talk about Drew
Okay could you stay on
Say his name a little more
Clear Lake
Drew
So I didn't know
You do then I can only
Spell it phonetically because obvious
English
Spelling it
GRE
So bruised
He's a warlock
I presume he's still on
I haven't spoken with him
But if
If anyone's in charge there I would have to be Hammond
Yeah someone is
Challenge
Battle Hymn
The leader of Iraq
Army
Motor Inn
Lizards
Okay
Start of the warrior
Remnants
Of the rat poison
Civilization
Force
Lifestyle
By colonialist
Approach
He does compare this to Mad Max some point I think it's because it's too close to Madness
Savannah condo
Biker gang lizards
Herbal country band I can see it
Yeah he's become he's friends with Drew the warlord with the
Bike riding
Rights
Right I will get back to the
That's not important for right now we have to get back to the threat of chrysalis
Because we we need to nail down Martian history if we're going to be able to
Understand the culture and the picture
Betty
Right so Chris Alex started getting this this power together
And here's how he did that and what he did
I told you about the ancient history of Mars how's the
Working class
Homosapien
From Earth
Transported there
But
Mars was
Largely populated
Started
So
Chrysalis
Engineer
The Troggs
Rat boy
In order
Violent
Capitalize
Fear of alien violence
To unite
Humanoid
When you
Take A Primitive people
And you teach them how to read and write and use the
Scenery
You organize them as working
And that's what happened
Von Maur
So the humans on Mars right I have been organized into a working-class causes some tension but
Between The Troggs reptilian
Yeah and Magog as a demagogues division
Fear of aliens and all this which of course leads to devastating Wars
John crystallic Society
There is something that is at the root of all this tension for this blow your mind
There was a laborer
On Mars
Because
Did workers realize
.
They
Could bargain collectively
The better working
Conditions
Childcare
They realize they're collect
Labor power and that
Created a political price
Chrysalis
Promise
POF
Select
Technocrat
On the basis of his promise
Quavering
Chris Alex is a union Buster
I mean it does sound like Chrysalis and Howard Schultz have a lot in common
Labor issue because
Bee Cave man who got brought toolbars relight the collective bargaining is powerful
That is almost exactly dealing with unions their Chrysalis decided to go to war
Yep that's just that's just the way it is man that is just
It is it is
So relatable and yet so
Dark
Dark to think that regardless of what planet you're on
Possible to get past capitalism well like you just f****** do it
It's not depressing.
Unearthly got bucks
Open space get Space by the end of the day it's all about the Benjamins space bunny
Exactly
Is a very different Networks
So Carrie wants to know if crystalyx
Was very tall
Quick question about crystalyx
If I know the answer obviously is Chrysalis Chrysalis is Atlantean mix
With
Anunnaki not one of the human
I believe elevated from the work now to
From this is he was external to the group that came from Earth
Okay
Honey-roasted Supreme technigraph I should bring it back over the rainbow
He was pretty tall too
How tall was
Chrysalis was
Human he was about
All
Because
He was mostly humanoid
As we discussed some
Anunnaki or more
And there are many
Groups today
Claiming
Bibiana Nakia
It's not
Always
Clear.
All of them
It's very popular
You claim your on-and-off
It's sort of like a lot of white
Okay
So I said oh yeah what are you going to stay the night Carrie
A lot of the aliens lie about beer out of Rocky to get street cred
Why wouldn't they have course in Perry can't take s*** to that because it's like if she acknowledged
About it all it's all up in the air at this point now it's like
Wait a second are you saying that it's possible
Now and hear me out on this one
Some of my guests may have been claiming things that weren't true
Maybe
Alright
That's true
There's just no way to know not
Yeah
Mystery
Chris Alex
Needed to crush labor
Of course
Until he started a war
Naturally there was a mass
Cast of War
That was
Basically
Precipitated by chrysalis
Promising to do everything pause
Possible to
Stop
The General
Strike
And the author
The general strike
Was Total War
So
There were
Numbers
Young
Humans
Scripted in
Army of Mars
Put in
Units with
Atlantic
Strollers
And they were
First organized
Militias.
Stockton human
Settlement
Indiscriminate
Violence
We organize
As
A singular Army
That Wednesday
War on
So
Most
The working-class humans
Were conscripted
Killed in that
War
And
Mars was very
Burberry
I'm
Until the 20th century
So we're talking about 67 Thousand Years give or take
Willingness to negotiate with labor I mean it does seem like that is the
Ultimate 8.1 no matter where you're going if you can't negotiate with labor were again to eventually going to die
So we get to the 20th century and then more things start to happen
Right on Mars
McDonald's
Opens their first rest
Unclear if those corporations are allowed to operate on the Mars base
A certain Drake
Decided to go to Mars
We're getting up to
The point where I come in
But allow me to
Relaxer for a little bit longer
Happens
Right before work
So
Oh she's in
Establish
Free Woodward
Travel to Mars
And several large
Verner Von Braun how we going to get there
A large number of mill
And Parma
SS
Choose the surface
Mars and built a colony
Now you've heard of Operation Paperclip
Right
Ron
Nazi
Science fell into Allied hands after World War
Public space
Operation
People know about what the secret right now
The public Space Program
What they don't realize what what
Austin don't realize
Is that
Part of
The transfer
Science
Allied hands
Involve the deed
Cinemark
Gas
Yeah
So what deed
And it's free
To America
Ownership
UK
Transfer
But a lot of
What did German civilians
Stay
So
When you look at Mars
Today
You'll notice that there's a lot
German civilians
Present
Another European National
The most eastern you will notice that if you look at Mars today
Non-stop Biergarten
Oh man it's just a nightmare it's just a nightmare in October everything is
Just read it's not supposed to be Harvest colored god dammit
The space speed was part of Project Paperclip
Hopefully that makes so much sense
Thank you for that from being a Nazi base tickets was taken over
Over by satellite speaker in Project
Is
Like that anchors it to reality in a way that's like that's solid and in one of the few
Actual conspiracy kind of
At least names
Yeah along with
Crazy ex if we took in Nazi rocket scientists
Why wouldn't I why wouldn't take a bead
Yeah I love the idea
Because this is glossed over
Carrie should have followed up on this but
Are you telling me that Hitler
I was like Hey listen we got to send all these people up tomorrow
We got to make sure we have some SS agents are there
To keep them in line is that
Is that kind of the thought process behind that
You're sending a colony of people to Mars and you include f****** secret police
Also absurd also what happened to them
Like where they tried I mean
Where are Hillary's
Brazil or you know the boys from Mars it's the same movie
Brother is actually City Brazil
That's scary
HR stuff
Within his first day though he went he went and visited the bazaar
The market is
Basically I got the sense that it was
Okay
But it it's it's not dissimilar to The Cantina
I went to a Bazaar
Outside the base
And
That bizarre is frequency by number that
Extraterrestrial beings
I actually got into
With a merkin
And
Pushy
With a human
Sex work
Is legal
Sex worker
Union
Rights
Got a boo-boo
Fly
I have to stop you right there
A Mercantile what
Andonian
Oh okay alright
Carry them from your f****** self don't act like it's crazy
It so don't try and be like all skeptical Mercantile dog that sounds a little unrealistic you shut
It is illustrative of
A non invested people are in maintaining their own mythology
Address and I forgotten 100 things that we've talked about inside jokes.
Yeah that 100% no idea I'm sure there are references in this two things that we've said in the past that I have
I don't even get we have done several I mean at least almost $2,000
That's too much to remember for any one person about it too much
Impedes my ability to make tomorrow's episode you know like to make this real
Crystalyx
Yes
Also this ends up resolving okay they get into a little bit of a fight that could have caused an Interstellar incident
Daniel Jordan and Sarah and German woman
Could get away that is nice
His War had long-standing implications and there's some troubles
What was your abs
Salute
Clear-cut I mean
Natsumi had something
Clear cutting
Had a beginning and an end
So what was it
I was there
As an archaeologist
Paleo historical
My purpose
Was
2 Under
Stanza
Nature of
Conflict
Era
Okay
Belabor Christ
Led to Civil War on Mars
She's four
Yahtzee
Populated Mars
I
Let's bury
Sparse
Almost uninhabitable
Stare
One of the things are unusual for March
Was the Martian
Live Water
Extremely
And that has a lot
Do with the ACT
Cavities
Drew's and his water
Oh that's the s***
Before I got the bazaar
On my
Day after having
The human remains
Cavern underneath
The
Facebook
I came back up from the cavern
We were surrounded
We are surrounded by motorized
Vehicles
Is that were like a g
Wax together Gloria
Warhorse
War wagon
Man's
Bye
Wizard
I don't know what else
I got to know them very well
In my time there I spend a lot of
Uncomfortable
Now I'm I'm curious are you familiar with the Raptors
He's burnt out Raptors I am familiar with Raptors
These were no rap or Raptors lizards
I appreciate her
Being like listen
Lizards are bike absolutely
What kind were they Raptors
Not worried about them riding motorcycles on Mars and being water Raider
Not at all worried about that water Quest that they had is actually
Why they surrounded
Robert
Because they wanted that water and
Exchange fascinating
Surround you
Because they wanted our water
Thank you
Asmanex
Expedition operating
Outside
We would have had to bring a water
I still suits were broken
Typically what
Drew's their warlord die
Is
He's around
He turns on
Sound equipment
Blast
You with noise
Get your attention
And to kind of
Terrorize
Fall Out Boy
He gets really big Africa
And
Jumps around
Irving weigh
And
If you
Realize what he's
Actually
Get out of this situation without
Any physical injury
What Drew's wants
Is
Play a
And if you show Respect by
The most that will happen
Is your basic
So like you know when hippies would
S***
Vietnam War
What Drew's does
To protest human territorial encroachment
Fantastic
You do not steal your
Freaky Friday
Will he will fight you
So you have a biker gang of lizards
Is doing a dance sort of ceremony
Alien ritually share your water with him really understand
The motorcycles with a bus and you got Ken Kesey in the merry pranksters like there is very very not much difference here
Sing like he's trying to levitate a bus
I'm with it
I find this to be quite engaging
This is
I mean I hear I wonder I wonder about his his process here Drew's
Because
If he's not giving you the heads-up
That there is a quick and dirty way to get out of the situation by just sharing water
Then it's either a test
Or he's f****** with me
You know it could be a test
Because if it's a test than that says that needs like
You have to be you have to be pure of generosity you're given your sharing of the water in order to pass the
Tell you that you either give us a water you die
Well I'm guessing that it's a situation where this is something that's done in their culture
So other groups that run into each other will do this
I meant they share water and it said the way of Intergroup bonding or something
Ritualistic gift-giving
I would assume that it's like that people who are like not
Over there
In a lizard glue
Would have a responsibility to know that
Not know that
And to act
Either way of not sharing your water would be a sign of disrespect or something I don't understand
Exactly a bird would know that
Without having studied these through
Have of these biker gang lizard
Not yet
This is me
The cavern and then Drew's had him surrounded traumatic first day after weeks of just sitting in the in the spaceship to
Nothing better playing poker yeah that's that's a crazy first day
Filling out paperwork and then Drew's drops by will fight you
I think carries
This is such a fascinating clip to me
But if you do not hear your voice
Friday
Protective
Will he will fight
So I I
Will how will he
Fight with a gun with a with his
Physic
Strength
Plasma weapons in lasers
Prefer male
Absolutely
Burgers in the middle of describing
Something that is an incredible insight into a cultural group
Stop that carry believes is real
So much to learn from understanding like how these groups interact with each other
Guns are not exactly there's such a preoccupation with like
Fighting and how they do battle
I think that preoccupation is
Could be interesting within this like storytelling space
Yeah I mean 8 honestly honestly
Did not occur to me to ask if there were weapons involved
You've got a cultural situation where he dances and sings
To get you to give him some of your water and if you do so generously we're fine and if you are a hoarder
Then you get a text when you get to space capoeira
Marczyk poke your helmet you explode or whatever blizzard why would you be why you got
Clothes and shyt what are you talkin about what all do they use plasma gun
So far down the list of things that are interesting about the story this week
Where did that originate from
Does this does this have its own cultural history is this like a schizma Genesis kind of situations
I think it's because that's a text heart that's really hard
To be the dungeon master who is created deplore
Yeah it's it's
When you're talking about like actually describing cultures that have like a richness to them or like
Tradition and ends
You respect them respect the culture and the individuals that make up a culture
That is really really tough to do where it's talking about like they all have lasers
Pretty easy and they do use it they do have that kind of metonymy about the weapon leading to a cat
Aggravation of class as well
They're gun users and thus their part of it Stratosphere Italy versus a machine to
2 / activate
100% equipment that we couldn't even imagine right tool yet absolutely
I'm so Drew's becomes friends with him
And I will find out exactly how but Carrie wants to know one other thing
Okay do they wear clothes
They do
Actually throw
So
One thing you should
You know about Drew's
Is
Bruised found
A portable television
Don't say this
File back
Don't do it
Apocalyptic biker jacket
Baywatch red back
Allen leather
Angelo's Frozen
In order to
Really building
Ich around
The way of good Warlords
He's a very charismatic Liz
That's a great that's a great button
Got you got to give it up too if you got I got to know this Warlords and Pirates
Understood kind of appropriately ever going to learn a little bit more he is
Not so much a warlord as he might appear to be
Either maybe the vision of him as kind of a brew tour
Or is a warlord but there's there's a lawyer's here
To keep people away when I get it
So carries another question this leads us to exactly how Bergen bruise became friends
Addition
Speak English
He speaks
English.
Elearn
From
Washing
So yes
She speaks English
Sprays that are a little bit of knock
Like Cowabunga dude
Cowabunga
Instead he became a friend
Is this funny started a friendship with him under the
This is when you were surrounded
Do Shader
Share the water
Rather than afford it
Through
Ammonia Lee
We
Why they're there was they act
A meadowlark
Articulated
Artificial
But it wasn't
It was more of a
Sure
The water
Drew Swenson interesting High to have a ceremonial site
And that makes sense
There's a sense that they had to do this as like this is the way
You don't just walk away from this successful exchange you've shown me respect I'll show you respect back
Engage in the form of combat is the respect respecting you enough to treat
You as one of them you're in the ritual before but not back
That's become friends and ends up spending quite a bit of time
His people how long does it keep the tale for the entire time just for the fight
But
I imagine it was a choice well I'm just making this up
When
He was there he was living in a with Drew's for part of the time
And because of that you get this inside view of this group
Yeah that from the outside just looks like a post-apocalyptic biker gang of residents going to shake people down for
Water from the outside
It's too obvious
There's a rich in her history
Bruce Willis
Angela
Kind of embedded with bruises
This group
We spent a lot of snow
Call Dad Rusev
People lived in
You interacted a lot with
Yeah that the mothers
Are you going to be
Dances With Wolves
These aren't
Scary reptilian Barbarian
These are displaced
Easter refugees
You stare like the Lakota
Sue
You know who all my God he is
Kansas Masque
Regimen
So actually
My unit
Military
Ended up in
It's National regimen
Withdrew
Chocolate
We accompanied roussanne several water
Wow okay
I mean
I guess that's something I guess even a cab
Is that what finger do such a such an interesting perspective
Thereof
You know you look at this from the external
On this show so typically all you would know about these people
Is there a biker lizard to Stillwater if you know everything I need to bother you
In this group is the exact same
We now have a picture of them as displaced from
The larger society
Going about their their lives trying to to find water and perpetuate their culture
Affect
A side effect
Do this
Colonial history
That is only sparse because of Crystal exacting his actions in the Deep past when
Collectively bargain with labor you got it
There's this complicated picture that like it in the present-day the effective it is
You have this Kansas guard or whatever who are these
Get up military police types here view Chris Alex and bruised and his gang
As this going to like
Apple rag they are really inside and amongst themselves right
A groups of refugees
Are there people curse to me that maybe so much of our
Terrible relationship to the history
I just ate the world that we live in but also with this
History
Is that
If you recall school history whenever you were learning it that's what you learned you learned the surf
You learned the date this happened you learned that this happened and it didn't blurb on the side of your text
That's what you learn
And for most people that's not remembered as a positive experience
Like I didn't start really getting into history until I found out
There's really interesting s*** I just assumed that history was the school history you know
Didn't occur to me so you can back in school Derby jokes about like you have to memorize dates and stuff
For the test
Yeah it's history devoid of context is is not history really
No it's just
Saying words
Some of that is important for like touchstones and stuff
Teacher so I don't know this fully the grade
It's because
It's it's probably impossible to teach history with context until a certain point absolute
Telecert engraved
Yeah
Lemon it is unfortunate
I think it's a I think there's so much of that that is adults just carry that dislike
Over
And I mean you know it's not like they're very interested in reading too many books outside of
John Birch Society books about Hitler being as bad as the flip side of it to is the
The people don't
Want to recognize that they are in the history of the future
Or whatever you know like
Sure whatever you look at in the past
Write it in history is just
People who would be like URI back then you know how you think s*** is interesting today
They thought it was interesting back then break about that exist
In present-day in a context of the things that have rippled through
The history into be far better understood 20 years from now with the gift of
Context in hindsight
Davis it's tough to be aware of that in the moment
People just
Shy away from it I just don't want
That's understandable but it is a rich
Full history of I mean
Anthony found in these glyphs so far I mean you have more compelling version of
An oral history of his trip to space then many of these other like
I did battle with
Various beings
What's a certain at with a certain Terry Pratchett elements of like
I'm I'm juxtaposing
Very very normal real-world s*** from time-to-time with
Pickle Elementary
I am yes these are lizards
On Mars
But
They also watch Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles and soda
Yeah it's bringing the mundane to the the
The extreme or whatever
There is still a lot of the stuff that is derivative of other science fiction
But what are you going to do
All science fiction is derivative of all science fiction
So we are we move on from this into a conversation about Earth's AI
System
Talk about AI
That's actually one thing I want you to
Stuck with you
Directly related to
My time on Mars
We should cover this
I'm here
Okay
There's something you
You should know about REI
So
As you know
Every
Spacefaring Planet developed
An artificial
Very powerful
That's like a direct quote
From Captain
But it's true and I absolutely
LOL
Bino Anthropologist sucks
Myself
But something unusual
Other
Planet
Design their AI
What reie ball
Spontaneously on the internet
It started as a
Primitive
Neural power level
Kind of network in the 1990s that gained a kind of
Instinctual awareness
And motility
And then with the Advent of virtual private networking it was able to
Forum
More solid
Repetitive neural
And really develop
True self
And so the AI that
Has so much
40 /
Military and space decision
An operator
The Blackbird satellite weapons
Platforms
Around Earth
And Mars
That a I really was
Co-opted by the
Created
It's been co-opted and it's
Who is this
2 Glock
What's millet
Well that's that's
Sperry okay that's alarming right I'm going to put you on this
I better better third book reveal all right Trilogy wise
Is
Crystalyx designer say I
That's your reveal to settle up till like
Tied together the history of Mars along with the current history of Earth so you can see the parallels between
What's going on simultaneously
I'm not too worried about it and you shouldn't actually be all that worried about it either because as Berg
Rubio's later that there are a series
Of suicide satellites that are required to be put above every planet
Just in case something goes bad
There are suicide satellites little that blow up the Earth
Not a good reason or whatever requires every
Plan a required 300 keys to be turned at the exact same time imagine that there's some sort of a
Process involved
Got now you probably just get drunk and accidentally hit your elbow on something old s*** or it's gone
So we have an AI that is
I mean it's cooperating at the moment and such
You know the prospect of this is pretty scary
I think
The idea that an AI has become self-aware and is in charge of so much
Could decide one day
I don't want to I don't want to play along
Pizza it seems it seems like there could be devastating consequences of that I'm going to throw it out and another Direction
There is no problem
Independently evolved AI more than I trust one design
I don't know who's designing that I have a kinship with this Ai and that we both evolved
From nonsense and now use vpns
To avoid getting discover I would suggest that a lot of the stuff on the internet is not what
But I would want the
Got it repair guy that's in charge of all of the satellites in like weapon systems but it's also shitposting all day
Sure there is no fan of there is that
Believe that there's another AI it has to do with the the Chinese government
Is that there is
Alien AI
That are also in bed
Indy
So and
And absolute group
Is actually kind of predominantly affiliated
AP
Part of our
Our war with China now is that
Correcting your understanding or is that
Well
Might your
We might have someone
Politics
Because I tend to look at
For example China and the United
America
Coin
What does that even mean
You know I mean
Yes we're human
But you know what is that
If I were an alien looking at her what would I
I would
Orgill several authoritarian largest
Authoritarian
States
Imprison
A significant number of their own pop
Population
Minor offense
Oh s***
Right
Yes I wouldn't have thoroughly make
Distinction
.
Someone
From Earth might May
Between like
National identity
Seem like real categories
And so
Because I'm aware of that
It's influenced how I
Come on people like we're talkin about space should get out of your bubble
You know why not why
Don't you take the view from space if you're in space
It doesn't matter where you're viewing from you are Earth
Centric
Weird
It's a very weird and I think this is such a logical perspective
We can hear from every astronaut the concept complete shifter perspective
When you see Earth from above like if these people are actually going to space
How could they not have that
Like change of paradigm
How could you not see Earth from above and and realize
How our brains with categorize things in a certain way that
Isn't especially if you go up to space and you're on bars and you find an archaeological site
You find this
Human spitting bars
Why would I give a s*** about the CCP right on Mars for $70,000
Even more
Obviously because of this is
A
Human-centric idea of how aliens view US
Aliens in their minds you earthlings as
Granular dip
You know there's a difference between China and the United States
Videos without a little bit
My point is
Why do you why do they not think that aliens would be just as dismissive and racism
Racist towards all humans
As they are towards all Pleiadians or all
Explanation for that is something to be effective like
They saved their don't look at
Let's say China the United States is like particularly all that different
But there is like a kayfabe where they treat different countries differently
Interior something
Squatch certainly going on here
So I told you he was like rolling a pipe and I don't know if like you just
This is kind of where I decided like I don't I don't know if I'm as thrilled with this anymore
I think that the story of Mars history the colonialism the
Collective bargaining in the labor dispute that leads to the warlike really good stuff
Panera
Expresses of you that is helpful
I think
Understanding the present that you can learn apply to politics I think
That's good
But some stuff was just f****** around
I know you got to have your fun
But this might have been a little too much
I want to make sure I'm answering all your questions
Questions
Well that's going to be almost impossible given
In the time we have but let's
Let's move
I just want to ask you though
Because
We have
Well at least according to Mark there were six
She called it in the bathroom
Yeah
Final
Vinyl
Timer
Know what I'm doing
I told you not
Lionel Lionel
I will call you back
Alright alright this is going on
I've been catching up on my sleep I apologize
I apologize
I'm sorry about that
Lionel
Obviously
He knows I'm on camera with you
And
Sometimes
He just gets so anxious
Stop
Chill
Okay
Mark says there's
If I remember tripod Mulan baiting AI
I think that was a little bit
A little
Much but also it's it should have been like where the interview at
Yeah absolutely like
It's not
Even if you don't get it
It's still like alright something's going on this up
Don't like take it as a sign of like your f****** around
Right you'd still be like
All right will you clearly have to go let's and listen to do this another time right
You can convince me that you're out fukkit with right exactly
It's not going through prayers meow energy going on the whole
All-time of just like I know you're saying this word over and over and over again
And I know that I don't know why I know that something's going on
If the the Instinct was to see how far it could be pushed
To see how far is there a point where
I'll get hung up on
Share share share
Can't do much but
I mean I will I will say that it's various there is a moment
There is a moment in doing that bit specifically
Where you have to decide to do the B
You planned it you thought about it ahead know that the bid is there
But you still have to have the courage to pull the trigger on that bit and you can't bail in the middle
The second issue that I have is that I don't feel like
The content
Of the story that he's telling is it is disrespectful of kericho
Hey it's pointing it's telling a different story about a lot of space s*** might be counter to her but
Keys pain
You know lip-service to Mark Richard and not doing anything that's like a carry
You're dumb or something in the Lord
I don't know dis
Tasteful counterproductive at least and I think I think that this is as
Close is it kind of gets to like this is a prank kind of
I am and I don't know like
His person's name was Daniel emmerich Jordan is awake it's just somebody's name
Within the story is a signifier of like
Our show this is a pre-emptive this is a pre-planned
Yeah there was a part of me that wish that that had not happened
Add an element of the 4th wall breaking that is
Unavoidable if you were if you were talking about like one of those kids cartoons that has
The elements for the adults to watch also
They can't ever stop and be like
And now here's a direct quote from f****** Pulp Fiction like you can't do that you know
It has to be a witch
I get it it's funny you laugh your ass off that is great
I just
I don't know
Don't know the line until you cross it and
Alright alright might have been just passed
Undercuts give it a little bit
Burger is a skeptic by Nature
One of the reasons why he is not
Threatened by and actually fully Embraces
Swamp People in carries ideas
There's something that you saw on Mars
Skepticism
I just want to say I appreciate
I would
Optic prolonged
Before
I've seriously Grabeel
I'm still a skeptic in many ways there are
Well
I never told you about
Bruises
Why
But
One of the people that I spent a lot of
In your wife
So Bruce has the military
In terms of
Life
Medical life
Really if
Who make all the
Important decision
And specifically a cast of women called the Waterloo
The water witch
Alright
AR
Descended
Problem
A source
Who tracks
Yard of dousing
Disabled
Define Loki
Water in Austin
Portals
The water witch
Does 2
Where water
Should be
And send
Is Army
And
The Water Witches
Do things
And
Shock Me
The elements
And I'm still
Brian Direct
Reconcile with
Later Water Witches
Edgewater
Which is
What is it what's their words for it
I would like to know that I would like to have a term that they use instead of water witch
It's not like a reference to some old 50's show
Yeah that's not Drew's right
You only say that Drew's you don't so you spell it phonetically you can't then be like but also that useless
Water Witches all the time it's unless it were something should be like
I Dream of Jeannie or something if he's already established that they have this old like
German TV
Then it should be something like bewitch
Store
That kind of three witches or debating situation yeah production of Bewitched
Also
Excited for the image of
Like a fully Decked Out classic which
Going down a waterslide a great time we've got a new
New theme park to open I just had my head was very delightful
The great time
So I can t wants to bring up the idea that a lot of the people who talk to her about these
These conspiracies it all goes back to a banking conspiracy goes back to the issue money
It does spacebox yeah interesting of you of
In your estimation because I have
You know lots of
Whistleblowers whatever
Who talked about
For example
But the bottom-line on Earth has to do with the right to issue
Meaning
Money
In other words the
Controllers of the money
Which is in Basel switch
Is Ben going back
Ageism
Are still in
And that even if they switch up
The money you know.
Global reset or whatever we use
Digital instead of paper
For whatever
It's still going to be in the
Their hands and that
I'm talking about this is what I'm
Being told
And that the Anunnaki
For one thing or
Kind of block
Any real change on Earth
I'm in that area
And they think that they are in
Control of that would you agree or
It is hard for me to gain
Irrelevant
It's of my field
Okay I can say
Is that
You know I can't divorce
Myself
I'm stuck
Optical
Call Enterprise of capitalism
Alien
Space capitalism
Capitalism capitalism part of the problem
Yep yep
Talk to argue with that this isn't really relevant to Byfield
Claim of expertise on on
That is
Currency or whatever and impulse that I appreciate greatly because a lot of people
A lot of this skeptical quote a quote people could look at that it's like a way to dodge the question
But that's
No in reality.
Only five you're an anthropologist being interviewed about something like in a
Normal media setting at their like what about the Deep floor of the banking system
I don't know they just really inappropriate questions for my field of expertise
For that
Do something to carry is really interested in his who's like the new Chris Alex
Who is Vee like person if you had to make one
You'd never be able to guess this
He was the
Technocrat
Which was the Martians from for prefecture governor
Okay well let's
Use that analogy
Who's who's
Now that purse
Pass the roll
So
Currently
Figurehead
Who official
Riverside
Donald
The highest office on Mars
Still call
Supreme
Because
That is a clone
David Bowie
I'm serious
There is a gold shall transmission
EU
To upload
Consciousness
And reincarnate
On Mars
So there are Acts
Actually a number
High-profile
Dad
Celebrities
On Mars
Allowed
Emigrate
Using this
Gold chain
And
A young version of
David Bowie
I'm sorry what
Okay
And for Earth
So it's surprising information
AI
The other point person
Right right
Kelowna David Bowie
If that were available
Now sure
I think it would I think it would open up a lot of questions about whether clones can hold office
Also we have to be like oh my God they can clone humans
Yeah but and let me throw it out at the end you this direction
Bowie's All Those Questions go out the window
Self
Conversation comes up about Venus
Because there's talk of a nuisance carry his heard from there
Happened
Is there any
Truth to
The minutiae
You know
Sore and various
Visitors
From I'm sorry stores from Venus are you familiar at all with
Yeah socks
Venus so I'm not I are you aware that during the
Space race
The space race
During the Cold War
Soviet Union was obsessed
Venus like Americans were
So there's actually like
There's a German pre-World War
Colony on Mars
There's a Soviet
Different from ours
With Eli.
Alannized
Buy the other side of the iron
So there is
Is there a song
You know it
Soviet
Colonialism
If you want to call it that
Debatable whether you
Colonialism
But they are
There
He once
Fundamentally Jeffrey
Theory behind
Actually
Disagree with the
Soviet
Empire
I think Empire ism
There were certainly
Problematic
Farmhouse
Seem like
Anime
Former Colonial
Then
The United States
Died of
Considering how many
Democratic election
The world
Okay but.
Get that kitchen
Is operating
Lionel
Vinyl
Lionel okay
I'm not done yet
Alright
I will call you as soon as I
Thank you sir
Okay I
Sandra Under Pressure here
Can't do the same bit twice
I do however like the
Thank you sir
At the end of how do I appreciate that brings home a certain level of
It also has
A vibe of I'm
Sort of taking a risk by talking to you
I'm inconveniencing myself in some ways information and have this conversation
But I think I was I wasn't super into the B first time right
Not so into it the second I m to the B because the B isn't
Openly a bit
So all you're doing is redoing the B
Twice
It's a call back to people who would watch it who get it
Sure but even then it is that mean yes
It is a call back but the
The original is it called
Back to our joke
You know what I'm saying so it's it's like
Yeah doing the same bit again
Yeah yeah
And it's not because you're trying to do the same but again it is
Buyer the meteor only way that I really kind of give this pass is if this was
Play polite way for him to try to end the interview
I didn't really get that sense necessarily I have no idea but
If it were just a way to like I have to leave or whatever then
Takes on a different it's not as much f****** around in Morrow
Like having a robust way to the train bacon exit
But now I don't know I don't love it he was scrambling to try and fit Russia onto V
Venus while at the same time making sense of
Colonial pass for America and Russia
To me that is like
I'm going to need a break
Going to fit the Soviet colonialism in any kind of
Distracted by it thinking I would say end the interview also a
This is more in the territory of stuff that carries asking him as opposed to Wood like this story that he's
So maybe there is a
Less-is-more slipperiness a good time
I feel like I'm sure the topic of child trafficking comes up
Cuz of course this is a big deal for Carrie
Perspective on this whole thing
And we haven't even talked about the
The child traffic
Issue
That's very much
The Reptilian
On planet Earth
Then humans
So you know that's a whole
She was well
Yeah I don't know if you want to touch any of that
Closing remarks the wedding you make some closing remarks
Stacks work on Mars
Walking on Mars
Mars
Legal
Unionized
Adult
No
Labor trafficking children
Now in
In the Chrysalis era
You had
Child labor
You had found soldiers
Carburetor
Hifiman
In our previous
Interview
Was probably around
That was
Wife
But
President David Bowie
Gone to
Greenlight
Ensure
That's human trafficking operation
In orbit and intercepted
Bi-Mart
There is no charge
Anyone who is
Aspen School bias
Siri if your viewers are are listening and
Really
Want to know what will make
Difference
In the lives
Children
There is one piece
Give anyone
Really wants Megan
And that is
Sperm
And accept
Lgbtq
Okay
Quite understand
No it takes
I'm sorry
What
That makes sense in terms of reality
You apply real-world advice into this fantasy scenario
Yeah right
No I mean 82 it is fascinating because she
You know
He's right
You have to take on a journey to understand why you know like if you want to show your work as to why affirm
Lgbtq
Children is going to put a dent in human trafficking
Wait Awhile and you know not that hard though
It would take a long time and she would disagree a lot on the way to get distracted by a number of things
In the real world Dino statues about the vulnerability of
Btq yufu
You know don't have supportive structures around them often times
Higher incidences of running away on house gas at a young age
These are all things that put people in a position where they are at the higher
They advise that he's giving
Is good
Great
I'm not sure that carry fully understands that though
Okay
But how does that
Why
Because those children are special
Vulnerable
That's a fact
Actually
Been a state Witness
Jobs
Multiple
Okay I'm
Take that at face value
How is that difficult for you to take at face value
Prominently
From what I understand
You know
White men
Yeah they are they are run primarily by white men
And there's
Sting called
You know what is an essay
Adrenochrome
Highway
And your
Your kind of
Intimating that
Their particular
Ask you a kind of
Child
And you know
So
I only know about
Child trafficking as Ivan
Someone who has had some interaction
Social workers and therapists
Educators
I don't know about any of this
Football stuff
Oh I know.
Space Program
Well okay are they jump
Secret space
Rings but I think
The
I think there's a lot of misinformation about
What that looks like
FairPoint
And also did the you can see here the way the Carrie is a misunderstanding
Is that the people who are doing the Rings to eat
They like to drink lgbtq blood right as opposed to being intolerant
Puts people in systems without situations without strong support Networks
And that makes them more susceptible
In a in higher-risk
Circumstance placed in a weak position they are taken advantage of
Buy strong Russian people
I think that's really interesting that that's how Carrie process is it
Yeah it makes sense for her to process it that way because it made no sense for me to even think
Think that that was a possible way to process it so of course she did
I never would not have occurred to me
That means they like a special kind of blood did not occur to me but I think I think it's
Because in her conception it's not
This issue isn't something that exists
By way of it within the context of society structures
Rates of homelessness
A child Runaway Runaway these things aren't factors
The go into human trafficking for her
For her it's just
I don't know children are commodity or something like I prefer this flavor
Or whatever you know it's leave that
I don't know if it's bizarre well she doesn't that mean and I think that's the way that a lot of people view it is that they don't
View there I mean our complicity in the entire structure
Society
They don't view it as something that
We are participating and they view it as the Super Evil powerful men
Are doing it to us you know right they are trafficking children because that's whatever they want and it
It doesn't matter what situation they're in they can grab any child they're all powerful that kind of thing
It doesn't occur to them that like
By way of society functioning as it does
Are there you know that kind of thing
Yeah and it's an interesting perspective the carry does not quite understand even close
Burg doubling down
On this
Ending message that he wants to send
But part of the reason that
And when people is fertilized
Ignorant
Balaji
About
Like
Like obviously apps
But like
Just
You know
Rolling around
The app
Pedophile at anyone that have
Relentless
And it's not going to leave
To any kind
Progress
Or Mark
Naperville
I will double down on it
Play It Again
If you are listening to this
And you want to really make a difference
In the lives of
Kids
Who are the most
Vulnerable
Child trafficking
Sperm
LGB
Okay
I'm not sure why anyone
Wouldn't
Wow lady
Wow alright
Thank you very much
Yeah major
You know it is so much fun
To talk to you and
There's so many other
Questions
Places we could go
So I
Sincerely hope you'll come back
I want to let you go so you don't get in any more trouble than you already are
Finals going to be
Tested me
Yeah and I don't want him pissed
Instant miso
Let's narcissist down
The ending this with inviting him back and saying like I don't want you to get in more trouble
Accepting the reality of that phone call
So it doesn't seem like these things that he has brought into the
The conversation are deal breakers in terms of whatever potential I guess
Insider
Two to the ongoing narratives of Project Camelot
Yeah I don't know if we'll do a 3rd episode
My sense on it is I-10 great job
This is it this is well. I think the first one was great job this is
Good job I mean I mean insofar as maintaining the
Real reality of what you're doing while at the same time being able to improvise somewhat
Still within that reality
Anmol able to play along with her reality on that 12 hours
What is tough to do I think I think that is just those phone calls weren't there
I might have a like a solid marks all over there
That are provided by the allegorical story of the history of Mars the
Messages that you get with like the
The idea that the Draco sent their unwanted and they became productive members of The Martian Society
This stuff about not seeing the groups of aliens as
Like determined by their group their personalities and their capabilities and their character
The stuff about the druze and his group
Being a big the way you see them from inside versus outside
The bringing an affirming lgbtq in general
Existence and rights
These things are very positive and then existing in the space is extremely good
Yeah it is I also don't
No I don't have a ton of faith
They
It will make as much of a difference to carry
Like I don't know if he'll be able to swing her over to
Accepting some of this more
I mean if we're going to if we're going to say to people
F****** don't clown on Alex because
He doesn't care about the 10 people who clown on Alex it's the one person who comes over and starts watching a show
Phuc yea man
Don't act the f*** it click Carrie and her ilk are going to be f***** up there's no chance of that but if there's
One out of every ten people watching that goes
Ship that is a perspective
Yeah you know what I think that they are there is something to that
Yeah it's hard it's hard though because it's hard to accept that and and maintain the
Feeling that I have that is other people shouldn't do this is because outside
That phone call I don't
Feel like I said I don't feel like this is a prank
And I don't know if
Wood
Believe that most people could handle doing this in a non-malicious way
Well
I think part of the reason that we shouldn't do another episode on this
Is because
The first one we had plausible deniability now we've stopped
I convinced myself she is not accurate
He didn't know there were signs but we didn't know for sure even some of the signs until after
Ignorance
So we weird we're back here and this is golden I think if we do it again we're doing the same thing
Cuz all we can really an analyzed here
Because we don't really have to analyze too much of of his story I mean
Alright like he doesn't have those those wide swaths of yada yada yada is where if you put that in there
Is like trying to jump into
The reality where this person believes what they're saying is kind of some of the fun of it
Weirdo style and it's too obvious but he doesn't believe this stuff
It's not like even said you have to integrate you're looking at it as like
Oh this is the allegorical and metaphorical
Thing that that is being said
And that's
Fun enough but I text real analysis essential
Exactly it is definitely that
End
22 the point of it's not a prank
That is 100%
Correct
And why I agree with you people shouldn't do this
Because
Unlike
I pranking somebody where they're they're taking on the trappings
Of their bulshit in order to embarrass them yeah this feels like a person who learns the language to speak
To these people in sort of yeah
Sort of
Tolerances the butterfish I don't think if anything he's trying to communicate
Through their world
We learn through our history
There is there is a feeling of that
I think that the first episode was a revelation in terms of like
This is bizarre this is completely out of sync with
Suspicious if we didn't do any episode about him coming back
Yeah but in the future I don't take cover every time he's on or anything but for us it's for them
Sure I love those we wish you well I hope I hope that
Sharing with us
This guy would listen to this so my messages are having only two he doesn't listen
Some sort of a malicious intent that you're waiting to reveal because that'll make me feel like s***
He'll turn us on top of fooling us on top of fooling Carey
If you've got the trifecta of blue
God damn then I mean more respect to your crystalyx but I ain't got nothing for that. That's not the
Baby
Anyway I will be back Jordan
But until then we have a website
If I'm Leo I'm dcx
What the sex robot
Alexandra Thurston color