Knowledge party.com
I have great respect for its knowledge fight
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
The altar of Selena
Alex Jones
Jordan Jordan
My brakes today is that our last episode
Brought to my attention on Twitter
Viola
Star greatest
Civil rights attorney of all time
Norm pattis
In a quart
Pra Alex's bankruptcy
Yeah we're about to I like the the Connecticut case
Getting the name drop
It's knowledge first I believe kelda or knowledge.
Appreciate that
If that was on purpose
Highmark top marks
AB not on purpose
Earned it
Attorneys /
Pantsless racist stand-up comedians
Woke Insurance AJ would have been like if he had written a bit about how these two
Chicago
Sjw Zur whatever that would have been good I would have been happier with that apparently we are
Cottage industry
I've been in front of a judge
In more ways than I ever thought I would be
That is definitely the case
You are technically in front
Facing
Just like soda
Spatial perspective
No
Not really thought you would be
Facing a charge
There was there was delightful
When I saw the Tweet Anna Merlin tweeted
She was following
That's nuts
But also
Possible
F****** contacts
Could this be a link to clip
And I was like what
Loser
You know it's not as exciting as I would have hoped but
Also just
Come on Norm
I want
There's just nothing you can
Can do there
I love the notion
That there is something
It disqualifying about like let's say
The plaintiffs lawyers appearing on our show or
Show me being a expert
Consultant for that case when you could just flash to Norm sitting next to Alex
Drunkenly screaming about how he wants the lawyers head on a pike there's that
Yes there is that there is that
It seems like you know don't
Don't
Pursue this line too far Norm lest it to fight you in the back to
Yeah everytime I hear civil rights lawyer
Man I just
Imagine addict
Spinach with his pants around his ankles safe
It'll Open Mic like it's just like that you can't be
I'm not even sure that didn't even feel like an open mic like a wedding reception
Corporate event
Yeah
That's so that was in the sequel
That's right
Harper Lee didn't want to be published
Smart choice on her part
What's your b b b b b b
Stylist easy Chicago
Adele I found out
Something you know in many ways I'm still this small-town boy sure you know
Shake Shack
By the lights of
Exiting
Can renew your registration in your car
Registration to just like a f****** currency exchange
What yeah I didn't know that I had no idea I'm going to the DMV every year for
I mean until they did the mailing things or whatever but I've been going to the DVD of me more than I need to do that's interesting
I guess that's
The currency exchanges probably have to diversify a little bit
If they're allowed to do that
Your underground registration ring
Is run through f****** West
Union or whatever
Yeah you slap them on your plate you're good
4 minutes
Wow is also pretty good timing for a currency
A couple times
That 4 minutes
Was enough time for a bunch of people to fill in the line behind me who are not going to take four minutes
Good timing my friend yeah I worked out to go pick up the new place
Person to this day
Episode to go over we're flipping this one
Because big news happened in Iran September 8th 2020
Me too
We lost the queen
Queen is out of play
Turns out
Cyberspace
Bye-bye
It is now bye-bye time
I don't think anyone could put it as poetically
5 x 5
It was happening 2019
Was Alex's take on the queen at that point
Absolutely
No whose
Air switch
Economy
Mama
World
Chaffey front
As usual
With the last
Be at this was a the queen had voted not to
Suspend Parliament stand this was Alex
Sega chaconpay.
And it's a great way to memorialize the Queen's leg
Retrospect 19 sounded maybe like Alex's
I was working on something but fell apart
Little bit rough
The Ender so he had a pretty
Positive impression of the Queen for a Day
Hated her
Before that
After that day
Try sometimes we got to throw out possible narratives
Hey baby maybe this ball will
We'll start rolling and we'll get the
The queen of the secret Patriot agent
What Bill Barr it just seems like it's always been a step too far for me
Any
NE Patriots
The line should at the
Bass B
No no Royal
Like no Royals
That's the Baseline it really seems
Contradictory to the very idea comes from
So we'll get to this she does not pass away until
A bit into the show so we'll get to
To see a little bit of what Alex was up to beforehand
Gas boiler
Super races
And then we'll see how he feels.
So first I love my nugget more than anything in the universe but I guess my stinky a fuckboy to thank you so much
Juvenile policy
Choosing to believe that's about pets
Text Rob do more like Rob don't
Thank you so much you and I'll probably walk
Celine was a DND God what would her domains be just asking
What does that mean
When I did the DND
I read a lot about it and then I was like I have
I cannot understand all of this so then I made up all the rules if you'll recall I was really hoping that you would have a definition for them
I'm going to go with the place whereabouts they hang
And if Selene her domain would be I think
Wisdom
Sure let's say that
I made a dreamy creamy in my pants this summer thank you so much you're now policy walk
Yeah next Mister Kiley appreciate
Selma's not gross
No
Here where Alex starts
Excited
Something he did
Just before he got on a
Literally 10 minutes ago
Before the show started
Hour-long interview
Now the most man man in the world
Univision.com it's brother
He's a really smart guy in or misrepresenting who he is
Is there scared of male leadership
Tomorrow
The interview
The Friday show
And Monday
Wow
Call court for Monday
You in full
Illinois
Check it out as well cuz we have
Very exciting got to promote and Advance this Andrew Tate interview
He's a like I guess he was a former fighter martial arts kind of got you
Came out like a number of years ago and
Not real
Get over it losers that narrows our dad Flash
Has become something
Of a chauvinist icon
Aggressive misogyny
Social media influencer type use on Tik-Tok
Dumbfucks
Just one of those people who's in the places where I'm never not but also there's like Trevor and I are always on that.
Never there but there's actually like Billy
Make a big deal out of interviewing Andrew
It really just highlights how legitimate
Alex is about his principles and how is business model isn't mostly desperately trying to
He can get attention for associating with
Real piece of s*** and all you really need to know about him is that he's led the UK to go to Romania admits
Allegations of him abusing women
He began to operate a webcam site where you had women lie to men to scam them out of money would you like to his home being
Rated by Romanian police quote
Following a tip-off from the US Embassy
Set a 21 year old American woman was being held
Against her will
Wait he's
He did that in the past
Yeah fairly recently
WhatsApp
Okay
This is now becoming ongoing human trafficking investigation which is totally one of the issues that Alex
Tears about very much
The Super Series
About
Pennyweight is hot right now because it got kicked off all the social media sites and he was on Tucker show to complain about it fairly
Recently as well
Allegedly
He might have been kicked off the social media sites because he's a violent misogynist whose content breach various platforms
The service but he might have also been kicked off for coordinated abuse of the platform itself
He runs a thing called Hustlers University which is basically a pyramid scheme where he teaches young man how to scam people about things like
Cryptocurrency
There are a bunch of allegations that threw his following he engaged in coordinated efforts to manipulate algorithms to boost
This content
With tons of fake accounts and things like that stupid Moriarty that's what's happening
I'm sort of center of the dumbest
Screw around ring that there's been
F****** crack
When is whether it's because of hateful ideology or because of abusing the platform anyone
Plenty of reason to kick and rotate off their site
And at the moment he's getting tons
Attention
Might be right for the
The picking now that it's harder to get teeth content online
So I thought I would see a prime opportunity
Try and scoop up some of these disaffected youth fit
Now the phone is radicalized vultures are circling trying to pick apart the car
Cats of that body
People who are going to be willing to give this fellow platform
Text coming in
Barely just a bunch of people coming in like hey do you want to make a lateral move to Infowars
Or whatever you want yeah it's like okay we've disrupted
Essentially
The business model
Andrew Tate was operator
He doesn't have these social media algorithms
The game and scam people
And so essentially that hustle is over
But he does have a currency
And that is the number of people who
He has turned into rabid followers
Essentially what you doing is
Trying to sell those followers to somebody
Yeah and I Alex's
Willing
Yeah
Yeah man
Yeah it's fun how often the audience
Is the product
Now they are happy about it
Make no mistake about it too though like this isn't a new thing
Because of his
Troubling views
Yeah that would make
So Alex gets into some headlines of some stuff
And it's like I said
Fairly racist
And by the way I love black people
Wonderful black people
Butter.
The really evil horrible wipers
Charles really evil horrible black person
My person
What
You've got racial attacks going on around the u.s.
Black-on-white now it's 21 or higher
Tortured and murdered
Crazy racist black people
But the media
Goes out there and do something evil it is the top
Story everywhere
White person is guilty
Muslim
You don't blame the bus you don't blame the truck you blame who did it but they try to surprise
What globalist
New World Order
Wait what
When he gets arrested
George Soros
Lady teacher
Division are pushing
The first things first Alex is just making up numbers when he says that the incident so black-on-white racially motivated crimes has gone
From 10 to 1 to 20 21
That's just him pushing the white identity
We fear that essentially Powers his shows ideology
We've gone over this a hundred times so I'm not going to get too deep into it again but what Alex is doing here is just pushing a very standard White
Supremacist talking point that many view as one of the most
Defective gateways towards radicalizing people
It's a deeper races
Famously it was lies about racial crime
6 put out by the Council of conservative citizens that Dylan roof cited as being the thing that began his path
Store carrying out his races
Does mass murder
There was a black man who is charged with the murder of a white teacher in Memphis
That's true but it's not clear that it was a racially motivated
The crime
Was black man who carried out a shooting spree recently but that was also something that I would approve had a racial motive a
He doesn't care about the actual crime
Need to seize any crime where the perpetrator is black and the victim is white
Is happening
Cuz the victim is white
This is shockingly consistent and Alex's ideology over the years and it's because he was a deeply racist purse
Also to his point of whether or not you know if there were white man who kidnapped black women and how is that did happen
It would be the biggest deal ever
I would ask him or Imo's
The people in his audience if they know who Joshua Edwards
And the answer is likely no
He was a member of the Aryan Brotherhood who kidnapped and raped a black woman in 2019 ultimately being sentenced in 20
I've never heard Alex bring that up
I don't think that's a something that is
You plastered all over headlines
It doesn't appear that he's particularly interested in black women being among it's not V
Highest percentage of
Victimized groups in the in the f****** country
Robert David
Fight
What's 230 years in prison in late 2021 for kidnapping a 14 year-old black girl he'd met online taking her across
State lines and sexually abusing
Or Wayne Marcel who paid someone
2000 dollars to take that same tiled from
Bikes home
Texas to Illinois
Where you picked her up and took her
Connecticut
Explicitly for the purposes of sexually abusing
Here's the thing though
These are horrific crimes where the perpetrator was white and the victim was black but even in the case where the guy was in the area and bruh
Brotherhood you would have to work
To prove that the crime he committed was motivated by race
Possible and you might make that assumption but it isn't guaranteed even though
He clearly is a race
And these are cases that Alex has never heard of a client directly in the face of the reality that he wants to portray for his audience
If anything he said meant anything these names would be household names
But they're not
Anyway I was just a racist Chinese bush
Standard white supremacist.
I mean those are those are like
Legit
Reconstruction Era South propaganda
This would be like man you're going
A little bit too hard
Status f*****'-a
Insane is every reason to understand the dynamic here and how
These talking points have been used historically
That's just too
We've been desensitized to it so much
But like that is literally
Hey you bring that straight from the Civil War
Into
Today
That is what that is
So ask her is I mean to this is just
Did this is s***
And the truth is
Real persecutions country is The Unborn
It is
Murder and torture and killing of white people
A suppressor story
She deserves it
Chicago
Oakland
Bug other black people
White people
Suppressing any story heavy coverage of the case of this teacher from Memphis Eliza Fletcher on all major
Media Outlet
When Alex says that the story is being
Suppressed what do you mean somebody's mad that the media isn't covering it as a
The crime committed by a black man against a white woman because
She was white
This is also a
Classic white supremacist talking point that racist crimes against white people are intentionally being suppressed
Alex deploys these talking points
Because they're effective
And because he's a race
Also that clip he's talking about from the New Black Panther Party I believe it if I recall correctly is clip of Khalid
Muhammad who died in 2001
Right right here
All over the place
You were saying the weirdest emphasizing there is a little bit of that it's true but it may even cuz I was listening to this like well he's swinging
Yeah yeah
Rudy's notably
Over
For him today
Yeah I mean indeed
It is such like
That is the attack be
The only Avenue
For that you went out with so many
Of these
People have to look around and be like
Why am I hearing about all these race
White people and not enough about people who are racist towards White
People and there's an obvious answer
But you can't
Do that
So instead they're like
Because they're suppressing
I see that makes way more sense then
But statistics and a
Massive history of this country working together
Now
You know you want to convey the feeling that you're under attack
By the author
Or whatever
Convey to the audio
Healing
Is what he wants to exploit
Venues engro
And if you want to look into
These feelings that you have
Maybe you don't find
The information
Then Alex would be
You know presenting it so you should be able to find all this stuff the reason is because it's being surprised
Steve Carell
Very fact
And it works for every group
Anyway Alex's easier on this
But I robbed one of the producers are just so happens to be black
Washing of white supremacy
We're all being targeted for lawlessness
Letting black people specifically
Specifically
Safety at
I'm sure I don't need to explain that the safety act
It doesn't make it so black people
Crimes in Illinois is Alex seems to be implying
I do want to point out that the ID
See if there are evil Jewish Puppet Masters who are getting minorities to attack white people is a Hallmark
Arc of white supremacist propaganda
I want to put too fine a point on this year but this episode is
Extreme even by Alex's standards
The beginning is
Really
Chock full of white supremacist tropes
Straight up if you if this was a k if it's a clan meeting
This is what you would hear
And you were here also the Edward on top of that so normal
Would be there
Like all good KKK rally we we shipped a little bit here
Alex has got some news he wants to cover
Harrison Smith
Padres
Can
Farewell little
Brian Humpty Dumpty stealth
I'm not mad at the key
It's not always easy being on the outside
Scrutinized and judged not having anybody tell you what to say
Sometimes I wonder
Converse shoes with a steady
Good stuff
Wow
Harrison could never get hired at any media outlet that
Legitimate because he sucks
He does bad work
Infowars is literally the only place that has standards low enough to hire him and he's only on air because David Knighton
Cheticamp to a fight now it's
Spire Deva
Like
Your your laughable
Fifth string
Behind David knife
Yeah you are only on are because like
Metaphorically
Six quarterbacks got injured absolutely
Absolutely
Just a badger look like
Harrison Smith if he worked at CNN would be hosting the primetime
Is the f*** out of here like one of those
The car dealership commercial people being my Blitzer
It's one of like those know Bob Rohrman being like man that f******
Jon Hamm narration over those Mercedes commercials or whatever
He's f******
Sucks they need the Roar
Robin does good work
That's because you chose to be a dissident but he's not
Easy path
What's up you think of his rocks mad that he thinks he's great at commercial this is all fun and games
It's cute but this
This High School AV project
Shuffle music video they're playing
This it's nonsense is so much easier to be in the mainstream media
If it's a message that
It's fun for them
But it's Hollow it's meaningless I made that video on VHS when I was 12
Yep.
It's a little bit
Maudlin
Childish
Also has weeks old by now seems a little bit
Makes you guys really look like Petty losers
Like I said you've got maybe two days
To turn that around and get it out and have it be relevant and funny
Now it is just sad
I also noticed that the first stanza of that song as a reference
This is because it was produced by Harrison Smith
Steam and he's
Much more clearly aligned with the young white identity folks like the Fuentes community so this is to be expected
Babies continuing the theme hero
Pretty races
Contact yeah we're going we're going with racial buttons
Quite a bit
The show
Sound system actual news
It's not till
Good thing the queen died otherwise. Nothing
Yeah
Aveda
It's harsh
Guitars
So that was a mister act on my part that was going to get to the news but you cook
Play Harris
Art project
Right
Actual news
I don't dislike
Because she's all part of this new ruling class
Were you have to either be a woman or be a homosexual
Power and then
President is a white
Really gross stuff I'm not going to stay on air
Investigating it last night
Because I didn't want to go down that rabbit hole
Yeah he stopped investigating cuz there wasn't
He is just
Gay man who is the Deputy
Rob Monk
Epoch score
Mater
And there's a picture of him wearing like a like a button-up shirt and then underneath there's like
Harness yeah the harness that looks like a pentagram
Sure and so this is now he is deeply involved in Satan
Of all the things that you might
Like when you're on your way to med school at the end you're never going to be like well I'm probably going to be the sea
Center of a monkey box
Conspiracy theory
Yeah
Sorry I find this to be a little thin
I don't understand Alex's conception that you have to be a woman or a homosexual to be in a position
The power
You know I feel like that's a talking point
He just deployed
2 attack
V
The people who happen to be women or homosexual
The power because he doesn't like that
That seems
Crazy wasn't like that happening at all it's not like a genuine observation
I think it's not
Okay that's crazy
So you're saying that he's looking at things and then making it up on his own
I know that's
It's not in his character
Foreign to us but yes
Here Alex gets really gross about this dude
This sucks
And is very
Cuz I didn't want to go down that rabbit hole
Destructive
Stop
Really hurtful things to his own body
Course
Photos of him in the past
Family August
He's into things like
Eating
That's so delicious
What are you talkin about
What is a real new thing
Like this is not something that I remember Alex doing
Pastimes
Like equating
Being gay with eating poop
I think we're in full regression
Turning big like we were joking about him being only capable of
Children's level thought for me
I think he's now actually descending back in
Into a larva
Allstate
Thick particularly virulent anti-gay propaganda hate speech to the Past
Involved like they eat poop
Regression to like more
Explicit big
Hey Mike straight
Points that are much more at home
In
Places
A little bit
No you go back to public 1998 and s*** like that and you just
You think about what was okay to just
Toss about
Yeah it's crazy
He rang its back everything old is New Again
Alex gets word
It's not good with the queen
Sure and
He doesn't really care
I don't wish the old Queenie
Who's about as British
Transylvanian vampire bat
She's dead
Was founded
In Defiance
Disgusting to sit there and watch TV
Worship
That is not what freedom is all about America's all about now should tell you that
I mean no no it's so ridiculous anyways let's
Think about how many presidents and their sons president
John Quincy Adams
Wasn't there another one
Don't think so I think that Adam things right
I don't know Transylvania bloodline
Yeah
Taft was actually his son was
Clinton I don't know a big stretch
Well I mean
Just egg
Throw it more towards the end established aristocracy
We can agree there's an established aristocra
In terms of like Kennedy's in
Clinton's and multiples
Yeah for sure there aren't there are sort of legacies or or whatever
Dynasty type
Actually president
Yeah you're right you're right we got Harrison was the grandson of William Henry Harris
Right right right
James Madison and Zachary Taylor were second cousins enough for Horseshoes and Hand Grenades
Does they say the fifth cousin of Teddy Roosevelt
Just a cousin
I don't have any of this is
Fully accurate I just Googled it misses on facts of monster so monster wouldn't leave me
Me wrong any anything over to cousins does
Account for me
Just doesn't count
Everything over
So the second hour is the guy who
Wow and you've got a book
Out
He's promoting
Actually comes out tomorrow so we've been doing this to pre-orders
One of the things that the enemy wants us to believe is that were isolated or that were alone or that name of the
The people that share our values and our worldview are are very small in number but
Is it is true we may copy no eighty-two 90% of this country
DC and in Silicon Valley and New York City
Country right now
Worldview and their values are diametrically opposed to us
Christian nationalism
There were explicitly Christian countries for the first 200 years
Those weren't countries those are
4 colonies
And that was
Our country Constitution that we
Because people say this is this dumb thing
Where words don't actually mean the things I mean you know like
We heard like
Dave daubenmire coach Davis talk about being a white nationalist
Understanding is a compound noun
Being a nationalist
Who is Christian is not the same thing as being a Christian nationalist
That's right torba is very
Explicitly
I don't think
Unknowingly trying to blur that
I mean yeah
And the thing that is so
Stupid that is so so so stupid
Is that
Keep saying Christian
Everybody keep saying Christian
Everybody keep saying Christian but with you did get a Christian Nation
With Christian ideals or whatever
You don't know what f****** are empower
You don't take it you know people think all its Christian Nationals you don't know if it's a
Catholic christian nationalism if you don't know if it's a presbyterian Christian nationalism a does
I think he does too based on his definition I think he knows
Anyone else you're all insane to me
Yeah and I think that's their particular brand of Christianity is not super mainstream
Some elements are perhaps a little bit more Fringe
Yeah I eventually leave
Good thing
That is that is wrong lesson
I think
I think it would be interesting
If you did have a Christian nationalism that was based around like
I don't know
Giving to the poor
Most of these people wouldn't even be an interesting version of it that's not what they would want
Berean Christian Nation like what eats it's so silly to me how many it
Sir divisions there are in that
Concept of the block
Christianity
And yet when it comes to electoral politics people are willing to
To go along with cristianismo what the f****** word
Crazy
It is it is a big subset of subset
So anyway they want to create a Christian
That's basically it
And that is Christian nationalism
To them
They're trying to
The two things
Blend together are being Christian and being nationalist
Which I think most people would view as like
Alright good for you
Being a Christian nationalist which I don't think most people would be okay with big eyes
Has to do with
Christians being in charge of literally everything about
The house the country runs
A country run by Christian rock Christian rule
And that is not under Sharia law
And that's what torba and Alex want
Sleepwalking
Engaged
In public discourse
Christianity was religious
We let people practice their own religion we don't make them convert
Pretty well encapsulate Alex's ideology
He doesn't believe in America everyone is able to practice their religion or lack of religious belief freely
He believes that Christians are right and should be in charge
Because they're so nice to everyone else to practice their religion
That's what he believes it's so nice of the correct
Religion to have the
The benevolence necessary to allow people to worship
False gods and safe
Magus this is nonsense and it's not religious freedom or tolerance
Having a belief system like this
Strongly implies that it's some point if they could stop allowing people to practice certain religions
And they would be well within
The right to do so
Obviously if that happened it would be because of particular religion
Just gone too far and taking their Christian tolerance for weakness
At least that's how it would be easy to sell it under this framework inalienable
Rights are things
It can be taken away front
I personally find it hard to believe that Alex actually believe any of this living light living on since he saying
He's very consistent in expressing his belief that all Islam is radical and incompatible with the West
He constantly yells about Satanist to be pedophiles who drink children's blood
He believes that atheists are secretly trying to
Dehumanize people from their connection with God so they'll be tricked into transhuman
He may believe the people in the US only have religious freedom because Chris
They're nice enough to let them but
He doesn't want that to be the case
If you even half the chance he would almost certainly try to Outlaw these religions
And probably others
It'll be so easy for him to rationalize considering these super clear that his enemies are all in League with the literal BL
Those above
Do load of b******* and it's
It's not a great sign.
The first hour of the show's been essentially a white supremacist talking point fast
And now the dude who runs a Twitter clone that's
Swamp with bigots is onto longer the term Christian nationalism
This is outrageous
I mean I know I know I just made this point but I can't stress it enough
If this type of Christianity is allowed to make a quote Christian Nation
You will not be allowed to practice
Your type of Christianity if it does not share it a bit you're just an apostate you're you're a f******
You're you're an Infidel like this short walk
Yes it's a very short walk to that there is no
National religion
Cuz your f***
So we get to the point where Alec
X finds out that the queen has died
And
Tour buses in in
In the mix
Play the Queen is out of play and Alex
This is got to rest
Husband
Is a particularly deadly virus
Cuz I love the queen so much
Do you think he could
Between
That's really what I'm hoping right now
The Audubon Society that he told
Boy challenge
He told Reuters
He said he want to come back
The lower population
You have nothing
Batteries
That is insane
Also there was a children's book
Type of thing where the key if I were an animal is this and then
It was published
In about like the it was cited some articles
Monster Energy
And it wasn't about killing off Humanity was much more thoughtful answer than that
Butter Alex Evans
Anyway probably maybe
Prince Philip
Came back as a virus
Just to selectively take out his wife weird
Weird that we can go from like
Because Christianity is right to Alex genuinely being concerned about reincarnation like
Listen man I hope this isn't how it works is that you know what happens when you
You died I think you're right if we're to take this to mean anything right
I think in reality Alex
Spinning his wheels
Suburbans got to take
Queen
Queen Elizabeth the second making the Jeopardy
Jesus Christ is our Lord and savior
Now it says it's unfortunate they're so much going on now
Important decision that you can make in your life
In our world there's there's so much uncertainty
I've heard Andrew torba on Alex's show before
It wasn't
This feels like okay this is your committed to this
Not to say that he wasn't
Christian before anything but
It seems like this is
To become
A big front
Center
It's it's it's
Creepy to the point where it's like that.
Team that goes away to Bible camp for a week and then comes back and there's like I've got the
Power of the Holy
Play spirit
Perspective though of like The Queen Is Dead I hoped
She found God or whatever it is
As benign as a response to the queen dying can be condescending bulshit
Condescending bulshit we all get used to our grandparents sing the praying for us
That's true I hope it gave her life over to Satan
Is rocket
Inhale right now next
Barbie doll rocking out with Bowie
You believe the king of Mars God damn well that's
So Alex for someone who is
Above it all
I have some interesting like
A preoccupation with Palace intrigue
That becomes the new king
Prince Charles
Prince Charles's mr. reset New World Order
World government
Bypass
Prince Charles
Make a prediction right now I may be wrong
But I think Prince Charles is going to be seen as the king of England
Will say something like for two years while his son gets ready
Charles
No s*** Prince Charles is going to become king
Talking about it's very clear the order of a song called I mean endless it if they're just going to start changing
What about the royal family now
The word where you started is get rid of them entirely well Charles would have to abdicate
Like
Possible but
To throne immediately
Change the rules that's why they still have the Royal Family
Is
Defining is
Ceremony
Almost
To a point that is beyond reason reach of it
The glue that holds
Together
The British Society
The queen it all falls apart
I love him thinking that he's taking a swing there
I think it's going to be Charles good for you babe
Can you plug.
Suffocate figs
Have no election or
Charlie TV Kamala Harris who are they they're probably Hillary
I think Charles did say something not too long ago about not wanting
2bk
There was something along those lines but that doesn't change
The order of Ascension unless he takes himself out of it
But here we are a part of the agreement with the royal families they also don't really have that much control over what they
To do
They're held captive at their own royalty
So
Andrew seems to want to talk about stuff and Alex seems to want to
No just music about the
The Royals
The grace of God we did it in and we're still standing
Supporters
Bravo
Jimmy Savile died in 2011
What
Jimmy Savile
The Jimmy Savile that I recall they be hosted like it was over pedophile
For like 40 years and everybody kind of tacitly was like
He's so good at hosting
Yeah I don't know if Alex knows he's dead
Yeah it seems like he does not
And I don't think it doesn't sound like that either
So dumb
Oh boy
So Alex said goes to break
Says farewell to torba comes back
Ding dong the witch is dead but
I got to say they did not keep it upright and so there is a long portion where the munchkins are talk
Talking about confirming whether the witch is dead or not at the
They could have cut off at least a minute and a half of it
YouTube clip I think so
Do not have a good start point
So I've eliminated that
I also don't want to get a copyright
Strike from The Wizard of Oz
John
Play ding dong the witch is dead
Hillary Clinton
What has officially said she's not running for president
I don't think we needed her stance
She's got
Maybe it
So she said she
She's not going to run which means she is but also maybe she's not cuz he has health problems but also his
Entire narrative during the
The 2016 election was that she was on death's door
So I don't know this yeah
Listen I'll tell you what to predict your buddy I don't think Hillary has much of a choice as to whether or not she was going to run
Brother 2024 I think America decided that she was done running
Probably half
I think
I think it's fun though for Alex
Text to be like this guy who really just knows his s*** gets cut through the b******* and he'll tell you the when Hillary says she's
Not running I mean that she is rather
She could be dead
Why don't you talk
Nothing happening here
The midterms well what happened in the midterms change whether or not Hillary Clinton is a tachyon forgot to keep plate
So much
I hated Selma
My chats annoying
Has been teasing a special guest in the third hour
Vagina vagina
Come on baby
Queen news from the picture
He killed her
Tell you how disappointed I was with the reveal of who the special guest was
A special guest here with us and shower and take some calls
Chrissie mayr
Mayyr
North Austin comedian
Chrissie mayr wow
She's hosted the War Room for Owen
Alliance Data
She was at the airport Studio to tweeted a picture of herself sitting on Alex's desk
The caption quote
My stripper name is Sandy Hook
See it's funny
Because Alex defamed grieving parents whose children were murdered in Sandy Hook and now there is willingly associated with Alex
Using his platform
Promoter stand-up career
Itsfunneh
Yeah I mean
If that is the problem with the zoo crew radio not really having the effect on bringing people out to
The shows as much
What is a used to you know you got to go out to different radio station
People are trying you know people are trying to
Fox Business
Seeing if they can get people out. Feld
City
Comedy Club
Now we got to go on Infowars
Forgot
City Comedy Club
She'll be there all weekend buddy no just Thursday
Just got to say she seems cool
She seems really cool
Hear the podcast called the Chrissy Maher podcast just this
Year she's had Alex Stein that don't roll on twice
Owen Benjamin
Savannah Hernandez
Brandon straka who's a guest
So that's cool man
What Infowars employee one dude who snitched to the feds about his involvement in January 6th
One sexual assault troll everyone guy who's too much of an athlete to be allowed to host the fourth hour of Alex's show
Good stuff good
Good crew
Videos of her actual stand-up coming up in search results. Find a video where she pretend
Greta thunberg
That's cool I bet that
Hilarious
It seems like there's plenty of blogpost though about how hard it is for her to be a stand-up comic
Supported Trump
And was against vaccine mandates
Masks for
Audience isn't comedy shows
Early on the pandemic and we have seen so many of those
He also recorded an album called live from January 6th
Because of course I she was there
That day when the Patriot
The capital G friends with
Jay Johnson
And like I was
Like what
I tried to find that I'm not sure when that was but
I wonder
She probably
IMDb page a number of appearances on redbar radio with Mike David
AutoZone
Scuzz.
I'm glad I don't have to be mean to her stand-up and I can
Just be mean to her as a person
I would have liked
To I would like to see some of the stand-up
I was trying to play her album on iHeart
Yeah that's me to sign in and I couldn't
I like I I'm
I'm not going Spotify for this if we've been on iHeart we're not going to play iHeart
She's she's got some thoughts I mean
It's a lot of just like hey I agree with all the stuff you're saying Alex
Hooray
Well I mean there is some point or she's she's making stuff that's clearly Lionel being fun
What else has
Undermine
There's a diner in Virginia
Where's the country club
It had a 911 themed
Menu
This is called tone deaf
Such as chocolate
Ponder flatbread
Basically for it
Descontrol demolicious haha
Menu with some pot names for things like
Some of the stuff that they were going to be serving on the
Anniversary of 9/11
2977 chowder which is a reference to the number of people who died
And flat
Responder flatbread like his the building fell on them yeah it's pretty f****** disrespectful
I made I made plenty of 911 jokes sure but I mean that's tomorrow
That's just bad
Yeah
When I was in college
This back when I smoked a lot of weed
I wanted to throw a 911 theme party in like 2003 so my idea was going to have like a 9
Layer dip
An 11 layer dip would be beside which is better bongs with lighters decorated to look like playing
But guess what man
As a complete idiot nineteen-year-old edging
Pothead even I decided that it was maybe something that sounded kind of funny in my head it was like a little subversive
The act of doing it would be
Be dumb and shity
Imagine
I guess this person who ran the runzas restaurant didn't quite make it to that point
Just felt like the viral Buzz
You get from the backlash was worth doing it anyway
Country Club
People are all psycho
Whatever the case this is meaningless s*** but it's kind of what you
Comedian comes on Infowars
You have attention-grabbing headlines from like
The Daily Mail or New York daily news and then your Riff on them in a way that's supposed to be about some larger point but it's
Really just an opportunity to make some puns you feel or pushing
Boundaries
Make you feel dangerous and anti-establishment
Pretty dumb stuff is exactly what you were talking about though it's like the Infowars version of that zoocrew radio tab people have
It is terribly about these 911
New things that are Maybe tone-deaf
This is the new story of the day what do you think about this
What are you doing
Also come on
Your comedian theoretically
Spell it
You got a f****** cell if you're going to say demolicious
And not be a sad loser
You got to try and sell your ass off for that
I guess
They do a little bit more of this run
On rhythm
The building 7 Seafood Tower
We should have like an inside
Inside pajamas get better waves
Tragedy
Pretty boring
Apologizing
Explain into it
Midterm 61 days how my God
Great transition from Alex
I'm also Alex
We are making fun of the people who died
Yeah Charter in the flatbread those are
Specifically about people who died
And so I mean
I guess you probably don't want to defend that because it's
Yeah more fun for you to fall back on me
We're making fun of the deep State being involved even though you'd
Can't really back that up in any meaningful way without nobody pushes you on it
Yes it is more fun because it is looking at this as it actually it is there's really no other
Conclusion to come to other than this
To do this
It's not
It's not worth like
F****** going crazy over it's a dumb
It's a dumb restaurant
I'd like
You don't have to do this nobody forced you nobody had a gun to your head put yourself in the position of
Somebody who may be lost
Family members
And imagine how they would
Experiencing
Baby Alive a little bit of an idea of whether or not it's a good idea
Okay thank you should be allowed to touch within your right
To do this
F****** shity
Yeah I mean great
Batman
Guy wants to apologize in order to preserve
Some sort of
Decency good for him but
I don't know
Anyway
I don't believe
I can't believe we're still talk
Some thoughts
The midterm 61 days out
Just trying to
Pull down and hold on to whatever they can
They just completely lose and
Interesting to see
What happened
Kathy hochul in New York
Then I thought they would be
Encouraging such as the New Yorker
A testament to the kind of Grassroots involvement we're looking
I hear look no further than the name recognition and ads
Secrecy is doing for
Some guy named Ali
Who's running in New York
Chrissy doesn't seem to know his name until she's reminded later but she
She's talked about Lee zeldin who's running against Kathy hochul for the governorship
Who became Governor when quavo resigned in August 2021 and is now running for re-election and put simply this guy like
Likely is not putting up good
Uncle is ahead by double-digits in the polls in this seat is considered a very safe Democrat fix
This is what you would expect
Given that someone who's promoting his candidacy on the national media platform doesn't even know his name
Yeah
Never heard of it. That's a guy who's probably going to lose my double digits
Never heard of him but apparently
He's putting the fear of Christian nationalist got into the damn yet also I mean
Do polling
Dinner has been coming out is looking pretty
Pretty good for Democrats
In terms of the midterms
And I willing to admit that
Some of my impressions
The ways that it could go
After the Rovers Wade's I definitely had a perspective that it could
Have a negative
Demotivating effect on Democratic voters is absolutely not the case I'm glad to see that
Yeah but you look like
Did there's a fairly decent Ram
Better than
Unexpected
And
Is my picture
Against the law to talk about midterms
Isn't it for it until 30 days before voting
I can't imagine what's going to happen in the next 60 days
Infowars Metro, and it should be against
The law
No one should even be allowed
Did politician is not with is there a f****** heads down at a desk working
And said they're campaigning month
Before the midterms
F*** off
Get out of here just don't know about Lee
I really
Really don't
So
Interview becomes a little bit of a discussion
About
The evils of
Abdominis
Sure why not
Okay I have some thoughts about the way that this anti-feminism or the opposition to feminism is Express
Because I think that there is
Something
Here that isn't
It's not productive
Time somebody is
Cancel.
Mortuary
Monday
Because he just like heaven Samuel they're offering up something
You know
People to be sheets
Brampton
Do all the things that don't make
All of humanity
Potential
Make sandwiches
They just
Chinese women as there
Front person
Women are easier to
That's why it helps
Send
Graduated
Short hair like
They're stealing your power
Sota Tuesday ignore the clear attempt at jokes in this clip like the part about women's natural skills being like making sandwiches
Good old-fashioned open-mic level joking around
Going to do what you do
I do think that there's an interesting perspective the Chrissy is expressing here though a type of
It's coming through as a little troubling
According to her telling of this she was into feminism in college which
She seems to characterize as her having
Open short hair and not wanting to get married or have kids
That's fine I guess but I don't think those things
Anyone who's being serious we considered Central pillars of feminism
Maybe just so skated with some people who are feminists I guess but
Something core
Yeah Chrissy also expresses that she believes that women are easier to psyop
Which seems to imply that
She herself was the target of the
Is feminism siop in that you fell for it
Would you like to the behavior that she's describing
In college
Thankfully she's a comic so she hangs out with a lot of guys
Sewer life easy to say
Through hanging out with these cool dude Comics who are targets of a psyop she was able to break free of the
Conditioning that led her to
Feminism
Honestly it sounds like what she's describing is that she
She took on a feminist aesthetic
In college was not popular with the men there
So in order to adapt and be accepted she adopted a new athletic that was more socially approved
The way it sounds this really doesn't mean anything about the validity or zapping that's a feminism
Really just more about how many stand-up spaces
Are heavily date kept by dudes who don't like feminists so worse
Incidentally along with these right wing ding dongs on her podcast
The cheese at bud
Drive like share
Owen Benjamin
Christie is also had a number of sex workers as guest
And I would
Suggested something she might want to do is reflect a little bit about why it is that sex work is growing in except
Done for the United States
What would the lives of the sex workers look like in a Christian nationalist
Country like the one the person she's talking to wants to bring into being
What are what are the things that you don't
Seem to think about a lot that are Z fruits
Of the work of feminist
Over history
I mean
But this is
This is the
Quintessential version of that like
I want
What's the popularity and notoriety that I can
Can get from being a woman in this space
And I
Definitely would rather die than live in the world that these people that I'm in the space of
Want to create
Like she
Absolutely.
Let the foundation of women in comedy is entirely based on
Hey we were oppressed our entire f****** lives in this is all Bulls
It isn't it
That's the entire Foundation
Enterprising
Strong feminist voices in boundaries
Entirely about how
Lucy was f***** over on The Daily you know that's where my God
Otherwise we have more
The Dick Van Dyke
Left
To the devices of the people who aren't being psyop
And her
Serta conception
She wouldn't be
Headlining Cap City comedy club on a
Speaking out loud in front of a male presence
It's
I mean
I don't want to be I don't want to be dismissive or to like
Do shity about it but I just think
Perspective is not really fully cook
Quite frankly
I think
I think it's a little surface love
This Foundation to this opposition of feminism
Kind of
I just don't think there's a strong Foundation
Does air conditioner in this window by myself
It's so easy to beat
Wow
Better Together
The government wants to do another mayonnaise
Props and things to my fiance
I was just coming out of my like this
Loot Guide Me In
3 clear her fiance is not Frank Pellegrino the actor who is dead
He's the Arabs to Pellegrino water
I think I just I find this to be so empty because I am aware of and
No many feminists
Kennywood
Be like
Oh no my principles have been corrupted by asking for help with something
Please don't
Seem to beat these seem to be hockey joke joke as opposed to a like anything
Real it's a hack joke
Bay by a dude, kin the 80s and then Rosanna rose up like a f******
Nightmare for these people and was like
And then I bought a f****** fan
Cuz I don't need you know like it was in it did you take it another Direction otherwise it
Stupid
I don't know I don't know
Yep it's tough to take this too seriously
For sure
I called
Let's talk about
Yeah yeah let's talk about Martin Lawrence on Def Jam in the 80s really get into those
That's really get into Martin Lawrence in the 80s
That subject
Come on
Jesus people harass you because it's a compliment
To you I mean just I don't I don't I don't know
On the one hand
You have
Someone who's looking
Median and so you would expect
Humor
Sure to be the way that you're communicating
Put at the same time
This is in the context of
Seemingly trying to make
Make points
It doesn't feel like they're bad they're not well constructed
So I don't have much to work with you
It is a combination of the terrible writing that they that Comics do for a clapter
And then also the terrible writing that they do for joke
Eliciting Nizer laughs
Nor clapping
Alex seems to like
Not be getting the Chrissy's also
She's trying to be funny
Is there is an attempt at humor and
In some spaces I could see you this being
I can see some people sense of humor being
Haha women can install an air conditioner delivery
Yeah
What are you going to do when you're sitting next to the worst
Team partner in the world
Do you feel about the midterm stand
Look I was trying to have a chauvinistic anti-feminist joke riff going
To ask me about the fish
Oh my God
This is great this is
It's like next level
Together is a ritual
This is big-time
Wow
Like I'm excited out with other comic
Hope my p**** gets hired again
Well we're out here.
You're going to head back to that green room
Where I belong
I think
Take that
We're all going to die
Play Percy Jackson position of respect
I think that
Feminism is not about random handjobs
Maybe it's about people being okay with
If that's what you want to do go for it
You know but it's not like
I don't know if they're family spaces that are like
Subway
I don't want to
Give random handjobs look you can't come
I'll tell you this Elizabeth Cady Stanton
Very against random handjob
0 random handjobs
We're giving out
What's in the early days of feminist
That's just drew
I just drove down this is this is an educational for me
Mary wolf
Rolled up into hating
Random handjob
31 last clip here cuz they take some calls
And collar
Perspective
And this is
Not good
There's there's a reason Andrew take out
Man he promotes Hatteras
Sexuality
Making money
Massillon
Will you make something out of this
Talk about reason take got banned from YouTube
Nothing but
Steers and queers and I don't see any horns
That's funny hahaha funny
It's not
No
Also
Paki also implies that there's only gay people and
Cows
No I don't see a lot of cows on there
I-41
I believe he was being insulting towards women
Oh that's interesting I didn't hear cuz I mean Betty things come for Texas
Right now like it's the
Raptor
Because men aren't allowed on there so he doesn't see any horns
You see what I'm saying
This is I could be mistaking that
No I mean
I'm not sure I mean he's just trying to save it and her tables
Kicked off cuz he's not gay
And that's not
I think I think getting kicked off for promoting hex
Heterosexuality and
What was making money and masculine values
I don't think you need to promote a thing
That you have no choice in the matter of
I don't think you need to promote a thing that is literally destroying the world as we
And I don't think you need to promote another thing that is literally the destroying the world as we paint the making money thing is
Our culture is entirely
Inexorably tied to that you don't have to promote making money
People love making money if I hurt myself I better have made money already
That's the country we live in
We understand
Time
I have money
There's an expression time is money
$2
Yeah
We we you know people who aren't
You know privilege enrich
Conceive of hours
As a rate
That you can make whatever like it's
You don't need to promote
Anyway
I think of the show suck
Queen talk
Almost
I would have loved to rant about how people like like a queen
Like you have this
Like this show is
Was was
Really
Neapolitan bar of bad
S*** you know like it was just a variety
You had this
Deeply deeply racist Pig
Right this very weird interview with Andrew turbo where he's trying to whitewash Christian nationalism in
Middle phrase
And then this interview was kind of just
I don't know
Bad comedy about feminism being bad
Fart
It's at the end
Time line of laundering the reputation of Andrew Tate
I just think all of it is
Is
I'm unspeakably
Pointless and bad yeah
Yeah it is a real
It's a real like just
Strikeout in every sense of the in every sense of the word you didn't get
The bat off
Off your shoulder now you just
Watch the ball go by
Slowly
Very slowly
Yeah
Yeah it's it's
We struck out on t-ball
Pretty bad
It's not good I feel
A little bit dumb
Weave
Speedo I made
Always I made the call that we were going to record late
Because I wanted to try and get this episode Ugly
The queen died
The world is like 100 years
Forever
Hey man this is what we got
Yeah I do love
The one Queen news that I really enjoyed reading about was people scrambling over like
We're going to have
To change our money
Cuz like you know you don't
You totally don't have to leave it there either you got time released
King Charles going to be like
Where's my face all that money is money isn't no longer good doesn't have that much time
I've left so you're just throwing your money away and make
Yeah
I'm not going to get used to the King Charles I don't think
You don't think Prince Charles my whole life
I'm fine with
You know I don't care that's the way to go that's the one I was going for
Anyway
It's bye-bye time
Don't feel that way
It feels like we are on our way to Cypress
Will be back
But until then
Upside.com Twitter
I meant to mention this earlier but I forgot
I have gotten some
Messages and feedback
Some folks about the button
Stop like some people have gotten buttons has to be working
Confused
The mail is not
They're coming out gradually because
We know this is an in-house operation
Mom-and-pop button
ShopRite
Don't be worried if yours hasn't shown up yet there will be it's going to be a gradual process
Maybe for the next month or two
So
Enjoy
Until then
I'm nearly all dcx clerk I'm Wilford Snapple Snapple of the brindle pitbull
The sex robot
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color