Jordan
I have great respect for knowledge babe I'm sick of them
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Looks a little bit about Alex
Jones
We are Dan Jordan
Quick question for you
That that was
Are you still trying to come up with memory
Stories of hey dude honestly I was thinking about ways
Is to keep water from getting into your window in the afternoon
In Chicago after a massive
Rainstorm and
When you showed up to record I discovered that there was a
A group forming in the middle of my living room
I didn't know what to do
There was a diverse ecosystem being built around this this Oasis in your home
I'd no idea that somehow there was a leak
Or something and like it was just
Just a nightmare and that's the only one in the house
Great so that's fun that's not my right
It is officially today the end
Of the dreamy creamy summer
True love and I will be crossing the 100 ice creams
Later this evening
I've not had it yet
But I am I you had I started the day off with a
A frosty ccino from
Wendy's
What it's a frosty in a cappuccino coffee
Cream is Ross
The frosty ice cream
That was an idea that took 5 minutes and that God no need to rework that fat at all
Fantastic night out of town I love that
It's good that was something that was some enterprising employee 20 years ago is just like anybody
I got an idea
I'm just going to put some Frost
I want to end things with one of the suggestions that you actually had that I have taken you up on
And that is the Insomnia Cookie I believe the ice cream sandwich
It was too much going to blow your head off so I'm going to finish things off this evening with that
Annapolis via the dreamy creamy summer
Man bought ice cream
100 is is a lot I like that you got 99 on the morning of vets
So good I might have had a number of things that I had already had
You know Patty
Padding the stats a little bit
What's it what's in a what's the difference between a rebound with five seconds left to go in the game in a rebound with 20 min
And I think there's some
But lessons that I've learned that I'd like to impart
On the audience
Classics classics for a reason
You know something
But you think like a
Your basic ass
7-Eleven or grocery store ice cream sandwich
Good never never ever since you were three years old you've eaten one
You don't know who make
Make those
There's something to it
And the scarf
There's a reason that those are still in business
That's good fantastic
Second
JoJo get too weird
Like okay
Frosty's on the subject in Frosty
When I was growing up there was a chocolate
Frosty
Now there's a vanilla Frosty there's a strawberry frosting
It really showed true
They're not worth it
Frosty is great it's supposed to be
McDonald
McFlurry
Eminem and Oreo right they've tried to Branch out and every time it has been a with
Don't do it
Stick to the safe ocean in there
But they don't put reasons they put like the Reese's Pieces from those are just I can put those and I think that McDonald's doesn't have a
I think that could be an issue recent hates Ray Kroc
Or something new just they want to give him break
Manresa MacDonald had a fight and 400
I also think that things like
Like a Dairy Queen
Peanut buster parfait I think cuz I didn't have one of those in years but I remember the
The ice cream the peanuts the fudge
And then the ice cream the peanuts the flood
Did the AAA or whatever
It might be great for a child I worked at Dairy Queen when I was younger and I have terrible memories of
Making a chili bar and what have you and I don't want to I don't want to open that can of worms backup
Define
Whatever other things custard Superior to frozen yogurt
Trailer sure
Some of these
F******
Overpriced
Ice cream pints
Are so overrated you have no business charging as much as they do
Parfait one
Those are a scam there's like this much ice cream with them and then know that's bulshit
Like a sundae cupcakes disgusting
Yeah that's another thing big loser of the bracket for sure no wasn't bracket
A bunny tracks
Spy Blue Bunny
Do they make a
They make a bar
Yeah
It's
Too much
Too much too much it's busy
There's like
Fudge peanuts
Hellboy rabbit shaped
Caramel filled
No I don't know what I'm eating
Yeah
So we'll see how this ice cream sandwich close things out but I'm excited for it
And
Things are going out periodically they're going out sporadically even has ended
This will go on for the next couple months or so people beginning button
Because I
Woefully underestimated hey goodbye
I underestimated the demand last time
And I thought it would be about the same
I have had to enlist
The help of a business
Frankly
I feel like the first time ever I physically dependent make this money button
The outsourced so
There are some folks who've been curious about like hey I haven't gotten my button yet but some people are post
Some pictures it's because there
Going first,
First serve basically in the email inbox
And I want to keep these fundraisers on the GoFundMe open in
Until we're done sending out the button
So people care to chip in and support these great causes
There's a link
And I got this is enough of my chores
Today Dan is there's a new show
Call
Bee and PuppyCat
Yeah I know
It is but it's made by some of the people who made
Adventure Time so it is not
It's more like that surreal uncanny
Point of view on a certain like
Almost magical magical girl you know like Sailor Moon kind of thing but imagine
More like it's a it's a modern woman trying to deal with s***
And then stuff goes crazy
You know that's kind of but then also it's so very mundane at the same time
That it's
It bounced things balances things out with a
LOL
Was non-existent chiptune soundtrack
Really really interesting in good
I don't know if I would recommend it to ones I like bills
Yes bills are piling up and then you have to have superpowers chilling
At the end of the day if you've if she achieves her goals
She gets like 50 bucks
Like with it with magical powers all of this s*** going on
What time she gets paid in change
You know like it is a tough life out there
Fernanda Galactica superhero toys
No she is not Abby she's just a regular old guy
Okay
Check it out
I'm glad you're enjoying it
It's enjoyable today we have over and we're going back to the past because I have been
Dealing with
Some stuff and I want to have a little treat
And I always find go back to the past to be a treat
And like Alex is off on Monday
Doing this is Andrew Tate interview is going to air that's right and
Out the door as a doctor on Friday okay
Called me
Back-end
And I will talk about that but here before we get into this business
I'll take a little moment
Say hello.
Jill L thank you so much
Thank you very much person said that the name is supposed to be pronounced like it was in The Witcher
And I was not watching The Witcher play The Witcher 3 but it was on mute so I had subtitles
I don't know anybody for NASA's anything
Takes out as best I can tell if brandylion thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
I want it to be brandelli enough some sort you know really remember that anyway
Might be right
Next Jason Watch Neon Genesis Evangelion love Madison thank you so much right now policy wonk
Can you very much you're smiling yeah that's Neon Genesis Evangelion
Do not apologize
But it's an anime I guess that I think I've heard someone mention it before so it's an anime
About forcing these children to Pilot
Giants organic robots
To defeat
The exist
Distance of separation between conscious
Do child Soldiers with a real life
Hard Psych
And they don't
They don't shy away from the child in Child Soldier they
Torture that kid
I mean
There's memes about
Just get in the robot if you hear somebody say like get in the robot towards that
Fairies
Decades
Torture
Easy kind of like
Not that heavy kind of entertainment that's why I listen to Alex Jones all the time
Episodes are live action serial Adventure nonsense
Text me space Ashley
Sofia in Scotland
Thank you very much also might be Sophia
Open the next year doing so
Four stars don't get mad until you're brilliant someone
Sodomites
Has a Caribbean
I don't want
Jesus Christ
Where you left off on August 6th
Picked up there and
Listen to the 7th
And it's
Just
Man it is
Yeah that is
Tootsie little bit of a round table with a couple pastors who are complaining about how like
They're trying to run a scam where they give teachers credentials but they aren't lice
To do it
So it's kind of a snooze
And I had to skip pass
Round table with pastors is never fun
So we get to Friday
August 8th
And there's actually something that I found really fascinating I think this is an incredibly helpful
Teachable
Episode about Alex
And how he operates
The story that he tells
Has to do with the child protective service
Feeling surrounding it obviously thinks they're just out to kidnap your children
Imagine her CPS of the path
Riyasat episode talking about
There are over a million
You have polluted
Private organization
Problem
Abuse
Statistically
Because baked
You go get a message
Analogy
He has to tell me to do that
But if you're middle class
So this is this is something
He's at
Blow this is pretty standard
From Alex's
The point
Something that needs to be brought up to is this notion that
The like
Child Protective Services doesn't need to exist because there were criminal laws for this
Is a little bit of a weird perspective
The cops will come steal a kid
And then they'll raise them in the precinct and that's where we get
Cops
I think
That sounds
Like a boss
But you might watch
I think it's silly to like this because
There are laws
And
There are
People who need to be specialized in dealing with certain laws particularly
Sensitive type situations like family Dynamics
Antabuse
That's not that's not something that you would want to
Entrust to your normal
Beat cop or just add someone who doesn't have
Some training in that field of course
So if you don't have CPS then you just have to take
8 unit inside the police department and
Turn them in
Do CPS basically
Yeah matter what you do for someone to accomplish the job you're looking
Looking for
Someone has to be there
Or do you have to create a situation where we like we don't do anything proactive we don't do anything
You know address situations and instead what we do is when there's
Something when they get a murmur of like there's some abuse going on we
Your normal detective in there I guess they are as parents
The kids can fend for themselves okay so your parents are going to go to
You'd be fine in this house by yourself
Was it will see you later
I'll check in on your once a week or so I'll bring you some food
I don't know what the the alternative for what Alex will take care of every
It's kind of the same thing he has about like he will not having insurance will take care of you
Be great if there was more of it but relying on it institutional and structurally seems like
We created a government because we wanted Community Aid on a bigger left
That's why we all pay the government to then provide Community Aid
Yeah it's something like that
So Alex is a story about the CPS taking the child and I do not believe that this is true
Criminal record
What
We go there and
Turn around
So then the cops are bad for this right
And then I went
I don't believe this story as it's told
How do you do make a really good point I guess Alex is responsible to be cops are only doing this
Because the CPS makes them do after something like that I'm sure there's
There's a workaround
Yeah but this is I mean this is scary if you listening to something to be scared of
Yeah I suppose
Coming in and stealing your baby in broad daylight with all of these people around witnessing it
And only one of whom is apparently retelling the story all of those people in the hospital all of the doctor
Monsters versus all the wrestling people never told this story once but he sounded Mike Hansen
Problem
I've not seen this I've watched a lot of his contact even from
The back of these times
Documentaries or what have you
I think this would be pretty shocking
If I was telling the story I'll be like you know what let's play that footage right now
Maybe it'll be helpful
Contextual but I think that it's more just a misrepresentation of something
That he wants to present as this they're going
To steal your kids
They are going to steal a particular kind of kit
Crack dealer they don't want your kids
Where they had
They go in
Baywatch
Surprise white babies
Right right what's the going what's the going rate for a white baby these days
I don't know but I don't think this is a major
Concerned for the
And all of this is being brought up
Open this is the theme basically the end
Entirety of this episode because Alex has found a story
In the Denver Post
That is going to basically spiral perm
Interview
So it's wild 2003 The Denver Post was a socialist publication
Especially considering that he was operated by media News Group Incorporated
The second largest newspaper conglomerate in the country
Seems like Alex might just throw that word socialist around randomly like it doesn't mean anything
Free with them from time to time huh explicitly endorse V severely right wing
In politics that I love
About a woman who had taken temporarily by child protective service
But there's some very important
Details in the story they're going to be interesting to see if Alex ignores
Because
The reality of the story
Does not work for the narratives that Alex is trying to build up about the CPS
Oh yeah they do
If you lie
That's such a good trick always get away with that
So here Alex gets more into the store
The police
So one of the sources that cited in the article is there past
McGinnis
And speculated that their Hospital thought they were homeless
And tell Alex brakes about it a little bit
Covers the story a little bit more
Department of Human Service
Confirm
Morning
She talked about
We were obliged to follow up on
So if you're just listening to Alex you and I
Very important context about the story that he's reading
He tells the story he wants we audience
To hear and hide the details are inconvenient for his ability to spin a bowl-shaped yarn
The biggest piece of information he's leaving out is that the family was unhoused a couple years prior and good luck husband
Pretty sure that this
Had to do with outdated medical record
Rides
He believed that there was a misunderstanding that's them for medical records They had on file being from a time when they were experiencing
Homelessness which makes the whole thing
Kind of make a lot more set bright
Over the years since they've had tons of temporary address
So you can kind of understand how none of these would necessarily be in the medical record
And CPS would be tasked with offering resources to a nun house family have
Sing a child
The second thing is that the baby was put in CPS custody on Sunday and was returned to miss
Good luck on Monday Eve
Evening
It's something that's unfortunate
May not have been handled perfectly and baby
Shouldn't happen
And then likely if you know better record-keeping was done by all parties involved
It wouldn't
But this wasn't the kidnapping and it lasted around 24-hour
It was needed to correct their clerical error and do the paperwork
The third thing that I was leaving out for now but we'll have to address later is that good luck is Navajo
Oh and her husband is
Lakota
Alex is not bring this detail up because he's trying to do this whole Jacobite other systems really after white children Act
Presrite not existing in this big story he's covering would be kind of suspicious
Especially
In kitchen
Another major problem for his entire Naruto
According to a 2017 release from the national Indian Child Welfare Association quote research and data from
The state's tells us that American Indian
Alaska native children are disproportionately represented over-represented
In the child welfare system Nationwide especially in Faust
Aftercare
This means that higher percentages of aian children are found in the child welfare system
General population
The over-representation of aian children often starts with reports of abuse and neglect it rates
Fortunate to their population numbers
But grows higher each major decision point from investigation
Replacement
Culminating in the over-representation of aian children
In placement outside the home
One study found that due in large part to systemic bias
Where abuse has been reported aian children are two times more likely to be investigated
2 times more likely to have allegations of abuse substantiated
And 4 times more likely to be placed in foster care than white
This disproportionality has gotten worse in the time sense but their rates
It would still
In 2003 but this is a dynamic that Alex is not equipped
To deal with
He doesn't actually care about fixing real problems with how the CPS operate
And he's actually over
To even acknowledging those problems because for him
The CPS narrative is really just a vehicle for him to engage in white grief
Yeah
It to the extent that he will ever acknowledge that these are Navajo mother in Lakota
Bother
You only will recognize it and I like now they're do going to do it like that that is the
Who's this
And
Actually looking at the real dynamics is counterproductive for napping
And it's just such
F****** b******* of like
You are you are at
Symptom number seven of the problem
That is
Why were they on house
In the first place
What start f****** way back when they're not sure allowing that to happen
And then you go back
Even further in you go
Not only are they on house currently in our terrible system
But they're from a people who were genocided by everybody
And we're not well and disproportionate to taking of children
Is a knock-knock apart of Gem State
Oh my God understood in the proper context this story that Alex's covering as a prime opportunity to
Discuss this very clearly did a discriminatory pattern and how these government entities treat Native family
Further it could be an opportunity to discuss the ways the benign mistakes like out-of-date medical information
Can we do really difficult situations but
They don't necessarily have to lead to disaster
Either of these options bring new real useful information to his audio
Neither would create the feelings that he wants to evoke
Namewee that all white people are under attack of the government is going to take your children
Taking note of the details that Alex chooses to ignore about stories is often a really important part of understanding is that
Editorial process
Illustrating
What it actually is
He considers it
The truth is informing the audience isn't import
The truth itself isn't
But spreading racially-based fear is
Pretty super important
Yeah and I want to be totally clear about
Alex is excluding information actively and intentional
So the audience doesn't get the full picture
After he comes back from break he continues reading the article if this is
F****** damn
This is right
Months
Here's what Alex accidentally started reading and then stopped himself mid-sentence
Good luck said she told Hospital admissions Personnel her address but why was there people
Coming up to me and asked me if this is right
She didn't understand it
The family had lived in a Denver area homeless shelter for about 6 months in 1999 and later in a basement
Apartment provided by a member of the church where Phillip Gates
Has become an ordained
Elder
It's just one chapter in the family's struggle
Alex you heard him say they have lived in a Denver area and then stop at right there
Right there at the word homeless because that validates
Why there might have been concerned
That went awry obviously
Not handled perfectly in the situation but it gives an explanation for why this situation is happening
Why there was cause
People to
Think that maybe
She was on house
He can't let that be it has to be a random thing where there is evil intent
On the part of the CPS people
He's lying to his audience
And it's so clear
When you hear him drop off right there when reading
Yeah that's
That's far
That's just
Fuct I'm I'm actually more
I'm happier when he
He's making s*** up whole cloth
Because that's just
Sad and Evil
Like that's an actual
Didn't you do it also very clearly shows that he didn't read this before he
Decided to dedicate an entire show to
Auntie CPS narratives based on
Fort Lee
Bolstered by
This kind
Bulshit seemingly precipitated by him reading this story
Pinpoint for him to have
A show all about the CPS of the evils of it
Fry pan
He doesn't even read it
You didn't even read it
This was before he
He spent three hours every morning reading
And then did a show and then spent 5 hours every evening read
This was before he got
Serious dad
And started doing a lot more drug
Yeah I'm sure
So this is also bulshit
Did I already get there
By this time
Oh man
Wow
Alex is not telling his audience of the family it already got the kid back by the time the article he's reading was
Published
He's also stopping himself from disclosing the part where it says big Gates
Permanently disabled because of that shooting that he mention which truly would be even more
Services to be interested in providing whatever assist
Baked ham
This stuff works against Alex's narrative though so it's centered from the most uncensored
And most unfiltered news program in the world
Alex
Truthful
Not because he's a f****** the same time tunnel liar
Truth to power and
Threatens the people
Hope you know I mean it is it is so weird
When we we can separate it because he's doing the radio show
But essentially
If she was there holding her baby you would be looking in their eyes screaming
You're never going to get that baby back
Holding anything
This is crazy
Just out of the days people are 1984 in all over the place here
But he's on the radio so it's like oh I don't even noticed this person isn't exact existing dryers supposed to distract you
Doesn't matter
Doesn't matter does fake emotion and
Pennywise real
Is that a
Is that a conversation that we
We need to have with Alex of like other people
Object permanence that's definitely true
So yeah I don't know I
Certainly
More
In the present then it was the past but maybe it's maybe it's always been there
John Birch books before you teach them object permanence I think we wind up here
So yeah you have just
This
Rio
Nonsense
Demonstration
He's lying
Very intentionally about this article
As a way to push
His
Gcps
So
Look
Goes to another break
Checking baby accidentally read the article
Good chance
But so many times
They're probably going to
Andover Andover
Over and over again
Read the article
He's aware of that information now but
Assuming that he has read the article he now knows
You know the thing that he's censored himself
And I was just saying it's because
The guy's a cop
Years ago
Yeah in the line of duty permanently disabled
Right
So
Great
Good work
Yeah
I just think this is trash to be awful
I'm going to get even worse because
This whole pageant goes on for quite a while
And then Alex has a guess
And it's his water
Filter sponsor
That's not reverse osmosis
Removing
Portable is awesome
Always a pleasure Alex
I don't know where you get all your in
Information
Be a prodigy to get all the
Stephen Curry
I mean
Yes I find it really
Sad I mean that they're in a commercial relationship so you don't expect necessarily
Weirdly like
You are so smart you got so much information than that being
Wolf and intentionally leave out
Information that is illuminate
About a story
There is that
Conman kind of feel
That you just
It's like it still blows my mind whenever you feel that actual conman feeling of that person
Something
Wow you are smart
We clearly making everything up and it's just like they got taken in the commercial relationship
Smoke
Yeah I would imagine that if you have reservations now is not
Yeah yeah
To be at the other thing I was thinking about a really good point
Is it
Alex could recognize every piece of information about this article and still tell the story
He wants to tell
He would have a more difficult time with a chat
We could not paint the picture that the CPS
Is randomly just
Accusing people
Of
Beat up being on house or something
It ain't like you think that
False accusation as an excuse to steal their child
He perhaps couldn't do that but you don't have to open it up you could open it up into a like
That is not caused
To take someone's child
And
It's more difficult in a way that leads you to actual solution
It leads you to reforming
The the system that is there as opposed to
Creating a cartoon
Tunis version of it to be mad about in demand be demolished ultimately it just simply
Allows you to identify
As I mean
Despite Alex
Insisting that this only happen
Do white people it allows you to identify with somebody non-white
Which cannot happen on this show
Bear basin
So Alex Dixon call
People who have situations trouble with the children
Now they made it up
So he's got a call
And this color is having a difficult time with her child
Weird things
Things to say
Diagnosed
With ADH
What time is it
Skateland
Different labels
Psychiatric labels
She was given to actually
The father who abandoned her at Birth are who has
History of abuse
In the situation.
Anda
Has been very hard
Well
In person
What
Alex Wood Faith heal
Wow
Forehead and pushed her to the floor and then when she stood up
She would go back and live with her mom and RJ eyes
I don't remember exactly where this woman is calling for a
I think
They're really dancing over something
If
His child was
Given
The custody was given to a father who hasn't been in her life who lives in a different state
There's something going on
And it's not just
She got these diagnosis that I disagreed with
Yeah that there's something
Really messed up here
Am dealing with
People who are telling these stories and being like yeah you're totally right
Morelia responsive
I mean yeah you wouldn't I wouldn't want to be like
You know I mean what you
Do I guesses
Say thank you for your call and then
I mean if you wanted to keep talking then you would have to ask like
Further probing questions like OK Google
You're totally right know you're totally right
Yeah
Bumblebee the f*** out
It's really want to thank you for your
Strengthen and your comebacks
Just about every day is off
Why can I stop
Doing what I'm doing to listen and learn
Girlfriend
I lost a lot of
Friends along the way and I've lost a lot of my family
Yeah
That is a bummer
That's called
Yeah
Boy I study your broadcast
And I told people in my life about it and I've lost friends and family
Yeah
When you start
With
Bye
Child was sent to live with a
Father she didn't
Really no
In a different state and then end with
I've lost friends and family because I tell them all about what Alex Jones says all the time
Then I mean you're starting to put
Some things together. That's not the full picture it's so bad for I know Alex Can't Behave any
The other way really but it's so bad for him to be like yeah that's cuz they can't handle the truth they love worship together
Yeah you've just doubling down on this
This abusive influence
Yeah you're never going to see a cult leader be like Hey listen you might be going a little bit too far with my b******* about you step back
Lights go out go go hang out with your friends at the at the Sonic
Or whatever it is you kids do and then come back and we'll get back into this called this is supposed to be a fun con
You're really bugging me out later
I'm just trying to screw people out of money and now you're telling me I'm hurting others so
Is it going to be time for me to look in the mirror but I will
Triumph
Deal I'll deal with my wounds by rubbing money on them that I feel better
Buy another house
So
That's a bummer
And I think we need to
Feel a little bit better by going to something a little more fun
It is
It's time
To go to Alex's memories of his past
Corner there's a fun story about Alex in high school
Call Art
Call
Tool
More
4 year Junior
That is a joke
That's why
Police
That's so true upright their man's like Mike has a joke
Like what in the 2,000
Three man they were born for each other they really we're barely Alex
Perfect grades and basically every class and also he's constantly having sex with
Fellow students
I'm getting abortions
And he's a Satanist by the elite in Rockwall
That's me of being the linchpin and God's plans to Vanquish the devil
Also at
Some point in the middle he uncovered a drug-dealing conspiracy to Rockwall Police Department who threatened to kill him
Austin the constants
Street fights because black people wouldn't stop harassing him because he was white
Right also you smoke crack a couple times
Amazing almost unbelievable backstory unbelievable is the operative
Words are forever to self mythology I would say a little bit over stuff
If I was if I was describing the plot of this movie here I would say overstep streamline
Streamline focus on a few important details I didn't get good grades in high school and I did end up dropping out before
I went to college
But I was friends with a lot of nerds and
I knew I was friends with the guy who was the valedictorian of the class before me
Year older than me
And
Look they don't just choose one person who gets accolades
There's like
First of all I dropped out of high school and it was a National Merit scholar
National Merit Scholars are all kinds of people who get scholarships
College scores
There's the valedictorian there's like a dick sometimes co-valedictorian
There are
The other like oomloud
Even like in high school
Like I remember there being a
For people who are like
The like not not like president vice president Treasurer and secretary
People who were who were like
Real damn good grace
Borderline Braun silver
Gold medals kind of situation
Also in high school my buddy Cole he helped out with the counselor's office going around and delivering passes to students
To an appointment so they could be
It would be counted as tardy or truant in their class and I do definitely didn't have all A's
He doesn't open. And the counselors likes him
But I guess now it's okay if they're really trying to secretly deputize him or some
I think that would have been the first like we've talked about the
The school-to-prison pipeline but we don't talk about the school to globalism pipe
Right through the counselor's office are not busy
Lovecore
I would sometimes come and help him
Hand out passes cuz
Skip class
That is great
That is great that was much darker collegial relationship
Three teachers and students in high school that was not the case for
Is very very confrontational
I feel like I know it went both ways
For me some teachers is very confrontational then some
Far more like
Treated treated you like a almost like a little equals now
My favorite teacher did say like well if they didn't f*** around with you then you they would have had a problem
As like a like that's probably not what you should tell to a fourteen-year-old avanade probably not but I mean
You did have a point around with me and we had a great time
Broadcast production class
The teacher guy named Ron with B
Auntie
I was in the class 3 years in high school
Key to the room
Because I had like an editing Bay
And so I would come like after hours and edit video on Hangouts
Mostly just
Just about
Making stories for the public access
Like there was a
Show called 16 minutes
Haha that was the schools at the students make stories about the local community
60 minutes but you only get 60
And so I would go nothing but you're still a fourteen-year-old I just want the story about how secretly Cheska
Club was like a hotbed of Communism at the high school
It's all I had my friend Matt
Pretend to be like a plant and like one of the guys in the chess club was a friend of mine until he played along
Decorate the guy who sponsored the chess club like the teacher and I house on friendly terms are game is messing around
Three aired
Music
I would always
You're killing me
But you'd still be still put it on that's good stuff I like it I like that
Okay
That's that's a good teacher move where you like you're doing this wrong but also
Come on baby on the screen
Alex
Gestapo for the counselor's office or something
Lie about
Why
Why would you lie about it
Incredibly insecure
All of the information on the test was because the batter information was everywhere else
Yeah yeah I mean I think if you do well in school and you're proud of it this is nothing
To be ashamed of
I think
That if you didn't do well in school and you're lying about it because
You want people to think you did well in school that's not good
Stop doing that
Hey listen
I didn't get good grades in school
See Now We're Off to the Races buddy
Easy peasy
Eminem line stupid rich is f****** proud of it
Another story from his youth
In school
Amazon's a little bit longer
Just a little bit
Confusing to the store like what the fuc
He should be allowed to say that
And we have some
Zara
And
Order me around
Call your mother
What
Yes
I'm sure
11 farad again
Yeah so he had a flu the nurse wanted to f*** him
And
Also she wanted to give him speed because he had a lot of energy so we let's get him board
Happened I am
Here's a here's how I feel like the story actually happy
Alex was kind of sick
Not that sick
Wanted to go home anyways so he's going to give his mom a call
It's the temperature in like okay
Well I've got you
Let me ask you
Are you doing drugs right now
I mean that's possible
And then it's like hey you know you have give me drugs and f****** you have ADHD you know so they
There's this medication out there I don't know maybe it might help you
Deal with some of your
You trying to f****** Gray
McDonald's
Google please
I have a story that's so glad school's carryout number
I have a story that's kind of closed
But it's not really a to pick me up in college I went to the Student Health Center
Cuz I had strep throat
And I couldn't
Like I couldn't swallow pills
I didn't know what was going on I
And had it before
And so like I have terrible fever and
So the guy who was the doctor that
Gave me some liquid
Steroids
And he did say
Careful
This is what the rappers rap about
That's the way you do it it's not like he was trying to give me bro
That was a little bit inappropriate but in a delightful what I really enjoyed it
The very what would I say
Uptight way of describing this is what the rappers rap about
He might have said the rapper is sing about
That's that taking up another level wasn't like an old out-of-touch person or anything
Dreaming of it is freezing was still weird
Play I can still remember that 20 years later that delightful moment where I'm like
Hundred something fever just like unable to swallow a pill
Hey this is the purple stuff every now and again there are those moments where I'm like
What if I could run into that person
You know after it's cuz there's tons of those little memories you have or you're like
This person has no idea that because they flipped a penny at me
20 years ago at that is in my brain forever like I want to go talk to them and have them have that
Very validating feeling up
I have no idea what you're talkin about
Probably come off real crazy because you would do be like
Remember this at all but I need to bother you
So we get the we had a fun time in that corner of Alex's remembrance
Nonsense
Where was the state
The man that story not exist in all of these actually the school nurse was working on behalf
Check on speed in order to take him away.
You going to be so important in the plot of battle later on
We've installed it
Smell something really f***** up happy
Okay I can't believe this happened
Alex has
The dad
From The Denver Post story on as a guest
No
And
Of course
On the show
So yeah
Which is crazy
Because this is so much more disrespectful
They had booked
To them as guess
That show
I was I was floored by the
That's why I said if you do like a nightly talk show I didn't I didn't I didn't think that Jon Stewart red ever
Free book of the purse
And he was interviewing that night he did his best for everybody I bet
Some people might
Equate to a
Stay single article
More than a thousand words of every single one of those books I will guarantee it
That goes interviews are probably booked pretty well in advance about this is like this is 2,000
Wife is probably booking the show right I mean like
He doesn't have a big team at this
He doesn't have his.
How did this happen
I understand
The booking happy
Chat makes sense to me you can reach out to them see if they want to come out and do an interview
Absolutely
How does it happen
That you know you're going to do this interview
And you don't read the article
You with the story
Essentially
How is it that you
Didn't even have somebody
Give you the
CliffsNotes version
Of the article
Yeah you know how to get the correct yourself that got their kids
I mean that's crazy
That's essential thing to the story how do you seem to be caught off guard in the middle of the story that the guy is
Is a cop
Yeah that's not good enough but the pretty big detail
They don't talk about the past homelessness
Steers away from a lot of the like Jermaine issues
Hey
Let's talk about how evil beef if you want to talk
Normally social worker
Or
What's
I believe
Stepdaughter
Call Wade
Out in the hallway
What went on
Charge nurse
That wasn't charged
Or there
Can get her purse
Stayed in the room
Should have the robot
Outlaw Way
I was going to say what is the vampiric celebrate
What's the robot because it's dehumanizing
It's taking a human and think about the characteristics of a robot
Do vampires
Traditionally what robot
Yes
I did not know that okay
In an Alex is
World the metaphorical robot
Metaphorical vampires want little robots along the lines of life
Ray Lewis's celebration dance
Cuz this is 2003 right
Do Ray Lewis and the Baltimore Ravens still reckon the world
You know yeah and so I'm assuming that
Like
The door
And then like did one of the things you know what I'm saying have you seen the
If I have not
Yeah I don't know I don't know what they're doing
Yeah Alex just wants
To create these images these like evil images that are evocative for the odd
The spelling is good for bringing those up
And
Selling them to the audience important
Before he's
Like he's talking
To the father and the father
Is trying to tell the story
And so whenever Alex says like all she was smiling wasn't
He's like
Well I mean she did leave the so he's implanted into that guy's mind before we even go any further
That it's possible in fact
Likely and then later
Guaranteed and true that you did the charge nurse was talk
Did you think it was inappropriate what went on in the room the conversation that the
That the CPS people had with the mother
It's unclear but it doesn't really matter on the show because it's all just
Does fuel on the fire of
Evading CPS Yelp
So what are the things that is clear
Is that the
Reverend
McGinnis and his father are both
Upset with the CPS
And
One of the things that they want to make clear is that there should be ways
Stop these
Processes when they're being done in error
You know they're not talking about overthrowing the CPS
Right if there is something that is erroneous
Outdated information to people are acting on their Speedway to put a Holt in the preceding
So they don't go so far as to remove a child's
I when you're just
Going to have them away for 24 hours or what
Like its
There should be safe
Basically
He wanted to say that there many dedicated social worker
Remember what we
We are really short
About
Is that there's no mechanism
I think you're listening audience
Weekend
Slowing down
Is the
Weight speed
Illustrates the dynamic
Titanfall
If there is in a campaign
It is
Legitimate
A request
Something that is a structural Improvement that I don't even people within the CPS to be like
You know what
That is something that needs to be dry
We could do a better job
If you just said to a regular CPS employee all day everyday just like hey
Maybe we don't rip newborns from their mothers hands
Like maybe we just don't do that
They be like yeah I think that makes sense
And Alex has a different take on it
Burn it all town I'm very.
And you can see that Alex doesn't respect his guests
Perspective
To get them tubes
Mirror his perspective
Because that's what
And that's what we'll sell the feeling to the audience that he needs to sell them in order to keep them
In that cult like state but Drew bump this out earlier
He's a little bit like he's trying to redpill them at the same time
We're at the trial you know he's trying to redpill the jury anything
He's doing it like
On the phone right here is like don't you guys want to help start a f****** w**** like no started
I started it on us
So this was the 8th
Maya Friday
I'm going to jump to the MonDay show because it's kind of also a wasteland not much going on
But
There is something
Really big
Going on
Call Joseph Watson
It is order out of Chaos
Order 300
Infowars.com
Improved
You are secure online
So please don't take advantage of that
The Doctor David
Murder
My murder
Not with no evidence
Botanica
Preponderance
So this is about a month after Kelly died and Alex's presented literally no new information passed the big insinuations
Used to call Kelly's death of murder when he first cover
This is something that the Alex Jones is always right about stuff crowd should really think about
Are these
Protracted long
Nonsense narratives that he gets up to
Also I love the way that Alex catches himself mid-sentence there
He said that the media is calling Kelly's death a suicide with no proof and he almost said so we're going to call it a murder with no proof
You already did he really did have a certain amount of like
Yeah if they're going to do it then I'll do it right back to manners
There right there
Also Paul's book is out
And that is just an opportunity for me to say that in my hand I have a copy of the great reset Alex's book
Oh my God I unfortunately did buy a copy of it
Money which honestly it's just me cutting myself and sword
But a
It sucks a little bit of that it's not good
Tell at a later date
It's maybe the next time we have some like
Really Monumental episode number like
720 something something like that we're doing
Some random number
37 OVR flight up
We'll fly out of 750 7777 really don't know how high it goes
Is there a 787 nobody 777 that's like a lottery that's like it's true
4777 not to wish account
What we would cover
Sodas balls
But the David Kelly narrative
Is now growing
It is no longer just that this was a guy who's going to blow the whistle about the Iraq War and be weapons of mass destruction
He's hanging out with Saddam Hussein's kids no no no but it goes deep
Free Press
Abrasive
Morton,
Yeah so now well recall Kelly being unvaulted race-specific Sister, you worked at Porton down and that means that
Is there a specific people are dying
And David Kelly is an example of one of the murderers
To cover up their race specific bioweapon
Because they're about to release it
There is a preoccupation that Alex has with
Race specific by I wonder what race it is he reaches
Warts
Race specific
I have some theories as it is ironic that he's
He's never been like and you know what would be terrible
A race specific
Not by a weapon that is a bioweapon for all other non raised was over by 11 you know what I'm saying
That's kind of what he wants
Well think it's
I think the people who don't listen to his show much
You might hear some of the the covid stuff
Let's say like especially in the early days of covid-19 like as a racist a bioweapon
And you think like
That's an interesting angle he's going on right now
Free specific bioweapon
Are always
Somehow he'll play it's always been like at the end of the
The Dayman
White people
Are the only people that matter
That's what he's trying to get across that's his
His raison d'etre
So Paul is on
Little bit
But Alex has a
Another little little Theory
Exercising panda
We'll also
Hear it
About a half-mile from where I'm at
Thumbprint you already
And
Whoomp There It Is
Eminem
About a year ago
They pulled out
And I have about 15 Lanes
Where it would be self-serving
Then they put the song
I mean
Filter have DNR
Michael
Denise Denise
Selfie
Supermarket
The government
Still waiting on those phones scanners in police ID databases to go into the grocery store is 19 years later here
Carlos cards
Like 3 years ago
Honestly
If you don't sign the back of your debit or credit card when you use it people are supposed to ask for your ID and they don't do that
What was going on here in Alex's. Maybe wasn't real thing
Maybe the move towards automation was more about cutting down operating
Expenses by eliminating human workers
Also I assumed that Alex's describing Israel
It was a woman just whatever
I don't want to talk to you
Football teams have no idea what he's talking
Right now McDonald's can refuse to serve you for any reason as long as it's not because you're a member of a protected
The class
If someone's making a scene they can be refused service
If you suspected someone's drunk you can refuse service
Barefoot or wearing no shirt you can refusing service
As long as you're not discriminating based on protected classes you have the right to run your business how you see fit like for instance
It's not illegal for a high-end restaurant to refuse to serve you if you don't fit their dress code
More like a hotel can. Take a reservation from you if you stay there before you cause the problem
They can do that
Get refused service said you have that right
Politeknik Lisa isn't it to putting in self-checkout is about being able to deny purchase of some particular product but this makes
WhatsApp
If you suggesting that I might one day go to McDonald's and they refuse to sell me anything but a McChicken because they think I'm high
I had too much red meat that day
But that seems that it's the self-checkout things
It's doing it then that would say
Suggest to me that you're
Bringing all of these items
You're checking
And you get it items that they're like not a
You don't get to buy eggs
Right like I don't understand I went in and how is that helpful there's not even a person there to stop it
I could just steal it and put it in my bed
Break from the self-checkout line by accident all the time
David Drake has that joke about everything is bananas bananas
But lock it is actually about this
That's making it
Depending on what you're getting
Unless you buy
Report
So this is dumb but also tracking
Your purchases of food would have no effect
Being able to protect the supply chain from any kind of terrorist influence
That's right like the consumer end of it wouldn't make any sense as an excuse for them I find the sun compared
Yeah you know it is it is like it is
So stupid especially now that we know about metadata
You know like before they had no
Can track you if they have a chip on your finger and it's like now man
Because your cellphone is someplace
They can figure out what your day is like
Easily
Just done
Your cellphone exist so they know where everyone is go there is some amount of data that is
It is not
Toby level that Paul is predicting in the next
It's not Enemy of the State
Starring Will Smith
I mean it's far beyond that even
DePaul
Play music
With the new development
Predicting the everyone
LifeLock fix
Brainwave
Is it recorded
Macy
Few weeks ago
Every breath
Brothers
MRI scanner
It look in your brain
Come over to speak with you
Samantha
You're lying
Is a great example of Alex is an idiot and stupid
He's saying that there are MRIs in the airport and then reporting it as some kind of a plan to detect aggression or nefarious intent
10 people
This is insane
But it's based on a kernel of Truth
Which is the MRI technology is used in airports
It's used to scan bags
Because the idea of human application of moriann airport is laughable
Have you ever had an MRI done you'll know that is a complicated process where you are put into a big machine and then you have to say
Completely still or else you'll ruin the pictures that the doctor is taking inside your head angrily yell
Velvet you have to give people like sedative
Imagining that you could effectively use MRI technology on something not staying completely still is absurd
And it would pretty much be useless in a crowded Airport terminal
One of the primary applications of MRI Tech in the airport has to do with Screamin liquid
It's because that's something that x-rays are not traditionally very good with
Also 19 years later and Paul's 10-year predictions look
City cuz I mean like yes there are things like data that's collect
There are things
About
Concerns about
Things listening
Or what have you
Even though that may be true
That is a far cry from every
Conversation you have being recorded by the government database rag heartbeat that you have
This is like a system that is
First of all
Would not be useful
Exactly
That's the thing about it
That we did that we do know for a fact evil folks would have
No use for that it would it would be too much it's too much information to find anything
White sweeping programs like when they start looking into how much used
They get out of it it's like
No now your signal-to-noise ratio is
All know if you have everyone
Heartbeat login something
I don't know what the heck are you listening to
Everyone in every single conversation and every breath
Cool
Anyway. Just to check in on you make sure you're okay
Strong predictions
Coming out here
Are going to end this episode with like I said the 11th
There's not much
But there's something
Flocking
Awesome
And it
It's a delightful note for this episode and Dawn
And I take it away pjw
Tyrese
Television
Control the other character
I'm friends with the other members of
Beyonce them regularly
Grab the rest of the show every woman
Survivalist
Interesting
All the other men.
Crowded around
Something
Hey guys
The New World Order
And then
Open
DVD loading flag
Turtle Red Alert
Gold
Greenlight is here
I got an old episode of
I can't think of anything
Dumber
Tammy person
Then the idea that you are going to pull up an old Frasier episode as proof of whatever argument you or May
Yeah
The end
I am
Depressed cuz I was a bummer
So
Is a great opportunity for me to go watch an episode of Frasier
Note with Kelsey Grammer but I put that aside and just enjoy what it is
X-Men the dudes Beast
Fine
Not a good Beast not a good beat
Plot of this episode
Goes to a shooting range
Because his dad was a former cop right
Snow gacha
Yeah there's a reason for
Lip doesn't want to shoot
He does
People who are at the booth next to him
Come on
Encouraging
Gets a little love Bob
Doesn't want to go because he's like I you know I go about once it once again I've had enough
Niles goes he makes friends with these guys who are there
If they end up inviting him to a gun show
And so the dad and Beth made decide to go along the gun show
He's going to get a like
Ankle holster in Daphne
And so it's all good time
Niles goes away for a minute and the guys
Forgotten friends
I'm over it
Hey they say something about the New World Order
Anti
Do use are these our militia types
Wow weirdos
Until they tell Niles like hey
You don't want to hang out with these people they're not
They're not your
Certipay
Traffic when I make intellectual friends you don't like my friends and now I weigh cool friends and you don't like my friends
I'm going to hang out with these guys and there's no compound in Idaho
He walks over to them at the gun show right there like around a piece of paper
The plans for the generator
We're going to need the New World Order comes out
Oh okay
So yeah there's a good
Justin episode about how sometimes they're those militia types
Buy a show that was famous for being famous in the 90s during
When all those militia types were everywhere little late
Yeah
Yeah but I also think that
Elks fairly often
Freezer one of the jokes
Is there snobby
Better day or the butt of a joke because they judge people too quickly
Often time
And dials or boat they have to deal with like
Are snooty presumptions about people
Are not right
I thought that for sure that was what this was going to be but just
Overthrow the Government Street and Niles almost accidentally went to Idaho
Should not go to Idaho place that Nile should not be involved in it
Also be plot
Yeah
Is getting a new job
Enter she's going to stop being Frasier's producer
Yeah
Start of a bigot
Justin Bieber lot for the for that up
Answer Frasier is making out with Felicity Huffman
I don't know who her character is I've forgotten what she is on the show baby
Yeah they're getting hot and heavy
How long did Frasier run for
Wow
Cheese's people used to just watch anything
Fraser's fun
Sure
I don't know if it was just because I had been listening to Infowars I switched over to research
Yeah you made you made all your snobby friends
Edmark your cool friends I get it I see how it is
So anyway we come to the end of this Andy and Alex
We got some interesting view into his childhood
Paul's book is out.
To take away from this
The control of information that Alex has in order to
I'll tell his narratives and his stories the way he wants the audience to experience
GameStop
He doesn't give access to the full picture
Because if you did
He would have a harder time telling
The story that he wants to
Patel
Not the mark of somebody who's straight up
Nope
Because he's a liar
Battle
I'm trying to get across
The other point is that
Cult leaders are scary man
Cult leaders are scary when you are
I can't
Cuz that's the thing that I really could never get across
Forget past
You know that moment where somebody says do you like
I've left my family and my friends behind
And you have to look them in the eyes and be like that was a great move
You know what's really weird about it is
Someone saying I left my family and friends behind
Is
Takes a little bit of
Try not to different.
All my friends and family have left
Because I'm too right
That's a diluted
Person who doesn't realize
True true
Yeah they're in a well I mean that's
Kind of funny there in a secret cult
That is hidden
From the rest of society
Controlled by a small group of people
Ina
A nondescript studio in Austin Well actually this was in Round Rock he was in that Johnson Millers
Studio
Yeah it was on the road broadcasting on this one
So your theory Falls
So Jordan
Just Dance
Indeed.com
Clark
I am Wilford Snapple Snapple of the purple pitbull
And now here comes
Alex
Kristen color