Knowledge party.com
I have great respect but knowledge B I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
MoneyGram
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
A little bit about Alex
June Jordan
Call me
And you
Haha bright spot I didn't
Prepare Perry song
My Wonka games are paying off
Ticket in Vermont
Congratulations Juniper this is very very exciting
I can't wait to see where these other ones turn up this thing I'm not
As you can see there's like boxes of but
Then I'm putting them in bags and then just
Thinking about taking the bags in the office elope
Japan
Too many buttons alright Outlet
We better move to Scotland waiting for you to have to hire somebody who's eyes
Ursone shot who's who's lost feeling in their fingers in order to choose
The correct but
I have put them in the right place I have
A non-problematic team of Olympus
It's like a Yakuza boss
So that's very exciting and I want to say
Brother Josh
The brother John just got laid off
I want to take this opportunity to see Josh
Keep keep yourself on the on the spirit
Prayer times when you lose a job
Being unemployed sucks
Manufactory creators I wish I could give you a button factory
Or Candy Factory or what
But I think that's when I look back on my life
A lot of times
There were times that I lost jobs and it felt like a worse thing in the f****** world
But it ended up being
Positive
Eventually
Yeah
You find you find some brother job and you know maybe you never would have
Had the opportunity to find that other better job later
So John
Deeper keep your eyes to Bomgaars I have no idea why that what came up
Because I am not somebody who's good at expressing optimism
Things will get better
BoBoiBoy
Jordyn Woods
Bright bright spot I'm going to keep
With the theme of cartoons Harley Quinn just finished its third
Season and it's a really good cartoon
Start from this place like imagine the old classic Batman the animated series with Kevin Conroy sure
The best cartoons of all time
Imagine if you started with that show but from the premise that we have
I've landed on now where
Batman is a billionaire destroying the world using his money only to serve his
Your game right
Right to start from that point of view and then make Batman the Animated Series
Fantastic
Really really great Batman's a piece of s***
Like it's it's so good Commissioner Gordon is the absolute worst
A cab all day like it is it is a very
I rarely check things out the maybe I will check that out
The only problem that I have
I have not seen the show so I'm not entirely sure but
There's a pervy preoccupation with Harley Quinn that I'm not comfortable
And the centerpiece is a relationship between her and poison ivy which people who have taken too creepy
But I would argue that it's actually way more of just a positive representation kind of situation always the create
Leaders intent ND
Material isn't always the problem
You're not wrong you are not wrong but yeah I feel weird
He's a great voice he's fantastic
What's grits great show
Sure
So Jordan today we have what was not a great show that is Alex's show at night also Alex's trial
Connecticut
BP 13th and Fort
Tuesday and Wednesday of this week
Some clips
And then Alex's shows from those days
And he's up to while all this is going down
Board exam himself
With a certain level of respect that he hasn't shown in the past right
Yeah man he's classic
Before we get into anything and even before we talked with the wind so I wanted to say we always used to talk about this
Logistical stuff on are all that much but you know today
We were set to record at a certain point
I needed to push back half an hour
And Jordan you accommodate me when these things come up from time to time
And I really just wanted to say
Nope nope
I just wanted to say
I really really really do.
Will be gone and all that will be left as you're selling board I mean here's what's going to happen
Where can I return to the beginning eventually there will be 50 people listening
Because it's just going to be you and me is old man with you just playing soundbites at me
Giggling it's possible yet
You really thought I was going somewhere sincere with that didn't you
Until I turned it was all over
Thank you for accommodating my time schedule anyway I was okay
First let's say hello to some new
The first
Bobby aka the other Shane thank you so much you're now policy walk
Very much
Hero to the swatch
Next my fiance Emily cuz she gets annoyed when
When I come to bed and turn this on to sleep from Laura Elise
Thank you very much
That's fair that's a free bit of marriage
Lake Orion
Don't don't
Don't play this a bad fall asleep to
Snot Curtis
Next music at
Okay Felix double helix
Very much so either way this could be Buttercup you or buttercup
I'm not sure but either way you're not a policy wonk
Thank you very much to your door so first
Suspect has no Heroes
Do you want our technocratic
Delayed on this and I'm very sorry about that but
Marcy the walking bear thank you so much you are now a technocrat
I'm a policy wonk I have
Risen above
A little break e for me
And then we're going
To come back
And I'm going to
Start the show over
F*** you
I got plenty of words for you but
At the end of the day
F*** you and your new world order
Horse you rode in on
And all your s***
Maybe today
Maybe I'll just be gone a month baby
5 years
And you never see me again
Really what I want to do
I apologize
Was legitimately having breakdowns on air
Better tomorrow
He's not now I didn't
So
Jordan I wanted to
To say
We got the Connecticut case started we've been watching the stream and texting
Execusource
Quite a bit I think we both came into this with the plan of like
I don't know if I'm going to watch the whole thing this time end
Actually
I would say
My defense
I came in with the perspective of I don't want to do this
Again
Last night was a lot
And it was very concerned about redundant
The same thing again
Right but it is
It's not
It's a different
It's a different Beast than be the Austin
Situation
First
There's a lot more planes
Second
The case accuses Alex of slightly different violations
How it has a bit more to do with the business end
Of his his operation
So there's a bit more there a bit more meat
Study can look at
Then third and most importantly Norm pattis is akam
Sweetly different brand of lawyers and right now is representation in Texas
We've long wondered why it is exactly that Norm is Alex's lawyer
He seems like a mope generally and he's a really embarrassing loser outside the courtroom what with his stand-up adventure with
Who's actually so bad that there's no need to list a second thing here in this month
That you're that forever
It's a little bit it's already like I've been a bricklayer for 30 years but you f*** one monkey
And they call you monkey f***** Jim you know they never call you bricklayer Jim they call your pants down racial slur Jack
Exactly
Norm gets paid because he will do anything
He's a mercenary with a law degree and he doesn't give a s*** how awful the things he's saying sound or who they hurt
That became crystal clear on day one and it really gave me a sense that as bad as how it's his lawyer wasn't Austin
He at least had some boundaries
He didn't seem like it at the time until I saw Norm
And realize how shity raynol could have been
If you had wanted to
80s crazy
We're going to start today by looking a bit at norms open
Statement and Toca Boca
Particularly shity things that happen
And then we're going to tune in to see what Alex was doing while this was happening
It's always good Whenever there is simultaneous like you can put up
Suck my side Brock
Sued into Oblivion
Airbnb like
We're winning that our asses off yeah things are pretty good
Do things considered
Also there's a pleat I want to yell about the most important we find
So here is a little bit from Norms opening isn't great on this
Yes I have to say
It's from the law and
Sort of
Big Heath
What money is
Award enough
He was mocked
Wild
First of all just being so blunt as we like we're just going to say if their claims are exaggerated
Yeah
Hey listen
That's fun and say that maybe we didn't actually do it and this time we're like
Sure we did it we did it we're already guilty
But it wasn't that bad it is to come on different
I think it takes a certain level of
Hello Miss to
Just say something like that out loud
Yeah one of the things that I noticed is the norm did have a bit of a faulty delivery
There was
Moments where it almost felt like you was
Thinking I'm going to say this
But I might be attributing that to him unfairly based on
What do you like the way he ends up comporting I don't believe he was
Like worried about things
I mean in my in my thought process I didn't see that so much as Occam's razor
Told me that like
He's just kind of winging
Delivery is not great
So
Norm
Does he does
Maker basically
Partisan
Xanax
The plaintiffs
Yep
Why not to chill
PowerPoint
Evil
Remember this
They walked into a
Divisive
Naruto
Your honor
Okay
So yes my client murdered this purse
But he did we saw the evidence
He did fight back is he a victim
Obviously not
There is a
Sickly
I can
What do you put in for theater is is
It essentially saying that they put themselves in the arena
It's just Alex's words more laps today
There was a sense that it's like alright
This is the guy who's taking direction from Alex
Trying to do something like a lawyer with Norm it really feels like all right
Swing is hard and in the direction Alex want
Hey and I'm going to use me words and tactics that I've learned in law school
Yeah you know it's f***** up
It felt like
Rain always trying to transmute
Alex is b******* into something that you could
Pass
In a courtroom
Enormous like you can put a powdered wig on Alex's bulshit
I say some b******* that's what's going to happen
That's not great
I think
That
This also is
Inappropriate for the damages portion which is obviously why we have
Some of these objections if he's ours is Chris Mattie the plaintiff
Lawyer here is
Contesting this is an attempt to unravel the
Default judgment litigated in a place where it is inappropriate
It is a bit like non of your honesty he's a public figure
No
We're past that
Yeah
Norm's continues to behave poorly after the sidebar
20 presidential
She never got it
Proper
That was
It is opening statement
Reservoir chinos like this is going to be bad
This whole thing is going to be bad
Based on Norms Behavior
He clearly knows that this isn't appropriate
And then
How many times did Iowa Jack
Kind of a response in open court is like this guy is unhappy
This could go any number of directions
As I described it to someone
Feel safe
When I'm watching this threat to me personally but I feel unwell like I'm not in good hands
Yeah yeah there is
I appreciate
How willing
Everyone else in the courtroom is to abide by Lexi
Oh I can't wear shorts
You know like that kind of s*** and he's just walking out here like
You hear how many times I f****** objected
How about that s*** judge
To the judge it's
While I mean we'll talk about that a little bit more later but if you do on the second day he wasn't
Standing up to make objections till Friday
He had to be scolded about that which is
That is a huge disrespect to the Core
I think some of the core perceived your stuff is a little bit silly from the outside hilariously stupid
You've agreed to exist within this space
You are a lawyer you know the rules
What are the rules are
You respect the f***
Can Court
Listen I'm on your team if you want to be like hey standing up two objectives f***
Stupid we're all sitting down here this is fine
If you want to argue that
I'm on your team
We're back
The time though you've already been in court for hours at a different setting I'm hearing that argument 100
Hey call about it
Search
Too late now that it's bizarre the way we do this stuff and I'm not entirely sure why we do great
The waterslide you like maybe we should add water to this you're already halfway down bad
So he's been scolded
About the Hillary Clinton angle
Who tries another one
He worried if you
Deptford m
I mean it's just
You know I was texting you I'm like
You keep swinging
Yep know there's something to be said for persist
I don't think my parents
When I was a kid
Persistent about things
Like being able to stay out to ride my bike or something and I wouldn't get my way and my parents
Very much like
This is bad
You shouldn't do this
But
Persistence is a trait that may pay off in
I feel with Indiana Jones and the Last Crusade like you lost this one today
Vacated let me put the Hat on you and you're still trying to get it back into the museum 20 years later I get it
Yeah
In some contexts
Persistence is a very admirable trait
In this one
New
I mean why fast just on a like from what I've seen level
Because
At assert
Points
You can only say one more time and you're done mr. pattice
Before I don't give a s*** anymore how many times you say one more time
Cuz we've got no one more time
Literally every day
Yeah that's
True I think
That's
The one more time maybe as a
I'm being serious
Blackpink
I think
Giving a lot of
WYD
Birth to this
I think that that is
Still appropriate
Like
It's it I've made this point
Before in these circumstances like you don't want to
To do any
People have babies
You don't want to give them
The ability to
Credibly argue that they're being poorly treated and so I think
I think that kind of have to act that way
There is sucks
There is a certain amount of your watching Wylie Coyote run off the
The cliff
And he still being a dick and he still running
And you're like there's nothing beneath you
You got to stop running
But he just keeps running your like
I guess I'm not going to be the one to tell him
When the floor it doesn't exist but sooner or later the floor will not exist and he's going to fall a long way
Yeah I don't know I don't I don't see much floor here
I just there's just parts of this that I was like I don't know why he's saying these
At the end of the face
What exactly
The world is filled
Allison
Liar Liar
When did flip
What is he even say
IR mean
There is a
First of all this very bizarre admission that he seems to be making there that is like
I ate you got to take it on face value that Alex has a liar like that losing a loved one hurts
That Alex is a liar
We know these things
Okay so that's great
Is this song up there
So
Guess
Hard to
Come back from that and be like well Alex is actually
Dunno you serious and tell the truth
Try some how to save this which is
What he has.
There's no continuity here second thing is that
You know
Yeah
Sticks and stones
Maybach price
That's good when someone's insulting
Right you know riseabove
The insults share whatever
I don't know me sing the Norms of
F****** child
Rise above it.
When your
Defaming somebody
And there is material harm that is done by Your Word
Osos no longer
I'd like the lies that Alex is telling I'm not Jeff Blake
Fun lies
Defamation law
If you do I mean words can never hurt you until you print them out in block letters
Out of a titanium that weigh 1,000 lb and then drop them on your head
Adventure
Just the words analyze or not
Necessarily the end-all-be-all of what this case is about
Right right
So that that's the other illusion that Norma's perpetuating
This this idea that Alex is just like questioning things the idea that it's just words and stuff
Is the attempt to unravel the default judgement
Deeply inappropriate
I mean
It is
A little bit I the result of the default judgement
But like
The default judgement
Is a default judgement
Because all of the arguments that they would have made in court
Are essentially it admits of
And they're still trying to make
Those argument
And you can't say
You guys don't get to say anything now
Because you lost
You can't say that I mean as you said you know
Giving them a wide berth is a reasonable thing to do
But yeah
Listening to his opening argument I was sitting there going like
Technically you can't say that
Michael you can't say that
Technically you can't say that you know just checking it off the list
Yep
What you going to do persistence pays off
I guess
Well that is long as those checks from Free Speech systems
Exactly as they do that
So this I took
Particular issue with
Another book
Injection Ian
You're welcome
Worries
The trails
Did Hillary
Shut off
Regard regard
An interesting tack that Norm is trying here because he's essentially arguing that Alex has simultaneously real
Serious and important in on the right
Track but he's also a raving madman who you should just ignore
At first glance this seems like a message message at Alex shouldn't endorse but if you think about it a little more you can see
This is exactly the kind of ambiguity
The cultivated about himself in official Circle
For his audience
You serious all the time
And all that
Stuff about Chemtrails and s*** is
Very much sincere and real
The rest of us and in a courtroom
That isn't going to fly
A different tactic needs to be employed
And it's bit sometimes he serious and sometimes you should just write off what he saying is crazy
It's a perfect evade any responsibility for anything you say but simultaneously allow yourself to feel like a big boy
Hero about things you want to be taken seriously
Shreveport
There's an uncertainty about whether or not any particular thing Alex says should be taken seriously and that works really well
In this
Take that deadly seriously and recognize that Alex was way ahead of the curve on that is essentially a profit
Claiming that murdered children's family members are actors and the whole thing didn't really even happen
Come on he's crazy you can't take what he's saying seriously
You can see how this game but Norma's playing works
Very transparent
I don't want to take this one step further
I do think that the things that Norm is listening off as the crazy stuff Alex says that you should discount as the ravings of a Madman
Are things that you should absolutely take seriously
Alex isn't someone at a street corner is Norma wants to
Implied
Talking to himself about outlandish theories
How does a multi-millionaire business
Is Miami's greater career out of disseminating these outlandish theories to masses of people
He's not the one on a street corner he's a demagogue with International reach
And the Ravens that are just supposed to be ignored
Those are things that is audience or supposed to know that Alex's lawyer would describe that way in
Court these are very serious very real
Completely documented conspiracies that are aimed at killing you and your family
This isn't up for debate on Alex's show but mysteriously
When you're a formal setting surrounded by people who aren't indoctrinated into the full
These are examples of things that Alex says that prove you shouldn't take what he says seriously
The ludicrousness of the thing
Things Alex says is used as a defense
Against him taking responsibility
For the real-world damage
Causes and I think that is something to take very seriously
Even beyond that the thing is Norm is listing offer
F***** up conspiracy theory
Many of which have their roots
Anti-semitic trope sarmista
Leah the eating of children and drinking their blood is A holdover from the blood libel
Many of the conspiracies about poisoning the water in the air hearken back to well poisoning accusations about Jewish people intentional
Please brighten the body
Plague
Leaving aside these bigoted route to this talking point
They're just very serious dangers in the way that
Anon
Insignificant number of people and
Some elected officials are using pedophilia accusations to rile up their followers into a state where there
Causing real damage to people
Primarily aimed at members of the lgbtq community
Even if we
We aren't supposed to take Alex's theories themselves seriously
If we responsible members of the public we do need to take the reason they're being spread
Seriously
We need to take the impact that they have seriously and the game Norm is playing here is an attempt to run cover for that
I'm pretty sure he knows what he
He's doing cuz he's a piece of s***
Fisher-Price ball bat sticks and stones
Make it balance
Dark yeah
I feel I feel like
We like watching this
Like
You know we've discussed in the pastor that the world got lucky that we haven't become
Right-wing Nut Job
On account of you know we went I
Failure of the time you know
That is that is right for becoming a right-wing s***
That kind of thing
But
If I were
Were one of those
Then my legal strategy would be
F*** it
Every
Nothing I say is crazy
Everything
And then I go into it in court and be like
Why would you be racing
I do not see that there's no genetic-based like I would go ham on everything I've ever said and be like sea
Look at how silly it is that people believe any of this s*** and then go on air and be like
I didn't mean any of that
Nobody cares
It's yeah it's
It is a little bit
It's a bit strange that there is like the rails for them where they're like I won't come out in
And say that hating gunman you hating like anti-gun she stupid
Also they don't want to blow up their game
I think the problem is that you're imagining a situation where you don't have like an elaborate business to protect
If you could do that in your hypothetical scenario where there isn't like
A warehouse full of pills
For me it would also be like oh I see the writing
This business is not going to be mine for that much longer so I might as well get me taken care of
Cuz I'm a right-wing psychopath s******* like these people are just aren't smart I honestly think that
The more you talk tomorrow
Realize you wouldn't cut it
I really would
Accepted into the circle
Is
Cut the kind of chaotic energy they don't want around your house
Hey I am the Joker I'll burn the bottom half of the money
Yes
Listening to Norm's s***
For now
But we were going to jump in here on the 13th
Alex's
It starts often
Maybe I was feeling too picky
That kind of data yeah
Everybody knows about the frog in the Boiling Pot of water
Analogy
It's actually
Louisiana Mississippi
Like to eat
The crawdads in there
Bullfrogs
Well sometimes they just throw the whole frog
In The Boiling Pot
Maybe throw one in the boiling water he'll just jump right out
Water
Turn the heat up slow he thinks it's a hot tub at first and then
America and the world is right
We're in the middle of the New World Order
This isn't true
Frogs don't just sit in water as you turn up the heat
People have conducted tests on this and its really can
Consistent 30 frogs have a way to get out of the water as it gets hotter they do
Also they don't just magically jumped out of boiling water
Also there are less people conducting this test for obvious
Humane Animal treatment reasons
Biologists have discussed the Prospect and it's
Pretty clear that you know frog being thrown into boiling water would just be burned immediately by the scalding water
Headache try to escape but probably die
Yeah even if it made it out of the boiling water
Probably circum to injuries
Prom viburnums
Barely get back out of boiling water
Response
This is a fun analogy for Alex to make because he comes from the school of anti-communism that he was all social Prague
Grass is the incremental change that is the metaphorical temperature of the Water Rising
It's all kind of a fantasy though and the real metaphor is that the rising temperature of this particular water
His Eye Is killing off Alex's ability to live in a society that caters
Solely to the needs of straight white Christian
The metaphor understood appropriate
Yeah
Yeah I hate I do I do appreciate he has a what would I say and almost
Fermental commit
Back to taking any down-home country aphorism and being like
And that's 100% true yeah you know Hugo Outback you catalog and then you're going to break your leg
That's 100% true if he comes from the old country
Ironically
The phenomenon that's described by this boiling frog analogy actually kind of does apply to our Collective response
What's climate change
And that scenario we are all frogs trapped in this pot and Alex has a frog yelling at all of us at the water is not getting any hotter and
In the globalist
Does pushing that idea
To get us to give up our frog guns
Senpai frog taxes
So
I just got out I just got an image of like a giant
Gumbo Pot with
Like 20 frogs on either side of it armed to the
The teeth playing a game
The chess that kind of that kind
To feel sure
And this is one who's just yelling at them the water's fine
So
Maybe a little nitpicky but I was bored
Anyway Alex has a big nose
And that's where we are as a culture
As a civilization
The culture War
Tucker Carlson talked last night about the horrible next level
Deception
Censorship
That is taking place
Master of Lies
The New York Times
Okay
Dishonest is the New York
Any idea what this is about
Do you want to guess what this is about God I don't know
I hate okay
New York time
The New York Times must have published I don't know maybe
Maybe Aaron judges 57th homerun wouldn't have gone out
Interesting
What C
How drunk was the
How angry is Hillary Clinton
Have her husband
What
Caucasus is very
Extremely
Is hard to put in
Towards
Describing the dishonesty of the New York Times
Sample
Connecticut tells you more
Paper towel
Set the best-selling book
United States
The titles called my mom died
Buy a child
Best-selling book
In America inside
Showing book in America last week with my God
Oh my God
I never of predictive it out of here
He's whining like Alex about Alex on his show and Alex's playing Tucker walking
Fuct
So one thing we should just
Get clear before I get into any of this is it for over a decade and probably way longer than that people have been a big can
Confused about how bestseller list work
There is not well
Really precise science doing any different publication
Guilty different listings
Because they use different metric
I went to check the New York Times list and sure enough I'm glad my mom died is the number one but if there's some kind of
Weird systemic bias
On this list
I don't have Jared kushner's book breaking history is coming in a number
Free
3rd week on the list
Seamstress
What about number 30
Team on the list of being a book battle for the American mind
By Peter gexas and David
Which is described as quote
Fox and Friends Weekend hosts makes his case for what he calls a classical Christian education
Time to just say no
Thank you to that
If they're just manipulating their s***
Inclusions I just don't believe for a second that there's like a systematic bias against Alex's book
No course not
There's one factor that I think is working against al
Alex and that is
Pain of his books are being purchased directly from his website at a giant marker
Stop playing quite a bit about how he has to sign them all before shipping them out
What is Wednesday show he said that he sold 14,000
Copies on his own web
Tri-C purchases through Infowars wouldn't
Confirm purchases the times of factored into the rankings
Partially because Infowars store doesn't report sales data to the
The time
This is a major part of how the time to make their lips
From their website about the list methodology
Quote rankings reflect unit sales reported on a confidential basis
By vendors offering a wide range of general interest titles published in the United States
Every week that wasn't the diverse selling locations report their actual sales on hundreds of thousands of individual Tire
The panel of reporting retailers is comprehensive and reflect sales in tens of thousands of stores of all sizes
And demographics
Across the United States
So you know they have like some smaller
Operators of smaller bookstores some chains
Amazon course
And so they have these
To get a sampling of
Where books are sold
This is where Alex is probably hurting
I would guess that he doesn't have like really great distribution for this book
Probably not being carried in many stores
You got his own website and Amazon
Buying is done online picture that is often
Ignored
Alex's book is currently number five
On Amazon's top seller list
That's just
Based on purchases so it's a little more straightforward in terms of ranking
Incidentally number four on that list is I'm glad my mom died so he's not beating Jeanette they are either
Also number two is
Cookbook written by Steve Doocy and his wife so really.
Why isn't the New York Times charts
Steve Doocy up there everyone should be asking
King is why try to write well
Why
It looked the point is the Tuckers not making a
Listen to your argument
No absolutely no
Also
Please remember this is apparently the top story on Alex's show the day his trial in Connecticut is beginning
As this episodes airing Norma's in court
Like anybody's Book Sales in the New York Times snubbing him well for his doing his disgraceful bulshit
Oh no that's all in character and s***
You know like
F******
Tucker Carlson is going on National to little degrading TV
New York Times
I mean that
Painful
You're the most important man in the world
It's a little other that is why he's the most important man in the world
Stryker gets into the numbers
56000 copies of his book last
Whatever
86 copies
Look in the country
Tucker's number for McCurdy's book is pretty specific
EXO is pretty simple to track that down check
This is from the Publishers Weekly list of top hardcover front list nonfiction
On that list McCurdy is number one with 30 4686 units sold
And Alex's number
2 with 30649 with 50
54 something thousand
No
Number of book sold from Alex
The several thousand copies
Please that he signed I'm guessing that he took the number of McCurdy's book sold from Alex
Stew because it cited in a bunch of Infowars articles about how the times is Shadow Banning Alex share
What's this
Books don't only come in hardcover and nonfiction that doesn't sound true
On the overall list from Publishers Weekly and McCurdy's book is at number 7
With four of the
Top 6 books being by Colleen
Hoover
I was just leaving on the top 10
Bipolar
Brutal
If Alex really wants to make sure that all is right in the universe and make sure that the book that sold the most copies as number one
Adult romance novel
Should be at number one
Not McCurdy
Yeah
He's not doing that because he doesn't actually care about other times Alyssa's
Compile this is just about him taking his own Petty grievance and insecurities about feeling left out
A pretending it actually reveals a political
Four point
You also very clearly sees the potential this has is awaited
Drive sales
I have the article on Infowars says quote
The New York Times excluded Alex Jones as the great reset from its rightful place on the list
It's time to end the censorship
Put conservative voices for bestseller list
That articles maybe 700 words long and it includes
6 hyperlinks to the Amazon page to buy Alex's.
Also I should know that the book is 36% off its original price like a week into its release
Which definitely doesn't scream
We fleeced people on pre-orders and now we're trying to sell off the rest of these books at a cut-rate
Play don't fill up the warehouse
Alex did well
He cashed in a bit on a book
HP proud of himself returning his incoherent something thousand books
But this whole thing is a bit
Really pathetic
For Tucker to be jumping in a basically doing
Based on an Infowars article about how the cool kids at the Times aren't letting Alex sit at the table
Yeah it's a little bit
Yeah yeah
And not just that but like wow
Only 50,000
Inbox
Like the biggest
That's the biggest book in America is 50,000
Rough it does go to show the numbers of book
Soldar lower a lot of the time than you think
Yeah but then the second thing it goes to
To show you is
Look up
It's great like if you were to sell 50,000 books
I would say
Amazing
Yeah that's awesome congratulations bro
If Alex is selling 50000 book that's not good
No
I was because
It's because of who he presents himself as
He's the biggest thing in the world is the number one media source is the Howard Stern of Truth
Absolutely
The Patriots in the CIA and the FBI and all this s***
World
Friends with all the most powerful people bolsonaro listens to his show everyday bright now that he doesn't want to directly associated
What's up with Putin listening to show all the time. It's much easier for him
50000 is like this is sad bro
No I think I think
Overall I think I had in the first two weeks like
10000 downloads which to me was
Approximately book
A hundred percent of our audio
You know like
That's the best conversion rate we can get that kind of vague
That's amazing it's not I don't have Billy I don't have a hundred million dollars in my back
It's good it's good for you and what you are great for reports to be
A bat
Also like you saying that 14,000
No sales through his
His website
He's selling something and I'm just giving something away
But
The number of button
Like if we're just talkin about straight-up response rate number doesn't look so impressive
If you look at my inbox true but
What about that Faraway necessarily
Tempe free Bryson
That's a variable
Anyway this whole thing is really yummy do know why he's doing this
And the bandwidth
Hundred thousand dollars a month
And the more popular we get with our own platform the more money I got to pay so I'm not bitching and complaining
Zeitgeist we are in the pole position we are winning we are hurting them we are inspiring Liberty movements worldwide
That means you are
But I need funds
Quite frankly
Find the books in the message it's the Death Star plans
Cam
Some money
What's this song
Green fiber capsules the highest-quality
Everyone loves green fiber capsules
Really even though
The playing of the Tucker peace
Sales
Whole beginning of the show is just saying
It's
Sad saying that if it was like
These swords
Are the best swords we have on the market
Actually know what
Play clip
Of somebody saying these swords
And then we'll talk about it because these doors are so f****** great
Yeah
So there's big news
He's done his peace
Bacon
Inflation's off the hook
Business sales
Across the border down
Stagflation
Football games all this crap
Please set aside some money
Bankruptcy
Continue on or this shuts down
And we are barely profitable
Able to show we're profitable
Those forward in just six weeks
So we're going to talk about this towards the end of the episode does Alex
Like it's a little bit more clear about this chat the way he's talking about his bankruptcy leads me to believe that he might be trying
Trying to defraud the bankruptcy court
And he might be discussing this plan on are in a way that is
Hello flagrant
NADA hide in plain sight
Do your crimes on the radio
Inflation is on fleek
Stagflation
That's in Britain that's what you do before you get married
Haversack
I need more money stuff
Sheriff keeps trying to
Pick me with this I'm going to get to the news thing
I like that
He played the Tucker clip as a way to sell his book
But the whip
He sold his book as a way to
To sell something this has a higher profit margin by saying don't buy my book
It's
It's a sale within a cell
So we actually do get some news on that this isn't a baton
We have them
And the good news is
Unjustifiable
John Hopkins go public with a major study
Shots 28 X
Worse than the virus
Okay
How would you do 98
I don't know
Substack
We kept this little gem for himself second smartest guy in
In the world which is pretty
Pretty cool
Guessing first place
Isn't his twin brother still Ben Stein
You still up
You was
Yeah see what what a weird what a weird life we've all had that show
To that's the weirdest part about it I have neutral feelings but Jimmy Kimmel now a negative
Of all the co-hosts Jimmy Kimmel has had
Never have made it past
What how many years talk about the Iceman 12
He likes
You're a good person
Person question who's worse benstein or a Syrah Cola
Probably Adams worst movie
I actually enjoyed the hammer when I was younger but I don't want to revisit it that's fair
The question
Is definitely answered
With Adam and here's why
He fell
Like there was rude you know you had a feeling that he was somebody who was being helpful
He was very funny
Maybe again I don't go back and revisit it about it but then to now off terrible
Was speechwriter for Nixon
Bueller
That's what that's not enough for me currently it is
Jim hoft
So this is as always what they're talking about is a preprint article that's being reported on by a covid denial propaganda
So this isn't even really getting my eyebrows raised
Skipping freon
Kind of thing
Absolutely did not read this study it's 50 pages long and he doesn't even sound like you read the title
Jim hoft
Blog before cold reading it on air
You just making up what he thinks he's reading
To the study itself is a cost-benefit analysis of mandating booster shots for people under 40 particular
Early in the contacts
Text of college
The argument is that these mandates may not have heard that many hospitalizations and I can see where that may may
Make some sense
I think that would be very reasonable if people under 40 of people over 40 never came into contact with each other but seeing as we all
Intermingle
And vaccines are a community-level solution to a problem not an individual level one I have some issues with the
It is the very idea of
That being said Hawks headline is b*******
The study did
Say the directions are 98 times worse than the virus is Alex's work
That number 98 is used in the paper is the high-end estimate of the number of serious Adverse Events you might expect
Seeing hypothetical College of 30,000 students were all given the Boost
Also the paper hasn't been peer-reviewed so their numbers
Methodology might be
We suspect
Play self-reported
I mean hypothetical University
Who knows
In this covid time preprint articles have like just math
Problems
Calculated wrong I don't know what to do with it
Yeah
Let's get that
Peer reporting in World talk
How do you
Claim that
Without having some
Concept of what it is that is 98 time
You know Snyder times worse
Mathematically how
Like Okay so covid
This is one covid
Is 98 covid
But I don't know what that be
It's like a Nicholas Shay of danger 98
Worst cops
Every cough
98 Topps 98 cost
So anyway Alex is the leader of the resistance
We are the American resistance
Pleasure
Glisters a bat
Your commissioning of this operation
Vicious
This is the Platinum standard
This is it right here
I don't know that
Don't think it isn't a giant weight on me
If you could
Temporary
Remind
Obviously of course America is
Resistance in America is coming out of a place like that
It's the way the world still is
Texas coast
Crocodiles
So goes the world
Who said that
The Eisenhower
When was first elected president
I looked it up did you look it up
Eisenhower won the 1952 election but he was inaugurated in January 1953
This court does not appear in that inaugural
Speech speech ever gave cuz it's
Not good
I believe if I had to guess Alex's misremembering this line from that
Whatever America hopes to bring to pass in the world must first
Come to pass in the heart of America
You can interpret that as being like the Heartland and Alex might think that's Texas or just the Texas is the heart of America either
That's as close As It Gets in this
Incidentally
In that speech Eisenhower also lays out 9 basic principles that is Administration would be guided by in terms of achieving
Let's hear those one of them is quote respecting the United Nations as the Living sign of all people
Hope For Peace
We shall strive to make it not merely an eloquent
Simple but effective for
That doesn't sound true seems like Alex would think that this is a dirty globalist speech
Yeah
You just get your just never going to get over
Quote not going to happen
No because in order to get a real quote
You would actually have to go look
For it
Or learn about it or read it in a book
Even Q eyes book of General quotes or whatever it was whatever they really said
Some of those were fake as s***
What you don't know
You don't know about quote
Yeah
The what is I can't remember exactly what state it always was
Azaman
Goes so goes the Country
IMM Thursday's expressions
I like the Electoral College
Yeah yeah yeah size Iowa does yeah yeah that way
Kind of framing has been used
About a number of states
It's over the course of our our
This thing
In terms of Eisenhower's in Ark
Colony of the Carolinas goes so goes the 13
So here's where I wanted to throw my hands up and just say I quit
Tucker Carlson the massively spending
Department attack
All every major national Trump supporter including Infowars
Shocks the conscience
Everyone who sees it
This should just be a Tucker Carlson recap show
Like it's just he's running a rerun of Tucker Carlson
This is nonsense
Why
Why are we why does this
I mean it's
Yeah it's national news show
Set wind for me
So I'm going to dedicate my entire broadcast to rebroadcast convention
Tucker segment
Much
Anyway Eddie Bravo side Alex
Sure that's a thing that we should say today
That's it out loud thing that should exist
Silence is reporting on this Instagram video that I'm reporting
It was just a light person but that's the most important people
Hundred thousands of years on
Instagram
Astrologist ashamed economy should I plug
Astrologist Shinigami implodes
All the stars
Why not
The globalist saying they would do this but
They do a good listing
Of some of the top back
Just canceled going out giving shows the next
Is 56 days out from the election
They're planning false flag
Alex is a lot of nerve talking down on astrologers and he gets his information from prophetic dreams he's had envisioned
Brought on by Chicken Fried
But those were sent by God not the Stars that's stupid
So this Instagram video that
Eddie Santa Alex has to do with like a bunch of musicians cancelling tours and stay
And it's like it's because they know that something's going to happen like a false flag terrorism concert
Frank is going to be another coronavirus lockdown or something I don't know
He has any Chosen One
So I found this video that's laying out there
Conspiracy
Cancelled events to make
The point that a lot of stuff
Getting canceled
First is the Weezer Broadway residency which of the headline that they showed says quote
Low ticket sales
So I don't know maybe it's not a surprise that Weezer on Broadway as not a hotdog Broadway
Bright
The next is about Luke Combs canceling a single concert because he had problems with his voice
I don't know
That happened
Shawn Mendes
Canceling a tour to take personal time
I've no idea who Shawn Mendes is good for him
After that is quote
Carlos Santana cancel Six concerts as he continues to recover
4 years old Nick collapsed on stage in July while performing in Michigan
Rob Thomas okay
Assembly
Like when when atoms become entangled I assumed that the how the what happened after smooth
Well I mean like when Carlos Santana collapsed onstage Rob Thomas said I'd give my world to lift you up
Pick you back up off the stage chair that does make sense
He was away though it has stood up in a middle of a restaurant
And started singing that and then somewhere off in the long-distance
Everlast is pissed off that
Put your lights on
My bad boy
Skip song
I think sure and don't Revisited
So that is another never heard of
The canceled
Fighters cancel all tour dates after drummer Taylor Hawkins
Death
None of these cancellations seems suspicious at all they're all
Pretty well understood we are ticket sales weren't going well Carlos Santana is old and collapse.
What guy canceled what got there cuz he had a voice issue and then
The drummer of their band.
Man did you see you didn't I assume you didn't see the the tribute concert his son playing the
Not a
Super
Easy song
DriveWise got it you got to have the string
Like to hit yeah you got to have the strength to hit on those and Euclid
The Poise
To be able to perform the path at all
Let alone
Free Foo Fighters
This crowd for your dad's got a lot of pressure it's rolls eyes
Does you play the drum solo that he wrote it's very impressive
Do to be able to be on that stage enough freak out yeah
I would be ready for it
Nope nope
Weeping
I think it's 60 I might have done a musical or a play at my school in it
Freak
Anyway
Honestly this is some of the stupidest most early 2000s conspiracy message bored as shyt
Eddie Bravo tipped him off on this one
Fingers crossed that we get to see Tucker dual segment about it next week and then Alex can cover Tucker covering it like honestly
Between
Playing
Multiple Tucker
Segments and on this b*******
I felt so embarrassed that this is the show we do
I feel embarrassed that this is the world we live in
Aaron the funny timer
This is turned into just like a water we
We doing here
Very stupid
Yeah everybody's making choices actively against their own
This is the part where I want to say
When I when I say going back to the past
Is more interesting for me there's more to do
A lot of it is because Alex is doing this like Tucker segments
The covid conspiracy of the day that I from so dumb asses sub stackshare and then Eddie Bravo sent me a
F****** Instagram video about some b*******
Skype
Find most important man in the world right now is Eddie Bravo
Totally
Dumb nonsense that I see people post that got like
100,000 views on Tik-Tok I don't think it's that hard
It might not be that hard
I don't know
Anyway
Alex is selling lots of books
And that money is going straight back into the show baby
Also the other coin
No thank you
I got $2,000 just paid them in the first payment
Growl
All getting dumped in
This operation
Come within the first few weeks
Lawsuits
The trials the attack
Fall the appeal should make $80,000
For years and keep this operation going
But it's up to you to find the operation thanks
Infowarsstore.com
Just shut you down
Every little doing the me they're doing to you we're just the focal point
All that fine
1776 koin.com
Liberty
I just show up 1,000 coins that are left
1000 yesterday
Yeah let's move these coins here's another coin you selling
As a businessman
I would like to see all of my business
It's done quickly
Slowly
I love to but he was like alright we're doing this series of four coins
Cisco before coins
Also hey I got a fifth
I remember when Batman Forever Came Out
You could get these mugs
From McDonald's or whatever is Frosty
I tried to get all of them
You know what I feel like those are worth as much now is that coin will be later
Right now I mean it is over price
So lucky take some calls
I don't care they're dumb
Boring
So let's go to the fort
Another
Covid-19
Conspiracy of the day story
Water broadcast you got lined up
Headline up on screen it tells you
All
Global bombshell
Confirmed covid vaccine causing a massive side effects and death
Top stories not going to show trial in Connecticut
All the fraud that's going on up there
Is the proof of the premeditated
Global un wef big Pharma directed mass murder
Wow
Curious about this bombshell report Alex is covering here so I searched for the words he was saying and imagine my surprise
He's just reading the headline for the article on Infowars
That includes the embedded video of the show that he's in the middle of doing
This is just a headline outlooks himself has written for this day's show
You can see the exact same wording
Repost it on tons of really shady looking blog
All of which are just reposting Alex's video
Weirdly none of them have links
Do these documents in this Israeli study that supposed to be the bombshell
But a little digging around and I found Alex's covering and it's
Just another post on Steve Curtis sub stacks
Jesus Christ there's a video on Rumble that purports to be from the Israeli Health Ministry having a meeting where they discuss
Findings better that
That's their Samba longer-term side-effect of the Pfizer vaccine that hadn't been known previously
Findings which are being said to have been covered up by Pfizer and Israeli
I can't find coverage of this on any outlet that I find even halfway respectable and I don't speak Hebrew so
So I don't know what's being said in this video
Right
The context in the original narrative framework for the story traces back to a post on Twitter by a woman named
First-year Roth
Who is credited generally as a health and risk Communications researcher and a health Journal
This translates to her running a website called real-time news which is kind of
It comes off as an Israeli version of a lot of the dicey sources that I run into on the show
Things like WorldNetDaily Gateway pundit
Steve kirsch's substack
If your name makes me wince
Then I know you know real time it is
That's not going to hurt its on creative and so Bland at me like you're trying to get something
I don't know too much about she
But it's worth noting that she was a major source of the fraudulent narrative that tons of soccer players were dropped
Dead because of facts
Seen side effects
You fudge data and miscalculated shocking numbers on that front
Which then became big talking
Points in the anti-vax world that we cover
For this reason and because there's absolutely zero reputable coverage of this video I'm skeptical of the way it's being.
These particular information sources haven't are the benefits
The doubt so I got nowhere to go on this
I can cover it as it's being told by these people and the ways that Alex is come
Coverage of it doesn't even
Match the version of it
I have no idea
Your day I mean yeah you're not going to win
Also why is Alex
Music I mean
So the Israeli Health minister
Has come out and said that Pfizer's lying about
Ostensible
That's the conspiracy no
So the video is of a zoom meeting
That
The is is like a group of researchers that were commissioned by the health Ministry
Tattoo look at side effects
And they apparently found some
Longer-term side effects
Handsome side effects that hadn't been
Seeing the signals
That Pfizer head
Take a note of
Haha I been Apparently after this the health Ministry put out a report
Or maybe even in conjunction with visor date covered up
These are the side effects
Better
That's alright
So then the government
Was covering it up
Yeah
Yeah the government advisor so
Okay
I mean
He'll just accept
Anyone who says what he wants to
Stepsis I like it doesn't matters like there's any resources that should be off-limits for him except
Anybody who says what he wants them to say and he'll also make up things
The add-on to thing right right
So we got another covid
Conspiracy of the day
But still won't release
They're desperately needs me some prison time
Thousand October report
So this is a fraudulent story
Essentially what it boils down to is semantics
The epoch times was running some stories about the
Cdc's monitoring of various data and they were contending that the CDC was not analyzing the data at all
The CDC it made some comments that they had used to data analysis method called proportional reporting ratio or PR
But in fact they'd only use that method
Between March 25th 2002
July 31st
S2000
This is clarified in the letter from the CDC director to Senator Ron Johnson who's questioning her about this
CDC and FDA chose to rely on empirical Bayesian data mining more robust technique used
To Analyze This
Proportionate reporting
Rather than prr calculations
To mitigate potential.
CDC perform prr analysis between March 25th and July 31st 2022 to Carrabba
The results of the EB data-mine
Notably results from prr analysis were generally consistent with EB.
Unexpected
If you signals
This isn't the story about the CDC not bothering data it's just about them using a different methodology that they felt was more you
Useful
Possibly someone misspeaking at some point of the
It is it is so funny
And end so just the world
Of humanity
That the idea of somebody
Going out of their way
To double-check if something's right
Is the source of a
Conspiracy for people are suspicious
That's only something that Liars would do sure
What
Fact-checkers throw people they're supposed
Flyers
Everyday
Articles
Football
Adjust
You're crazy
Not a single blood clot
But it's 6 ft of blood clots
Right so this is a headline that Alex's reading from CBN which of course is the Christian Broadcasting Network
This is about a high-school student named Kayden climber who had a large blood clot
Multiple
Nowhere in the story doesn't mention climbers vaccinations
Status outages make
Combat off because reporting every story about a young person who gets hurt as being the consequence of the
They're getting vaccinated
He can't make it
Point by discussing reality so you just makes up whatever works best for him so he can keep his audience
It's scared and it is sway
Incidentally the CBN story include this but Alex never talks about doesn't mention this at all
It's unclear what caused the extensive clots in his body but doctors diagnose climber with a condition
Called inferior vena cava at Tri-C
I just disorder can be acquired or congenital
Even the CBN is letting you know that there's a decent chance
Climber was born
With this condition
I looked up other sources on the story and no one mentions whether or not he was vaccinated
I did find a lot of angry blogs
Stories don't say whether he was vaccinated as proof that he is and they're covering it up
I think that's dumb
Also in July 2021 Ohio where this High School is located passed a law prohibiting mandates
For public school so there's
Literally no reason to just automatically assumed that he was vaccinated
Howard Stern
Care about the reality of the situation
To him this story is useful if the kid was vaccinated so we can make it look like this is a consequence of vaccinations
Don't need any proof to justify reporting
He was
That's so simple is brain is and how little he cares about what he tells his audio
I want to I want
Alex to sit and watch like a Premier League game
And just every time a soccer player goes down just be like
Forget all right next time
It's back to nation that cost
Default
It was
Actually
Five at least references pre-2000 today I think
I think we're old and I think I don't know forever was like 97 or
Something like that
I want to say
IWatch
World Cup with
My brother
Cuz it was like a hot dogs last
Emerald shop 2004
That sounds about right
Try to remember years I saw I saw that headbutt live
Yeah I feel like I did because I remember having a woohoo
Reaction today
And then there was a rap lyric
I'm like zidane how I kick it
And remember that I think I told you about it as no one else has ever heard
Probably
Some Nida debarros yelling at you
What is the date today
My brother was big into the French
Love tarot reading
That's all I remember
No
I only remember a couple of those French players and then the US
World Cup team
From when I was a kid they tried really hard to make like Alexi Lalas
Like a really cool grunge
Figure ghetto
Red herring
Yeah and then there was Marcelo Balboa
Very cool name wrong with a Marcelo Balboa I feel like he did the bicycle kick
And that
But you know sometimes remember you sometimes you think of you see somebody's name and you think of the moment
That their parents named
And you're like what were they thinking
But after like a Marcelo Balboa they must have high five like that's the best name we've ever come
Come up with
We nailed it feel like there were a couple other
People I remember on that team but let's
Let's move on
Cuz
A big name is about show up
Okay mediastar Bobby bar
But he's not on to talk about the trial
Constitutional lawyer historian good friend of mine
In the next hour
And no he's not here right now to talk about the show trauma Connecticut
He's here later to talk about
But he's involved shooting Pfizer Robert Kennedy Jr with the big whistleblower
The help this whole ball start rolling
Are butterflies around
Hollywood stars
Quarterbacks
I do like
Aaron Rodgers
Loving
But I I just get butterflies
Weather for Liberty
Wherever there's a battle against
Outside to save himself because he had just spent a while talking with her cool Aaron Rodgers was right he was on Bill Maher shiting right
I was doing the mityvac not Sanjay
Adult
Defrauded the welfare system not talking about that one right
So yeah Barnes is not talk about the trials you're talk about his
Doom the lawsuits
How do you how did he swindled JFK jr. Robert Robert Kennedy
It was hard
That's fair I think it works it's a
Perfect arrangement for the both of them it's a going nowhere and they'll both
Scam a bunch of money off their followers for it
Is true
Alex got to complain a little bit here about his trial
Number one again every major News Channel demonizing us lying about us
Explaining that you don't find somebody Guilty by a judge
And then have a show trial about how guilty
The are they
Time and the lawyers in Texas tying the hands in Connecticut with a difference is
And a wallaby like turn it off when she was spending hours lecturing
Because you took their own trial but then we can't defend
Borders are for me at this time
He's able to lay this out he's been doing live streaming with
Million viewers yesterday
With his colors
When Michelle got a bunch of Clips but just
Tell me my lawyer
You can ask questions about this you can ask question about that
We want to shut them down and take them off air
I asked these people
Question
It's incredible explain what's happening
Accurate at all but looking really expect
Insist that the plaintiffs are political operatives who transmitted their grief about a tragedy into activism against the second
Amber exaggerating the trauma in order
To use money in the legal system as Weapons against Alex
Because he's the only true supporter
The Second Amendment or something
I have a consequence of their default sanctions algaecide is
I'm permitted to make certain
Client which they could
Is contested and raised in an actual trial
If they hadn't engaged in a very clear pattern of malicious non-participation with it
Discovery process
It's the third day of the trial really seem to make clear
Many things that were intentionally withheld from Discovery
Particularly Google analytics data and it's not hard to see the reason that they were withheld probably has to do about it
How bad they look for Alex has ever use Google
Yeah I can only go by what Infowars says
Now sure
All those emails
They they look like we did Sunday 3 what we're referring to here
We have largely been the
Questioning
Of
And a lot of Thursday day 3
Had to do with the question of Google Analytics
Because they were supposed to turn over these Google Analytics
Fix data and claim
I just didn't use it I don't even use it
Decision
Right
And so it was
A lot
Of instances Bill brought up of Google analytics being referenced
In
And emails
And snapshots of Google Analytics
Yeah yeah
Witches.
The date of that
It's full without a full picture
It's not what was
Demanded and Discovery chat but it does very clearly illustrate that they were lying
And not turning over this for a reason
Well okay
So so okay
So here's what you're going to say when we turn this data over to you
Because we had a huge spike in traffic
And we knew about that by checking Google Analytics
We use that to decide what our coverage about Sandy Hook going forward would be
And we saw the
That the right way to do it was to lie about it and apparently there's a deposition of
Alex's dad David
Who said that when something works well they try to replicate it
Conjunction with
Looks really bad good doesn't look good
Have you considered
I've never heard of Google
The latest example of things they clearly didn't turn over that were responsive to Discovery demands
The texted Mark produced in the Austin case they'd included the word Sandy Hook
Clearly demonstrate either inactive decision to not turn them over
Or that Infowars didn't even look for the stuff that they were required to look for
Which is still
Against the discovery all the rules
Don't exist
Got old long ago but we're in another trial so we're going to hear this quite a bit
Ultimate irony is that Barnes was Alex's lawyer during a lot of the beginning of the discovery abuse so he might not
Alex's lawyer now but he's in essence the architect of getting out
Into the situation he's in now
Seems like the perfect person to interview about how you're being wronged by the courts
I mean that you can't help but look at this as
Barnes's idea
Write like from the beginning the idea was don't cooperate
Barnes was their lawyer
I think
You could maybe make that assumption
Incompetence is certainly a possible explanation
Strains credulity a little bit
I don't know if Barnes intended it to get to where it is now
I mean that is definitely
Open the air for sure because we have replaced a lot of lawyers
Many of whom in depositions
We have heard implied
We're not stoked about what they were doing
Mylanta
Said that they're considering suing Barnes her malpractice so there is that
The judge in Texas didn't turn off the internet feeds and lecture Alex's lawyer for hours that's just completely made up and actually might
Might be defamatory
Chris Murray the plaintiff's lawyer here in Connecticut did say that A fitting punishment for Alex's to get him off air
To make it
He can't profit off hurting people in the future
That could possibly be argued to be a little bit out there in terms of an opening but I think
It's fine
It's a damages hearing and the lawyer saying that fitting damages would be to impose whatever punishment makes Alex
Unable to continue doing this damage in the future
Misrepresenting the issue with Norms questioning of the FBI
Who was the first witness called by the plaintiff
Had to do with Norm asking inappropriate questions about whether or not he was one of the people in Connecticut
NBC-2 not are the mega
Can Kelly energy
It wasn't trying to take Alex off air per se
And Alex himself filmed a bunch of videos where he was trying to get that interview pulled so I don't even know what the point is here
Also Norm had no reason to believe that the guy was
Involved in that and his conduct was way out of line
It was part of a chain of things he got reprimanded for where he was trying to present to the jury that I was only getting sued because
Hillary Clinton
Putting on a Target on
Compromises that cool documentary Alex's War
Betfair
Partial documentary Alex's wargrave sounds very similar to Alex's
Defense
You know that I I just saw one of the best
Soundtrack
At 10
That is what Alex is war just did
It was a great soundtrack if nothing else
It's a Barnes has some thoughts
What about Norm
What are they
Well
Thurgood
Are they
I would have good. If you want to see what good
Advocacy looks like
Against a rogue judge
Play hostel setting
There's no better example
Does represent a
And I recommended
Watching that that video in this part of the trial
Do people all across
Interested in this
Particularly
Because how do you
Alex Norm pattis
You don't come
On the first day of the trial Norm almost got the jury excuse because he wouldn't stop making inappropriate statements in his open
Remarks
On the second day Norm got chewed out for openly disrespecting
By not standing up to make objection
On the third day Norman fell asleep for a short stretch
And then quote
Cuidate post from Mike cernovich about busing immigrants
To Martha's
You tweeted
Katie fell asleep I just the moments
Like we texted about it because it was the setup for a Three Stooges B where where it was like
The judge saying to the lawyers in the jury like hey
You know it happens sometimes where the jury has to get up and go out and get up and go out and I'm going to try not to make you do that
We're just going to talk to the lawyers here
And she's
Don't do what you're doing you can't do that
I'll have to set the turkey
He's like no
You're right you're right
I won't do that
And then 5 seconds later he doesn't she just screamed
Over here that was the moment
It was like
You can't you got to be kidding
This isn't allowed like an hour later
He's asleep but he's got like
Ping pong balls
It is an idiot
This is not a good job
If you would never seen a trial before
Ever
In your life
You would watch this s*** and go man
Bee stings are a lot crazier than I ever would have imagined I thought they were just
Quiet summer fairs I mean it's not it's not like
As chaotic as maybe you're making it seem
He's going to get a little loose
He's got a power up button
Yeah and I'm like I said
It's not fun
It makes me feel on it
It makes me feel worried
Cuz it's so disrespectful and
You know
Family members
Are in the court
You know that is something that has been brought up
Right and the cameras panned a couple times I've seen a couple people that I recognized share
That is a reality of this
Being
A s*******
Bright
Satisfactory
You should grow up
Woke insurance
So
Some bonds are pissed off
I want to make this about Hillary
What's the one name
That is all about
That this judge says campamento
Stampy asked about
He talked about
Opening statement
Disgusted in direct examination
Call Joshua question
Apologize about of contacts hurt somebody's feelings
Wow you will not bring that up
The closing months of the campaign 2016
Because of Hillary Clinton
And yet Hillary Clinton is the one name that can't be talked about
No it's a
Trying on
Do
It's it's a stab
You are liable
You are doing
By default
You can't pretend that you didn't
That's going to
Going to
F****** the entire kit
Hate to admit that she's lying
And he kept saying the word lie and Norm objected like
You can't say lie that makes it end
The judge has to be like overruled
It is a lot she can't just say like
No don't answer it's like yes you she's lying
What else is there to say
Not much
And the whole thing with Hillary
That's a really interesting
Thing you could have done in
In court if you had
Not gotten yourself
Assaulted by clear pattern
Of abuse
I mean
Sales
I-55
Yeah
Ridiculous
But it would have been appropriate in that other setting
For a while until the judge was like
You know this has nothing to do with anything rest
You are I believe allowed to defend yourself by being
No just completely like saying
Stuff that is like well that doesn't make sense
That's fair entitled to a nonsensical the fence
Suppose you're not
In this setting
Write the damages hearing it is a damaged
Just hearing things
Is real
Yelp
So they don't seem to understand
I mean it
Obviously
False not understanding
But why Bill Oldenburg the FBI agent is a plaintiff
Doing that you haven't
Damages and yet almost none of the oven
And look at their lead Witness
The media has
Covered everybody except
The lead plaintiff in the case who's the lead plaintiff it was the first Witness
It's not a sibling of anybody who died
It's an FBI lawyer in FBI lawyer
He's the one who's there lead number one playing at
I questioned something he can sue me
This is bureaucrats setting the precedent
To shoot people that disagree with him
No no it's not nope
But Barnes has decided that because he was the first Witness
Tell what this is all about
It's not evidence
Spell that
It's not about
Alex
Being
Call the person
Then who did
The thing at Sandy Hook
If the FBI agent isn't a member of the
I will say that Alex does again say that hit
People he knows and his lawyers
Don't know who Adam Lanza is which again is
Accidentally
Poor preparation on their part if that's true
The witches.
Here's a high-ranking well-regarded FBI
Council
This isn't some low-level smut
This is in he's there lead number one plane
Define Witness
This case
This is not about
This case is not even really about
The parents and the families or they would have been the first Witness
Are these lawyers
Usted
It's a FBI lawyer
You never even mentioned you never even reference
Has likely their first witness because he's a very powerful story about being one of the people who responded to the school
The horrors of what happened for sand
And then was subjected to a campaign of harassment in a text
Because of information put out by Wolfgang halbig and endorsed by Al
This has to do with the accusation that he was an actor and accusations that he and one of the parents were the
The same person
So it is all connected to the exact same stuff that is relevant
Barnes and Nobles this he's just a piece of s*** and he's pretending
This is just an FBI lawyer because Barnes is a piece of s***
Sticks and Stones buddy don't worry about it
Just an insult
Also weird that Barnes doesn't bring up that the second witness was Carlee Soto who was a relative of the
Toria Soto the teacher at the school who died
I guess you can really only get the sense of a case by the
Witness.
Probably want to just ignore that because it was
Especially
Call Julia for week-long
Another thing to keep in mind is that what
Covered does have a lot to do with images
And that aspect of this case
It's just acknowledging that is really dangerous for Alex and barn
First of all the anguish that these people live experience is incredibly real.
Secondly the details about Alex's business operation and how things work internally demonstrate the extent to which
The profitability
Of acting in ways that
Cause that anguish
It's all super relevant and if Barnes really wanted a chance
To deal with his stupid arguments in court he had his shot
I guess you could probably bring some of the stuff up to defend himself and Alex Susan for malpractice
Is that ends up happening
But yeah
Probably won't
Baby will
Deal right now is
Is trying to
Obfuscate the the connection
10 points between
Cuz here's the here's a fact
Do you know this is how they're busy
It's works here this is Avec
This is what they did this is a fact this is what happened all of those things
There are those Connecting Point
It's that the that the lawyers have to get
Do you know Alexa
Directly
Connect those
Thanks Jeff
The only place where they can argue is just like
I'm going to attack this connection and if I can't attack.
Flick connection
I'm going to attack
Whatever this space surrounded Hillary
Well I mean it's all healed
That's what connects
All of them
I mean
Alex I think you could argue
He's afraid of
Actually occur
Alex is not afraid of any
Should be evident
I don't have fear
A a a painter the dentist
We are now
On the Frontline
The New World Order
You want to back your family you want to back the future you want to fund something that's at the tip of the Spheres of slacking
We're at ladies and gentlemen so go now
The 1776 koin.com is a fundraiser
NPR fundraising
Yeah
You know there is something about a good Jam that either makes you a dancer say inspirational yelling things
You know what they'll have any true that MPR sells memberships and you get gift to the memberships that would cost less
If you just bought them at a store like a mug or something
Proofpoint difference though and I don't think I would be super into paying that much for a mug if Kai Ryssdal was desperately
Yelling at me to buy the mugs we can pay his legal expenses to fight a lawsuit that he's already lost
About how you define family members of murdered children into the pledge
Yeah
Hey
Marketplace is a show that I do just
Just so you know everybody knows where do
Fundraiser right now we're
Opening subscriptions for as many people as we can because
As we have been
Sued by
Families of Remington's owners really it is just a Hillary Clinton said it all
Something about the BBS
We're not allowed to defend ourselves in for
The connection
Offer
Clear end
Kangaroo court
They have already decided
So
Barnes has some Choice words
For the
The conservatives out there who aren't helping
Alex
Conservative
Oppress
Anybody that's involved in the legal size
I should be embarrassed and humiliated
I dare any of them
To watch yesterday
Proceeding and call that a fair trial to call that the
The beacon of America
America's justice system is supposed to be the beacon of Justice
The world
And right now it looks like it does
Dystopian
Just now
Alex
What Venezuelan show trials have you seen
What are you talkin about
Jabez
What
They were tried in Venezuela which one
Woodward trial we talked about there
By the Castro
He's out
And Alex has another gas
That's our boy Rogers
Any of them interesting
Shocked
It's to block
It's bizarre
It's not something that we're not supposed to talk about on Infowars
Let's let's go to the Waterfront Arrow Trucking in Florida
One of the things that's a disturbing me right now Alex are the actions of a Peter teal
For those of you don't know Peter tail is a
A billionaire was
Major financier of Donald Trump's candidacy
So real quick just a just a butt in here
Peter tales and brought up on it for
Second
You're not supposed to acknowledge that Peter till was a giant
Founder of Trump's campaign while he was self-funded with
Peter Thiel
Right button
Associating this
Right wing
Billionaire guy
With funding Trump
Is not something that is
Generally an acceptable
Rogers bringing it out
But he has some other problems
And he's
Forward
Essentially the underwriter
Millions of dollars of the endorsements of JD Vance
For the US Senate in Ohio
And Blake Masters in Arizona
Strongly support
Both of them America First candidates
But having Finance their nomination
Richard teal is now declining
To finance their General
And both of them are behind their opponents
Slightly
Behind their opponents
Mister chill comes forward and says wow
The Republican party has not
Defined enough of a
Positive
Image
Appositive
Program
All election
About the incumbent
Party about
The job that is being done
By Congressional Democrats in combination with the Biden
So Rodger is problem with m
Is that he gave these guys a bunch of money in order to run their primary campaign
They are unpopular and not raising money and Peter Thiel isn't
Continuing to give them millions of dollars right
To to prop up their General campaigns
That's an interesting gripe here's the problem
Okay these candidates
Alright
Sold themselves to a billionaire right in the billionaire bought them
But then the billionaire toss them away that's not fair place this with a Democratic candidate and George Soros
And
Here's how much here's how much it cost
To own a politician
Would you like to own a politician this is how much you have to spend
Wow Rodger
Rodger and some other complaints this one about Kevin McCarthy
This is what I want of the
When is your bedtime
Secondarily you have Kevin McCarthy
The following
Footsteps of
Newt Gingrich
Has
Put forward of a
Proposal
That is
Kind of reminiscent of the contract for America
Problem with this is
Honored to have a policy
Broad enough for every Republican
To support
I'm all one needs you to look at
The flipside of The Binding
Another words
I don't care for everything forward
Pale pastels
We need to have a bowl policy but it's easily defined
As being the direct opposite of that
Which of the demo
See Rogers really smart key
You can create a fake version of your enemy
And then to find yourself is
The opposite of it in
Trick people into supporting you
You for no reason
Basically the story of Alex's career
Guys
Stop it
Just say you're the opposite of this
We don't like this
All of this is basically Rodger his entire take on the midterms
And this interview is
Just classic Rodger
Attack
Don't defend ever
If this midterm is going to be about us being worried about your trial after the Sandy Hook stuff
About
Abandoned getting arrested but Michael lindell's phone being taken away
Trump being in trouble if they're Mar-A-Lago raid if we're going to
Like play those games at all
Fuct
Attack
Ignore everything
Just classic Rodger Stone tactics
You're not
No
No it mean it would be better if he was like reminds me of whenever I was an intern
Her Nixon campaign
And he was like
Should we just say why
And I was like no don't say it
Young Ben Stein
Are you going to say whites only on your Shoney's at
So Alex wants to know
Big Quest
Straub running bra
Rodger Stone
We know he told a lot of people including you and mg
Well I'm going to run
What is the inside base
Alex the only thing that's predictable about Donald J Trump is that he's entirely unpredictable
In a certain that's not good presidential on his home in Mar-A-Lago
Has galvanized his support so that I don't think a
Immediate
Announcement
Is a either
What you do in the offing
Or necessarily desirable
So maybe it'll be a little while
Maybe I mean
Re-enlisting the Mad Hatter to run for president
Because if the only thing that you guys need
Is that he's unpredictable
Dude I've I got news for you
If you don't want to study ham
That's crazy
Necessarily going to announce anytime soon wrong to play around but I wasn't doing on 4th of July
But yeah looks like Rodger get another definite
I happen to believe
The governor
Who's the governor of Florida my governor
Intends to announce his candidacy literally
Immediately
The election
And I think the president remained needs to remain mindful of that
I still think it is more likely than not
The heat will be a kid
Rodger stone is rarely wrong about his political
Sorry what
Analysis
Your opinion
DeSantis will announce after the midterms
In 56 days
A daddy's that's hard andjelija
Alex
Just my instinct
That's hard intelligence and by the way
As President Donald Trump has said
Ron DeSantis
Has the right to do that it is just bragging if to run if he
Wishes to run well Trump said it was cool
Wow
Is Trump's permission to what a good boy what a good boy he's been he got a pat on the head
It's hard until
We'll see
I told him you would be too surprised if it doesn't make sense
Make as much sense if you did it on the 4th of July
Taking back America
Taft
Another idea about this
Horses Australian got a secret agreement to run together
The Electoral College prevents that
Correct you cannot have a president and vice president from the same state
Because if you do you would forfeit the electoral votes of Florida
27 V that's too precious for us to do but couldn't rub your swing back
You think he wants to pay New York State income taxes I think
Wow this President seems cool
Shriya billionaire do you think he wants to pay us light percentage think that he
He cares enough about this country to take more taxes I mean
Come on man that the amount of
Grifter
Open
That Rodger can just talk about
As being a grifter that's wild
Acceptable to say it happened
What's Rodger found God
I guess maybe it's a I don't I don't give a s*** anymore
As God intended
About how I lied everyone all the time
Yeah
So we have two false Flags coming right
Horse absolutely
Football Flags
When you got
Hillary Democrat Party members like
Tim Ryan
Eagles
We saw the witmer staged attack
The number 141
They're obviously provocateur
Your take on that
You know as I have said here on the show and another places
I still yet
A fear
Some other kind of
Manufactured Health crisis
It's some kind of additional
Joke
How
How did it not work
They tried monkeypox cuz they didn't kill enough of the rest of us. How did that work if Alex has misconception that these super
Powerful evil people
Can just launched
Pandemics whenever they want and all this
Why didn't it work
According to Ali
What is
How
How is there a super villain group
That goes
Who's through all the effort
Right launching a bio-weapon
And then they're sitting in their their bunker their underground base and they're like
F***
It didn't work well well well
You need to understand though is that the devil is impa
Patient
Which is why he did the whole falling thing in the first place and he was behind and he's a quitter
Heize ain't listed the monkeypox thing it didn't work pack it up
Packing up around to the next idea
Pinky and the Brain
This is stupid Alex's fighting against
I told you we get back to Alice's bankruptcy
Dicey
Yes and that's that comes here this after Rodger leaves
And like
There's a weird tone
After I will discuss that here in a minute
Bankruptcy
Trial where I'm already found guilty
Budgies promising goldlink
On my children
I don't have
$1000000
Operations that says that's like
All those but
Just a week ago where like they were doing well in the chapter 5 bankruptcy
Ether is the future
Who cares
Open
The judge
Supposed to do
If you understand what he's saying
Basically what
He's trying to do in bankruptcy court
Artificially inflate the amount of money that
It's coming into the business to make it appear that he's profitable and solvent
Bye-bye just doing these things like
Do you know the release of the book
And it's 1776
Coin share all this stuff is like really pushing that hard
In order to
IMDb
The presenting things as a fundraiser be overpriced Menace of the coin Demarco
Bone the book
GameStop
These things are in order to create the appearance of a business doing well
So he can
Coast through
Bankruptcy Court
I am Baker
He won't be able to
Go to
Keep it up after that but then ideally I guess
His image of it is that like they won't crush me
I'll just
Not have money to give them later
Or something it's a bad strategy but I also think it's
It's it
Feels fraudulent
I mean it does feel like Alex is just
Coming out
And saying on his show
I'm betting they won't find all my money
Like a baby and it might as well he might as well be like listen
I've hidden a lot of money
They're not going to find all the
Like that might as well be what he say
It does feel that way
We'll be able to like just sort of
Sully sullenberger land history
Nobody's going to be happy but we are we're going to get Awards when we land this thing because it is impossible to land
And this just really captures the vibe but towards the end of the show
It's a bummer
Today
Time's the vaccine poison will bring all my job or will bring us down
Murder me process
The judge the public judge the planners have already found us guilty
Show trauma damages
Dupree Scream by lawyers questions
He just plays
Clips from
The trial by himself
I like comes in from break if there's a weird lanadelrey thing but like
Here's the vibe
It's like
You've had his friends on
Party
Yeah I know like Barnes and a talking about the case they're having fun he's coming in with like a freezer
Now he's looking at his empty bottles on the counter
Show got the baggies putting s*** in there like
No no no no no it's 3 a.m. 4 a.m.
Still drunk Jim drunk
He's just like
All my friends have gone home
Up here alone
Soothe Myself by doing a
Amazing duet with Lana Del Rey
Complaining about my own victimhood
Myself if that was a commercial and Alex was like
Sitting on a bus with his head leaning against the window
As the song played in
Money
Power
Like that's that's what else
Zoloft like that's what we are looking
It just it just had the vibe I can't I can't stress this enough
Felt so much like a guy who's friends of laughs
But he still is drunk
And has to finish something
You know there's something that like
10 minutes left to do his job so he can't stop
Right right just play Special Report better thanks to complain about how he's getting jammed up
In the vodka bottle right it's right in front of them and he's getting better but I can just go to bed
So I can drink these tomorrow night
It made me sad but then I realized
I don't really care it's Alex
That much
Much
Exactly
So
I would say that the first couple days of the trial have been
Interest
2 days of
Just
The
Plaintiff's attorney
Questioning
The corporate representative Brittany Park
Banded with theirs
Still probably
Do you know tomorrow Friday absolutely still going to be some questioning apart
There's going to be cross-examination
Are you know like it Norm
Going to get to come in there and I'll make
I got ask some questions that I don't know
What is a Libra match
Do you like me
The only question I could
Am I cool
How do you say
How do you feel about that check I said
Not big enough is it a going to come work for me we offer a lot of friends benefits
Woke insurance
I do
I will be back on Monday with a check in on Thursday and Friday
For sure trying to keep up with the things going on during
Trial
Which is important
Because the show sucks
But
Ben is what it is
Sadly sing-alongs Lana Del Rey
So we'll be back jordan.com
We're also
Lot of people are missing your life treating you don't think they are
We'll be back.
But until then I'm you I'm Leo Uzi X carti and Wilfred
Snapple Snapple of the crippled pebble
And now here comes
What the sex role
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color