Knowledge party.com
I have a great respect for Tenaya Lodge babe I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
MoneyGram
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Saline it's like a little bit about Alex Jones
Question for you
What's up
My bright spot today
Big Show
I need some
Be watching
So I had Survivor last time around which is great
Made it all the way through
I very legally got you some New Zealand Survivor I believe so
Tapped into that you actually forgot that I had that and I would also like to
To say
Text Jordan
So I was looking around
On Paramount plus haha I saw that they had two unsolved mystery
Can I watch a couple days I was texting you about everything
Seems to happen at gas station
Aldi crime
Gas station
Say we can gas station in the 90s
Stay with my f****** gas station
Show me was like the Town Square
Okay execution-style murder and then the next story is about we found a bag of mail
And I will never know where this male is this is so is so totally inconsistent I am not going to
Watching you this year
Execution-style murder that's very very lucky with mail also maybe there's goes
Style that's probably bad
So I decided to skip away from that so-called contraction master
Edith is great
It is a game show. That name through
Little clunky option master
There's this guy who kind of looks like a friendly happy British
Al Pacino okay
He's hosting a show where two teams compete to create contractions
The Purge episode like
I think it's they have to
Get this to the tea kettle turned on haha from the tub so it's all Rube Goldberg all Rube Goldberg
Okay machine
53 days one in the room to make these elaborate Contraption I love
Yeah
The guy who judges it every episode he's like a
World famous
Contraption Baker
What are the weather
I think it's called a chain reaction machine circles
Rube Goldberg
Respect about it is even he is like
I love
These things because they're so cartoonish there's a recognition of how ridiculous
They have a great respect for like
Explaining to the audience
Physics little bit
There's be like here's why
There's a light educational aspect fun I really really like it
Happened was
The British Bake Off
Exploded and then Britain has slowly claude's
Through every possible thing that they could get
A small group
Put people to do
Competitively through Pottery they've gone through gardening
They've gone through
I mean it
It's it's absurd I don't watch most of them I will tell you I don't know how they do it
Yeah the contraption ones good that's great recommended I appreciate it I don't know how they got that Dave through
Master is not
What is
Just released a new album okay
Fan
Tastic
And I think I think you will appreciate the name
My man is demon time
It's demons
I don't know I think there's something as I want to attract
Something like that but it's fantastic
Really really good ears what's great about this
I have no idea who this is
And if I were to guess what
Genre it is give me a hot or cold
Classical
No but that's also that is bossy
Hot
Hot hotter
Instrumental Hip Hop
Here's the problem with that okay
Yes
Edna
Jazz
Ihiphop really okay
Dial pops whenever a producer does
Hip-hop albums
It's about how spectacular they can make all these items is there total
Used to be all instrumental and now he's got vocalist coming out of the Wazoo be like yes vocalist
Big monkey
Yeah I do enjoy
Some of that that genre
All over the place it was an amazing track
Really really good
Problem with that title
I'm not a square
U8 sounds like a square
I just remember how funny I thought it was
When Akon and Eminem came out with that song I want to f*** you
If it's just like
What why what is this
Right
I appreciated that and what what makes me laugh makes me laugh is now
Not that that I appreciate the reservoir with snoops
Snoop Dogg I'm not sure it makes me laugh it is
Let's make love
Parentheses
With Tim McGraw
And it'll never it'll never did Faith Hill and Tim McGraw duet let's make love
It's titled let's make love parentheses with Tim McGraw I don't know why
That's the worst thing I've ever heard
It's a terrible it's terrible
What are you doing
So do we have an episode to go over and it too is tarah
Yeah we were talking about the end of last week Thursday and Friday the 15th and 16th of September and
Trying to track the
Goings-on of Alex on his show as the trial progresses
Not much not much
We lived in reality during this time
You're dumb
Pizza but it's not dumping an interesting way
Kind of like
Blustery but not in a font look at
I don't know
There's not a lot
Is what I'm saying
Picking on those bones
Yeah
I am Tuesday I believe
Is when Alex has said
But he's going to kinetic
So I receive it probably this whole week
Alex is going to be at Studio
He said that Alex Stein is hosting for him on Tuesday
Really yeah
Damn damn
Access
Good names to close to a comic that we know
It's not Alabama
Alex Stone
Well there's definitely that that go I think that's a, could we do
No I think it's yet
I don't know
We'll see what happens if you free map to us
Is a Jefferson scholar thank you so much you're now a policy wonk
Thank you very much I think that they sent that phonetically Spell doubt
Yeah I would like to know how it's supposed to say it right but I accidentally read the dashes as click
Slowing down
Nevermind
He'll night thank you so much for an auto policy lawn
Thank you
That's safer Waters help night is much
Safeway
Text Mack formerly known as trash Panda Coupe. Doing business as
Your mom taking your dad
Thank you so much right now policy walk
My favorite song title from Eminem and Snoop Dogg
Thank you very much for getting her doctorate
That happened last year I apologize
Now you're not about to walk
Congratulations next my friend Julius lunch thank you so much
Thank you very much
And we got to take the trash to the bookstore and I know that we're always behind on
Install Waze behind I'm so what I thought we would do a flip the script
No I'll be early
Okay
So we got an anniversary message
Early
How about that
I love it I love it the alternative really is a we do it in
Yeah yeah we know about it either happens or it doesn't
This is from Jessie
For Cairo
Happy 1st anniversary is on October 18th so about a month ahead of this month
Looking forward to visiting Germany
As soon as we can
I just might you are not
I have
Risen above
A list for me
And then we're going to
Comeback
And I'm going to start the show over
I got plenty of words for you
At the end of the day
F*** you and your new world order
She wrote in on
All your s***
Maybe today
Maybe I'll just be gone a month baby 5
Got to hear tomorrow
And you never see me again
I never want to come back here again
I apologize
Was legitimately having break
Weather tomorrow
It's not really no no
Our contracts dropped from Today Show and I think this fits for just about anytime Alex has a gas
A special gas coming up next hour
Moron
That's alright
That's always
Alright okay
The 15th Alex begins and
Getting repaired
Empire is on the Run
On Amazon
World topping all charge
Thanks for the people's hunger
The truth
The New York Times
Okay
What's
Passed out in the men's room
Yep so we got this we got this going on again
Multiple times on on this on this day
Yeah you know I'm starting to get offended on behalf of
Packer fan
Eli's a good time Green Bay Stadium come on man it's cold out
Cold
Tucker probably freeze to death he doesn't have anything he's got nothing on them
Packer fan so I decided to check in here with the the books
On Amazon
And when we last checked out to the number five
Amazon telephone number for
Steve Doocy number two
Amazing
Steve Doocy has arisen
Number one
With his co-star
What is it going to take
For the world that makes sense
Okay
Here's what I need
Alright I'm a huge fan of Steve Doocy
But I did not first not first
Political takes man his wife has some great recipes
That's what we're here for
Jennette McCurdy number 5
Alex has a number 12
Slide
I think the interest in that book his
Probably
Blown over
Probably done what it's going to do
See if there's anything else in
I mean I could see it becoming like a I can see it becoming like a pie
Posthumus thing you know like people didn't really appreciate James Joyce until after he was dead
I think having not read the book
I can only compare it to what I assume is it
It's closest
Literary equivalent which is
Ulysses
So I'm imagining that
The portrait of an artist as a dumb f***
That's a good one
Officers could be a good one on Alex's he toes The Very Hungry Caterpillar
Alex
Pictures of Amazon sale
So little time
Past time to stop tooting your own horn.
So Alex is a very exciting
Guest coming up later
The author of The Hunger Games
We have a huge gash
We worked at Health and Human Services
And was an advisor to president
Trump
Operation warp speed
For a fall
This is going to be a huge
In-studio interview
In 2 hours
1 p.m. Central Standard
Time really hyping this thing up
So this is Doctor Paul Alexander okay he's
I think he's been on before or at least Alex's talked about him cuz we've covered him he's the guy who was
Like a radio guest
That was
How beloved by one of the people in Trump's Administration Caputo Michael Caputo
As an advisor to the HHS
Community now
I've already talked about I don't know his interview was just like I thought everyone
How to get sick
That was a really vulnerable people in society and then just let everyone
Get it Damn the Torpedoes thing
Get off yeah I mean I would say somebody
Essentially arguing for a culling of human
Beings
Is probably not
Can I give a good interview
Well I can kind of understand where the thought comes from
You know like
Kind of understand I think it's misguided
Yeah but like the
The notion of
Having a discussion about like whether her Divinity is the right way to go at the beginning of an outbreak
I can understand
One of the reasons that I think
Especially now as we've gotten further on
I think one of the reasons why you wouldn't
Necessarily want to do that for two
Clearly would like a really novel unknown thing is you don't know these
Yeah that's the one syndromes can be caused
Brought on by having
The virus
And there's there's a lot of unknown unknown
So is it worth
I mean I do
Just come from it from this place of saying like
What is the point of living in the f***
Future if your plan for dealing with a pandemic
I still like stay let's all get together and have a party and get sick and then it'll be over like a great Beatles song
Not good health strategy
Space
I still have to get sick
Bulshit
No refuse well I mean you can ask Alex to get the globalist
Health machines or whatever
Absolutely
Going on
And that is
Immigrants Martha's Vineyard
Yep yep
Some have described this as human trafficking I don't know how it is the definition
You can't lie to people
Different state that's
Lion guard
Legal level on some way right
Alex loves
Common sense
The governor of Texas finally doing something good
Florida
Are delivering illegal aliens to Kamala Harris's house
Call Cheryl
Martha's Vineyard areas
Barack Obama and globalist
Mansion
Yeah so I mean like if you want to look at this is human trafficking Alex thinks that's a good common-sense political
Tool
Cool the Ron DeSantis should be in prison
For this. But he's pulled
Because he has an opposition to immigration DeSantis chartered two flights and sent immigrants
To Martha's Vineyard specifically because it's an area that the
The symbol of rich
Liberally
You can see how that your hand is very clear in the way that Alex describes the
If that all wasn't bad enough the immigrants were lied to when they were about where they were
One of them told reporters quote when we got on the plane they told us they would give us jobs a place to live everyday
Another said quote I simply feel misled because they told a lie and it is come
Nothing
According to Domingo Garcia the president of the league of United Latin American citizens
The people who are who are being used as political props were even giving fake document
To fool them into thinking
That there was a morphe
Official back into the idea that jobs and housing were waiting for
Interesting Lee according to NPR these flights were paid for by DeSantis but originated Intex
Switch does seem to apply some level of f*****-up coordination
Between him and Texas governor Abbott
Or else I guess maybe is this interstate
Kidnapping
Am I
Am I understanding this story correctly
So if a b DeSantis
A group of people
And it paid for
A group of
People were lied to were told that they were going to be given a better life
If they got on this plane
And then they landed
And it was a and then f******
Like that's what happened
And then we're going to act like that's not a crime that if you were I did would be a crime for me to be a wild thing
NPR talk to some of the Immigrant
Here's their description
The migrants said a Woman They identified as Perla approached
I'm outside the shelter in
Appliance saying that they would be flown to Boston where they could get expedited work paper
She provided them with food
The migrants said Perla was trying to recruit more passengers just hours before their
In addition to all this horrific bulshit
Didn't inform the folks doing the transportation of these migrants didn't inform officials in Martha's Vineyard of the beep
People's arrival
Specifically so they could be caught off-guard in
Chaos would be more likely
Because that's the goal here
This is an unacceptable and debased level of political theater where we need to stop as a country and recognize that
Things have just gotten
Too far
Accepting a really far past what's
The fact that the organizers of the stock which involves fraud potential human trafficking and possibly some other crimes have
Arrested already is a
Bucking bummer
The game is being played here is really simple
Ron DeSantis wanted to send immigrants to Liberal areas because he hates immigrants and he thinks that Liberals are all talk when it comes to support
Boarding immigration
Unfortunately if you were to inform officials in these liberal areas that immigrants were coming they would be able to prepare and accommodate
Which one really cause any problem
Through the propaganda value in that
However if
You don't tell officials
Defraud the migrants with Promises of Housing and work
Can you create a situation where the officials in the liberal area of your targeting
We're going to be outraged
You can be super offended that you would do this to me
People and likely speak out against you for it
You ignore their criticism about how what you did was fraud and possibly human trafficking
And pretend they're just mad at you because you sent immigrants
It's the pressure other precious liberal Enclave
Event sell that message to your audience to reinforce your narrative
Reality no one wants immigrants around and Liberals are just lying about
F*** this s***
F*** these people and f*** Alex
And his inability to even be
Consistent with the one big thing you supposed to be
Caring about so much
Do the king of human trafficking
Corrupt
Can sniffing it out manually care about any of his principles he claims mean so much
Watch they're all negotiable when there's a chance to quote own the libs
Or to advance
Extreme right-wing
Text yeah
Yeah it is it is nice to be reminded that laws are
Pretend though and they all you really need to do is amass enough power and it is small enough area that you can
Control that you can get away with doing whatever it is you want
It's I mean law. Don't mean anything if they're not arrest
I mean I appreciate that we're all up in arms about the Supreme Court's ruling
But if Ron DeSantis can do that
Then all you really need to do to get an abortion
Is it get a bunch of people around you with guns and then go get an abortion and then shoot somebody if they try to stop you was going to win
F****** insane
The re-election
Dino dino game
2024 presidential election
It's over
I I try to imagine myself
In a younger time
Like
I don't know
10 fifteen years ago
Experiencing some of this stuff
Now this is Becky
Uptime
Hyper tough time putting
These events
In two other periods of time
Yeah I mean yeah
SMS
Yo Russians losing in Ukraine now
Yeah and Alex's know this week
Okay
And there's a new story as having once been going on
We also have
So out of control
Ukraine dragon
Washington Farms
Didn't survive an assassination attempt
Russian generals
And a bunch of other Russian leaders
Mobile
I'm shooting him strangling I'm poisoning them
We are
I'm sorry what
With weapons
Yes directions to put up a big fight
But they're losing
Hardline
Now see this sounds like a guy who's
Questioning
Wow seems like a guy who's just got questions
Not a guy who's
Saying. That's why I'm making a statement
The assassination attempt on Putin 12 rumors that are going around
Confirm
Stop it Alex is taking it is very serious and very real
I bet it probably had to do with like
Slow-acting sedatives that they were putting in Putin's Diet Coke polonium
Any number of different
Bad it is
It is
We should feel bad
We should feel bad for her
For Russia cuz they're under attack by the globalist
That's why we feel bad well yeah I mean
This is just the either way that
Alex has decided for today to argue that
Rush's
Dresser
The country
Fun
So we get the covid-19 weenie the sound effect for that or something
They were never going to do that but
The British medical journal
Came out yesterday we have the article right here
And said okay we think it came out of the lab
Virus
Artificial
It's a match
You believe this
That the British medical journal has suddenly taken a huge about-face
Way long after it would make any sense and said that the
Covid-19 came from a lab at specifically probably one in China
No I don't believe that good insta
This isn't even about the British medical journal
Published in the Lancet
Oh okay
Put together a commission to identify lessons
It's for the future that we can learn from covid and they didn't find that it came from a lab
Premier key finding section
The proximal origins of SARS Cove to remain unknown
Their two leading hypothesis
That the virus emerged as a zoonotic spillover from Wildlife or farm animal possibly through wet Market in Aloha
Location that is still undetermined
Or the virus emerged from a research related incident during the field collection of viruses or through a laboratory
Associated
Commissioners held diverse views about the relative probabilities of the two explanations
And both possibilities require further scientific
Investigation
So that's what Alex is reported
It is
People who like to say
Definitive things
Do not like
To read what scientist actual
Sounds like Alex is questioning thing
Yeah I know he's questioning
Iraq
Findings NES The Source wrong because he doesn't know what he's talking about it all and just making s*** up as it goes along
He sucks liar
That was bad that was pretty egregious though to be like we already knew it was made up whenever it it's not free
From the medical journal
And it doesn't even
Man
Yeah little
Young Dolph
So what Alex has a gas that's not this Doctor Who Wants
To get everyone sick
It is a guy
Let me see if I can give you a clue that won't give it away
He sells pillows
There was too much of a clue
Too good of a clue you know I don't remember I don't know who invented the assertive that they didn't ask
Invented the memory foam he didn't even invent any pillow
Power 85
Mustache
Michael del zotto
Alright two days ago is on a hunting trip early in the morning stopped in to get
Hardee's in
Surrounding
Fullbacks toriel recap
News now
Investigating election fraud
That's always news then finding stolen voting machines look at it
I guess he was across the border
NBA
No I think that's
That stuff that was stolen from
Machines
Investigated
Mike lindell's Associates are very likely going to go to prison
Well see
That is where we get
Into an issue here
Because they're talking about fake things
Right well I mean what's fun about that is
That is in a backdoor way
Will force them to investigate the voting machines
Will finally look into your b*******
So we can prove
Europe time Commander
You know there is an argument to be made that technology has gotten too out of hand and do you know
Takes away the ability for people to vote
Real
Assurance in their voting
Which is why I think we need to go back to
The broken pieces of pottery I think I used to devote
No other system is accepted
I would go with
Dog food
Okay
What's the
Prettiest person that we can find
Haunted house that a vote
What was yours about
Oh okay
Mike
I don't even know how to
Save this
700 episodes account
710 into a fella
And Mike has been
Defrauded by
Anyone into another question
When did you first meet Tina Peters
At the Cyber Symposium you guys already know that
He's talking about the SBI asking
I said
Call Aurora country
Cyber experts
And people are
People from around the
Politician stop and then I said
I said oh you must be trying out the
The dentist Montgomery terabytes that I own now
Which is sitting by the way everybody
In Nevada
But the government has a
32 terabytes of the whole election
November 3rd November 6th
That's what I think they're afraid of
They're not
Things to do with that is Montgomery
S*** that brings it
It's sucking guy
That's a real full circle moment
Good at this
Yeah it's so good it's scamming these these
Money marks on the right
It's it's outrageous
He's got it he's got an Mo yeah and it's not like it's hard
How do you not just talked to somebody else who has been scammed by Dennis Montgomery and be like oh okay nevermind
Is Joe Arpaio not in Market Mike lindell's
Giving them one by one and their friends
Ya couldn't
Alex warned him
Alex's had run into a break maybe they're just too embarrassed to admit that they got scam so they're like old man
Oops you're in there with I think a lot of them
Probably our I think it might be right
Talking about it is
Mike's willingness to say this came from Dennis Montgomery
No he doesn't know he doesn't know that that name is something that like
Alright alright
It's something that gives you a like oh your arguments dumb
There's nothing here you have invalidated your Old Point
By bringing a noted career con man
I need the fraud the government
Certainly the government and people of stuff
Yeah I'm just knows who to pick to fry
IFit butt look
Pastner
In the present I don't think it takes much
Skill to notice that Mike Lindell is gullible as a lot of money
He's alright
That is it
Conman to walk by Mike Lindell without trying to
Steal something
Must require superhuman
You got to give up your time card
Got to try and caught about himself
That guy you can watch
You didn't scam like lundell
Ivory concept meeting at the American Legion
So
I I just I can't have any conclusion other than like
Dennis Montgomery got Mike bad he got him hard
Finally my body is more Americana than you and you're the Great American we love you and are persecuting all of us together
They are scared
Well they weren't there very worried everybody and I want everybody to
Montgomery's terabytes
For the last
Deer and a half and there's a reason
Symposium
But we were advised not to
I'll put up a
Don't try nothing and Alba
Symposium was that what everybody at the moment of truth Summit
Right onstage we had the attorney out there
And he told you why we could not drop them
Because I think it is there's something so f******
Funny about this being her Moment of Truth Summit
At the last minute we're like literally could not be
More names
So ironic
Sing
I mean yeah
Yeah
The public
There's a government gag order on this information
I don't believe that
.
There's now I own all this stuff
And I bought the
The different stuff
One of the smartest man I've ever known by the way
Oh
Just so sad
So sad
There never is always is a gag order with Dennis Montgomery's stuff
Because it's made of tomato pretend nonsense
I believe
Mike Lindell
Probably
Quite a bit of money for
It's about incident real information that is
Amazing
Not good
We're not related
Or made up
Wow
If you weren't such a piece of s*** and the information wasn't used so negatively
I mean I wish I had the front of this many right-wing propaganda
That's an accomplishment
Tremont that I do respect
I think more people should screw these guys out of their money
Because they're dumb
It is just something that is so weird
2 event
He is
This thing that key
Keeps coming up
You know
That you would not expect that this con man would just
Run through so many we haven't even talked about him and
Forever
News from Friday
Yeah
Crazy
Oh man I felt like somebody was saying that he was
Is dead
Recently I don't know I kind of thought he was dead the first time we talked about having no
Investigate
700 episodes ago
Sabaat episode 2
Yeah I think you still kicking
69 years Young
Nice
So he got Mike lundell
Got him hard
Pool
We need to have like a ton team version of I think it'll be someone we're not aware of yet
The prominence I don't know
I don't know once I hear Tucker
Say those two magic Tucker
Montgomery
Or you can go to Janice Montgomery
You work for the government
He made this thing called Hammer scorecard for the government
Patriot just still Lex
It's going to spy on other elections around the world
Turn this on her own people
The government doesn't want you to see this everybody
And that government
I'm shutting down there if that judge releases this to the public
If they release this to the public gets over everybody
They're definitely scared of you
Viewers Michael Alex Jones our own a symbiotic
Defense
You better big sponsor people can go to
Big sides
American companies
Tell people
How to check out for savings
She can also sponsor us really appreciate it
Your new website as well
It really feels like these two dudes are playing different game doesn't realize that
Memories of long-term con man who's been part of at least
A few of Alex's busted narratives in the past and Alex knows not to take that s*** seriously
Because of that or just because he's out of his mind
Lindale seems like he actually believe
If this information gets out
Yeah it's going to have a huge political effect
Conversely Alex just want to bike
Money and he knows that the only way to get it is to allow him to say whatever he wants on there
Still taking this Montgomery should seriously or else you'd be insisting that this is the biggest story in the world may be covering it wall-to-wall
Blase nonsense that you hand wave way to get your promo code
Promotion
Mike Lindell is that guy that
That you just got up like
I don't he has too much hubris or something because like anybody
Coup
Who is a right-wing propaganda
Is worth a damn
Yeah we're just be like
Shut up
Shut up don't say anything
Just give me money let me put your message out your doing this poorly
If you want his money you have to let him talk
He reveals
That he's working on information
A bed is Montgomery
And the whole thing pasta
Yeah
Do you need an intermediary bird-like is his message but
Asaka defunded intermedia
Right right
He wants
Ape s*** crazy
And he is going to pay out the wazoo.
To get a check crazy now at the same time and that's what you are
I don't think the
He recognizes it takes you crazy
I mean you I hate it whenever I hear him talk because if he was
Yelling about like
The f******
Betting lines for
Football on Sundays on ESPN or something
I think that could work his voice is right for it like Blues / 3
Brick-and-mortar building
That works for me
But this is sad this is a terrified man
An Alex Billington Stampy's let his Montgomery. But are that's why Alex is like
I better f****** get some pillow money
Yeah alright well as what gates are open
You're given Montgomery money going to give me some too damn
Yeah I'm going to have
To go ahead and save that ethically speaking Alex is piggybacking on Dennis Montgomery's defrauding of Mike Lindell
I don't know when the Montgomery information
Started to be part of lindell's thing
So
Alex might have been calling him before
Who knows
What the first con begin
We were so young
Alex gets back talking about bees
Immigrants coming to Martha's Vineyard
And he's a liar
Boston little kids have been kidnapped
Men
To all these different places
Illegally
We're going to put them on my assistant say hey
Going to South Side Chicago or south
Places like South Dallas in South Chicago
You are going
In the Bronx
You're not going to d.c.
You are
Going to Martha's Vineyard where you're going
Kamala Harris house
It seems like he's
Totally fine with human trafficking as long as its adult men
Cool man
To know and it's not
Yeah there were children's at the Martha's Vineyard
According to reporting available at the time Alex is on are the group included quotes seven families with four children
From 3 to 8 years old
I was just lying to his audience because he knows that the reality of what the scientists did looks really really bad
Transporting it would be interesting contradiction
With his imaginary principles
So in order to you know you don't have to choose between being a coward or haven't
Instead you just create a false reality to respond to
He's really lucky that none of his listeners really even care about what's true or not oh s*** that's
Also the migrants are told they're going to boss
On every level this is a fraud being perpetuated at the expense of vulnerable people in order to score political points
I mean
Do you also in danger
Don't like
It's outrageous
Yeah
I just
And to be a dick to say
After we just like well at least they weren't trafficking children you know like the Democrats do and it's like no they were
And then he said
Which they were smart not to do and you're like well
They would be if they hadn't
What they did
That's why I'm saying that how Alex is freezing
He is accepting that this is trafficking children
Be human trafficking children
So they are human trafficking
According to Alex
But instead of that
He's just going to say that the Democrats are human traffickers
And they are smart for end that
Will you deny that the thing happened
People who did it
I didn't do it
Yeah yeah yeah
Yeah I did that really is that really is going to drive me insane
It really is going to drive me
Brian
With Alex talking about cars
Horsepower of a Mustang pretty good
College
Thousand
Horsepower
With twin
Superchargers
0 to 60
Dangerous
200 miles an hour
That's black
Press down accelerator
What
1 a.m.
Is that political
In the arena
And we are
Alive
And being alive means
You know you're going to die
Being alive means wasting a full minute talking about nothing
You like you know Lewis Hamilton is the greatest Grand Prix driver the history of the sport
Liberals don't drive that
The best ever at driving so fast it still drives fast they don't understand what it means to me
July
At the fastest
Right and I think there's something that's being
Expressway hours
Tubi
Don't drive fast
Because they don't want it
Experience the danger of driving fast
And the danger of driving
Fast he's knowing that you
Who died right just the only way to really be alive
This is silly.
Insane want to talk about cars a little bit
Didn't seem like he was just bragging about his car
Like
Man they just said they want to try and own just that
Anything that comes into their
Fear
It feels like vaguely mascara
Yeah
Yeah which is like man driving fast is not masculine or feminine
It's a playing with the toy everybody like playing with toys
It's playing with toys
I don't particularly like driving much
No but you like playing with your toys
You like your choice yeah you got bud
I have video games either
No not really
No that's true I haven't since I've lived in Chicago I was just such a bad driver
I got bored really easily
I don't think I have ADD but like when I was driving it was so boring
Right they'll write every now and again I would hit
The curb
But not like
It's not like highway hypnosis or anything anymore
Imany I may end up having to get a license
Begin at some point just want to live in the middle of nowhere without a
Without a car that'll be tough
How to be tougher
Not if I got
Drone
Noah's thinking more along the lines of
You know an assassin
Creed Valhalla you get that ride around
I don't think I need the lights right above felines in this area
So
Viewer discretion advised
To this nightclub
Terrible or anything it's just Alex is talking a little bit about sex so great and this is a family show
And a few times thanks for telling us
Incredible woman
After you get out of here
I'm sorry
I don't want to punch you in the face
I want to beat you with a bullwhip
The point is I'm not into pain baby
I think I just kept it in cuz I'm not into
Is that what we say for the
Save that
That's our covid conspiracy of the day
I'm not into pain baby
I think
But Alex is also mixing up a fair amount of BDSM
Here in terms of their
You know obviously there are some people who like a little bit of rough
Stuff
It's not the entirety of
Of bondage
He has a full
Understanding this but
It might I'm not sure that I believe his childhood stories now
Barriers
I'm terrible with knots
I'm terrible with nuts I did tried to watch a video one time I was asking but I was asked
About how to tighten some good knots for the stuff
You know the type
Sure not good at it
Real bad got out
That's that the real disappointing hostage situation one which is a fantasy and you still let the hostage
Well what time what time is young lady who wanted me to bring some.
Set the bedroom
Big mistake
I do appreciate that 700 episode took 700 episodes for me to really want
Now you know how I feel the time
Medford
For slightly different reasons
Alex has a story
We heard this tale of a football player who had a lot of blood clot
I know Alex has a story about someone having a hard time
We have tens of thousands of percent increase
People having heart attacks
Has your heart
What is the tree of death
Cross country
EG earnest
A seventeen-year-old Bartlett High School cross country Runners recovery in Florida
After undergoing emergency heart surgery
I just completed
When he started complaining
Of chest pains
Barry G's Melissa Moon reports he underwent a 3-hour surgery and now teammate
Community or praying for a Swift
Return
To help
I consulted tons of news stories about this case and none of them say he gotten vaccinated
That's just an assumption that Alex is making which you may notice is a trend
Ddreports
Hyping up
Instances of young people having medical conditions but never actually does the works
To connect them to the vaccine
Seen it all
That connection is already made in the minds of his listeners so it's kind of a waste
The time to worry about actually damage
What's trading at
It seems like this never happens or can't happen but high school athletes
Can have heart attack
Just do a little digging into the subject
You can find instances pre covid really easily
Impact in 2011 Denver public schools began installing portable defibrillator is that schools because quote
Sudden Cardiac Arrest killed an estimated 300,000 Americans over here
Including about 7,000
Some children
Alex is a
Exploiting is audiences understandable feeling that young people shouldn't have heart attacks
And then weaponizing that buries anti-vax agenda
It's disgusting and ultimately he's using the deaths in medical emergencies of these young people as props
For him to use to accumulate power and profit
Sort of like how Ron DeSantis is using
Please wait
You're connecting these two things
Brothers pneumatic similarities
Where Alex just assumes he never does any of the work that you need to do to actually reported stories just guessing
Some s***
But notice the adults all have Stockholm
Call syndrome
We're just looking for something weird we don't know what caused this
Well we know what caused it
You bet your bottom dollar
Moderna
Knj
Shot
And so
Any of them are all three
You know the bug did it
Apologist
The know
I don't need to be
The shot
So who's thinking is just stupid
And assuming that you know and can just guess causal relations between things without knowing more about the variables that
Painfully dumb
Like for instance what if you get bit by two things
Which caused the reaction you're seeing
No no no no what is your composting variable complicating
Also you can clearly see here that Alex is just guessing that the runner in this case got the vaccine
Even if he had
Alex can't prove or demonstrate any calls a link but
Alex can't even prove that the thing he's claiming cause this
Perfect even happened
He's seen it affect
That he knows he can exploit
So he's decided what the cause is based on no information
This isn't the story that's going to be followed up on so if you're in the audience
You'll just experience the story of the dopamine rush if Alex
Proving your anti-vax ideas correct
Never even worrying about whether or not you were just the target of a parlor
But he's just questioning
Really I mean when you think about it Alex
Question thing
Thanks not make things up
He really is a cult leader in this respect because you could absolutely see him like
With his
His loyal info Warriors walking down
Street and pass by a guy with a broken arm and also be like
Haha it was a snake bite
Nunda just keep walking
That was a snakebite clearly
Like there's there's nothing it doesn't matter if it
Even make sense
Yeah that's what he's is descriptions like
Well if you get bit by rattlesnake in your leg does a thing then you know that it's a rattlesnake
Well then you have to say that he got the vaccine
And then the thing happen
Right this is like thing is like
Swole up clearly it was a rattlesnake like no that doesn't have anyone proven that there is a rattlesnake
We don't have we don't have a rattlesnake
ITube
Snake in this situation
Interviewing that Paul Alexander
Give a f***
So we're going to jump
Do
16th Friday show
Wolf
No man's land
Nothing happen
But the live show headliners
This is an emergency
Emergency
Even mitigate
How bad
This crash
Is going to
So you go to infowars.com she's alive show
Headline
It says emergency
Friday
Broadcast
Deals with
Absolutely
Key indicator
Not just here but in the world economy
FedEx
The world but I told you in the last month
Because I know
People in
A lot of areas of infrastructure
Basically
The
Economy is Flatline
This is all been done by Design
As usual
Here are some of the headlines
FedEx shares Plunge
Dow Jones indices waiting on right now
By 70%
Company says it's going
To get worse
We're going into a worldwide recession FedEx CEO warrants
Numbers don't pretend
Very well
So there's some serious concerns with FedEx announcing that they're seeing the decrease in shipping both domestically and internationally
This could be a negative indicator for the economy and the future but there's also a ton of other variables to play into the
One that pointed to pretty frequently is that the Asian economy is weakening
And that impacted showing introduced
Freight
Another variable is that people are starting
The shop in person more now that most people are acting like covid is over
That is the effect of reducing shipping to previously normal rate
Which are lower than they have been over the course of the pandemic
Thirdly Amazon is made Moves
Listen to be Logistics and transport or Transportation space in the past few years
And that has had the effect of reducing FedEx's
Is overall market share
All that being said FedEx was down about
22%
Which definitely isn't a good
However if you look back at their stock price over time they're trading at about $161 a share as I was
Preparing this episode
In March 2020
106 dollars and sixty-three cents a share
Before making a huge jump as the pandemic led to more people ordering
Things for more delivery
A people ordering things that
Maybe needed to be delivered immediately
Time frame
Which does have
Demand goes down you still need to offer that delivery
In that window that you're offering right
Which leads to like
Can save a plane being a hundred percent full you have to send it with like
Half full
This may be a bad indicator of things to come but it may not be a cause for an emerging
Episode
The theatrics but Alex is putting
That said he does this all the time about everything and it's always the summer of Rage coming and I'm not
Not surprised at all
Yeah girl there may be economic issues there may be some difficulties
FedEx might be in some trouble
But whatever it is has nothing to do with it is no connection to anything Alex the same
I mean if we live in America if you look at us historically the fact that they don't reckon that we don't regulate
The finance industry whatsoever
As essentially led to a series of crashes that happened every decade 22-dec
Happens every f****** time
Where do
Ridge cumming
Oh boy
Great prophet
So what's Primacy and review
Not really real
We have more people assigned to investigate white supremacy
Actual white supremacist in the United States
Almost not exist
Italian all this
Try out other political opposition
Next hour
I'm just going to say this now
Broadcast
Opportunity
Because you work we've done together as change the world
Find this place
Incredible products
I'm not going to bet you complain
We put everything we had into buying this product
Tells you what I told you a month ago
Flatline so I know people run out of money
But you must
Absolutely look in your life
And decide
What is most critical
What are generous person Alex's
Given the audience an opportunity to give him money
That's the kind of selfless character you rarely see these days
Going out of his way of being like
Hey
I know you're hurting
But it's important to still give me money
Need money
What an opportunity for you
Just I just
Man if you actually admitted if you really believe that
People are struggling
And you ask them for money after you agree with that
That's crazy
That's bananas down to me to look at somebody who is struggling more than me and then be like
But
You should give me money that's crazy because whatever I'm doing my project is more important than your well-being
I would give you money
That's just an idea I don't understand how you're struggling and I'm not so then you I can help you not struggle
What's it that complicated
Because he's a good guy
Understand
So Alex plays a long B
Of Josh Hawley
Interviewing
Someone from Facebook
And just
Someone from
From the company yeah yeah yeah
Not just like
Okay
End
And
Boring
Yeah I think this
Highlights of boring it is cuz I'll accept
Start yelling
We do know that people
Started and hoped
From the
That we would help them get accurate information about
Covid during the unpress
Especially
Isn't there a
Prince between use app
Form putting forward information and censoring
Your users
The best of
The White House
The
Administration were broadly in the CDC
Is there distinction
We specifically
Wanted to work with
Health experts
To understand the relationship
Between information and behavior
Until we did Consultants
Buy them
Collusion
What is weed
You didn't just
Consultant understand how they
The public house if you actually
Censored on their behalf
Yeah it's it's
Whatever
To indicate there's a long stretch
Of that being the coverage and I can't even keep it together
Just watch it
No he's not he's not cut out for I would
Would say like analysis of
Dense
Like more boring
Rang frere
You know that's kind of his bread and butter
I think it'll be fun if you had
If I was running Infowars
I would have a little m
That is like Alex's tolerance meter that would edit edit would like have a little graphic where is Hedwig
Would start to pop
Cuz that's what
It feels like when he's watching that at there's just the m going m
Bad influences and you don't know what they're going
Space on screen it just automatically blows up
For some reason you bring a llama in studio and everything's fine
It's just fine
If I would be more frustrated with the
Studio
That's what I cuz it's my apartment
Like llamas
But not my apartment
With the big nose
WhatsApp
Something that's not true
Flooring class Rob is the head of the UN and said he has full command
Yeah
Carswap was sworn in as the head of the UN
Don't they have to have like a whole thing
Alex's just questioning text don't you understand
Sordid and Secret
Why would you have
Eddie swearing-in ceremony if you can do it in secret
I don't know
Didn't happen
Yeah that's it that's an issue I was looking around I can't even figure out what he might be referring to as misreporting
I have no idea
What
Where where when and why doesn't explain
Bulshit okay
So look Alex likes to talk about memes and stuff and he saw video on social media that got a report on
I want to play Annie mom here somebody gets muzzle to General
That's not true
We talked about Tik-Tok
Destroying messages to kill the family and a Kill
Minds and our future
In the very same algorithm in China
Puts out a different message
Estella
Military
Is mathematics
So while they're building men and women and Families
They found the video that Alex was referring to but I don't know who the
The person is who's talking and I have no idea there even an Imam or anything
It's just someone who kind of looks
It's like they're in the attire you might think any mom would be in but outside of that there's no indication but his identity at all
I found the person who originally posted this on Twitter but there's no citation to who the person is
I have no one in the comments identifies him either
It's baffling
I have no idea who the person is in larger point
Neither does our
You just all random video on social media that made a point that he liked about Tik-Tok so he's reporting
It's a process
That's what you doing
Death even leaving the anonymity of the speaker aside
Who cares about this claim
It's not backed up by any data that this guy is presenting it's just a thing that someone saying someone who
No idea who they are or the larger context of their combat
Essentially what I'm saying here is that I don't really care about this video
The only important thing to point out is that
Alex has no idea who this person is
There's nothing backing up what they're saying and he's he loves
Alex's broadcast has become an audio version of
Uncle's Facebook page
Like it is just a series of like maybe I'm an idiot
But yeah it looks like a bunch of
I saw this and now I'm mad and then you just move on
Flamewar in the comments for a while
And then the next day you're like I saw that
Looking awful right
And
Berries
Just like the like
The wave
Is it social media
Makes things
Things like what
The next post yet it's almost like a new cycle or right
All those things that I said yesterday don't matter about alike since I got this
From here so I got a
Move on
So
Still talking a little bit about Martha's Vineyard here
The difficult challenges are
This is one of the leaders in Martha's Vineyard
Believer
What you're telling them come here
Any voted 85% Martha's Vineyard
To be disconnected from reality sorry start over
The difficult challenges are
We have to fit some point in time to help
We cannot
We don't have two services
Do take care of 50 immigrants
Down and
Island and everyone here that live
50 more people
Silence is presenting this is one of the leaders from Martha's Vineyard because he has no idea who this person is and he is not in
Really sure if Martha's Vineyard has a city or what he should call their leader
In reality this is Lisa belcastro the coordinator of the homeless shelter in Martha's Vineyard
And when she says that eventually people need to leave she's talkin about how the shelter she works with
Isn't designed for providing long-term health
When you understand that what she's talking about is the services her shelter can provide
Not like the city or the city
He's he's deceiving with it
Eye contacts
So the larger context of that clip italics
Even playing is about how the community has come together to help these migrant
About how this is a disgraceful political stunt that's essentially an attack on the personhood
Of these migrants themselves
Conveniently cuts that off
Adjust
Is there is there's no other way to describe it then
To save it
He is taking these people and reduce them to
That's what I like
M2
Just a
Cuz I like soda
Reverse of this
And all those
People in DC and New York
We're beating their chest
Same day
They were so proud to be
The sanctuary jurisdiction
Saying how bad
It was they have it
Your border
The minutes
Even a small
Fraction
Of what does Bordertown
Deal with everyday is brought to their front door
They all of a sudden
Go berserk
In there so UPS
This is happening
And it just shows you
You know their virtue signalling is
Fraud
Okay
They
We can survive as a country if this is what elected leaders do
The fabric of the country just won't hold together if we have trolls using humans for publicity stunts and a weirdo
The lubes
Do you reveal their virtue signaling
Even if everything to Santos was saying was
True
This is how a distasteful prank show operates not a governor
Beyond that what you saying is b*******
People aren't upset about migrants and refugees going to different cities
They were super offended by the way to Santa's is doing this as a political stunt using the safety of migrants as a prompt
He's endangering human
Including children for his own purposes
Largely to increase the chances that he's able to
Increases political power in
In the future
He knows well enough that he can't acknowledge that this is what he's getting pushed back for because
Very sensible pushback that he can't just write off his
Triggered virtue signal responses
20% that's what people are upset about
Pleases the
The aggressive audience
I can't
Hear him talk
Like that without
Getting an immediate urge to like
Bum rush the stage and just start slapping in the vet
You can't
Believer
Yeah
The biggest ginseng wake up
Not possible for a human being to think
Is true
Yep any meaningful for a person who has the responsibility for representing a fuk
You're the governor of a state
This is Ben
Yeah your station
This is beneath your office
I think a lot of things
Maybe it's elected officials do our baby Ben
Nephew off as well but particularly
Yeah.
Acting this way to
And then the response being like
Oh look at this
The Virtue signaling it reveals like that to me is like
This is
Social media trolling
Just isn't this isn't
Other Florida Governors do
And
Get rich off of your s***
And then leave
That's what is
That's what the Professional Russian like Florida
That's what they want
God dammit
So the third hour of Alex's show on Friday if he has a couple of doctors on who are suing about remdesivir
Beer but they're clearly on a fishing Expedition
They're making outrageous claims about hospitals
Murdering for-profit but they are no evidence of anything
They keep saying we hope will find things at Discovery
Like 80
In terms of like an interview it is a nothing
But very excited
Hopeful find things into
We'll go from there
I say I sue you and then you have to give me all the information that I need to sue you
I make bold claims that are baseless and then
MBA law
So where will my score
And it's about the lineage
Which of these
Sorts of
Publicity stunt
And
Probably start to happen
There's one from Despicable Me
Illegal migrants
You're full
Reservation
I mean Laurel
Illegal alien
Border to the California border
Pelosi's house
And she got arrested for
Let's get Laura Loomer on Sunday
Very exciting about this book
Dan Weber.
Say that you won the election
Secretly
So Alex is lying but what Laura Loomer did
She picked up man she assumed for undocumented immigrants from a Home Depot parking lot
And convince them to accompany her to set up a tent in Pelosi's back
Pretty unlikely that they told
Got that you told them that they
Be trespassing on Pelosi's property to do so
Almost certainly didn't tell them as part of a publicity stunt aimed at Boost
Stinger profile
With the Altima
My goal of being to accumulate political power that you could wield against
Immigrants it would be a very difficult thing to ask
Explain in the Home Depot parking lot and Usos
Successful
It was pretty clear that the real aim of the stunts
Was to do this
Legal thing trespassing in order to create a confrontation between the police
Ambient
This would allow Willmar to do exactly what the scientist is doing now with the
Do you want emigrants here but apparently not on your property
Kind of game
Unfortunately Pelosi didn't press charges if
The emigrants just left will summer at The Daily Beast quote
When it became clear that the man wouldn't be arrested and deported as was apparently the plan
What are Bloomers Associates ground and shouted catch-and-release at the FM
The police
Uber didn't get arrested for this. But again you can see this
Need to use
Fraud to try and set people up
And eagerness to use people as Pawns in politically cruel stunts
That's Alex's ideology
And this s*** is totally fine to him because they aren't people to him.
These people are things
Turn off Rob.
You have
To use fraud
Because you are
Complaining about people that don't
Exist
So then you have to
Because they're not going
To do what it is you're complaining about
Then you have to try and create
A Contraption of sorts
Let's try to get them into a situation where maybe what they do
Could be construed from a distance as what
You have been complaining about this whole time
Contraptions Contraption Oklahoma
It's like a it's like a chain reaction machine
Yeah it is
I think there is like a
Able to make
Connections
Laura Loomer stunt is similar to this
Anyways
Yeah
If you would sit and think about that for a little while
Maybe
Maybe you do
If I was
Who is DeSantis I would sit and think about that awhile and go am I really going to do Loomer s***
Oh yeah
That's what I would
Yeah I'm a boomer hack
And that's not because
I mean in my in my inhabiting of this character
It's not morally that loomer's
Immoral things
It's that
Sheesh it at the
It's just
Garbage performance art
You know
Like Marcel Duchamp put it upside down
Urinal in Martha
Vineyard how about that
Blow everybody's mind would be interesting it would be
But you know what the Liberals of like that
Would be confused by it a challenge
Since everybody be wearing shirts and it be greedy and then the upside down urinal of Martha Martha
Vineyard that's the way it would go
So I mean look there's not much going on here
As Alex's trial progresses
We left off on Friday the end of pauses acrimony
Norm was trying desperately to bring Trump into the proceedings
And I got slapped down to that a number of time hilariously
Yeah I don't know I don't think
That's
I don't know whether they're in a big points
That you would want to bring up
Over the course
The week
I mean
I supposed to be
Midpoints for me is just been
So much
Is it clearly especially with the elongated
Trial now
Is so much of it is so obvious that the judge
And
Norman and Maddie and and all of those people
Have the rules
Setup and the rules are Norm cannot do everything that Norm is doing
Yeah but
Because it's a trial and we can't just sit there and have the judge say Norm
Sit back down
You are not allowed to talk so she has said that a couple times if you don't stop
She's had to say that
You keep saying that because
That's their entire
That's all they got is the stuff they can
They don't have a new argument
So they're just going to try and do different ways to like
Back door the same s*** there not allowed to say in it for more weeks
Yeah
So we'll give you an update on that
As it goes along and the rules are broken
Who's going to be there probably testifying next week or this week as a
Is that things are going
We'll see
I'll be in touch
Sure will
Another episode in the near future
We're also
We are on Twitter that knowledge
Emilio Emilio mdzs
Clerk I'm Wilford Snapple Snapple of the Gravel Pit Bull
The sex robot
Alex
Christian coloring