I have great respect for knowledge by now I'm sick of them posing as you're through the good guy
Knowledge fight
Acknowledge
Sit around worship at the altar of sleep a little bit of
What's Alex
Jordan
What's up
I will I will tell you my bright spot then
My bright spot is there's this TV show
Amazon company that I despise
Spent
More money than is ever been necessary to make this show about the Lord of the Ring Spud
I'll be goddamned if it's not f****** great
I would prefer they'd spent some of that money elsewhere but guess what it's a great show I love elves
My lover
I've seen a lot of
I've seen a lot of mixed
Opinions about
You know it's weird
About what's happening it's like when you know what's going on in the original trilogy movies you know you're like okay that's a nerd
Things to know when you're like looking at your wife going like all these are the men of numenor all right you don't even know
What can I come next after about
2000 year like okay maybe I do that
I need to stop I'm not going to I'm reciting the silmarillion to her every night whenever we watch
Terrible but it
It's great show
How about you buddy
I don't trying to think
Probably doing these days back-to-back
Yeah I guess I'm playing a fun game
I've
Valkyria Chronicles
Nothing
Esquire
Scratch the itch
Of three houses
That was just
It's like right in the pocket
Spot I like to enjoy a little bit of this turn-based game
I think I think that Vibe is
Something I never played growing up here obviously
Most of my game
Video game stuff that I played
Growing upward Nintendo
And non-violent
At all
Those were
Verboten
And the only way we got video games was that my grandma like
Nintendo's
Answer whenever a new system would come out
Did you give us her old one
Nice and so we would play like Nintendo but late
Grandma gamer is a
Great I didn't have one of those grown-ups
Interesting I was pretty pretty cool
Play Mario playlist
Peacock country
My model
There were
Turn-based games
And stuff
Never really was in my my view
I think we're older now we like those games that don't have as much action
On with your
Writing this right noceros
Andy
Jump
Square response
Next time I'm not
Not doing it geometric fashion at my pace
It's fine
I'm enjoying it
Jordan do we have fun enjoy as well
Sebastian Murdoch
Huffington Post
They're at the trial in Connecticut
He was for the home
I was also there in Austin
It was just nice to have a chat about the
The differences between the two trials and just go to the
Experience so
Fantastic time we were going to have them on when we were in Austin and I believe I rambled about that
It's great to finally have them on I'm I'm glad that we got to make sure
So we'll get tonight here in a minute but first I wanted to bestow a raptor Princess ship
Somebody
And that is the
To put out the email for the butt
Last over the email address
I'm so people didn't know if it was
Plural or not okay
Did they email address that was the non plural version
Real danger people sending emails to this with their addresses
Got that email address to protect people
From sending her address to somewhere else
Cool and appreciate it so much
An unforeseen possibility of life
Real trouble so jail
Thank you so much you are a Raptor
Four Star
Kelly Aprilia
Over for Humanity you're beautiful
They're coming for your balls
It's all over your God
Very few people
When they are
Comet
Hey juice
Thank you so much thank you very much hope everybody
Button
Coming out
We're surrounded by them
Yep butts
Who knows it'll be awhile they will be at
Yeah but if you want to reserve courses
A lot of people Exedra
Trippin for
Shipping
And what have you I don't want you
To do that to pick you like Japan in
Chipping for a good cause
Hey now
Without further Ado Jordan let's enjoy
Our interview
With Sebastian
So hey everybody very exciting joining us here in the theater
Podcast
Studio
Digital
Over Zoom
Detail
I'm very excited to have this joining us we met down in Austin for the the trial and
You wanted to have
I am on 44 that
Stirring up your diet but our schedules were not
Accommodating
Thrilled to welcome
What's a podcast
Writer for the Hop
Post
Sebastian Murdock thank you for joining us
Thanks for having me on fellas
Appreciate it
I feel
So self-conscious about that introduction
I'm saying that there was quite a bit of fanfare
Come from the school of beat like stand-up introductions
Have the gas I loved
Appreciate that
I'm Sebastian thanks for joining us first of all
And second
How's it going
Going good
Just got back from
From reporting a
Connecticut
So trying to
Give my body a rest and you do get back to you get back to
Where what a little bit
Yeah you've been bit up here covering Alex's second trial it seems you're on the beach
You're on the other the house
Npost Alex Jones beat
I am indeed on the beach I like doing it though I mean I like
I like
Watching
The downfall of Alex
And I like
Watching
The Sandy Hook parent
Get some
Accountability
Out of them
Cathartic on some level or absolutely it's really the only two good things though the rest of it is a slug
Bulshit
That's alright
I was just telling you guys I mean I
Get out of court at 5
Straight to the bar at 5.
Oh it's you got it
Car Wash It Away
It's a good place to get a little work done and
You know it
It's a
In video game sometimes
Be like you know you get
Composure by having alcohol
I understood that until the stats
We're talkin about here yet the bar is my saved
Do I got to get in there right now
I was wondering if internally like edit
Sartorially
You have
Like our conversations that like
You're the outlet
Text Jones guy around these parts
We got an ID on this
Yeah absolutely but there is also as you guys
Know so much
Minutiae and
The b******* about Alex Jones Infowars so there other times
Tia where it's like
Alex Jones you know send
Santa
Messages to Rodger Stone of his naked wife which
Preserve at Rolling Stone
A rolling stone article
Entering Federation like that II saw
Certipay
Yeah so much
I find that myself even like as we do a Podcast Addict ate it to him like there's still time zones
I'm going to punch on this
It's kind of a self-care thing to you know weeds
Sure I mean unfortunately both of you got really good at a job nobody else wants to
To do so
Then he's like well hey guess what
You guys did it
Cursive like may you get what you want.
Make yourself indispensable
Smart move
But I do I do want to stress
I do like your
It's not like
You only write stories about Alex I was looking over like your bylines
You're all over the place writing about all time
Stop
I'm primarily a breaking news reporter so yeah I cover
Politics
Mass shootings that we have and
Yeah yeah dude Nene cobra
But yeah sometimes investigative stuff too but the Alex Jones saying I've been
In in one way or another reporting on
Definition lawsuits
$40 bill
And now I'm
I was actually talking
Attorney Mark Bang
Do I know all the walks out they're very familiar with
They're concerned
But you know it
It's
Interesting
Need to finally
Jeffy
4 years of of not
Reporting but of this
Process and now we're finally in not even at the
The first
Trial now and then there's going to be a third on the way and a
It sort of feels like
I don't know if I
I call it the payoff but
It's all sort of color
Into
We're getting toward the client
Max here it does feel like
Things are speeding up
Toure what's that first trial hit now it's starting to feel like always
It's the next one's right around the corner
This one's going to be you know it's safe
The function of like the delay in garelick it's
Just the ball is Ben
Kick down the road so far they like
Like a lot of this would be the kind of pace things would have gone if I'd been stalling
Involved exactly
What's it been like
Being in the like when we were in the Austin Courthouse you know there's a lot that you see and kind kind
I have noticed that you don't
Don't just by looking through the
Mystery Mike
You've been in the courthouse be the entire time right
Yeah that's right
I I think
What's what's very different about this trial
Is that
In some ways
Somehow even more so
Sabrina.
Listen to say that the Austin Trail wasn't but
Here we are in
Connecticut
The state where it happened
And there are
You know so many
So many plaintiff so
The family members are there
And that bad I think it's been
You know incredibly impactful and
Can you use two
Just sort of highlight you know because for all the sort of laugh
That we all do it Alex and of course you guys know this like
This is
About what
He did
Didn't need parents and soda
To have them there you know
It's a humbling
Experience and it's also a
Incredibly
In a lot of ways
I found that to be
Incredibly palpable
It is not in Austin
There was a moment I'm just watching the Stream
Of this
Sky Connecticut
CaseNet
I thought
That for sure there's no way I could have handled being there for it
And that was when Norm
Not patties
Was giving his
Is opening
State map
And
Yee
Sort of did a
An act out
Of Alex
By being like
Alright I killed the kids
I killed all the kids
Antioch
The recognition that these parents worth
They are and that Norm would bring himself to do that
Like I do
Not that I would freak out and jump him or something
But like I don't know how I could emotionally handle
Being
It was
Or even on just a stream
Yeah I mean it's sad
It's a level of of
Respect right honey we also see it by the fact that Alex
Can't even show up
For these opening statement
He's going to show up when it when he has to test
Dubai
But it's
You know and and
Jordan you what you had talked about this a lot when we are in Austin but
The idea that
Yeah there
Have been a lot of news media that were
Reporting eyeball Alex Jones says
He's sorry he regrets
And we know that
That's bulshit
Because again he's not showing up
To the trial at all
He's on Infowars talkin about
Kangaroo court and then like you're saying Daniel
It's up there and he starts
Doing that that mimicry in front of the parent
Whose kids were killed
Yeah and I also know I'm saying that their argument is that they're exaggerating their trauma
Yeah well well Norm also fell asleep in the courtroom so he was also
Nodding off
Yeah heat that's what you were saying that like something
What's different about this from the Austin
I have to imagine that just
The existence of norm pattis
Makes this
Feel entirely different
Yeah you know what
What kind of surreal though is
I still can't see
Figure out who the worst lawyer is
If it's going to be bad if
We've we had some disagreement over this ourselves
Genuinely think that Norm for what he's doing is doing about as good as he
We could possibly do
I mean falling asleep in the trial.
Power nap
I made that point on the Infowars even he was saying
This is how you deal with a rogue judge or whatever
Been like that is obviously not the
The case then.
Situation but what Norm is doing is
The only thing they can do which is throw bombs
Basically
Yeah exactly swing bud and hope that
You know Daddy Alex
Backing off
Yeah where is reynald seems like
Maybe I can win this thing and then what happened
I do find it interesting
Because
It does feel a little bit like Norm saw the first trial and rain all went with his life
Halfway up
Using halfway trying to slimeball evil into places
And then he was like well that lost
So f*** it I'm just going to try and swing as much s*** as I can and maybe it'll lower the judge
Oobi like I guess they are exaggerating iyl
Or maybe maybe you can make such
A problem that
The jury trial
We're looking at 4 I guess
3 weeks
At this point now so it's going to be a long trial.
Only two
Plenty of time
To do something
I feel like I heard them
Some say that they had agreed that it might be a shorter
Her trial then
Okay well I
I bet everyone would love that if
Ends up being the case
I feel like that was something that I might have heard whispered in a sidebar
But I'm not entirely sure if you listen to the
Pause
Just watching her constantly be like
Now I'm pretty sure we've never heard of Google Analytics
Take me to the head of Google about Google Analytics
Pretty sure we never heard of it like
You have 3 days of Brittany pozzi I don't know I don't remember
That was going to be there Stratus
Intuit
Here is proof that the business uses excuse still argue the business doesn't use x
The trial should be sure
Yeah less of that beat
You don't like
You beat her if you beat her over the head with how she's obviously lying
Often up the
The first try
Then you can use that as a shorthand does the court goes on your like oh well I don't have to
To prove this to you remember pause
This is that
Situation again
Pizza it seems like Alex is going to be there we recording this on Monday but it seems like he's going to
To be there
Tomorrow
So we're putting this episode out on Wednesday so by the time this comes out he may have already
Been there and you might have already gotten
Experience
Are you are you headed back
Yeah so I actually I came back
Friday
Brookland my wife and I actually had a little wedding party we got married earlier this year but now we're doing looking to your quiet
Congratulations
That's my bright spot
Of the day
I think what
Or just being cute belly
I think what I'm going to try to do is
Go back
At least the last
The trial
To be there for that but yeah I am I was
Disappointed to be there and not
Not have
Like show up.
It wasn't
Huge
Shocker
That you don't want to go
Yeah I remember we were standing next to each other in in Austin when Alex
First entered the courtroom on the on the
The first day we were both
Quite shocked
He would be there when you didn't have to
The whole Court was a murmur as it will he won't he kind of
Welcome
But yet it's like he
He was in office
That's his home turf
You know
So I think I think Connecticut
Go to be alive
Yeah and he doesn't really have that much of a bench
Bakhit Infowars I can't take
The months to go to
Connecticut
And and expect there to be enough people to fill in
Alex Stein
Filling in for him
Beside really
That's the kind of talent
Deadpool
Alex Stein harass
What am I
One of my recorder colleagues
She worked at Vici anyway he's
Advice
It seems like that's kind of Stein guys ammo
Is a horizon
Pokey
Yep yep I mean I got a job
Yelling at people at the protest
Yeah yeah
It's an unusual form of audition but it is an effective one in certain areas
If you're auditioning for a troll fact
Control
So when we were in Austin
We we got lunch
Fairly near the courthouse I'm on the way famously
On the ground we saw and Infowars bumper
Sticker
Used as Alex's prop
Put over a very bumper sticker that wants touch
What's the lips
Satan himself we found this discarded Relic
Julie
In the in the community about whether or not I had taken
And the answer was no
He belongs in a museum
But in
Connecticut you
This is this is
Huge got a lot of affection yeah you found a bumper sticker
In the wild
And this this caused a little bit of drama
Yeah so it was
On my way to the
The court in the last
And the first few days there were
Play Van fine
Right outside
The courthouse
Which was an intentional
Directly out of the courthouse this was that you know me block
Toxaway go into a restaurant or something this was
Right in front of the courthouse
Which is a by so many Infowars
Sticker is it why put them up right outside
Infowars.com
Store
Put I finally I finally the last I was there I
British singer all that I
Take a photo of it
It is not
The most courageous thing in the world that I've ever done you know I just I just raped office sticker
I understand
The other part of it though is that
Again
These families are walking into the courthouse
And they have to see that
And that to me is just that goes back to
The disrespect
Just shown
To these families across the board
Continues
To be shown to them
Yam
So yeah II
Rip it off and on
Ben
Tweeted about it and then and then Owen
Destroyer guide
Real mad about it
No see now this is interesting because
Shroyer is
You kicked off Twitter
Yeah it is all I do is Owen
Campbell
Oh no is that is really
I never have to look at it at
We could probably have gotten that
Destroy three but that really doesn't sound
What's good
Has found this tweet
And shown it to Owen
Or he has some kind of a band of Asian account
Which is probably the case
Furious
Cheese
Duck Destroyer
Cannot handle
I rattle them I rattle them
He's been destroyed
I got I got a
What a comment from Infowars people so yeah
The video edits
5 minutes
Love him of him whining about me
Take it off
It's thicker and because I said f*** Infowars which
Which
I did do that
Airport Atlanta course as a journalist we try to like maintain objectivity but info
Or if it's it's pretty black
You know there's no there's no moral gray area here
Ejective opinion to say f*** Infowars
We can't say that that's cuz they're f******
Crazy man
So he
He gets on
He gets on Infowars and he offers
He has an offer he
He begs me to come on
Intubate him
And then feather fight about what
Okay
Set up
I'm not going to do it
I'm so sorry
And you know that is
Bad is the traffic
You want the lady bear is
Come on a debate me
Yeah no s*** I will
Why would I lend
Legitimacy to you
And also you're going to profit that video ends
With an adverb
He played Grace
And he said if I had
If I defeat him in the debate that whole retire who's going to judicate
Defeated
I mean that I feel like you guys are all missing are you the greatest opportunity to
Like
It's say it has
To be a video interview debate
8 thing
And then you just move them
It's nuts
Exactly what plaster to my mine
Yeah that retire
Let me get away with a lot but I don't know
Boundaries
I am fascinated by the idea of challenging you to debate
Because
It's so open-ended
It's a bizarre request
Yeah that's fine
That really fun
So he challenges you to a
And if you win this
Debate
He will retire
It wasn't like specifically were to debate
About whether or not
Stickers should be removed or like
Just said yeah just the most open-ended again just goes back
Please come on my show
Play it please give me attention and then the headline of it will be Owen Shroyer destroys huffing
Wheaton post
Globalist reporter at it again
Feel like facial hair facial hair debate you've got
Okay cuz his
Is garbage
I think he's covering up a
That's what I thought
Well yeah
He also has I'm not sure if it's
Super consist
But he often has the beard with no mustache
The most disgusting
Well that's a sensitive to my myheritage
My Mennonite heritage
You look great
But I have the.
James it grows back in 5
Resign myself to essentially looking like a hobo
So I'm just I've made peace
Where is home
Still track it
That's right
Man it's so fun I wish there is like
I don't know I am a little jealous honestly like
I think I respond exactly the same way that you
Have
In terms of like
No I'm not doing this this is ridiculous
But I I wish you know what it is I want other than Harrison would have ever
Set our our name
But I think I think
Here you guys are way more of a threat
To him
Then I am
I really think that's true you guys are just like
Add it for
For so long
You are so knowledgeable
You know that
That I think they they know who you are
Right they are actively ignoring you
Tatoosh Channel aspect that you have of the Hub
Huffington Post
That is like
Announce
Irresistible thing for them to to
Try and grab on
After you for the huffing post for two reasons one it's a legitimate Outlet
Right so people have like a this is a news thing
You have a boss
Who says you can't do stuff
Come after us
We don't really have much legitimacy Beyond being everybody knows we're the only people who know what no one can tell you to do
Turn in your gun and badge
And if I said I will debate you and then showed him my ass on-screen there's no negative
Consequences for me
But we'd get over it I would
Give me a singer wife
Disappointed
So they don't want to fight somebody who doesn't have rules
The same way
You forgot the third reason but they would be out to get him as a husband
The post reporter 13 years ago
Very nice
Just gold
You want it back
So what time
Some of this stuff
Would you identify as like being the difference
Exes that you feel
Between the Austin and the Connecticut
Is there a real
Vibe that's different
Yeah I think and I hate you know I don't want to
Inflated ego too much but
Nothing
That that Mark
Did so well and end out whole team quite frankly
But they brought
A level of of
Charisma
Sort of like
Dick swinging
Bad
B trial doesn't have
At the Jazz.
That
Yeah the point
Deployers
The Connecticut case
Doing a great job
I think it's also
Much longer trial
So that's going to be
Part of it
At what I've noticed and in the Connecticut trial you know this first week we've only we had Brittany
Pause on the sand for 3 days
Tiring
But through that we have.
I think a lot of
Good new info
Formation
Of the
Internal
Innerworkings
Infowars
They've got they've got the the marketing
Kits that
Infowars
With signing out to advertise
You know we have the
The proof that they were using
Google Analytics
It's being bad Jones
Infowars
Infor
Minutes before the trial even began
Yeah
So I think
Italy
In terms of that I
I think it's it's
Creating a pretty powerful argument
We saw
I I want to run this one
This number offer
Real quick because
Really did
Shock Me
September 24th 2014 Infowars store
It's $48,000
The following day
Baby
Push the story at the Isis
Nobody killed at Sandy Hook massacre
It increases to 200
Sand dollars
Yammy that is it
Insane
Is proofs that
When they push the life their profits
What up yeah yeah there is
The other thing to visit they have them snapshots of the Google Analytics
Express on those emails
And you see that
Neatly tracks also to a giant
Spike in traffic
Yeah it's at the website and it's
It's pretty difficult to look at all those numbers and Nazi like
Well I don't know you'd have to find some way to
Connect their sales pitch to the stories that they're actually doing on the show
And I just think there's no way to possibly do all the weight know yet
Really notable to about this is that like I've seen some
Sales data that they've had
Iqc increases
In in the cells I believe like a
At the end of the author
Trial
Mark presented some of the tech
Which improves a that showed
That's some of the they were like
800,000 in a day
Distract
And like
That
He's definitely notable but what's missing from that context was that was like when they were doing the marathon
Like that was
But they were doing a 24 or 48 hour marathon
And obviously they're like
Pushing the sales
It's going to rain stuff
That Spike
In the 2014
I am now they were doing the nobody the FBI says nobody was murdered
That is just organic
From the traffic
It's driven from the
Yeah
Really get around that way
Yeah there's there isn't like
Weird X
External contact so damning about that number though is that even if you wanted
It would be on the jury in somebody's arguing that now we don't really pay attention to that kind
The numbers I'm mad just
Because that's so bad at business
That urine set you don't like
If the people on the jury or think are all well I saw my business going to pull I'm going to do that again
Like I ate is too ridiculous to think
That they would not notice a massive Spike like that while you're absolutely right
Especially because that is they don't have morals they there one desire
Is to get money
So that's
Bishop that they're going to pay it
Yeah and it strains credulity to imagine that like
They run
A warehouse and shipping business
And all these like
The pills in all this
And and then
They don't do any kind of analysis
Of the TV show
Is that Britney pause as the corporate representative
Can't be certain who works there
That be
The s*** out of credulity and leaves it out back behind a f******.
Speaking a company I don't know who has a show
Harrison Smith that's not a compliment
Cuz he was deaf
We forgot about
Have you been to other than Owens
Challenge
Look a bit monitoring the content at all of you been
Fencing any of the year the coverage
Through Infowars
Yeah yeah
Yeah I've seen some of the I watch the video on the
Kangaroo court
Yellow b******* bring it up
Brought up
At the trial as an example of Alex
Seriously
Which is just I've loved every time
And now we're on
This is the second time it's happened now where they judge houses
I hope that in
That's created yeah
Yeah
And you could argue that he's taking it more seriously cuz he didn't
Say that you connected
Is the pedophilia
Wild trout not done yet
True
That is a bar that most people would not think that you could cross
But yeah I got me now that I think about it
That is a certain level of restraint
There is that is it
Tangible level of restraint that we can see
I would almost accept that argument
See I'm doing better I really well I think that
Physically I guess that's true look I'm saying you're full of s*** I'm not trying to get you hurt
Try
Exactly
Outlander
So you you said you started covering some of this stuff
It's like at the beginning of the trial
Is that is that like where your
Newsly
But that's not the right word
For the news purposes covering Alex
Start in 2018
Yeah yes
Before 2018 I didn't really think
Kind of way
What ended up happening
Because I had gone
To Parkland
To cover.
That's what shooting would it happen
And then
And I was approached
Spy
By Mark Banks
Because
Marcel Fontaine
Was
Misidentified
Is the Parkland shooter by
Towards
And I'd brought a lawsuit against them
Giselle
And I believe
His attorney is saw
Parkland
Brought that story to me
And then from there
You know that
Half-witted Lewis case
Came in
Back so I guess I kept covering those cases
And I didn't realize you
Just how
The rabbit hole 5
I was going to have to get with this
I was glad to have done it
Alex that's how all of us wound up here we all were like
Well we just looked over and there was Alex Jones and then it's five years later and I don't have as much hair as I used to
Scholarship
We all jumped into the abyss and now we're more tired than ever
But it feels good
Always falling it's like you're not falling at all right
What's the weather think about it
You didn't have like a
Like a
Babe
Long
Standing like interested in
It's like right-wing misinformation
Not
Maybe not.
Secretly misinformation
But definitely have done a lot of Co
Right-wing extremism
Yeah big dog
White predators indio.ca
We've got that we know you're real
What what what brought that on
That was
IPad man I can't remember which
Time
There was
The time we
We help.
Uncover the leader of the bull Patrol they called bulb
Has dylann roof
Haircut
I had one recently of an Illinois police officer who who was
Dabbling
Pretty Harden's wife
Courtesy
Predator Harpo's actually sounds like a good Illinois that's nice
Not the right word to use actually
It was pretty fun
Okay
Post in general yeah it's a
It's me and and several other reporters
Right-wing extremist
Andy Campbell
Christmas ideas were in Charlottesville
Yet I wouldn't with a deal.
Please March
I went to
Charleston South Carolina
Dylann roof
Yeah
Detergent
So
Yeah we could have run into Jakari Jackson when he was down there
Possibly
Yeah
But yeah so
Sort of
You know Alex Jones
Just would have seemed like the next logical
I mean he is
Very much
Within that realm and and
Stirring the pot
As much as as much
Yeah
It's it's interesting that
Like how do you how do you deal with that
That like
Can you do this coverage
Are these extremists within organization
You know the bowl Patrol
Created their own by
Innovations
And you do coverage of it matter
That's important
It's newsworthy people should
You know about these
Things
But then the consequence of it
Comes with this
Attention B
You turned back on you and
Threats and the thief the personal information
Lakeview
You find yourself needing to
Havlik's
Security measure
Pictures that you
We do have a good
Security team
When we get to heaven
The dogs in a while
Bucket knock on with you guys
But
Yeah our team does a good job of like
Getting our information off a
I'd like another
They're definitely measures that you
Even taken
For Everyman
And then another time
My my parents Act
She got dogs
But their bag of Republicans
Jokes on them
They got dachshund people descend
Yeah exactly the liberal booking report and they're like yeah I know
Like I always think about like
If you have
Personal information like your you're
Address
In the hands of these
Nefarious
Dangerous weirdos
Do you move
Like
I mean it kind of tastes like I would move
Right now I don't know
It depends on the level of harassment and I actually
Whatever I'm done
30 really tails and
Comparison to a lot of other
Journalist particularly if you're if you're a
Female journalism
Far is it harassment goes
Any friends or whatever I can
Ignore it or you know not
Not worried about it as much but I think
If you're a female in that
Really got back cigars
Is it those are the journal at 2
Who I
Worry about it
My heart goes out to
Yeah
I guess I'm just sort of thinking about this like
Because I haven't
Really thought about it too much like
It's always been like the Expo
Fixation that like something is around the corner
Of some kind of angry info Warrior thing
Doesn't happen no no we never we never get any of it
Yeah we've we've barely been contacted
Twice three times maybe and
It's so disappointed when he says that
Leaving about the trial you got a bit of people
We're not on social media really be but I mean that's a big party
Seasoning is people when I was on Twitter people didn't come after me they went after people who were like
Tertiary
You know they were people who are around and so
If they said something similar to me then they would go after somebody with like
30 followers is up there but nobody spoke to
To me at all
Disconcert
Scary scary dude Jordan distorted just a f****** have the median devil
I wouldn't I wouldn't recommend
Good idea I'm just surprised nobody just gave it a shot CU unpredictable you yell a lot
You're too good at it probably in Austin with your pit
Yeah like his heart must be going
Nu-Way Jordan you also did you get admonish by like a bailiff
Something when we're not sure I got a couple but that wasn't really for anything just cuz you were about to yell at
To be a I was about to be a problem
That's good cuz I got to go back to the trial if I had gotten away with it also taught us an important
Is that you respect Bayless more than me
So do you plan to go to the the Posner case as well to you
Absolutely because that'll be I mean that's really the
The end chapter on this in a lot of ways
Is that I'd like to say that
Yeah things are done but
And you know
Muddy Paws R & N
Very nice
There are the ones who really
They were at they were the ones who really started going after Alex first
Whispered for the lies that he was Fred let Lenny God
You know Alex's videos
Taken down off YouTube
And so that is going to be it's going to be really
Things to see and I think
Is going to be
That. Trial itself even though it'll be the last one I think there's going to be so much
So many news
Story is a narrative and
In fact that come out in that
Blackheads
It's going to be really worth hanging
Yeah for sure
That's that is something I'd like to go back to sari 22
Take the conversation to step back but to go back to something you said earlier about how the in the text
Australian Omar
Can Company brought a certain
Big Swingin Dick Energy to
Yeah the proceedings you know you'd be threatening Gummy Bears or gummy world of Oregon
Was Bill a lot of bills got that car
But
In in this trial I felt like
There's much more of a almost nerdy granular elements
You know so when were when you compared the the lawyers I do think that the Connecticut lawyers are doing a really good job
Getting into the
Mary minor kind of detail stuff
Have you noticed
That kind of fellows
Sleep song
Nevermind question retractable I will say I might tear it to your point Jordan I will say that
And I keep saying this but like
There is a lot to come and there's going to be more testimony
Be a testimony of Bill Altenburg the FBI agent
I mean that was that was
Really difficult
Jawatan
Yeah he's essentially hyperventilating on the sand because he
He is
Not only did he have to
To relive
The horror of what he saw that day
But
He had
Let you
Say it in front of the family member
I think that's what was breaking his heart even more
Yeah he said that at one point he said
Achoo that he pointed to the family and I'm say he said I'm so sorry that I that I have to
To do that that I have
Talk about this
Yeah
My my heart breaks and I think
Those again or the sobering reminders of like
But the impact
You know they aren't on these people and the trauma that
He continues to exist
And the fact that Alex
An ant
Still won't let up
You know and
Still want to make a mockery of this
Just shows that they don't
They don't care they don't care at all
And I can't
I can't wrap my mind around that
You know I'm
I'm a journalism
Human Bean first
The end and there is
A real Line in the Sand
When your
Attacking the parents of dead kids
You know you're either on the right side of this or you're f****** dead wrong
Yes but not much
Not much gray there
It speaks to it speaks to the
Mitsubishi
Extensive what
Kind of s*** we're dealing with is like
You know any in your line of work especially you you know you've rattled off a list of atrocities
And you were there
And it's it easy to go
Get desensitized to
To a lot of that but at the end of the day
This is so f****** bad you cannot get desensitized to and yet
You know that
Weather tonight
It's
I think it's because
To become desensitized you have to have a starting point where you can
Ryan
Do you have to have a baseline event
State that exists
For that I think I think
From my experiences
Watching the show and
And looking
This
World for so long it's
It's a cynicism and it's a it's a
Baseline
I was like
Whatever works
Yeah it does
Completely disconnect
Did Trump
What you need to get
To become decent
And that cynicism goes back to Owen Shroyer trying to get me onto.
Because at the end of
The day it's still away.
But he gets a profit off
This trial right right
How are you how are you handling the you know like we as we've just kind of talked about that kind of disconnect
Where
You know you see
Bill Altenburg on the stand you see the families there and then at the same time
Minutes apart uce Norm badass making
What amounts to the legal version of dropping his pants
Saying the n-word of the dark
Yeah
You know that's a duck such a good point Jordan
Because I think and I know you guys
I can relate to this like
You have to be able to do both right I mean
Can you take it seriously in and let it be somber when it is but
We're also allowed
The point and laugh at the
The clown on stage
Right
So are you. I think both
Can kind of work in tandem but it is it is sort of emotional whiplash
You know
Fabian of the day I'm still
So going back to have a beer to just sort of like
Process
What the hell did I just watch
It's natural
Go to like
Like record
Big knives the clown arsonist
But like
It's still
It's so weird to have
But I guess it's kind of what we
We swimming all the time
This is funny
It also exists as a
It's painful and it sucks
It's not dark humor
That's not what it is
No it's it's like we're where we live at the
Demarcation point where reality and surreality are crashing together and it's your birthday
That's a reality is trying to come into the real world
Like like it is it they're trying to bring it through this fictional doorway and we're like
That's a wall
But
Kool-Aid man oh yeah exactly
Kool-Aid Man
Something that I thought
When you're talking about the bill Alden
Testimony
To go back to that for a second
What events I thought was really
Kind of horrifying about that that I didn't even really think of
Was the part of
His experience with
The entire
Aftermath
Is it
He was accused of being an actor
It was also one of the
The parent
Parent David wheeler
Yeah and so like
His experience
Of the
Denial of his
Experience
Also was
They can
An element of it for him was
Mister wheeler
Yeah like
I don't like an almost
Appendage to an already
I feel like
You are a part of what was being done
To this other person
I felt like that was something he was talking
Sing about
That was
Horrify
Exactly.
To me I think
Was was the most heartbreaking as a one-point
He said something to the effect of
I wish I had done
Differently he said he said that he took
Could some responsibility
Uniform
There's nothing
Think you could have done there's nothing differently he could have done that would have stopped
These days
People from
From still
Filmmaking trying to make this
Disconnection in Philly
Throwing his life and everyone else
Ulta flight into Indy
The chaos and turmoil
There's nothing he could have done it and yet
He still has
Clear guilt about it
That's that I think
It's got to be rooted in that to that overactive a
Nothing to like
Right he just walked
Think of some way there
You could have helped
You know but the cynicism is too great
On the other side you know.
It doesn't matter
Yeah it is it is weird
Because
It is it is a little bit like
Hearing some people describing like what they could have done better to stop a hurricane
Yeah hurricane was coming
Yeah you were just in the way
More sandbank or might have had the water get in somewhere else
Damage was going to be done
Exactly right
It sucks
This is a force of nature
In our mine
Well I mean
But now I don't know if it's that the line bulshit artist are the force
Nature so much of it as it is like
These types of
Panax r4c
You know like how many people got caught up in the satanic panic and all the sudden their lives are f****** destroyed
/ imaginary bulge
This is an arm of
I'm social undulation that so f****** weird
But it is kind of a force of nature
It all at the hope the hope is
Is that you know
With these trials battle
That'll help the
The koala the storm
Get Outlets
Get up from a hurricane to a drizzle
Right which is so which is so fascinating in terms of
The trial because Norm keeps bringing up that that thing that Maddie said the opening state
You know
We should we need to shut
We need to shut up
You know that kind of thing
And if the defense lawyer says that
You do feel like oh there's something prejudicial about
Right
But that's just being honest about what
Needs to be done to handle this cuz we can't you know
If it was a criminal trial with a put him in jail forever
Enter into that point to its like
But they're saying that
We have to shut them down to end this
Because the proof is at
They're still trying to profit off of it you know there's it's about the trial in the kangaroo cordon bleu
Autobahn so
Yeah
I mean the only way they're going to learn is if you take
Their money away
Yep yeah the ultimate lesson I think is
So much
It's just
They won't learn
They had learned they don't want to
An argument
Pretty easy to make the
A fitting punishment
It just has to be like
You can do a podcast
Honestly
It's almost like listen
I don't want any punishment other than that you just
Can't talk on the air anymore you can do whatever you want with the rest of your life
You just can't bother people
Like it is it is a little bit like you didn't you just can't be that guy anymore
Yeah I can I can think of some other punishment
But I'll keep it to myself well listen hey you know me I'm a
I found it interesting that Norm in his introduction
Who's kind of like
Conceding the fact that
Take it they're going to prove that Alex is a liar
And like
Take that one of the things you would
Think of a second
An appropriate punishment is like
Really
Recognizing that this person is full of s***
In a very public
Space
But I ain't then I realize like no they'll concede that
Yeah matter
Yeah
Sucks
Norm Norm also so a couple you know somehow
Colorful
The trial is Norm had a sidekick
Cake with an
Who liked another lawyer
You helping next to him who had a slightly shorter ponytail
When you get fired at to Paddy's Loft
They cut that off
They're legal Knowledge Tree
What Betty chops Patterson half with a lightsaber things are gonna get real into
It was a it was a stretch
What time the pet his head like a weird like quarantine beard going to I was wondering who's going to show up with
Just like
Giant beard I'm glad
Glad you didn't
Hanakai sucks what a weirdo
What an adverb every time he walks around
I mean it's just everything about him is wrong
I don't like
Necessarily but I figured maybe is inevitable
So much of the conversation about the trial
Like whether it's with
With you here or even on our show when we just talked about it
Focus is around Norm
Like I just
It's hard not for it not to be like he's such a
Yeah he and he's with a picture and Alex
This world for a long time now so
Yeah he was there when Alex put out a bounty
On Chris Mattie
It was instant right well I was drunkenly screaming about that
Yeah his Antics like he's he's a dancing monkey in the courtroom and every now and again you just Arts
Banging symbols together and you can't not look at the
Monkey banging it
Together what are you doing Monkey
How did you learn this is your master
He'll be there tomorrow I'm fascinated
To imagine how
Cross-examination
Going to go or just
Norm
Galaxy Quest
Can't imagine
MS
Exhausting
I've already started my objects
I'm just going to say objection for now
Season
I can't imagine him
Being Alexa
Kit Medi more than two or three questions through to Alex
Before their like we're just shutting
Norm's going to have a tough time as a week
He's already
Nodded off in the courtroom and he
There is a
Recess and so he was like
Tweeting
Just like other s*** you know Mike cernovich
Yeah
About the migrants being sent to Martha's Vineyard
Heaven the game Norm
You're busy right now Coram
Okay little bit of nonchalance goes a long way
I kind of suggesting that you got your you got a tight hand on this ship
You know I actually did that you're mad at that way
You might have a point
He's trying to nag
Falling asleep in preschool
If you hold approval and then it will come to you
I don't want to load Judgment at all I'm so cool right Cheryl
Judgment
The first trial the strategy was redpill the jury
Second strategy for using the game
Amazing
Probably wrap this up before too long we're coming in
Close to an hour here's that I'm figure before we do those there
What is there anything else on your mind
Do you think is like
Important
From your experience
Like maybe
Yeah every trial that you want to bring two
Bring the Forefront
Yeah I mean I think just
Set up before but I think
Worth always repeating that like this is
Is about
The Sandy Hooks
This is about
Piano.
The parents who lost their children this
This is about the the mothers in
Consigned to lost their parents
Listen
About the teachers who
Gave their lives
Is protecting the
These kids
And
And it
It-it's
It f****** sucks and I think all that we can do is
Is 2
Things a little bit harder for
People like Alex Jones
Wall also
You know
Doing our best
To beat also
Walk with Kyle
You know what I mean like
There's one thing that this
Taught me it's it's
Yeah
Meb
The parents are just so courageous
They're there in courtroom every day
Alex is hiding
Texas
And they're they're not even
Are they they're not test
Pathfinder showed up to the
The courtroom
And that is just like that that level of Courage is something that I
We'll never know I hope
To never have to know
And so I decided all the Lovin
And all the respect in the world
For those people
That's all I got to say
That's definitely something that's even though we
You know we bring a tent
Listen to that
It can never be sad enough absolutely
Exeter brings to my mind I wanted to bring this up
Cuz I forgot to ask you about this
But there was on our
Subreddit
Are plants subreddit
Mark
Did post
A proof of life
Were you around when there was a confrontation with the
Yeah so yeah
Why does
Jogged into my mind was
Because you know you're talking about like
The courage of showing up
These families showing up everyday Court
You know there is the emotional courage of
Being there in this
Really difficult
Cold
Horrific setting and then there is also just the real
Like literal physical courage
The risk of being accosted by somebody like
Yeah
What happened
So it was a it was related to
To meet killing the cigarette
30 people are idiots
Been triggered by me on defacing your property
So so I am not 100% sure but the running theory is that it was Corey
Glencoe who is Wolfie
King Hall Biggs driver
Connecticut and that he might have just
Driven out there
To see something
Sticker download Mark is next to me I take a photo of it
He is smoking a
Cigarette and very aggressive
The lady tells me
Need to move on
Oh so this was your fault
I will yeah so it's so then so then as as we were walking
Into the courthouse
He the guy is walking in behind us
End
Start saying
Tomorrow can I believe says tomorrow
You b****
About poison ivy
Sort of loudly
Sat in front of the
Payless that I said you know
Looks like somebody
Probably this morning
But then he just
Yeah they let
Security no
Ran away I guess but
I like the pterodactyl lamp in The Flintstones in the city
Somebody's girl
Just try to keep it light you know
Oh yeah my last words
Before I get my ads
Nobody's grumpy
Might do
I do appreciate Mark just has that way of bringing it out of people absolutely
Really good other people scared and make them want to throw take a swig
Was the sticker
Who cares
Betty's with the other way that we get through the abyss
Yeah
Same time you know if it is in fact
The case that this was like
This guy was Wolfgang halbig associate
Threatened you know we're hearing on this and the Wolfgang is reaching out to
These Infowars people in like
Sexually harassing them now
The trial is going on like
There is a reality to this that
It's like it's still
You know
I don't want to say luckily it was directed at you
But like
Yeah it was it was directed at Mark too and I think
Between the two of us we went by
Plural you
I supposed to like a family members
Is that this is a man who's lived most of his life believing that the
The TV is talking to him
Look at
The TV on
At Wolfgang if you're listening to me right now what
That's a weird thing for Norm to have done
I wonder I wonder if it does,
Macross azbetter
To be like I'm not going to directly communicate with him I'm just going to say this through the medium of
The Stream
You should take care of that so how just briefly
That a Wolfgang after the author
Central he's he's letting me a couple voicemails
Which adjuster
The rambling
Ghetto sad boy
I thought you were excited
But
What are the days of the trial I get an email
Not to me directly Wolfgang just sends it to
FBI agent everyday
Everybody at yaddo imma I'm on his
Newsletter you know his mailing list
And and
The email
Guy for that one well I'll keep an eye on it and I honestly use MailChimp
Yeah
That's a good segue into
No but he is the email was about how the Connecticut Governor light
To him about Sandy Hook he's still doing this
You know he's still doing this even
The day
Of of testimony in the second defamation trial if
Even after he has lost
Arby's
Bee suits
You are like bright
Well and and his family
He does have the ultimate freedom of literally having nothing left to lose your pot committed
But that's also that is
Going back to what we're saying that is
Danger right
When you got nothing left to lose
You know
So
Well
Fingers crossed
Find something
But he doesn't want to lose
I got spell yeah not a great situation
Weather
God
I guess I just started
Getting to a like
Negative thoughts
What's spiral about like
Maybe get a hobby
Brian
Expensive
To you
Will either one sounds fine
Sebastian thank you so much for joining us this is been a delight
It was really great meeting you down in Austin and I love you boys and
And just have all the f****** respect in the world for what you guys do
We we definitely appreciate your coverage
Of the
The trial has great to have more voices saying put the parents and families and all that is
The Forefront of everybody
Field respect
For that thank you so much
There's a there's a
Slight chance I might
Come down to Austin
I admire you being able
To go to these trials but they was supposed to exhaust
Well let's talk about it
You just want us to f****** supper with you
That is exactly my
Yeah that makes sense
Alright
Alex
Same color
I love your work