Knowledge party.com
I have great respect for its knowledge B I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
We are the bad guys
Need
Everybody welcome back to knowledge fight I'm damn
But sit around worship
But the altar of Selena talked a little bit about Alex Jones
Nordam question for you buddy
My brakes about today I feel weird about this but
It is
I have been
Trying to find entertainment to watch well abma kebatan to
Buttons out
And I've walked
A few online
YouTube videos that are
They're basically people explaining
Hoax games
Quick interactive alternative reality games
Okay I can't okay. Going to say what you say
YouTube videos up at f
Clues and you got a crack
Okay okay alright but they're like used as like narrative storytelling internet
Scavenger hunt
Stories but sometimes they have their like horror stories
I don't know I would never want to do one of these things
Or be involved in a lick
Be one of the people crying
Crack the puzzles
The man listening to
People just
Like Bass
Basically pretend that an art project is real
Kind of fun
I enjoyed
So
It is is it the like unfettered just
Willingness to commit
To this world or are you just like
I just like
Any any
Enthusiasm
Yeah absolutely
My bright spot
What is what I'll tell you this
Do remember how I ABC and HBO and Warner and all that stuff there's all of that merge
Stop.
So ATC Owingsville
The challenge
Be real world real world
Not called that
Write out so they put out a season and is filled with like ABC reality stars you know those types of people
And they were
You know
But but then my my partner found a season from the old days
That we had watched before
Man
I don't know you need some kind of Dirtbag element to that show you mean dirtbag
Who says Dirtbag about
That's the only reason that any of those he's got to have that we're watchable at all know it's not a competition
Dirtbag
And it's so unethical
Because it's just like
Give them all the alcohol and hope the Dirtbag goes crazy
Is the fundamentally unethical but at the same time like
If your Continuum is
What my Continuum is the Great British Bake Off at the challenge
It's like any all of the reality competition shows fall in between those two poles
That's Scottish lady with a dirtbag
Talk to you in a few of the Great British Bake Off
I don't say that about Liam
They're called hollywoodism
Someone who is not a dirtbag
Thank you I guess
Joining us
Returning to the podcast were very excited to have her along to give some
Insight
Into things on the ground
At The Alex Jones trial
Connecticut
Elizabeth Williams
It's Williams son and thank you for not calling
It wasn't wow
Legitimately we've known you for years you know what happened there is I was in my head arguing
About whether or not I was going to say
The New York Times or Brianna.
Can I drop the Sun
I can't believe it said of the New York Times Sun
Yeah probably
I have to put it somewhere that does please accept my apologies and what is your brakes by
Absolutely
Here I was thinking
So okay
My bright spot
Because I've been all day at the Alex Jones damages trial
At the end of the day
A in a truly by
Brightspot
The sun came out
After raining all day
At the end of The Garden Court
And
Someone convinced
Alex Jones that there was a security threat
And so if they prevented him from having a press conference after his mouth
Countdown in court ohwow
Somebody
Somebody trolled him into
Being an a******
Exactly and I have a have a Siri now I know I shouldn't you know because we're talkin about
Jessie theories I know I shouldn't do this but
I did hear two bailiffs Talkin at the end of the hall after he left
Andre said well
Something like
That works
He can't shut his mouth
There's a number of things that we experienced he recording this on Thursday there's a number of things that you could probably be like well.
That worked
The day of that work
Maybe their phone
Or something like that
But it was you no right after
After he got onto the elevator and he kept saying they're telling me it's a security issue
I think the only conclusion
We can take from this is that the bailiff
Are under the employee of Klaus Schwab
They are talking about the trial as a whole
Considering they are part of the global
Which we have to assume at this point
Even more funny is that he would believe that
Because
When you went outside the courthouse
There was maybe
One guy
With a
Microphone
A couple of
You know
Reputable News truck
And really no one else Tumbleweed going good
Accounting for it how many rooms were there around
Yeah yeah yeah
Equalizer discount rooftop band
If you are a
Disreputable assassin blood say
Why wouldn't you was trying to
Supposed with a reputable news organization
You camouflage
It makes total sense for Alex to believe that because it's
It plays into his like
Importance
Absolutely
Yeah yeah
You can trick people couldn't be bothered
Turn up just a
Support them in court I'm not sure they could be bothered to
Turn up to
Do whatever he was afraid they might do so
Yeah
A question that I was meaning to ask you
Elizabeth not there
I was wondering
About those press
Cuz because I like not to
Poison the answer
But I find them really really gross
How do you feel about
The fact that like no matter what
You do like you could
Choose not to
Duke one of those
There will be other
News organization
They're right
No matter what you do
So you might as well be there
But like how do you feel about the actual event
That happened
Filthy
Yeah no I
I have I actually had this very conversation with
Another journalist
I'm in the elevator
Deciding not
You do one of his press conferences
Because the other thing
Here we did one yesterday where
He did at the lunch
Break but he was late showing up and so by the time he started
Talkin
It was almost time for court to begin again
And so there you're really faced with you.
The thing that you're
Absolutely talking about Jordan witches
Do I go into the courtroom and listen to the Sandy Hook families tell their story or do I
I said here
Outside
Stand here and just listened to
This word
Salad immuno
Repetition
We've all heard it before thousands of times you know do we just
Listen to Alec
Alex Jones bloviate
You do deliver what he usually delivers or do you go inside and actually
You know rejoin the real world
Yeah so what are the things that I think is really tough about that
Pat said that choice therealak
How to put everyone in by showing up late
And having a press conference is that
Press conference
Itself is a disrespect
Text to the what's going on in Fort
And then it's forcing people to make this choice
Between Lake
Watching him disrespect
The court or go into the court
I know that we were watching it and
Airline crime stream
Was showing
The Alex outside
If you got a minute left right what are they going to do are they going to cut away from him to go in
All right it's just one guy
And yeah and
Thanks Dan because I was going to make that
204 room service came of course
The mats that
You don't fit this whole thing is
This is
Does Neil heslin put it in Austin at the trial you attended
It is an act of
Cowardice
That Alec
Jones does not show up
The courtroom for his own trial
Unless he is compelled to because he has to test
So this trial has been
Been going on now for nearly two weeks
And
This is the first day he has shown up
But he's been in town for a couple
Couple of days and he's have these press conferences out in front
And even when he's not in town he's watch
Watching everyday on his show and he is near
Maligning the process
The judge the proceedings
And setting up a website as they said in court today
Kangaroo Court where his viewers
Can watch
And donate
To his legal defense so
You know it just is
After the last
Trial
One of the jurors that was shared with me
Said that his
Failure to turn up
And the fact that
He was tearing apart
The entire process on his show
Really pissed off
Because it
Said that
He has other contempt
Did you just show processing this country and that's
Really what
Where is today right
Compelling case for why you got
Default that behavior
I need to get that confirmation
From you just because
It's like
While I was watching the trial in Austin
I'm sitting in the courtroom looking at the Jersey no kind of
Getting an idea of how it is they were feeling you know there is there good Poker Face
But I do know there were some of those moments like that the one that will always remember is
The guy who is writing notes
For the first
Our two of Alex's test
Tamari
Putting his notepad down
You know what there's no
Keep doing that I get it
It's nice to know that that
He's
Specto behavior that they account for because that there is a part of me that's like
I don't know if they would care about that so much that these are people who are taking time out of their lives
Old was civic duty
And it probably would be an affront to
To the sacrifice that they're make
Race
Exactly rather than collecting my heater per diem and Dad
No I am as you recall
In off
Austin he was maligning the jury themselves
Right he was calling them you basically death
Blue-collar Folk
They don't know any blue-collar folk who love
That's what I'm going to insult them
I will I will say one
Something about his press conferences out front was I was actually on the phone with you Elizabeth
The story about his bankruptcy
Record and
Just hear him in the background starting to talk
And we rushed off the phone and on the stream I saw you walk behind
That was kind
Great bankruptcy content that was what I was in
Search up
I got a little bit I thought
Right I mean
He did touch on that to you did get a little bit of the banker
He he he recast you know what was really a
Pretty devil
Stating hearing for him earlier this week
That's exactly
A bankruptcy judge in Texas
To remove
My lawyer and Mike
Infrastructure in office
Officer
Because
That means we'll get additional oversight over Free Speech systems that we just so dearly need
Someone who is completely honest Billy unlike the lawyer and the chief restructuring officer Who We Are
Someone who is completely unrelated to free speech systems imagine that
Yeah he is
You've got to be thrilled like
Exactly what he wanted before a bankruptcy judge
You say
Something along the lines of I hope I never have to
To do something like this in my career again
But they dropped
The Gallows
F****** talking about I hope I never have to
Is there a bankruptcy
City Court Judge get the f*** out of here
Sorrow not anger
There is
Are beyond your parents
Being disappointed not angry
Saro nothing
I am so disappointed at this bankruptcy filing
I'd say maybe there is something to this for the for fries which system is because based on
Pause and Alex's testimony
I don't know if anybody knows how that business actually works or where money comes from or you're being so nice
Somebody to finally know what that actually going on
Strategic unawareness
But might be
What kind of what kind of two words are those to put next to each other
Absurd
The thing that I also liked another sort of meta aspect of this whole thing is
So
One of the things that the bankruptcy
He judge raised as a lack of
Candor
Transparency and a quest
Questionable
Business expense
Personal expense actually by Jones was the $80,000
That he pulled out of
The company to finance his trip
Cheer
In Connecticut
Where he has a Cadre of bodyguards
Jake Sutton Court today that
He took a chartered jet
To Waterbury Connecticut
And
Browser
Sweden
SUVs under staying at
Free Posh Airbnb
A short distance from the courthouse so
It doesn't seem like
Bankrupt
Behavior
Wasn't the 80,000 just
Just for security wasn't just like security detail
Yeah that's what
That's what the judge said in the bankruptcy case
Is it that they took out even more
Honestly
His his nitpicking
Response
About the jet
With so much
What Alex
Is to me is like
The same time as he's supposed to be like
Defending himself
He can't help
It'll be like the first time we ever charted a jet
You know when you're like
What are you f******
You do it you would same Madman
You said that
He never chartered Jets
Before 2018
RaceTrac
Amorous
Security problems
In other words I don't want to be hassled in an airport
They don't have Security in airports
You know or I think if there's a a second
Interpretation is at
Before all this I couldn't
Afford one
What you mean
Morgz
The point
Such a difference Europa
How is it been on the ground they're like
Comparative Lee we talked to the Sebastian our last
Episode
And
We got kind of a sense of his feeling but
Premier Premier
Comparing the house Things Are
Feeling them
The Vibes in Austin versus
Does Connecticut
What are some of the big
Takeaways that you're noticing
It is
Cooler
Cher
Giving temperature
5 degrees in Jordan now
Sweating through his shirt right next
Estimated endorse me feel
Thanks
There are there
There's no
Voodoo Donuts
It's
It's not a it's not a special
Cuz you guys aren't there
We really liven up a city
Which exactly why it's a good thing we're not there I think I think the problem is
We liven up
Trial not a thing you want livened up
That was
The Lively stay
I you know is a little different
It's
It moves more slowly
I think
Partly because there are so many places in the case you know this is the
These are the
The families of eight Sandy Hooks
FBI agent who is implicated in these
I'm in Jones's bogus
Conspiracy theorist
Mysterious forgetting that the FBI themselves are shadow plaintiffs
Oh yes
Yes what did he said
This is kind of a deep State deal
Sing yes
Jesse's going to live on in infamy
Alongside such things as like
All we have to fear is fear
A slash globalist
Golden Krust robloxia
Oh and he stands for freedom
Freedom
And
And his
Listeners are buying those 17:7
76 coins because they like
First Amendment
Well actually I I want to get back to your observations but I I want to point out that he was not lie
Lying about
Being clear about the markup on the coin
No it's true
Yeah he does lie about margins on other products but that woman is totally
About
When it comes to physical
Currency you cannot
He said on the stand like
The conservatives know about gold and silver and I think that's why he couldn't get away with bluffing the margin
Whereas other things at the how much
Beats cost
His audience knows
The price of gold but I guess
This is my audience doesn't know that the covid-19
Adidas free
But they do know 150 percent markup when they see it
Are those coins gold or are they gold
Downtown I think they're silver
Call Oakview
I feel like Alex is always been a little bit more of a silver
Hawk then a gold medal made it clear today he even pointed out he was like
The point
99 silver coin or whatever it is
Yeah
That cost you - $2 2 to buy Teddy Roosevelt going
His demeanor in court was
Unusual I mean it was not it was sort of the same and that he was sweating
To him this is the same temperature as as Austin
Definitely sweating
But but also a very rapid sort of eye blink
Yeah really
Really kind of a running his words together and you know doing that
That sort of
Thing that he does
That's where he
She hasn't like a
Hausler of words together and then he
She gets to the right place but there's just it's almost like
The connection goes in the middle of the sentence
Do you know what I mean
Oh yeah I was
Edit certain point
So off
Put by the blinker
But I was Googling around
For like
Is it a symptom of something
Time does really like a
Nicole damage
Despise me too much but I received more than one text
Amphetamine abuse
The
With the CNN reporter in the courtroom
Mention that during one of the breaks
He pulled out some kind of manila envelope
Took some
Kind of medical
Acacia
Well that's how we all carry our meds around
Goddamnit what a weirdo
Abnormal first
Aquaman
Who knows
Superman
I did not witness this myself I hasten to add
Okay so this is technically hearsay
I would go and Cersei
Reindeer say
Rainforest over super Bale for this country has liquid though isn't it
He puts it under the tongue
Or the base El Paso
Debate that happened
The recipe
Yeah the beats
Yeah that was it that was an interesting thing
Ura you've been in the courtroom obviously this entire time and
Today's display was one of
The more shameful things I think that has ever happened like how does it
Feel The Beat
Really
F***** up intense hatred
It feels like
Between everybody
Professionally involved there
Like the lawyers
The judge like
No one's happy
Yeah it's
Pretty
Yeah
There's a there's definitely a vibe that goes through the room when he was walking in now
I was kind of wondering to myself
You know
Especially the first three rows where you have the families and the people close
Not all love lost there and
I was wondering to see thrive on that
Or does that
Bother him I couldn't really tell
You know
I mean is it isn't just
Any kind of
Focused attention whether it's like
Focused hatred or
Neutral attention or
Or admiration is it all the same to Alex Jones or
Or what
I think I think from his earlier career you could make an argument that folks
This negative attention is actually
More
Appealing
Thrive in situations where he's
Yelling at people in there all
Yelling at him or
You confronting somebody Ori
You know
Years
The bullhorn
Approaches I don't know I think
He doesn't do that as much
Now
For whatever reason but even
Even around the time of like a women's March
No he was going out and yelling
Cupcake
You know like
Eat
I don't know I mean I think he likes negative attention more and
Just kind of
Weird
Imagine that
Extends to a courtroom
And Sandy Hook families
Yeah
Well I guess
That's one of the reasons he's not showing up in court I mean I think the kind of negative attention where he's yelling at someone in there
Trying to go back and he's drowning them out is exactly
Yep sitting you know in a place where
People are
Quiet
And actually very dignified but also
Hating him down the last
Yeah might be disconcerting
Yeah and you got to think for
For Alex
Like I mean
If I put myself in this space and if I walked
Cindy Court I would
Feel like
Psychically like I had hand
Topside regardless of what
Courtroom I was walking into for whatever purpose
That's what
Associated
My brain
But
Cuffs mean
Half as much
The Alex as not being able to scream what he wants
Still at somebody
So like
If I were going to diagnose what his main issue I don't think
He cares about the
Attention
So much as when he's
Talking
He's not allowed
To say what he wants
Do and it's going to dry them
You know it did seem to at the end
Yeah I boiled up he boiled up lady
T-Pain you could almost feel that
That
Resist
Breaking down
Or whatever you know. There was like
Alright I'm not going to ramble off a bunch of nonsense
And then at some point
Yeah I buy tea kettle boiling
Iqu
Call Dad
That end of the day today
Was
Banana yeah I don't know what to I don't know how to put it like it's it was so
Unnerving
It didn't feel good
It's
Ikea
Saying that I feel on
Unsafe
Sing this trial
Yeah like
I don't know what's going to happen
Things
Don't feel any
Control
Norm clearly doesn't have any kind of a handle on
Alex told the judge
Yeah
He was muttering to himself
Walking down the corridor after court
Adjourn
Saying
What way
What was this thing I would he said I am not
Appliance keeper and I thought you swear to God I almost I almost interrupted you and said I am not
Not My Brother's Keeper I swear to God I was the waiver.
That's awesome now this also reveals
Unawareness
The Bible because the answer to m i My Brother's Keeper is yet
Norm
Is trying to knock
You know the good guy in that story was not the one
Who is that
Who is this
Vets
There is a
I don't know what I mean
I think there is a delinquency in Norm's laissez-faire attitude
I am grasping at words
It's here but I think he's being negligent
You know you got the distinct impression that
He is performing for Alex as much as Alex is performing
For him that's what I was thinking
Yeah that
Let you know as soon as
The things God
Heated
You started
Barely jumping up
Up and down and set up jection objection objection and as the judge pointed out
You are objecting to things your client
Is saying
Which is actually a good thing when your client is Alex
You know
You can't complete violation of the rules
So she was so she was saying
What are you doing Norm you know you're basically
Object your ear
Your your objections first of all
You're a client is ignoring you so
You know when when your own lawyer of Jack
You stopped
Talking and you wait for a ruling cuz chances are you're not going to have to answer the question
It right
Stephen just kept talking
Didn't matter if Norm was injecting it didn't matter if Norms objections were sustained which men
Alex wouldn't have to answer the question
I was just
Kept rolling cuz what he was doing was looking for a knob
Opportunity
To break the rules against making this a political
Kind of trial
Not supposed to talk about electoral college
Presidential politics are political figures
He's not supposed to make this
Partisan
Thanks
She was a b
Absolutely looking for every up
Opportunity to slip that in there he's not supposed
First Amendment rights he's not supposed to talk about it
Does bankruptcy
He's got a
A lot of you know use the term handcuffs handcuffs
Cheyenne bus
Do Olive
So that was all he was looking for
Eleanor was just so you know I'm going to show Alex that I'm objecting objecting objecting at Stanley's lawyer
Where is going out
So we just got to the point where he was just shouting objection
Do you know if you would have stopped him and said what are you objecting to I don't think he would have had an answer cuz it was just he was
Adding to the general tumult in the room
Well you can't just say shut up Alex you missed an opportunity to be like this whole Court rooms out of order
There it was
Brunuhville you know what
Cuz I hadn't thought about
But you bring it up in that list of things that Alex
Couldn't talk about
The partisan politics
6 aspect
Makes it
Steam
Like there was
Kind of an intention behind like
Conservatives know the
The price of gold
Ben silver
App for no reason
When they do back
Back and forth exchange was happening towards the end
Alex said
Something along the lines of you liberals wanted to kill everybody in Iraq
Turn it off and on
Yeah but like
It's interesting that
The Liberals are to blame for
It seemed like a non-sequitur until I was imagining
Looking at it through the prism of like making this
Sort of a partisan political idea
Yeah so here's what I
I think there were two things here
One is that some of the Sandy Hook families in this case
Have been Act
Given the gun control movement some of them have been Act
They've been democratic
Politics
He wants
To bring that up
Because of course his false theory of the case
Is that
This is enough
Offered by the Deep State and the Democrats and all of his political enemies to silence him this is not
What about you know the abuse these families have been subjected to
Because of his years worth of lying about
Sandy Hook
No
Be you do a persecution thing so that's
1 and 2nd
I think and because Norms doing it to a he knows Alex is watching him on TV so he is
Performing
For his clients
But second
Get the sense that there might be
They have
Nathan
There are
Some conservatives
On the jury
And they are playing to the gallery basically
Not forget the element that Norm is also just
Crazy
Yeah he is a nut bag
That that is a fact
Yeah I mean I think
Based on the way that I'm I'm
Interpreting
You know what you're saying and then
Experience was with
With the Jerry and Alex
Is just like
I feel like
In his mind
In a murder trial
All you have to do is convince one member of
The jury of
Reasonable not-guilty that kind
In in my mind what I'm seeing him do is like
We've seen politics
Override
Everybody
Thoughts
To the point where sometimes
Do you see people say absolutely in
Saying s*** just
Because it's like I'm
I'm with
Which team
I'm with the Republic
Continue no would make sense
That he would think you know
If I can get a couple of these conservatives
Completely remove any and all independence
Thought
Which is possible
Then maybe you can get out of it
Well it's that by the way
Yeah it's the
Alex talked about this and has historically for a long time there is a philosophy of Jerry Nolan
Application
It has to do with
Usually in like criminal things like
What was the jury does
Don't think what you did was wrong they cannot
That is
A dangerous
Kind of idea in some apple
Occasion
Yeah I think everybody knows the
Set the Constitution wanted to
The jury to take the law into their own hands
Ignore the
The judge and the lawyers and judge
Just think about who's on there
I think he's hoping for that
But hey
I think after today at
Probably is tough
Most
Of the jury to think
He's taking this
Seriously
Right I mean
Pastor Buell prevalent feeling
Yeah
Because
You know it wasn't
Just I mean that the Outburst at the end in the craziness got all the attention but
Throughout
He was completely mendacious and he was pretending
Daddy's really didn't know
What was going on on his show you know everything about you know this headline they did it they put that
Bravo somebody might event
You at the same time you had Infowars employees who have been deposed under oath and they have said
Alex Jones calls all the shots
You know for better or worse
Usually For Worse
So
Yeah so the idea that
You know he wasn't
He wasn't sure what was going on in his own shop
Consistently
Visa V Sandy Hook
This doesn't make any sense
I've never been to Greece
Set reminder
He's so much whatever he said every time he was like I didn't know who titled that
We're at it's not my finger I don't get daily updates
I just remembered Ari is testimony as the Corp
Representative
I mean there were so many times where I remember just being like
Well she shouldn't have said that
Nope that one says Alex
Controls
Everything you know like
You should not have done that
That was a
Boy
Video of the two corporate Representatives you know Brittany pause
Who is the corporate representative in this case vs Daria
Wow that that were those were two different types
Yeah yeah this
This had a real mercenary a-spec
To it
Where is Daria was like
He'll also a religion
I will destroy all of you
With one look
I wrestle with this
I'm not
Rich by any means
But I can't imagine doing the job that Britney pass did
For 30,000
Dollars
That is yeah I think she really went home
Feeling ripped off
IAAI
I hope
I mean I don't know if I hope I don't know what I hope I were if I hope it at all but
I kind of hope there was a bit of under-the-table money
Workers rights
Why are you lying with labor no matter what perfect
It's 30,000 Infowars
There's enough of them wga East my actually take them in
They're fixing writer
I think I think
Today obviously the big thing
King is this
This outburst
Kirsten and how the day ended
But I actually think
There was
Maybe the most important thing that came out of today
Was
The questioning
About
Matthew Mills the guy who interrupted the Super Bowl
Interview
And one of the reasons that I think this was so important
Just to give a short breakdown of what it is
Alex
Had Matthew Mills
On his show who is the guy who
Is the 2014 Super Bowl I believe
He
Interrupted
Did the MVP press conference at the Eldorado 9/11 was an inside job
On the show and
Was like you're the best
You're so great
I love you I got to give you a job you're my Soldier
Not whatever
Yeah brother
Very enthusiastic about him
And Alex had to own all that
And then
It's revealed
McGee
Matthew Mills
Was arrested later
For harassing
DeSoto family members at their charity 5k
Yeah
The reason I think
This is so critical is that it draws this
Straight line
Between
Alex
Endorsing
Offering to hire
Congratulating
This person who is doing essentially
Let me know how is it any different than harassing people at the 5K
Actually I agree with you guys
That was really a revelation to me I mean
I really know some of that I mean he
The facts
This is what I didn't catch even when I was writing my book you know I wrote
I put an entry in about Matthew Mills
And what happened at the
The 5K
But I did not know that on
Infowars
Jim Jones said and they played that clip
You know I've got some other disruption I wanted and I'm paraphrasing here but I've got some other destruction I want to talk to
You about offline
And this
You know this disruption of the 5K came after that
So whether it was exactly that or not and of course Jones said it wasn't
It does as you stayed and robbed at line and
You do one of the challenges here for the lawyers
In this
Particular case
Is that
Very few of
These plaintiffs have been named
By Alex Jones on the show
And it's
Harder to draw that
Direct line so this I thought I agreed this was really kind of a revelation I didn't know he had had
That guy on celebrated him and then he went on to
Disrupt
That event
For Vicki Soto the teacher who was killed at Sandy Hook
Yeah and I think one of Alex's
Good primary
Maybe primary defenses but one of the things that's thrown around a lot is
Even if
People were harassed
Nothing
Things to do with me you can't draw the line right
Check with me and I think that this case of the Matthew Mills thing
So damning
Because it disrupt
That are
Yeah
It's not just
Somebody who like maybe
Emailed Alex or that like
Like tenuous connection
This person had Alex's full-throated support and
A job offer and
They conspired on air about
The behavior that is
Boob
Disruption of the 5K whether or not they actually
Conspired and Alex paid him
You do that
Leaving that aside right
They had the conversation about him being employed to do
Physically that right
Well I mean they made big enough I think it was raining all who made the argument in court he was he was saying like
Okay
Isn't
It a crime for people to do these
So for people to harass somebody like that it's a crime
Is a federal crime
Why haven't they been arrested
So how can you say that they you know that it was that
That bad
Done a little bit of that this time especially with the exaggeration claims and and if you
If you got that
Boy
F****** that sucks
Yeah
If Alex can just yell jussie Smollett whenever anybody says he makes things up and why can't everybody.
He's like you can't connect me to any of this baby with Matthew Mills
That actually was
Criminy
Flat out
Suspended one-year term in a couple years probation
For disrupt
Sing that 5K
And you know that wasn't just like
I stood on the sidelines and yelled he had
Photo and
Approached the family and they kind of got him corralled into one area and
You know it was kind of a scary thing for them there were a lot of little
Children are and
You know about
Was bizarre
But I
I had no idea that there was that
Direct link
To Alex Jones and that he was encouraging
The type of
Destruction that would be
Like the
Destruction of the
The 5K
I'm just very hopeful that
I'm sure the jury does understand the importance of that but they see that
And the
The disrespect Alex as for the process
And that really does
Sort of in
Inform
Their understanding
King of the case
And like
I think we already said it.
The way he's he's acting is like
Why did you get the faulted oh I get it
It's really funny just on a on a
Count of life
Alex
Say
Cuz it would be it would almost be worth
He was like no no no
When I said I was going to give him a job
I was lying to a c
I lie on air
People in order to make my own now that doesn't
String them along to keep her ass people for free
Exactly
It was funny to see him sort of faced with his own hyperbole to either wear
Yeah he's saying
My broadcast reaches 10% of the English-speaking world and you can just see Jones on the
Pakistan going
I know I should disagree be
Because that's
That would help minimize
The Damage Done
But the way I love the sound of that 10%
And from depositions who knows that they have audio of him saying that on his ship
So his
Is compromised I I appreciate it
Who compromises to be like
Not everybody speaks English that's probably like two
10 million people Max Wright
About 10% of the English-speaking world there's like 20 guys you speak English that's one person
Have a Tanto now
And that his soul thing of you disagreeing with
Clint Walker
Social media expert who said that
You know at minimum over the ghetto 6 years
Neil from the time of the shooting
That's 550 million
Pageviews
Alex Jones Sandy Hook
Content
Came by a social media
And Jones turn that in
Into
Systima in his press conference yesterday
Earlier than the week
550 million people
There aren't that many
People in the English-speaking world do you know it wasn't 5
150 million people it was 500
50 million views
Yeah
Use a straw man and
The
Appearance of
Being confused
In order to avoid
Responsibility
That's just kind of like
It's a simple tactic
But it's also like
I don't know it's
Kind of a self-directed form of Gaslight
Yeah
Yeah more than 550 million people
Speak English on the
This dumb planet
Like 8 billion people practice
Yeah I would say so especially a second language
Yeah
Well
Dickwad
Probably baby
But don't have the internet
Or are you the Sioux are going to Infowars
Test whether or not they can respond to English
Word
In order to see whether or not they are capable of being in the English
Object permanence and then see if they know the false flag
Is speaking of
English speaking and reading world
I ran into a couple who run at an anti
Bookstore
Very near the courthouse
And I was chatting with them and the wife
The couple said
You know we were thinking that
The local newspaper interviewed me about the trial coming to town and saying is this going
Bruce the fortune
And she was like God
She goes
Hello
A trial of a conspiracy theorist in Waterbury is going to boost the fortunes of an ant
Aquarian bookstore do you really think any
ORS
Fans are spending much
Diamond the store like ours
And they must
Be reading the newspaper because she got a bunch
Abuse after that article came out
Open
I think our business would boost
If I had decided to come
Trial cuz that sounds like
Exactly where I want to be worried about her if I came to the trial
Yeah I would
Single wide
Female that lady instantly
That's the life I want to live
Aquarium books
Stewart would wear a wig I would pretend to be married to that guy that's
Oh that's by the way that's where I go immediately
There is a
Used books
Bookstore here in
Chicago
That I think might be attacked
Shelter I'm not entirely sure
They have a bunch of old books and the guy there is really grumpy one of the greatest human beings on the planet
Spent so much time in there
Everyone that can
Comes in his store and everything I've ever wanted and dreamed of
We should we wear out
Candy reviews people
And
Wait a minute
Connection while one of them involves literacy the other
Very much literacy so much ultimate
Two poles that are ways to go
We should probably wrap this up here before too long cuz
I mean you've been so kind with you
Your time and you have room service there
If they don't want to keep you
Afroman
But
Buffet
Before we goes there anything else that's on your mind
About the
A trial or about
Current events that that we haven't brought up that it's anything
Anything that
Final the other I mean we're talking about this and there are a lot
Our moments where you just got all my God but I have
How to say there is one
One you know aspect
To boost that really does bother me and that's
What's that
You know
This absolute circus that's been happening in the courtroom and
Just every time they bring up an Infowars video
I just look at these families and I I think
This is yet one more
Yeah
Mountain of
Abuse and disrespect
And
That that part is really disturbing
You know I mean it's just
Yeah day after day
Having them sit there you know there
Carrying that law
Wherever they go and to be sitting there and watching this all unfold has
Got2b
I mean they have
Yeah I've talked with them obviously a little bit not not a lot
Because there's not a lot of
Either they don't want
To be worse
Giving interviews or anything like that but
I think
Ghetto
They take it in stride but it
At the same time I'm sure there are many moments where they sit and think
How did any of this
This happen
Yeah
And that's the real shame of it
Yeah and there's got to be a
Feels
Through the the screen
A little bit of in some of the testimonies of the plaintiff
Yeah
I'd almost
Disbelief
Like
People are Act
Things away
Alexandra
Rrak
Yeah I mean
Idea of life okay
I Am David
Respa several of the family members who have
Testified already and I'm sure more will
Express this
Yeah just this idea of
I
There has been so much unbelievable and not in a good way you know just this idea of like
I can't believe any of this happened
And now
This
You know seriously there are people who
Actually say
That my child or my
My wife for my my mom or my sister
Didn't didn't die
You know it's only as one of the moms put it you know if only it wouldn't that be amazing
If that actually didn't happen
But just that idea of like
Okay
I just getting your mind around the fact
Set this
Unbelievable losses occurred and then there
A significant number of
People say that
It never happened
And
It just
I saw one of your tweets somebody said it in the courtroom next
Yes
That's crazy
I'm sleeping through all of it
Not all of it
Yeah I know today about I came into the courtroom and
He was
She was hot
By the bailiff cuz he said
Is this the first amendment trial
And I thought oh and then
They played
The tape of
Robbie Parker reminiscing about his daughter Emily
The night after she was killed at Sandy Hook in the press conference that we all know about because John's
Spent the next several years you know using it as fodder on his show and
I'm calling Robbie an actor
But the guy behind me
It starts snickering during the stress conference in a lot of the families were weeping it's one of those
Those you know
Kind of
Orange that no matter how many times you see it
You think
Oh my God you just feel his pain and he is off
Offering forgiveness for the gunman
To the gunman which is just amazing
And so a lot of people were
Pretty emotional and here's the
Doofus behind me
Snickering enjoying word
Yeah I know you knew you could see I was trying to yeah
It's not exactly the word I'm think
Eddie's going
Steak
Nitto
10 years on
Yeah
Thinking is
There's
There's a reality that
Everyone else is a
Experiencing
Yeah and then there's
These folks
You are not
Willing to live
In that reality
I understand Alex's unwillingness
I get it
From
Studying his
Career in
Knowing what
Profiteering piece of s*** he is
You know I understand that motivation
Sorry I'm sorry
But I just it's still hard
To understand how people can be that
Deeply invested in
A false reality that
That's
Then why would you even be in the courtroom in the first place
If that's your
The way you're going to behave like you
That you made the trip down there
Benefits Rob do
Yeah yeah
Contractual obligation somewhere along the line but
Yeah hey Rob do is in town and he didn't even show up
He is you know
Rob dudes in town
Lock up your daughters everybody
Warning when Rob Duke
Liquor sales breakdown at 11
No Elizabeth that's that is kind of getting it goes all the way back to that that
Question I had about
Press conference
You feel filthy about it because
I am
I mean when I put myself in the bath
Headspace
If I'm
Family member
I just sit there
And see that and go why
Why are you guys doing
Why are you helping him
Yeah
I know yeah
It's it's
It's brutal
Well
Speed proof of
The argument of the
The case essentially that you use this fear and you use these tactics
It's an order to
You get people into a mindset
I'm at where they're willing to do things like show up at a courtroom
We're grieving family members know are having their day in court and say things like
This is so fake
I know but
Specifically when it comes
Things to do there is that but it when it comes to you know like Alex
Dallas does that on the show he
Proves every bit of white
Are you got where he is
Why is the wire people
Aiding and abetting him
You know
That might be a quest
Jen will never
Bully
Hello
Stanford
Well
Erica Williams thank you so much for joining us
It's been a it's been a pleasure
Bob
Bill Bob is way better than jordanne yeah that I truly better
You know it's an hour later there for you and you have spaghetti
And if we really appreciate you taking the time
Being an hour later they're being spaghetti
Cost plus plus
We're going to find out on our necks
Next episode
Spaghetti and it'll be it'll be a scandal
Oh I know
A lot of the walks
Already have
Read your book they enjoy the air on
Has been
Talk to Barry
Highly of it in the in the message
Bored. What have you anybody who doesn't know it's Sandy Hook
The Battle For Truth
I believe is that
The subtitle of American Tragedy
Williams
I am just
Cutting off a little bit everything
I'm blowing it
All right I think it's what I realize that it is you did
It did work out that a few years ago you interviewed us and that
What did
Good for your sales several years later on
I think it worked out well
Right
I think you guys got a cup
Patreon folks out of it
It's a team effort
Self-licking ice
Oh I just got an idea for
Invention
Stop licking ice cream
That's going to put a button on the dreamy creamy summer though
Well thank you again we will talk soon and thanks
Also for your your coverage of the
Navigation
Very much for putting the families
In the in the center better than than just about
Thanks for having me on you guys
Love you
Take care
Holding
Alex
In color
I love your work