Air Jordan
Knowledge party.com
I have great respect for this knowledge B I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Alex Jones
Jordan is I mentioned this to you the other night
And that is that
Hope Springs Eternal
Sure that the first time you mentioned that to me the other night but no but it's it's this context
I just
So recently that there's a new Sonic game coming out Annika game
I was a big fan
18/20 of Sonic Adventure 2 battle
Play the hell out of that on a GameCube
Big fan
The rest of the games of that ilk
Absolute garbage.
3D games have had a very bad reputation
Finally by history
I'm going to
Okay this new one when it comes out I'm going to try it I can't I can't
Hope Springs Eternal my friend you could be burned over and over again income
Come back to bed
That blue
Hedgehog
There is something to be said about a
Hedgehog that goes fast I don't I don't know what to say about that it doesn't really make
Make sense but
It is a part of my brain forever something also I think just really evocative about that sound when you get a ring
There is that
Takes you back really satisfied
My bright spot will soon be a blast spot whenever it
I have a bittersweet
Brightspot
Over the weekend
The Laver cup happens named after Rod Laver use the tennis player
And I
Rodger Federer and Rafael Nadal played a doubles match and it was the last match of
Rodger Federer's career an exhibition kind of thing just for fun right
Everybody else their there was like a tournament or whatever but for the two of them they like what are we we're just here for fun
Afterwards
Everyone cried
Uncontrollably
It was ridiculous to see like
Just grown men openly weeping in front of
Thousands of people Pete Sampras was there waiting
Andre Agassi
If you want just enough Wimbledon
Nobody was it was a really really amazing moment that you will never ever win
Miss again that's very sweet
Is really really cool
Mibor of tennis
But I am very happy for you
That's a big guy that's a big-time
So Jordan today we have an episode to go over
We're going to be talking about a special report that Alex put out on Saturday September 24th
No
New new news
And last week
Alex
Better blow up in
And I did get a little bit of feedback that on our last episode where we talked to Elizabeth Williamson
Did I give a whole lot of context
For what was going on in the courtroom
When Alex is having his blow up in somebody's face
But I had prepared but we had some recording difficulties
I wasn't able to use a recording software that would allow us to
Of course I am so we had our interview and
You know this already that the three of us had with what happened totally headspace where
The little inside baseball league and I apologize we should have done a little bit better job of laying some of the ground
I'm working
Yeah it is a little bit weird when all three of us have missed maybe two to three minutes of this entire trial
How are we going to expect
To come to the show having already known all these whores
It's so I mean
What I reflect on it a little more
It is almost as
Easy as a Galaxy to blow up
Regulate Every Lie Is there is not a ton of more to it there was
He was being questioned
About his coverage of Robbie Parker
Chris baby
I asked him
Questions along the lines of
You put a Target on this guy's back did you not
And then Alex got really mad started saying about a liberal
Wanted to kill people in Iraq
Oh you pick and choose who you care about right
And meanwhile Norm
Paris was yelling objection over and over again anything and
Without the reason it was like it was like a TV show where somebody is pretending to be a lawyer and they just showed up
Injection in the judge has to be like
You have to have a reason to Norm was like I'm a real technical lawyer in the universe
He's unbelievable more than Shakira
Play the song
Cai mean that they had the jury
Leave the courtroom
And the judge was confused
By the fact that normal subject
Think the things that Alex was saying right as opposed to things of the other Council sayings
It happened repeatedly that
Norwood Macon
Objection
And Alex will have already answered the question and won't stop talking
Constantly tried to explain to him
When your lawyer object
Stop talking
Absolute cuz you might not have to answer that question
We didn't register
No no it was it was like watching a t-ball game where the kid hit the
33 straight times and they're like well technically that's a strikeout but this is t-ball so I'm going to put it right back on
Mighty one more time alright Alex you can do this
Maybe next time and then the other thing that was a
Constant source of tension and a problem was that Alex would be asked yes or no questions
And then answer with a what was
Starting to be a monologue
I need to be reminded number of times you could just answer yes or no
If you answer yes or no
Makes him look real bad
And the issue there is which I Feel Like We Do
Fully
All understand in the courtroom
The reason that they look bad it's
It's because he's guilty
And he's already been found guilty
Reliable or whatever the right terminology
That you can't
You can't answer it away this like I'm maybe I'm going to get off on this one
That happened on Thursday and then on Friday
Norm
Announce that
Alex was not going to be
Cross-examined he was going to waive his right to cross
Examined
Cuz I was going to leave town he was going back to Austin there's a surprise move
Yeah they reserve the right to call him again apparently early this week maybe Tuesday or
Hindu to be back
To be questioned Sommore
Call him again under subpoena cuz that's what you would have to
To do at this point but Norm is also said he's going to plan to call him to testify on his own behalf
And the main reason so he can actually monologue and not have to answer yes or no questions
Well I mean you know where the bread is buttered and why Norms getting a paycheck is a
Give me some time on that standard Run cover for me
Nobody's ever gotten
Airtime out of valley
Are Alex's got married
Yeah I understand not on cable but it'll do it'll do so
Alex came back to Oz
A.m.
You know why
Why did he do it
We have to we have to see this Saturday show to find out
He's telling the exact same story that I would tell which is that
He got spanked and then ran away with his tail between his legs
That is not what he has to say before she walks
So why these two just ahead of marriage
I just got a marriage recently
So congratulations to mr. and mrs. mcawesome
Very much and congratulations or tomorrow thank you so much
Thank you very much I do next existential Greg thank you so much you and I was he want
Thank you very much that's magicians
Okay I was what I was really worried it was something like problematic
How many we got a couple of technocrats here in the next Jordan
So I want to say hello and thank you to Daddy's kissing boy
Bandits
Gary with a hard G and there's a long explanation of how to pronounce this
Not like Jerry
Okay
With a heart G
I'm a policy wonk
I have
Risen above
Go take a little break you down
A list for me
And then we're going to
Tombak
And I'm going to start the show over
I got plenty of words
At the end of the day
F*** you and your new world order
And f****** horse you rode in on
All your s***
Maybe I'll just be gone a month baby
I'm Yours
Tomorrow
And you never see me again
I never want to come back
I apologize
Yesterday that I
Was legitimately having break
Better tomorrow boy he's not this is not a good show
As I was getting ready for you to show up
I really did feel like this
It feels like it's been awhile
It was just really only just been two episodes we had interview
Other people they put out one episode a week
So they're like well what are we doing our last two episodes that was practically a month ago for us like what their Lifeboat
We did that yesterday
Emotionally it feels like
It's baby but I'm up
All but it is not but we're back
After a Breaking of interview
So Alex
Came back
From Connecticut
Really big reason why and it is
The headline
Of his emergency
LOL
Yeah mushroom cloud a fire
I just got back last night from Connecticut a show trial and I'm following the news globally a boy
Ward
Incredibly dangerous levels in Ukraine and I'm strongly considering not even going back to testify
On my own behalf in our part of the trial
Show trial
Concern
Without my family would a war Rec Center
That's why I took my wife and my youngest daughter
Midnight
Grown-up or almost out of school
Tore out
Moana showing High School
And they got my parents
And family here
When it's that serious okay
I've never acted like that I never behave like that
Beefy's frequently acted like that but yeah apparently it's I do want to be stuck in Connecticut with a noob starflyer
That's that's a that's an all-time great
Excuse that really. Really is it's not bad if if I was a teacher if I was like a first grade teacher and a student was like
I'm not going to do that homework and I was like why and they're like
Well assassination could happen at any moment to my father and I don't want to be stuck doing homework
Instead of taking a bullet for him
You the bad person in this scenario I would rather I would love to do this book report but Putin's out-of-hand
No he's
Also cool that is other kids can just be fine
I'll handle Dukes on their own but the young ones
I don't know about new I don't mind being separate separate from the case of a nuke
Yeah the team
Listen you don't want to be trapped inside with them even during a nuke sorry
Maybe a little bit but that is a headline
Nuclear war, right around the corner.
The New World Order is upon us okay and
Flip through here that I can even I almost
I seriously minute email to go to Connecticut to defend myself
We're going to Global depression the borders are collapsing
People are dying by the millions in the poison shots
We are inside the New World Order license John
You're absolutely inside the Louisville take over the great reset it's all here it's all happened just like they said they would do it
People are dying by the Millions
I was trying to
Forget whether or not he
So he's saying that that's cap
Currently yes
We're losing millions and millions of people are dying because of covid-19 cuz of the covid
Alright
How many millions of LK
I feel like this is one of those this is one of those
Math problems where you're like
Okay sure
You say a million a day that's a problem but it only takes like a week before it's 10 trillion people dead or whatever you know what I'm saying
Population
One of those problems
Noble
Little boy can't remember it's like that's right that's the wrong one
Real factorio you got it probably not right either
Yeah I think this is a little bit
It's silly but if you were to ask him but how you knows this you'd say something about actuaries and then we
Move on it
Assured
Scumming
It's going to happen
Millions of people are already dying cuz of the vaccine nuke seemed almost like week
I mean I guess it depends on
How wide
Whether or not nukes
Who killed Millions not fair certainly there would be Fallout
You know that that could have
Some pretty serious after effects
Screw up air travel out of Connecticut
That's one thing we know for certain
I find that difficult to understand the direct
Who won the Duke I think people would still be flying out of kinetic Rent-A-Car
Nobody's driving
Connecticut
So
DMV the nukes
There,
But there's
One way
That we can stop this thing
And the way you trigger the public to peacefully protest
And the flood the streets with Candlelight vigils a transcend party
Is by checking the slideshow fever right
On mainstream platforms like Twitter and Instagram and Facebook
They don't get her and and
Independent groups like Gab
And
Everywhere else
Because you are the info Warriors and without you ladies and gentlemen we are not going to be able to stop this we have a good chance
Shopping list
Predict
A 50% chance
Tactical nuclear war
In the next few months in Europe
That will cause a global depression
Incredible problems
You'll be nightmare Beyond imagination
And
Fremont animal Santa Cruz I'm doing about a 20% chance
I'm a full-on nuclear war
Show
I have a lot of trouble
Publishing all the side issues
Melissa's going on
Yeah that's if you want to stop nuclear war you need to spread Alex's content all over the place free advertising for him
Will
Initiate
Write series of
Bipartisan Candlelight vigil says not to Nuke anybody that's a good idea
Yeah that is a good idea I mean if your Alex and you just want people to
Spread it around that is a great idea
Does he and throw this out at cuz I think based on what he's telling me
Because nuclear war is so imminent and almost
Brinkley unavoidable I mean it's a coin for
Whether or not we have a new attack
Pickle nuclear war
Which I would argue if you start with the Tactical one
You're going to get a full one pretty quick
Yeah well one leads to the other attack
Is he still selling stuff though
Oh yeah
It feels like that's not important or like if the court isn't important it does tertiary things
I feel like money is less important now than it's ever B O U Back
It's not though
Suspend this is a three hour long
I would say
45 to 50 minutes
Straight edge
It is so much I was going to say how many you cut out all of the not add so we're going to listen to about 15 minutes of
Free show who cumulative available
I mean I have Captain some of the ads just
For flavor but like
Seriously though
50/50 chance
I mean that's a truck
Yeah that's very serious I got a hug
The kids
People better take this more serious
Anything I've ever taken in their life
Is that real
Are you better
Your children
Better better hug your mom your dad
Your brother your sister your mom
You better get right with God
I'm telling myself that when I point my finger at you
3 more pointing back at me
But we're coming under judgment ladies and gentlemen now
Are all the serious documented news
Couple weeks
Countless text Anson County
Videos
Talk about the 24th
Of September
And how
All these historic historically of happened on this day
Jewish calendar and mysticism the rest of it
I'm not putting in stock in that
Clearly every time the world's on the verge of a cataclysm
The general public will pick a date and decide is that
It's not that.
Causing it's the place
And point in Time Warner
Bartels at something that
That's wonderful
September 24th stuff was like weird qanon
Going around online
Are you Alex choosing to do things on certain days because of the numbers
Prison their Arcane by meaning
Closer than it had been a thousand years that he was like yeah they totally choose that day what are you talkin about
Interesting when it's convenient for him to be into Arcane esoteric b*******
When it's convenient for him to just ask her to look down on it
I mean if he looked me in the eyes and said
Jordan
Correlation does not equal causation I think I throw hands
Instantly
Like I wouldn't be able to stop myself what a Visa Jordan
Factorial
I'd be like I was looking for that word earlier thank you think I was looking for grateful
So Alex
You know of course. You look like you didn't care at his trial because
Nuclear war was on the mind
And that's why you was look like a aloof.
Dick I get that
That but
There's other things that are happening
Allegiances are shift
Alright loyalties are being tested okay
Ted Cruz
Kill the queen sported
Merging with big media
Having total immunity
Normal person
Accurate the other line supports World War 3 by the way
Really now unclogs and shows you the horrible person he always was
I tried to hope that he was an opportunist and went against Trump and
All that because she just wanted power
But I hope that you don't in the end
He cared about his family but he doesn't
He is a Goldman Sachs
Operative
Bad as they get
You went against
Trump
I mean this Batman sequels bad 922 so we'll see
Do it again I'll write down the date there we'll see how long it is before Ted Cruz is fine
Probably a week
Ted Cruz is actually a secret Patriot but he was a double secret Goldman Sachs double pay for something extreme that
I got me back orders for real this time or whatever
Is this a that Beto is better than Ted Cruz cuz at least paid I will tell you what he's about
Alright well
I guess I was going to be alright fundraising for Beto
Yeah but a baby boo
So Alex has been dealing with some bankruptcy
Situation naturally last week
The the judge Judge Lopez right bankruptcy case
Removed his lawyers and his
Reorganization officer
Because of conflicts of interest and the lack of transparency that was very clear on Alex's part
And excessive spending
That's suspicious
You wouldn't expect somebody whose business was going in through a bankruptcy
$80,000 on security for a trip
I took Connecticut that you cut short
Yeah yeah but I mean
Nuclear war
Fair enough to save your life
From a nuke
With eight other guys really feel when it is it is
Yeah so and anyway Alex has some spin
For the bankruptcy
So I wanted to bankruptcy.
Extra money
The donor that scrutiny
And
A lot of people see that ago you're closing your door so chapter 5 is emergency reorganization
Where you show your having trouble paying your bills
But then you do and reorganization wear it
Sets The Benchmark for how much money you actually have
So we can stay on here
Continue to operate and also
Show the state quarter body else
When they claim at $4000000 like they falsely did the Texas show trial
We can show certified all the stuff that's just a lie
Infowars
Preach me systems to stay on air
Operate because they have federal laws
We're not supposed to just be able to sue somebody
And shot him down
We're very transparent about that
Why we're doing it
And I'll just address this now here
I never been in bankruptcy
We never even
Taking loans here
And
Except for my dad
I looked at the big
Situation was doing on the fact we were in solid seeing all their lies
The table
I know the bankruptcy and then most lawyers don't work
Most people don't work that's what I got some good lawyer
But then where the Court's work should have other Shepherd lawyers that don't work for you
Bankruptcy
And those lawyers
The judge ruled last week Judge Lopez in Texas
Had not been transparent
About everything
They don't the past not bad things but
The fact that they publicly done our last bankruptcy
Democrats kick back
We got Infowars the website back
And if it works Health it's a successful company
Very real bankruptcy
What kind of free speech systems to buy quote pay debtors
They wanted to show true
I didn't want that bankruptcy.
Hold up Alicia actually owe them money
Find a lawyer the cro that they pointed
Did not disclose you know what's Publix all the news
Clothes that
But they done the previous
Bankruptcy just months before
Bankruptcy and a another
You don't say
Former
To the judge removed
Cro
And of two Shepherd coat independent lawyers
We're all by the way
I want saying anything I'm just saying
Okay your old lawyer in Texas was a former high-powered democratic
Right
This is not
Really
Fair Tucker. Quite accurate
What are the concerns was that these people who are the other bankruptcy
Employment at Infowars
And there was a
A concern that they would
Have a conflict
If there was something that was inconvenient to Alex
Right I am so they were not impartial in a way they could be trusted by the bankruptcy court
So you're saying that if you hired a lawyer who is very interested in getting a job for you
Right and that lawyer did a good job
Then that lawyer would get that
Right
So maybe that lawyer would have an incentive
To do a
Float
Good job
Weld opposed to a accurate what these concerns could be there and then I believe also
You know
Somebody
Who have somebody who's
Holy independent because
I've ordered of what you're looking at you
Like a web of family businesses
And you know
If you're somebody who has any reason to have deference towards Alex
You're going to
Probably run into some brick wall
You're going to run into brick walls that you didn't even know you needed to ask about you know it's that kind
Even if you are doing a good job Alex will say something
And if you believe any word he says
He's going to get away with one thing
Ghetto like it doesn't matter if he gets away with all of it
But you just don't
Have the capacity to get
Every single thing
Unless you are completely
I supposed supposed to his
Oranjestad
Completely neutral to it if you were just doing your job
Well right by the book
No attachment
That's fine it is it is so infuriating when he
Complains like they claimed I have 400 million dollars no
The guy made an estimate
Based upon what he
He could glean
From the amount of Life finances that you gave
To him in the first
If you'd given him your actual Finance wasn't it he wouldn't have asked you mated s***
Also along the lines of like this is an estimate of what a business test numbers license
Wellwood looked at
Well-run business
Speaking of a badly run business Alex's book
Deal apparently wasn't so good
Get the great reset with the world sign
That's a donation as well as was $99
Something bucks
World right now
And again blisters also FNAF world
Teddy's house
$76,000
Came in
2 weeks ago
That's great
I'm so running out of money I'mma keep 20,000
And put the other
Groudon and yeah
Another 80,000
But that's how books work
It's not the number one book in the world
Also it said number 18 on Amazon now
Every now and again
January 6th report number 15 okay performing Alex on Amazon
They sell the January 6th report Steve Doocy and his wife
Cookbook
Sliding down to number 1080 of falling
Also still beating Alex
Be very hungry caterpillar
But that's should be there forever
The Barefoot Contessa's cookbook is a number 16 beating Alex
Wow
Who is the Barefoot Contessa is it all of us or is it like the friends we met along the way
Oh okay
Also Colleen Hoover
Killing it
So many so much
Book Sales
Damn people like that why a romantic really do
Alex should have negotiated a better deal on these books
And also
Where are we at if you need to
You keep 20,000 of that for yourself as opposed to putting it into the business
Right
It makes no sense based on
The way he lives
WhatsApp
Yeah okay fine then you get okay then don't tell us you're keeping 20004
Yep so Alex
Answer some
Clips from the trials that he wants to play
Cuz this is about
Nuclear war
And I would have now are before hit more news and bring Robert Barnes on hit this other news
Some of these little excerpts
That the crew put together
One of them is where they attacked me over
Cryptocurrency like I'm a criminal
Charlotte Craven little promo together
And then we're going to
Go ahead and air before I
Left yesterday Connecticut went to a apple orchard with my wife and daughter
My five-year-old
And I'd AJ
What
Talks about
The ultimate Revolution God's green earth
The counter to the tree of death
What apple orchard did you just tell me what are you telling me that he's going to play a clip
Of him in the courtroom
AAA
Compilation
Put together by his
His team is also going to play a clip
Of him
And his wife and his daughter walking
Through an orchard
Because that's got the Ultimate Green Earth Revolution
I mean it's just really kind of a nice Saturday I suppose so
I'm fine with you having a nice Saturday
Chicken playing piano on the Georgia guidestone
Problem
With the Alex's getting crypto or anything like that and it wasn't in the case
That wasn't the problem
The issue that was
Trying to be elucidated by Chris Mattie
What is the issue of
Alex
Do people know that when they give you crypto it goes to your personal account
As opposed to
Because that could be seen as maybe deceptive
Fund the infowar donate
82 this we're going to go straight
His wallet Rhino that that might be
Manipulative business has he said in the dryer
Right he said
I understand what you're saying but it all just goes
Through my personal account
To the business
Now I would argue that perhaps
For a good piece of evidence
Sty maybe we should be
Be suspicious about that
He said
I'm going to take $20,000 right now cuz my book money that I said I was going to put all into the business
Reason to be suspicious
What is definitely no Trail
Is it going to be aware aware of than that money did go
To the business and I mean I guess if you want to put it like really super abstractly like a going to his legal fees or some
Being like that
It still hasn't?
Bright
Highway Barnes is going to be on
He's going to do or use on to talk about Russia in the nuclear war
Going to say about the case
Robert Barnes joins us Robert will also Odyssey into Russia the huge escalation there that is the
Big Central story
But there
Baffled wrapping an output in Signal not bluffing Friday nuclear war
That's coming up the shower as well but I think it's important
Front center
To talk about the show trial and
Your observations
Who are you seeing a bunch of crying parents
Bargain Bin Ford Avenue
A lot of former judges and current judges in a lot of people call my lawyers instead
Wow this blow up in their faces is not going well
Yeah
That's a vibe
Then oh
That's that's not something you like
Here yeah it is
It is fun
Because I got company
It is
It is fun to like
Listen to Matty in court
Just be like
You're using this trial as a fundraiser as we speak
Irony because
You did say went out to talk about the crypto things like you're going to use that in an ad liquor and then he did
There's a part of me that wonders if you would have used it in a diff
You hadn't upset
Like maybe that's trolling
And if so
Fairplay
You know I guess it's
Duo
It's a little shady but dude do what you got to do is
He didn't have the idea
At all gave it to him he's like
That's a concern how could I possibly have left money on the table like that
Yeesh
Yeah it's a barn sucks
Stu
Allison Barnes
Boy this is a bad display of
Just a bunch of psychos sitting there being weird as s***
Yeah
Just lying
They showed a magazine we put out
With Obama on the cover saying Obama comes for your gun
Let them talk about how I didn't like Obama in case yours are Democrats
When my lawyer tried to come back
And cross-examine the judge said no politics
I mean
There's a point of this whole trial
Is 2% a trailer only one side is
Is allowed to present their case
And it's the part of the case.
It's not considered relevant
For this day
And that's that's exactly what
Play sand
Fortunately
Fully resist their effort
For you to play there
Script for you to stay
To their tail you to play the villain in their rule
Oh yeah I don't think so
It's why they could never afford a trial on the merits why they couldn't
Never give you
You're dating
In court as we've seen president mean
Lead Witness
Was an FBI guy
You know nobody who died
That day
Why is he suing
What is DM
You still in the FBI FBI lawyer
FBI lawyer
Doing Alex
Never heard of me
Until the suit
He did not admit that Alex ever said his name he says he didn't
No it doesn't know if you did and Alex can't say that he didn't
No
No because
There are so many videos but they did not produce you got it so legally Alex can't make that claim
And this is pretty shity on
To try and prevent this person
Bill Oldenburg as just an FBI lawyer who is no
Connection to the case as if he wasn't somebody who responded to the school
As if he wasn't somebody who was the subject of
Conspiracy theories surrounding
People being actors that ended up conflating him
With the mister wheeler and grieving parent has if he doesn't have to
PTSD from just
Walking on that say
Just being there be a lawyer
Contrasting API lawyer
It seems like their rules and s*** but if Barnes is allowed to save this stuff in public and still be
The lawyer I feel like there aren't
Really is even
Much of a lawyer
Think he does stuff for
That's quite frankly that is a good point I'm sure he would be disbarred if anybody had reason to
I mean like I think that a lot of the stuff he does doesn't end up getting into a quart
Waterfalls on Alex's show and talk about
Do the vaccine people
So Barnes just as a completely distorted
War
View of what happened in that courtroom
Yeah I was waiting to hear
From any of the plaintiff
Call
That their injury was
Caused by something you said or did
And instead what I heard was stories
Been mostly relate
Do you at all
So I mean you could he's just pretending to that whole thing about Matt Mills
The guy who interrupted the Super Bowl press conference
Didn't happen in the courtroom
Because that would to satisfy this curiosity that that he has
This is just selectively removing these things from the conversation about the because they're inconvenient
You want there to be nothing
You want there to be no connection editor needed no connection for your argument to make any sense
So there wasn't anything there was
It shouldn't get in the way of whether or not what you need
To be a good time
It's a good time
Anyways fireship
So Alex
Believes
He is scared to play
Attorneys
Well I mean emotionally Maybe
He thinks that they are like
So worried about the the case now he's blown It Wide Open
I can't get into attorney-client stuff obviously Robert
But
They were calling her lawyers back there
Yesterday morning they were in full panic
They were on the ropes
And
They basically didn't even want me to testify yet
Yesterday
And didn't know what to do
And we said yeah we'll just come back we're a little quote for sour case you know where handcuffs
And it straight jacket in the restricted
Next week
Why even have your normal cross-examination
Unlimited stuff Maddie said because Maddie
Better nor Patterson's words but
They were in complete panic
Even the media agreed they blow up in their face
So yeah
Is real worried real scared of of Alex's
Righteous
Triumphant
Outburst
Oh man this is coward s***
This is coward s***
That wouldn't engage in this real bad
Week
Oh man
All right I mean I don't want to
You don't like what out when I play baseball
You know I didn't
Get a strikeout and then I was like see the problem was the ball was afraid to hit my
Mybat that was the main issue right it was that it wasn't the picture was good
Is it that bull was I got them terrified and also I want to I want you to write down really quick here
Norm said that Chris Maddie
S*** the bed
Yes write that down that'll be important later will do
Barnes
These people aren't ready to deal with
Truth people doesn't sound true like a boss like a Norman Alex
What do you see all this going
For me I think they're
Plan B
Because there's
Is false and that's their problem
So they're trying to die
Because Norm Patterson
Is refuse to go along with their f
Trial
And I and you
Refused to go along
With efforts to limit your ability to defend yourself attic
Quidleys York
Usually entitled to within the rules
They're not having sex
Success in your seeing their
Frustration be
He publicly Express
I mean to be honest with you from
Pure legal person
Employer lawyer
This has been very
Incompetent
I mean these parents
Effective represent
Understand that this is a very politically
Play powerful
Tolconnected Law Firm
In Connecticut
I heard from many people
We're on the plane excited
Who thought that
The plaintiff lawyer
And it's because he's more politically motivated
Did the prosecutor
It appears to me
Phineas actually can get
Truth or Justice
Is because
Would rule against him in action
Truth
Is in fact
And that's why he
He can't at least
Situation trying to
To do a soviet-style
Sassy styles
Cuban Fidel Castro style showed
Trial
Because the truth
Is still leaking out
Anyway
Chris Mattie is bad Council says
King of bad counsel Robert Barn
About to be sued for
If we take anything that the Infowars corporate representative testified to under oath seriously
Etheric
Considering suing
Hugh Robert Robert.
Mediastar Bobby Barnes for malpractice
It is it is ridiculous to say that they're doing a bad job
Because
Barnes believes that the job itself is is like impossible to do because it's
Spec right so you can't do a bad job
Unless there is a real thing that you could do a good job for rights like if Barnes had advice up here's what you should have
You should have called this person or you should have cross-examined this way
Have not brought the suit
Yeah
Souls like
Shut the f****** also was the lawyer who filed
Alex Against The Young Turks so it's a little bit to pot
Iams kettle
Seems like way here was where things got real messy
Barnes
Has a conspiracy about Sandy Hook
That is not good that's not good
The question was
Pick any better skin with a false flag
A false flag originated
From Pirates
Putting up a false flag to trick
The boat they were about to
Hijack
Inlet and loop
That doesn't mean the Looting
Didn't happen
Didn't happen to post Flags event
Did in fact
But the cause
The culprit are in accurately identified
And that is precisely what happened
Issues concerning Sandy Hook
Which is it turns out the politician
Pocketed the money
Rather than put school safety
And if they have done so if they've done something as simple as allowing teachers to lock the inside of the doors of the bathroom
Inside their class
Be able to lock the inside of the door
It to their
Be able to have other means of self-defense available
Train people with guns
In the teachers and schools
Personnel
What date did paulito
Couldn't let that message
Get out
And the reality is the Democratic Party
He didn't like the fact
You put up a pole
What might be a
False
But that's because what's the political reality right now
Political reality right now
Is the more school shootings happen the more plaintiffs lawyers like his firm profit
The more school shootings happen the more the Democratic party with their gun-control agenda process
They don't have an incentive to Max
Text my school safety
And that's why there today that's why they
Cover up what he
Sandy Hook
In the school safety inadequacy
Wow
Alright so Barnes is getting added to the suit
Well this isn't even as bad as he gets
On this episode
Wow cuz he should be out of the suit he's now part of him towards around
Interesting
Desi territory said that the government covered it up
Yeah
Damn that Democratic politicians
Embezzling and pocketing money that was
The shooting happened at makeup covering that up by
Bad sort of making an example of Alex or something messed up
Did the thing that you get sued for
In the thing that
In the place where they're getting sued for it
It's it's strange
The strange tactic
I mean if I were him I would I mean I would say that many might have said to me that he is
Is not doing a good job as Council
Well he's not cancel
Amino acid uses
Stalking law degree as a prop basically extreme right-wing shows and his own podcast
Is
That pull that was brought up is actually
An important point so there was a pole on a Infowars
On the homepage that was what will the next false flag be a bombing a shooting or whatever right
Import of this the point of it was
To illustrate how Alex's conditioning in advance for the audience to believe things that happened
Baked before they hatch
Anything if you're predict
Sting something is going to be a false flag
When something happens
You're going to think it's a false
This is something that we've discussed
Quite a bit
In terms of Alex's baby
The way he acts the way he
Get these
These narratives in place in advance
But V
Itself was a really helpful visual
Explanation of that and of course
Barnes
Doesn't like
So
Look Barnes
Just
These going for it
He's swinging it something
Alright cuz they wanted to blame
The gun rather than let the world know
Big Pharma has culpability here
Because the way in which young men are being medicated on some of these
Drugs is often back
Firing in Arizona
And has side effects
They often don't fully
Know about or meaningful remediate
They don't want to talk about it
Safety because that is stated the Democratic politicians and political class
In
And they don't want to talk about culture that glamorizes violence
Because it's a cultural a prophet
And they don't want to talk about media glamorizing
These individuals that commit
These horrible crime
Because big media process
It's a lot of the pot pocket
The cash the most
Anybody
And that's why they had to
Blame the gun
And blame Alex Jones
They couldn't blame the shooter
It couldn't blame Mental Health
They couldn't blame school safety
They couldn't blame big Pharma
And they needed to continue to happen because
It's the only way that
Continue to politically
Prophet
Off of the school shooting
And that's what's this
Disturbing that was maybe most unsettling
Is it case
It's about preventing the harm from
School shooting
Consequences
Vulnerable
Is being used to cover up
The true culprit
Parties
For the school shooting
Cantu falsely blame those who are trying to defend
Personal rights and liberties
This is just b******* I mean
Even if you take
Everything
As true that you saying
So you shouldn't
Yeah but even if you do the trial that's going on isn't about school safety
It's not about any of this stuff it's about the
Harm than Alex cause to these people
By way of his
Lies about them
The
Denial of their children's existence
Yeah so I don't know I mean
Interesting to throw a bunch of
Mud at the wall and see
See what kind of designs you can make out of it
This is
Disgraceful stuff
I mean I just
Sometimes you like with this clip especially I feel like you should play that in front of the jury as just
It doesn't get more obvious that there's no other way to stop them then to stop
Because
The lawyer
Who started on viskase
Yeah
Who's Back years later
During the case
After he was kicked off of it
To do the thing the cases about
More less and I mean he's been monetizing coverage of this case
Eva fry Regal Barn
Spry podcast or whatever the f***
So he has every reason to have seen all of these things
He's pretending it didn't happen
Like the the Super Bowl press conference guide
He's pretending that bill Altenburg is just an FBI lawyer he knows that that's not the case right
The trial and made money off the analysis of it right this is malicious lying
Play no other way around
No he's just intentionally lying to appease Alex and
Create like
Some kind of a weird reality where he
Aggrieved
Yeah I mean this is just
This is just textbook
Like
Here's punitive damages the only punishment that will affect
But like when you say punitive damages the point of
Punitive damages is to
Punish the behavior
To get the behavior to stop not to like
Find the behavior like hey okay
If you kick that dude in The Shins you always five bucks but you can kick him in the Shins as long as you got five bucks
You know right is you have to
To stop this
It's happening on the show
After trial already did that
Oh my God
Make money printing cost money
Fretboard
So he's got to try to hide and lion grants
Because he's
Dealing from a deck
Deceit
He can't come across as a
Is a credible office
Truthful voice in the courtroom
And that's why he
He continued to look
Bad is because
Cuz he was unable to track
He was unable to provoke you
Different talking about Maddie
Unable to provoke them a little
Steve
Richard response
Play Imagine You Are
Any was unable
How to get away with
A concert
Lies in the manner and method in which he made
His presentation
He couldn't get away with it
In his grandstand vision of this
Political theater where he's the hero at the end of the documentary in the
The film
In that span fyp
I thought this was about
I thought this was
News about
Personal injury
I thought this was about under
Disputed
I'm not seeing any of that
I'm seeing politic
Politics
Theater
Theater theater
Because that
The plaintiff Scout
Has always been about
They have used
These Perron
For the game of the
The political class
With which they are aligned in the political causes
Which they are assigned
That's the real
Might be
Plaintiff
B b
I think you should be added to those
Case I mean I don't know what else
To say other than if you say
The parents are being used by powerful interest
Then you are
Part of the Sandy Hook denial
How if you are the plaintiff
How do you respond to that
Because if you say no I'm not being used by only you are you just don't know that you're being used
Best way to use somebody's if they don't know they're being used
Right if you have a sincere belief in the case that you are
A part of than this
Is a denial of your trauma
I do lose the denial of your experience
At very least
If not legally actionable
So shity
It's unbelievably shity here is what
He is saying
That ultimately
What they went through was meaningless
And it has nothing nothing to do with anything
And no one cares
Yeah so your barns
Start sucks
Yep
He also thinks that. Sandy Hook
Conspiracies
This is a Tesla
Show me on this one is a fun one
In stock
Anybody in forwarded
Send people to
Woodstock anybody
Relief
Even talk
About Elmo
Everybody suing
Infowars mostly dinner
Was a
Critic is Paul Joseph
Watson the editor during the summer
Time frame
Critic of the Sandy Hook the Niagara Movement
Infowars was a restraint on the Sandy Hook deniability
The
Skateboards made no money off of the Sandy Hook Taniya movie
We have had honor debates on who was right
Absolutely Indie people were mad at you
You calling you both Bridges
Saying that you were fake
Because you were critical
Deniable
For so long and
And so often
And so many other people were
And info
And the reality is the reason why
People went to
Conspiracy theories in the denier movement was be
Because
The politicians in kinetic
We're covering up there
Complicity and culpability
Indian attic
Receive school safety
That's why they're destroying this
School that's why they're hiding
From the sunshine laws
That's why they're not
For your information act
Open records Act
Request that triggered a lot of
Conspiracy theories
Say anything wrong in there
Conclusion
He wasn't fat cover up take
Taking place by the
In Connecticut
In the only case the kinetic
Quartz didn't allowed to go
Who's the one that exposed
Schools for inadequate School safe
They allowed seven
$3000000
Shakedown
And now they're allowing another
By the way the judge bars me from letting them know about that
I can't get to let people know about that
I guess there is apparently a cover-up
Yeah
This is not something that is
Long-standing as a defense
Alex Dusty I've not been aware of this this life maybe I miss
Just a couple episodes
This was guy to now when Barnes is on sometimes so. That might explain it but this
This team does
Pretty f****** over-the-top right it seems off the beaten path a little bit
There's that and
Just
Disgraceful
Well I mean it might as well be a full-court buzzer beater is what he's going for
He's he's trying to throw it away
Not good and there's a couple things in
That explanation that he was
Offering that
I think our
Farpoint one is it Paul was fairly critical
Of this
Right you don't get to use that he was not listen
He was critical of you
Yeah and you didn't listen to it being critical of other people he said specifically
You guys
Yes Alex you need to stop this Alex he use your name
Alex is going to complain about other people. There's that and then the second thing
Is that
You know Barnes does bring up something to did happen and that was that some people were mad that Alex was
Olympic streaming
On this conspiracy
Guess what
He got more extreme
I think that this argument works
Very solidly against Alex
But I guess it
What's better for him
Is that if you ever get to reality
In any of these Siri
You're going to find it works
Against Alex
On account of reality
That is true every part of reality that you would
Inject into their
Conspiracies you're like
Well that sounds bad for Alex that's the real world it's a reality of stationary in in some ways
So we on Friday
Interview with Elizabeth Williams
I did not expect
But she factors heavily into this episode
Alex is mad about a tweet that you put
Let me do that
And all the other huge news it's not that it's not going to shine there I want your view on Russia
Economy Inn Maggie
Elizabeth Williamson
This woman is a
Sandy Hook grip
This woman writes her book
Proud make money on San Diego accuses me of it
She goes around for years and says stuff that's not true or Twisted about maconce
Winner really follow her
But
Yesterday
About to leave
Leah
Airbnb
We decided not to
Do the cross-examination just do my own case next week
When was Korea guys walked over his look here's the New York Times all over the news
Can your lawyer just attacked you in court and said you were horrible person
Everything you say is fake
Terrible job
Call Norm
Videos
He said that we didn't talk about you in the court cases
What's behind this was it was in Chambers
I want to cancel this there there there there on the roads I didn't say that
I think you're the great job or B called me said you did a great job
If you're joking
I should have the text that he literally
Play lost control
Turn hallway
And so she's I'm sorry I'm sorry I shouldn't have done it
Norm
I want to trust you but it's hard to believe she lied that
Because I'm telling you
Veritracks
It's a lie
Cheatham said I'm
I'm sorry I made it up in a tweet
So suffice it to say a lot of this is nonsense
Here's what happened
She put out a tweet
That was essentially saying the Alex could have testified today if you wanted to
But his lawyer said in court today
He looked so bad in front of the jury some time away from that right
What the Tweet was
Now the issue was visapur paraphrase
Then
He didn't save that Norm didn't say that what he had said was
But he wasn't going to have Alex testify
Cuz I needed to lower the temperature
This is the miscommunication bad paraphrasing
That is engaged in
And cheap
Put a tweet out saying hey he didn't say this right so out of courtesy I talked to him and I'm on it
Delete this tweet correction and I think
You know I think
Your your mileage can vary as they say but I think that's a fair paraphrasing
Absolutely no that's what I that's what make
Okay maybe that's not how Norm would experience it and then I don't know exactly what else you would have met by
But we got to lower the temperature
And I understand why she retracted it and I do
Write a note that's the poor paraphrasing
On the other hand
Words have to mean things
And the words that Norm said
Meme the words that Elizabeth
So if you don't want words to mean things
Then don't have work
That is but there is enough wiggle room for interpretation I think that when you say he said
It gets it gets a little bit messy but I think it's alright paraphrasing but technically
You can make an argument for it is inaccurate that's my main problem with it
I think my main problem with it
He said if you accept
That hit what he said has wiggle room
Then you are missing that what he said was what Elizabeth
If you're going to tell me that there's wiggle room with what
He said I don't believe
But there isn't a world where Norm could believe
I think he's sincere Leah saying I don't want Alex
What's the testify to lower the temperature because
He's worried that Maddie is too hot
Or something like that
I could see that perception being in his head when he says that I don't believe that that reflects real
Bright spot I can see
Alex
Or Norm
Having that be there reality right
So to them if he's a misrepresentation but them having a reality is the problem
That were existing in the first play
I guess so
Indulging them in their reality which is clearly not true
Is the problem I don't really know what else you could do that's a good point you know who we are who we are now
Across the global a crush their false
We have to I think we need to
How would you
A false reality Crusher
Anyway
We can make them up in false reality World tiny bullhorn
So we needed to make up
This life because
Alex to Tooele
1 quart
Norm's doing Victory laps everybody's calling him saying
Chris ready crap the bed
Judges are calling and everybody's flipping out it's incredibly everybody agrees to blow in their face
He gets up there and says
Well if everybody you know this is a big victory when I can do this
And then
Delete the twin says this
Folks
I'm going to delete this tweet after talking with
Pat Patterson
Jones lawyer
Raisin in the courtroom
Though not with me
I asked him after what's wrong
He makes
The accurate point
Study did not say this
As I rode here I apologize for the Earth
You're a lying witch
On a broom
I mean
She didn't tell us.
Call maryna break Nico's
You're joking she did say that
Talk about you and hearing
They were in shambles
Biagio's
You're joking right you didn't believe me
She literally pulled it out of her butt
So you have Alex did so well they needed to spend some housel is came up with this fake
Sweet rice
Also a bunch of other people were calling Norman saying that Maddie crap the bed
Sure so maybe Alex is misquoting somebody
Maybe he said that Norm said that
Did Norm actually say that cuz if not exactly
He will he will
I'm sure it's just a dumb childish game.
But I know you got to get where you at
You got it you got to do what
You know you only have a few opportunities where people I have like a mistake
Sure
You know I am not a huge mistake
Something that she apologized for clarified
And because of that Alex
Canal pouncing attack
Well in case she's trapped by having a real job and not being able to say
F*** you
You said that
You know like
That's because that's
What I would have done
Well
You're not like North because
Norm
Thinking about suing
Do it
Coincidence that Elizabeth Williamson
Grifting off of
Sandy Hook
Personally
Profiting off the pain of Sandy Hook
Would lie and libel about you and alive right now though
Because it once again reaffirms that if the truth came out
Even with a bias
Jury pool
The truth came out
They would not get
How much raise this
Ignore Ms really thinking about legal action against
Was just curious
Because not premeditated
Pure whole-cloth fraud
Excuse me I'm to claim
The lawyer try to destroy his client
We could destroy his job in his legal career
Enormous so angry he couldn't believe when I told him he was just flying never seen it nor so angry
Child
The fact
She thought she could just do so let's put her picture back up there
I mean who
Issues are official photo
Mars Attacks aliens
She has no self-awareness of how nuts she looks I mean
Charlie Manson can't make a face like that
We're doing this
Yep it's Grace you know
I really really really would like it if Nora
Tried to sue her
Because then
That they would be like
Okay well
She took the Tweet down right
Really fast
Until then this suit goes away
Which would make you think if Alex had
Stop talking really fast
Then the suit would have gone away
Did Norm actually say that he was considering suing because if he isn't then Alex making s*** up about his way of lawyers
Which is maybe worse
Exactly what Elizabeth
So anyway Barnes is a real pile of s***
Harvesting the
Pain
Who's harvesting the paint of these families
These plaintiffs lawyers
Depressed is Elizabeth Williamson
Weather personal
In political
And partisan profit
It's really disgust
And it's important for people to know out there
Admit to my knowledge
/ 90 /
Percent of the people who have
A relative who died at Sandy Hook
They're not suing out
The Bassmaster
Some people refuse to go along with
Only a small percentage
We're convinced to go along
That's another fact
He can't have
Well especially if you say they refused to go along with it
Because that implies that it's all being driven by it
Basically
Based on the thing
Is that we've seen based on the behaviors the experiences the people have gone through I fully fucken understand why someone would choose
Choose not to do it
It is a
Horrible thing
To go through what these families had to go through in the trial if there was not a sincerity
Behind what they were doing
Very much don't believe they would have made it
Even close to this far
Weren't
Sincere and dedicated
Working on behalf of
The the the memories at Ed and f****** all of us
Then they could have settled
Years ago
Alex would have been happy to pay the
Off. Like whatever 20 million dollars
Play my victory out of it
Yeah undisclosed settlement and everybody would have just
F****** allowed him to keep doing that bowl
And that's what would have happened cuz that's how we live most of our Lives we would powerful people f*** off
You know and do whatever they want
Yeah it's possible that could have been how it went
But it didn't and now we're here and Barnes
Is possibly defaming these families even more
Admitting my knowledge
Over 90
Percent of the people who have a relative who died at Sandy Hook
Are knots
Suing Alex
Natsu
The vast mass of people refuse to go along with
Only a small percentage
We're convinced to go along
That's another fact
He can't have
Presented to the jury
So it's part of a process where there
The ones worth
Responsible
Or more risk of more mass shootings
The ones
Responsible for covering up political
Cocoppa billeting complicity
And what
Sandy Hook
Where kids lives could have been
Say
Because of Road pilot
Pocketing money
The reasons intended originally
For school safety
You're the ones covering up for
Pharma and Airfield Mental Health
Institutions for young men in America
They're the ones
Prophet
And they want to blame you
For standing up for the
An amendment to blame you for second-guessing
The politicians were doing
It exposes what the whole case
This is really about
In a simple Nacho
Alright well said we're to come back into 10 more minutes Robert Barnes
Well said you committing the crime
Well I mean well said this is being
Express
A very
Simple reading of this
Could be
That the plaintiff
Who have decided
The to go along with this case
Our response
Possible for further school shootings there gauged in a cover-up of the things
At the school safety at Sandy Hook
Definitely follows
From pronoun reference
You know how pronouns are in Port
Into language
And understand
Yes you use the pronoun to refer to the people
Even if you don't say their names individually princes
You didn't say the name of every single person who had a relative
At Sandy Hook so sure but however you did use a collective pronoun
Describe all of them meaning you are talkin about them
Words
So
We're not done talking about this place apparently
I am I'm genuinely
It's supposed to be a lawyer
Lawyer and he's doing nothing
It's supposed to know this is about nuclear war. I wrote that down at the beginning
Now we're going to talk about
Conspiracies about Alex's day
Militarisation closing at the Russia news
I'll let you go to a great job at a barn
You watch the trial knollview Club
Prismatic Democratic party operative
Literally gets up there
Over an hour
Brings up
Now we gave them total discovery
We're not allowed to say when you miscarry
Of the 286
Weeks after they file suit on us
In two thousand and
A bunch of emails saying I want to get you on a hurt you were going to kill you Alex Jones
Sandy Hook
Any better
People
There are secrets
Embedded link
Stafflinq
Shall we turn the email over they know how to scan them
And magically find the secret links
Highlights with your car
It's up there and says okay follow lawsuit against The Young Turks that you filed
Stop saying I'm a child pornographer in all this
He said yeah it's true
I said you didn't do anything
It was said to you you didn't open it
Later he says show you Dixon child born
Let's just admit it you did it
He wanted to cover himself earlier knowing for Clips on the internet
I said what you just said earlier I was jealous
So imagine the evil of that
That's not what Alex said Alex said yes
I don't fully understand what Maddie was asking him but he's pretending not to because he doesn't want his audience to understand the situation
Maddie was asking Alex about how he'd Sue The Young Turks over statements they made about sending c********* to the Sandy Hook playing
Just lawyers
This was meant to really make it clear that when he's on the other side of things Alex fully understand how damaging
Claims can be more than willing to sue people for making such claims
Maddie was very clear that the FBI it looked
Intuit the emails have been opened and they were sent
Text to Alex
And they were turned over unknowingly
Which is why Alex Felton the right to sue
However
If the claim was just that
What's Joan sent lawyers child born in emails
Then that claim is technically
True
It wasn't intentional and Alex didn't know what was in the emails but those emails did get sent from Alex's team to the plaintiff's and
Only did contain child for
This is what the
The Tweet said
That was included in Alex
Who complained Against The Young Turks which is
Why Maddie was making this
Distinction
The thing that Alex was suing over was a statement that was technically
Accurate but what's the
Suggestive in a way that could lead to reputational damage
This was all to illustrate that Alex is posturing and Defiance in the
McKay's are
Decisions that he's making
Play more than happy to use the courts of the weapon when he feels aggrieved even if the technical claim that was being made
And being called defamation
Is strictly speaking Acura in this case
If they wanted to file a free-speech defense
Towards this
The Young Turks maybe they could have fought their their first amendment rights or whatever
And maybe they would have won or lost
But they would have had that option
In this case it is not
Yeah I don't know if everything that's said in the videos on The Young Turks
Because I can't imagine
Them
Making the kind of claim
Homestead Alex is saying babe did but be really in the bit of the lawsuit that MattyB
Brought up in court it was
Just the claim that is technically true
Albright illustration
Of Alex's willingness to
Use this these things that he's pretending to not respect what he's on the other end of it because
Jesus
Piece of s*** liar defenses
Lackadaisical
A generous word
Willingness to
Give over discover
We're just going to give you a million emails that you can't go through and we definitely won't go through them oops they have c*********
Alex if you recall
Early on
When this happened
Alex
Chris Mattie
AMC speculated about these theories with the norm pattis
Sitting at the desk
Clearly drunk
Yes just what I wanted back to that.
So imagine the evil of that
To know how to secretly find secret in bed
Invisible images
I'm not saying he did it he said I said that I didn't say that
Very suspicious
And then at the end
He comes on hour later and says the jury he sent c********* the families
I mean
This is unbelievable these people are on
Believable robber they had to use
High-tech system foretold
The skin
And a skandam
And they reported us the FBI V information
The FBI said we're not guilty cuz we never opened it
This is just too good
I know.
What
I mean
Alex's is dancing around this
Good
No
I mean that's again another factual statement I don't know I don't know who he thinks this looks bad for the bib
Plaintiffs attorneys
I'll just say this
How do you get 287,000 emails
And then scan them for secret links
And then they 5-minute just it doesn't sound good
There's a lot of
Concern at the time
Mr. what the source of this was
In weather was somebody aligned with the plaintiffs lawyers Allied online lawyers
And Ally
Exact
It was days
Sought information
That was guaranteed to produce
Stuff that you didn't even know exist
Oh my God this is also suspicious
Yeah
I mean they're just getting closer and closer to like
It was a setup
I was never really sure
About what was going on until he waited like
Like 45 minutes an hour
But you did some c*********
I was like oh my God you just did it
He did it right there
Completely misrepresented your public presence
What you said was
Whoever said that
Child Point information
To have out
Million dollars
And then he spotted that I said he was doing it
Is this
You just
Projection
You did like 5 seconds ago
I'm you said he did he did that he's a nice person
What
Uno's
Who knows I came to a revelation tone of voice that went
You did
You said
He did
He did it right there
Play-Doh just not existed for these people
How can they be so mad when people change their pronouns and they have no concept
50 what they are but look Alex doesn't think
All I know is that he completely misrepresented
Presented at the
Time how that
I came about any misrepresented in
In court your Public Presentation
You made it sound like
You
Stuck his feather photo op
10 pointed to it and said you wanted his head on a stake
It's all false
I just this is a lot
It's just one more lie
I don't think Maddie sent me that
All I know is all things disgusting aren't 5 minutes I'll give you the floor
Unbelievable
F****** real
Yeah I mean if you're listening to this what
You Come Away with
What do what how confused would you be
But what point is this guy trying to make I mean I think I think
Anybody would be justified in thinking
The conclusion that I'm supposed to go to is the
The plaintiff lawyers did send Alex this but he said no no
Rides like sort of a facetious way of
Not getting himself suit again
Nice person
After you defamed
Secretly
Maliciously sent you c********* in order for you to send c********* to them
And then
Are part of the conspiracy
To convince the families to go along with a
Fake
Lawsuit
I think what you would come away from with this broadcast
Is that the Sandy Hook thing was a false flag
Run by the Democratic f****** party because they need to finish Alex off they've planted
Stephen is emails and
To recap Alex is being sued
A little bit
Fly Barn system ideas
These ideas basically just f****** give most of Ukraine to Russia has hair like that
The parts of Ukraine that want to be part of Russia
Loud
Be part of Russia
In the dispute
Finish it go on
There's no reason
Continue
Backfiring economic saint
Considered
The great reset
Agenda
Can world
The pound is
Dropped to the lowest level in 4050
Years
The Euro has dropped one of the lowest levels
It's ever been
They're having a fuel crisis
Since in Europe they're having a
Food crisis
Cineeurope
That food crisis
Expanding to other parts of the
The world
The net effect of this is going to be really ugly
That the West
War on Russia has
Failed even head
Kissinger his acknowledge this
It's time to
Who is trumps
Suggested do a deal
LP Steel
Get out
If we look at what's happening in China
The relevant pertinent issues
You've got five minutes
Some of the rumors that I got
By sudden
Flight cancellations in different place
Abso Barnes Bend is it now yes to spend some Wheels
Oh my God
You realize Alex said I'm going to give you five minutes here's the floor it is still a little rude
Dawn
Yeah he was hungry. I love I love that this is just how things work
You can invade a country and then you couldn't hold a referendum to see if people want to vote
To go
And be totally fair election and then
I'm amazed it burns
Foreign policy
The Acumen I think
Basically what he saying is
Guys
In Ukraine
I understand
You want to be people
But the Euros law
So
Your Russians
What is Canada invaded like
Wisconsin
Well we got to give it
Right. They wanted to become part of Canada tomorrow remember whenever that Civil War
We're happened why didn't the South just say fine
Wii U on us
Reborns leaves and this is two and a half hours in Alex's a little bit upset about
But man
It's hard that estimate how dangerous this this this Russian situation is only this
Crazy
I've got some other news I want to hit on the economy and I'm super
Megacities in the New World Order
Let me come back
You know we are
Okay. This whole thing was about it was I did too
But it was
An hour plus of barn
Yeah
Probably an hour straight of ads
Yeah I mean look this year was mostly ads listen to some of this b*******
1776 coin, Teddy Roosevelt
Manley Arena coin
Is a fundraiser coin again
We haven't watch MPR PBS your lucky man
When are you talkin about a hundred dollars for this
$70 for Ed Woodberry for coffee cup
Everybody watching knows the coffee cup cost $5
Everybody watching knows the t-shirt cost $6
What are silver
The point is
Is that it's a memento
And you were part of that
Taxpayer money to fund in br
Bvs we don't have that
We don't have that sugar daddies
We have you
So that's why it's
The fundraiser coin
Have your founding member you get it for $99
Rihanna founding members about the other three coins or one of the other three going
It's $130
And the money is needed desperately if out of operation
I signed copy
The great reset in the world
Because we need the app
Extra money desperately
Please don't let me prove how much trouble we're in a time of trouble you're in
Lassen Plumbing or shutting down
We need your help now I thank you I appreciate you
Infowarsstore.com
888-253-3139
And yeah a lot of this is no-brainer
Free products
Sold out
Location
It just goes on and on
And on like
They're like
Maybe
A bit earlier in the episode even there just
Blong stretches like this
I was listening to this I was like
I can't imagine
Watching this and being like mayonnaise guy
Get the news on the ball
Like how
Is there a value in
This as something to observe
I don't know I just don't know
Put in a number of clips about like how Alex is like hop at Gates
Apparently Biden said something weird
Did you know little bit of these new things
Sort of just vague proclamations of nuclear war coming
And then
So much
Petty grievance about his
Israel
Yeah I mean we've
We've seen this existing Alexa
People who've escaped called to oregano like scientologists in that like you know they'll
Don't come back unless a like
The leader of the cult we would every day he would just talk
Yeah and we would all just sit there and listen and it
Didn't really matter what he say
You know
About the Basking in the glow by father is is proud of me I suppose
I guess there might be something to the casino you hear people who were like I've been listening for 10 years
How to what
Yeah what do you hear
Yeah you know
How can you handle your brain being jostled all over the place like that
Anyway we have one last clip here and this is how Alex
Pennsylvania
This is so sad
We're shipping out within
24-hours if you order Monday through Saturday
You're on Sunday
Take a few days to ship your product but we are
In many cases shipping same day
Four Corners
Infowarsstore.com
Melinda French Gates
Giving a little speech
55 seconds here.
Tireless work she's doing
To help steer the world through covid-19
For being an extraordinary champ
Champion for Global health
And for the immeasurable
Inspiration she provides two girls and women around the world
Including me
I am thrilled to present
The 2022 Golden Globe Award
Two remarkable leader of our time
Ursula
Von der leyen
Ahead of the European Union and you see that rainbow sloths really different cakes
That's the symbol of the great reset and the Bilderberg Group
Coronavirus swab
The wef
So
Literally cutting off your up literally pushing force inoculation
Any questions
Weather
Melinda French Gates is a globalist are
Absolute Troy
These are eugenicist
These are the population is he
Keller's
The very
Worst magnitude there
I'm going to end the broadcast
For the first
89 minutes of endgame blueprint for Global enslavement
Melinda Gates is bad again so I got to go watch a little bit of my movie like God
That is f******
The clip was not about her nose Melinda Gates giving an introduction to Ursula Von der leyen
Who's the head of the European Commission
There's no rainbows
It's a circle
There's a circle 8 just called it a
The swastika
Circle
I don't
I don't know. I can't imagine anything more trivial
Then
So much of
What he spends his time with
Yeah but at the same time
I think
Make that this episode
Is
Deeply troubling
Barnes's behavior is legally it's deeply troubling
I've no lawyer
Monroe Barnes
But it doesn't seem okay I mean I just don't know what else to say I don't know what else to say
I mean I think that
I'm no lawyer
But I do know a little bit about diesel
Right and this is
Past that one might say you do not know karate
No
But you do know
Crazy
Yes
Sure
So yeah I hope there's some consequences for this sucks
Yep this is got to stop but somebody's got to stop this
This is what Alex had to leave Connecticut for
To stop this
It's it just I can't keep going on
It's Barnes is
Barnes came on to do anything
Yeah like there's no not saying that he didn't do the thing
Yeah I do wonder if there's some
Some sort of a cushion of whatever he was saying
In terms of legal
Disability
I think that it's
Disgraceful behavior and
You should lose his life
Absolutely
Indeed we will. But
Until then
Website
Dot-com
Yep we're back but until then
Emilio Emilio
I'm dzx Clark
I'm Wilford Snapple Snapple of the Gravel Pit
Alex
Same color