Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work
There is a little bit cuz I got a lot of
You've been in Iceland for a bit it was wonderful and I leave for a goddamn we can you let the
Not sorry that was on me. Sorry about that
Your fault your
You're turning down
My voice in your ear
My ears on the recorder we have it on Matt Riggs alive
Forgot to go to Iceland
Anything about
That's where we find our fun avoided the entire United
I can't imagine how great
Wonder
Wondered at 8
10 million-year-old thing
And how little and help
Petty all of our squabbles I got home and I wanted to burn down
That's what f***
No Comfort after that
So
Love your Traditions are new donator
Not so much a new donator
Foreign policy expert I believe is what we decided to call
Thank you so much
For bumping up that.
And thank you very much we appreciate it we need your support quite frankly it's going down
God dammit
That is exactly what we would like a policy wonk
Bigweld
What does already
This is not news to anybody we have actually looked
At a button
And I imagine that we will be
Sending those out very shortly
Perhaps
Good point the perhaps this very important your address
I promise I won't spam but if you'd like
This whole thing with a stealth
We actually work for what you cannot send a message and knowledge fight at gmail.com
Or at the Facebook page
You can do that
You can send us your address and we'll try and send out some button
Absolutely
Ruger Forum politics
Absolute we'll see about that but for you and one for your friends and I'll
Australia rosinski
Jordans
Yes sir times ahead of us
So I would have got some wine for drinking a little wine today
81 g of sugar
In their soda
No ma'am
We're drinking
Because that is
I think what we should do is
That sounds great it's the perfect perfect
Pairing
I used to in college maybe even before College
I used to be a tequila tequila
I actually secretly didn't like the taste of it
Eastwood completely knock it out
Oh they're completely knock out the taste of tequila
Tequila and secretly didn't like
But everybody was doing it
Like I did it
The double down on tequila decision myself but I always told you I got
Like the combination of the flavors but
As a 33-year old man I'm ready to tell everyone I was f****** lying I just hated tequila
But I wanted to be at
Tequila guy
So anyway
That sounds like a that sounds like a bad girl
Speaking of people trying to present themselves as something they're not
It's time to talk about Alex Jones
I want to declare war on all of humanity
But
Forget to that I have an out-of-context
In the course of the subject matter for that I have to go over this episode
Like three times
Or on Media Matters
Like something that I would want to say
If you're listening to this in a conservative conservatives are b****** no knowledge
Contacts dropped from a guest
Source
We have contacts drop from the one the only Donald Trump
I think it's appropriate
Obviously agrees with everything Trump says
Yeah I am so full
So we're not going to deal with him
I'm talking about Trump's press conference at all
This
F******
King of words
Isaac is being under-reported
You know the media
That I think it's hilarious
Okay so here's an out-of-context drop from Trump
And have a good time
God dammit
It's all my God
Every single f****** person who voted for Trump
You should have your right to vote taken away we're starting out hot
Respect
You should be spanked
I mean that in a very place I don't even care
Almost an argument
How to send it all but dude saying that it should have been
It should be retroactively a felony to have voted for Trump
I don't know if I agree with that
Walking the only way to really deal with
Six bells Dan
We had some
Some trouble in America
Over the last couple days in Charlottesville Virginia
33 minutes
After it was
Heard of it
Murdered
A woman
At least
Twenty-two other
And
Yeah I think
I think that is the one thing that
So-so
Before we even get started
Going to get into Civil War
These people are literal not
So this is
Put out manifestos that they're very clear
Support
They're done irons if you go to play it like I really don't encourage people to do this cuz it
Ruby
Jarring to your mental health but
I subject myself to this s*** for whatever reason
You go to places like Stormfront or the daily Stormer and stuff like that
You'll see exactly what their perspective on all this is
It's what you'd expect they're thrilled
Play love it
Trump refuses to
Call them out he refuses
Save a white nationalism is a problem
He refuses
To say like
The clan
Get out of here
He says that there's trouble on both sides
Is Manna From Heaven
Two people
Like these Nazi groups
So you're saying
That's that's
And and frankly at
I cry halfway
Disagree
But the other part
F****** nobody
Stopping this
Nobody doing
About it
I got off the plane and thought now that I'm in America do I need to
That was my first
Twitter
At this point
Give me a couple of days
Need to get classes you don't know how to handle a firearm be useless with a gun
Currently it's super cool to be racist right now
Well in certain
I'm so
That is that
Car incident
Then we'll get into and we'll discuss
But beyond that that was day two of an ongoing
Situation in Charlotte
Alright the night before there had been a unite the right
Type of rally
We're of a bunch of people with torches
The statue of a confederate general that was going to be taken down
Confederate generals statue
Taken
Yes
Deeper than people are dealing with
Just white people get
Together to be
No in May on May 15th of this year there was a protest
Because people were moving
Two-door no starting to talk about taking down the statue of Robert E Lee
That was in
Downtown area
Richard Spencer
There in May
To protest the take
Of that statue
And then in June
Of this year on June 8th
The Klu Klux Klan held a rally there
Basically
Around the same thing protecting him
And stuff like that
There was another Klan rally on July 8th
You're in Charlottesville again
We're about 50 people
From the clan
Showed up
Santa Rosa map
And 1000 people
Account
Demonstrating
Over the last few months already
These tensions
Coming to the surface
Charlottesville
Pyridium
But around this
Specific issue there is a pretext
Do what's going on
That you didn't even know
It largely was
This statue
Statue right
It's tough
Michael
Jordan from the United Center
Care
I mean I think
Think that would be offensive to
Confederate roots
Didn't they take down the giant Marilyn Monroe downtown
Seriously
That is something
A little bit reductive because it's become so much more
Internet
Yeah so this rally saw a bunch of people from
Very disparate groups
Including the
Plan
Including the league of the South
The proud boys were in effect
Biker groups that are just malicious
There were the Fraternal Order of the all tonight
Which is the military portion of the proud boys there was identity evropa
Which is a
There was talk about a bunch more Vanguard America
A bunch of
White nationalist
LARPing
Yeah that's exactly what that they were all coming together
Before we get too deep into this
I think it's important
For us to say that there are reasonable
Conservative people in the world
Come on
That's not fair
It can be fair later
That's that
The situation is it
Well it's like saying there were reasonable people who supported Japanese
No that's not fair because not all conservatives
Defend
Situation
Important for us
To clarify cuz we're going to get really hard on these folks I don't want I don't want it to be
Be some sort of like
Everybody who I have conservative feelings were painting you with this brush
Because we're going to get into a territory I believe
Especially in the near future
Where
You're going
2 speed
A lot of radical
Groups
That are attacking
The center
There are Centrist
Conservatives are Centrist
Liberal Folk
And it's not fair
If people are blind lead sitting by and being silent about this
There is some complicity
In silence I agree with that
I think there's
Simplicity in
Meaningless words
Like other thing that I've seen
A lot
Throughout the news and all of those things
Things is
People would like
Stronger condemnation
For a stronger condemnation
Yeah
It doesn't matter houses
They condemn it says he condemned
F*** him
I don't give a s*** about what he says
He's part of the reason they're there
Dislike
Oh there are Centrist like
F*** you
I have troubled by this
But just happened to lean conservative
Yeah but that's like the log cabin
You know if you are a gay
Conservative
That seems
Insane
I get that you want
The gop's trying to eradicate
That's like that's like a
Jewish knock
Like that's what that is
George Soros
You're right
Considering we deal with Jewish Nazis all the time fair enough
Exhaust you today and I think my position is fair and there
It's a complicated position that we're all going to have to wrestle with in the coming months
Some s*** but be that as it may that was the first night that was on
Friday
Yeah this first one
Then I'll fighting broke out
Deemed unlawful Gathering
Which is something that is illegally Define
Were there a lot of cops
There were they were they
People in cups
Swear they
Making sure that they went to jail really wasn't so terrible
Were the peaceful protesters White
I get you I'm sorry
I'm going to break you
You going to lose your voice
From screaming
Unlawful Gathering
Three or more people who are gathered
To disturb the
Peace or cause some sort of illegal actions
That's not protected by the First Amendment
Slander and libel
That's not protected by 3 ft
If you're gathering with the intention of
Like destroying something
That's not free that's not free congregation or whatever
That's not that that's not protesting
That's not demonstrating
The police have every right
Do demons act like you got to go home
Activated that the first night on Friday and then Saturday the reward
So we're going to be
We're going to get into all that
Is Alex Jones put out a hour long video on Saturday
Emergency
Broadcast
Because I want to talk about
I found some really weird to talk about
Or even I had planned to go over Friday because he's got a bunch of lies about
Would like
To get into but we can't
Steven pisses me off
Recording this on Sunday
He's doing it Sunday show I'm sure he's got a f****** whole new spin for all this
How to do a live episodes
Almost
It feels like this might be outdated in terms of propaganda even by the time
The stairs
Even by the time we record
Yeah but it's worth it to go over in the Sun so we can get a sense of what is his
Deal with it
And maybe I can get some
Catharsis
Maybe we'll see not all that much
In terms of
Explain where I've got stuff out and when I do but it's mostly just
Segmented pieces
Yeah
Ladies and gentlemen
6 months
You would see Riot star
Lake Park in the summer
You've been predicting it for 20 years
George
BB
He was getting
Black lives matter
Race pace
Grinch
Civil unrest
Confederate generals
Bulshit
You are
We got the other two.
Protest
You are
Black lives matter
Cultural garbage
Probably White
MP3 is Pikachu
Of what Martin Luther King's death
Already we have listened to the first of minute-and-a-half
Half of his video or not
I'm into it
All these white supremacist folks
In
Because everyone keeps
And he's not he's just misrepresenting and misunderstanding things that he sees
And pretending that they're mainstream culture aborting white babies was on a very
Radical blog
Yeah that was a blog post that some
Glittery far-out
Radical
Where is that
Did we have we gone over
It's just
Owner of 100 readers
You find these terrible examples and then pretends that it
This is the mainstream idea
Really searched hard for that
Demon screams
15th page of Google search results
Until these right-wing out with pick it up and then
But then also you pointed it out even as the video is going
He is such a dick
Because
He's saying that like as I predicted
Like if you're listening to our show you've heard in 2015 he was saying
In 2016 he goes on about how Obama is going to cause
All kinds of Civic
Disorder so he can become president forever
Palace of the italicized
Completely falling apart and not come through and he's never been like
In the same way with the financial stuff next week I'll wait next week
Come in the winter
Yeah until eventually there's something like this
This
What's going on is bad cuz I got it all along
So stupid here later you're going to get one
Makeup over and over and over
It's going to rain today
Today it's going to rain today sooner or later it's going to f****** rent it would not be impressive as Babe Ruth called his shot every time
And every time we going out
Every single was going out
Some of the shine of your predictions when you've been wrong all the time at your
Saying the same thing
I mean we got it
Using whiteness
He wants to create he wants to create strong men attacking White
In order to justify
Profound
And like we said also
We got the proof
We got plenty of proof that you are a bigot
You f****** and you know it
It felt like we had something up
On the internet
You being a f****** racist
Google
What are the clips that you are
Doing diligent research
You just open the book up first page
If you want to pull that s*** at least
That's the same thing with the Trump shirt
Oh I I can't take it
I can't because those are
The people who like me the most
So you have to have that just like Trump
White Nash
Let's because
They're the reason
They even said it
Quote here
Was this represents a turning point for the people of this country
We're determined to take our country back we're going to
Fulfill the promises of Donald Trump
And that's what we believe.
Then that's why we voted for Donald Trump
Because he said he
He's going to take our country back
And that's what we're going to do
You know how white people
Play detector country
So help me info
All of the all of the people who are afraid of white genocide
Are really making it hard for me not
Want
I'm leaning towards
Outlook
I was at a hard no
Sterno
Now I'm in the 5% nation
Do you get what I'm saying
Frankly
You can't take it out a continent
Really
Contacts
Exactly what you need
Next Clipper boots-on-the-ground
Infowars dead
Of course
The boots-on-the-ground more info specifically like an employee
Show I mean
The elite not you
Here is the breaking news
Nope
Millie Weaver
Rainbow stats
Good
Good again
The police were ordered to stand out of the Hillary supporter
Charlottesville vote Democrat
Reportedly
Facebook
Civil emergency declared
No public meetings which is martial law
Nope
Emergency
Going to start so far in Virginia
This is all about leading to martial law
Just not
What are you doing
You are weird
Yeah
Okay
I appreciate that
This is
For less than 24 hours you can handle screaming for as long as
You might feel like you should face in this episode of run out of throat
Man that's a bad I'm willing to take the level
Because this is my first opportunity
To do anything
More that's like I haven't even I haven't even been around other
Human beings
So so my my instinct is to get out
All of the ship that's been building up
For the past 20
To dial it back
Okay
.
Okay I don't even want to engage with what
Because if you want to
If you don't pull its National
Emergency
Martial law
Going to run
It's a problem martial law
I think he kind of
Does
But it's only against
Antifa
People who are against fashion
Exactly it's really interesting
I've built up an entire career that is
Tyranny
Against police oppression but please
Police go squash those leftist
Frantically
Rainbow snatch was in effect
I want to say I don't think she was out there Millie Weaver
Cook County
She's out there and I don't trust a word she says
So this idea that he's reporting based on what she said I'm going to need more I've got anymore
Is the clown I don't believe
She's like we are at we allegedly have
But you can't afford it
Reported
Jackie reportedly there's videos you can't report that you can't pretend
Cuz your dumb ass listeners are going to hear that is
It's very dangerous
Oh yeah that's the other thing
I'm really running low on
Mater Lakes
F*** you everything is vaguely or obliquely India
Exist
It's in the Sun
Alright well
I'm not sure which.
Spin City sucks.
I'm for it
So we kind of have an idea of what happened
I was worried about that myself I don't know
I certainly haven't been thinking about him lately
I don't know
You know what those kids really simple medical shows
A rabbit hole
A lot of the information that we have is in
Complete is going to come out as
Witnesses are interviewed
There is a larger more robots
Reality
But
With
With Twitter
There have been a lot of things where
Please come out
I was there in my
My friends were all of this stuff and I like your knee
To believe them
But I I
I try really hard to be like
Yes I know and the spirit of this
Is correct but if it's not something that week
Confirm
Then it just
More fuel for the Alex
Assertive trustworthy sources and stuff like that Elizabeth
Those white National
Does not
He's beating the the
20 year old black boy DeAndre Harris
That's not reportedly
Confirm there is
Glee video of
That no
He is clearly not
Accident where they were threatened
Sing like that they was legitimately just erased
Nazis beating a black eye with
The images in the video you see that they're in khakis
Ethan white polo
The reason
To make fun of it and be like haha you dumb
Old Navy
Going motherfuker and stuff like that
The people are taking into account that that is a uniform
What's the uniform of Vanguard America
Like
There's a group I thought it was just a bunch of dumbasses
Is dressing like Trump on a f****** Golf Course
Is WhatsApp
Vanguard
America dresses
Cuz it's I don't know
Traditional
Yeah
The Nazis
How to wear a
Armbands
But you know polos and khakis are very unassuming
And they have like a preppy fuel to them people feel like
What happened
As of
Burien
Interesting spin
About the reality of what happened
And it's very very
Bizarre
So they bring you in
Bobby all the way on the gates coming in on each side
Reporters in a small conservative March
Blood everywhere
Really really
Give the antifa a victory
F*** you
A few people for Central Casting actors dress up yard
Unify the right
Don't be racist
Whoops
Have we ever talked about that before we may have had a long
Conversation
For quite a while it's
He's relying on a lot of that sort of Lies
In order to
That like
This is like one of the f****** balls I got out of the horse track yesterday very
This is just
Bed
He's so far wrong
Yeah because these got water
Nothing even to hang a
Actual Nazis
Is good oh well obviously
The Southern Poverty Law Center. Together
To discredit the right
The f****** thing was organized by a literal Nazi Richard Spencer
What was it f****** called the right to unite the right
Anti-racist
Yeah well it is but there would be no more
I'm the Longview he's kind of not lying
He's terrible
On of all of all days
You do look like on a normal day which we have not had for
For several months
Or even with our investigation and all of that
I'm far more pace
With this car
Call Shay
It's fun to laugh at it
He's got nothing he
Throwing bulshit out
Today
Is not the
A f****** day bow
With it
They dismiss pronunciation
The Vietnamese food
Everyone Infowars pronounces it wrong the same it's clearly some sort of like
Different editorial decision
You if you retake
Their name
We should start calling it
Infowars
Sister the f*** you
I would prefer info
Alex joins Alex
What is he normally wear
Sweet
Play fear oblivion
He said he wears
Be at the idea that this is all because antifa needs to get their win back
Is really bizarre like a pro wrestler whose like he's lost too many matches
Anymore so whatever
Put them over
So also this
This thing about the people and our reporters and
That's up being taken down this Gauntlet where they get attacked by antifa
Is it because I'm doing is misrepresenting
Permit
I think he's misrepresenting the idea that like this is the area you can be in
Because it is
Piano public
Area protesters and the demonstrators
The Nazis
Had a permit let's not even come close to calling them and
The cities do that if you get a permit and you can be in
This
Specific space right
And I'm sure that the other was
Was cordoned off for
Reporters
Space that was
Protected
The police
Some of them
All of these things
And that is
It's getting
It's it's
Queen of pride
I truly believe that the point of
Pride for all of us
Even these people believe
So much more
In the ideal of America
That they're willing
To protect
The very people who won
Want them dead
Yep that's amazing
Stop
At the same time
God I want you to turn around and beat the s*** out of them
American
What was it North or South Dakota
North is North Dakota
F******
What
Destroid beat
Arrest
Things done
God I want every single cop
Punch the s*** out of these white
F****** Nash
Maybe night
But I can't
No
Because
I didn't want it to happen to them
I don't want it to happen
Damn these white
The problem with any kind of idea logic
Consistency
End
I think you might be onto something
Because Alex Jones couldn't give a s***
Clean up beat up Native Americans
But if you hit a white person
There is the worst person in the world
Goes by Whitesnake
They're fighting a war
And weird
Note totally one-hundred-percent reconcile that with
With our American friends
Let's think about it and we'll talk later
Cuz I don't think we have a
But there's a another point that I wanted
Little boy there was one more point that I wanted to get to about that narrative
About
People being taken
Antifa
That's not the way I feel
Speed energy sources reporting
The situation
Except for one
Which one daily Stormer
I can't think of any reason why they would have that
There's a real decent
There's a really decent chance that Alex Jones is getting his ideas
Scrum
In terms of this Narrative of what the protests
Counter-demonstrations
We're like
I don't know maybe there are other places it is reported like that but that's the only place I've seen
I got to be totally clear I've been looking into this stuff
And I think the daily Stormer is mostly just trying to make people mad
Tell for sure
Nazi bigots and I have you
But I think they go way over the top
Interplexus trying to piss
People off
Because the one of their headlines today was about the lady who got killed
The car
Attack
Tell me what it is aren't
Bouquet
I got to tell you
This is this is basically
Leave it this lady was a 32-year old's that flood
You know if you're a woman
You're 32 and you don't have kids
You're a complete failure to the only thing you're supposed to
The really do is reproduce right witcha
So insane
Parody right
The issue on the right is if you're going to parody
Anything
You just have to
Far out there but exactly
Comfortable things
Much different than a lot of other b******* I see
Exactly so I mean
It's a tough I don't ever want
Akira
Refer to anything they say seriously in the future
Bring that up because that is like the parallel between
Alex's version of what happened
Declaring
So
Alex
Or ordered one of his reporters
I wonder if we had the resources
I wonder if we could actually
Traits that down like the same way those
Those Intrepid reporters
James comey's
Twitter account
If we got to a point where people
No I can pay my rent doing the show if we had the time to put into it I could find out a lot of connections that are there is that it
Now I got to go to work
And then on weekends to go to the horse track
Address that is
Just say I'm never going back to you
Alex Goes On
Was filled
Hey by George Soros
That's just a fact
Also I lost my bet on the pizza man
It didn't come through for me did not deliver wise man says forgiveness is divine
But never pay full
In this next wave Alex
Through breaks down more of his version of the events
Not
Being fair about
50 guys with torches
Everybody
Call Ben Victorious
Stanford University
Suck your own dick
They did this at Berkeley
They did this at other universities in Europe
Control
The outnumbered few conservative
Lesbian
Libertarian
Facebook
Google
Luring in the right-wing
Is there a
All the peaceful people
Civil emergency
You can't have them
Because what we saw happen
That is such a complicated version of what
Things happened that is so far off base
Much simpler explanation
Ben
Everything is fake
Storing them at like what was there a box in the
Stick in the box has mail written on it like what the fuc
Protest
The demonstrations there since May
These f****** ding dong
Chose to go there of their own volition
Buses and shuttles
People from Illinois.
Pictures of people from Illinois
To go to goddamn Charlottesville to Beaver dick they are in real life
Doing a little bit the guy who was driving the car that ended up killing that lady was from Ohio
Sadly unaware of the
The stuff her son was getting into
He thought it was he was into somebody named Albright
What is the alt-right idea of the white supremacist was being radicalized
Or is it all right. Albright organization so I mean
What do you what do you think about his narrative
I think what
I'm what I'm hearing
Is
Deal with
Like this is not him
I think he's at my
What I'm saying
For his listeners
I think he's really spending it for him so
Because
I don't think
Process
That b****
Him
His fault
Like
Propagated
And this is part of who he is
So he's
Rewriting this as
He speaks because
He can't deal with the fact that
He is a Nazi
It's often difficult to
Does the jarring versions of yourself and other people especially when their billing
Every single thing about this
And I'm talking about
Everything like there's
No reality there's no thing for him to have
Hang his hat on cuz generally what we used to sing
Is ham trying to find one little.
Detail tag Longmont
Yeah one little thing
And this isn't it
Tire rear
50 is like the script of a Dirty Dancing Havana Nights
All the Nazis
Nationalist
Sewer they're great f****** reference
I don't care
I'm sorry
Try and Dad I'm trying to find some sort of
Havana Nights
Is the way to go with it
Turn up filigree to disagree
But the idea that all these people I were there are
Plants is absurd
Like it's just absurd
The depth that you would need to
A pre-plan that
Prohibitive
VIP the peace organizations
Exist
Their membership would have to be known
History of doing the same action
20 year-long plan
And not only that but even if it is
Sincere
But even if it
So even if it was
Instigated by the
There would
Astilbe
Real guys
There
There were
Yeah there were even if your
Is that it was
It was a false flag or whatever it is
Volkswagen
Real f****** races
I don't even want to engage with that cuz leave the post black narrative is so f***** out
I just don't even
Lincare
But be that as it may
We know what it's all about
For Alex it's about white
Next clip
Come on
He'll be running for congress as well
What is what is b******* Kid Rock face
Kid Rock
North Korea missile
Kill from
Sure
Newrez
It goes on to say when show you
An article right here in my stack
Says we're going to kill him
Disable Kill from
This is the narrative from Friday that I wanted us to get much more in-depth in an hour
Because it's too late
Who was on
Contributor to really weird interview with Stephen Colbert couple years back that says worth watching
Awkward
Colbert Report
He said that is
Basically
Trump
Is
Basically saying
Putin thanks
Thanks for taking our dudes out
Is a very bad
Driveway to govern
It's it's not good
And he said
They're going to kill him
The government's going to kill him
And then immediately the host I believe it was Tapper
So it's the same we take that out of context
Stand
Talk about how we're going to destroy you in
Award-giving the same
Accuracy means nothing
Every time you see anybody point out hypocrisies
C on the left
I feel like it
Nothing to
Who Revel
Did they can get away with her
He threatened to beat up Trey Gowdy
He's going to kick his teeth in and s***
You really at the Benghazi
The actual clip that that came from was
Philip Mudd
Someone should kick his ass
Because he's lying about
Open question
In Congress
None of that right but I'm going to kick his ass he doesn't like Alex ads all these like
Flourishes of kicking his teeth in and stuff like that that you didn't say
Because he knows better
He knows what he's doing he knows what he's willfully misleading people in Congressional question
Right
Sure it's a little bit 100%
Sure
A little aggressive
Cuz I am.
So I can workout
Will Ferrell Elizabeth
Addiction
So give me a second
The process that
They left it standing up against tyranny
Vietnam
Into a tyrannical possess
Well the that yeah the
The anti-war movement in the 70s
PlayStation 70 is was
The leftist
Trying to impugn the good name of America
And yes then that would bring a
What network
Makes less sense than everything else you said so far confidently so I don't
Listeners are going to pick up on how stupid it is
Fun
It's fun at least it's different than a lot of his other narratives
A good point
That's a good
It also
Even process it
Like if you believe this
We've been going over his ship for like a year he's never talked really about how it's been coordinated plan
The anti-war movement
Just f******
The brain Forest done got good to him
The outcome of what happened
From this the day of the movement
Nope
By the way called
Pure race war in America
Nope
People leaving it
Wichita
Automatic weapons
The coffee room
Seven Springs car races racism
The quote minority bring up the
Always
It's stupid for us to bring up at this point 100 episodes in very clear that it's the same thing
Globalist stuff is white nationalism in a different
And what have you
It's alright
Call misrepresenting what people are actually saying
It's great slot of fun
It's a lot of fun for him
I'm glad you can have this kind of fun everybody
Answer
Lit on fire
I wonder why do male Vitality is flammable
Do you do you understand because I don't I don't know why my voice
Just did
Ifucking Jeff Foxworthy right there understand
Why why do they
People find whiteness
Is to be so important
Because these guys were
Don't you dare
It's time for us to really get to the bottom of
I don't know why you're asking
What is
Because there's a history in America of white people being the only real voice
They're the only people
Comfortable position
And it becomes
Essentially what is the norm what you what you think you deserve
What you're entitled to it's what our grandfathers
I just masculinity and
Were the default Norm
And everything else has to be sued
Subservient to it after
You have to any any needs
Of marginalized groups
Come after the needs of white
It's what we talked about a bunch
In terms of
If you're used to a super powerful position ready balancing of the equation seems like
We talked about that as well in the past
But now I'm running out of
Why is it
Why is it that you and I
White
Mail
With all the same privileges as bees
And these guys aren't
Cuz you look at that
That's a big issue for
We've been exposed to very smart people
Exposed to people of other walks of life
Experiences
And instead of
Being like
People have we realized
Peoplescu my headache
I guess
Struggling with
Like like if it were cuz cuz the narrative for the longer
The same thing
Post Civil War recap
The only way that the white folk
Can feel good about them
And the only way that you can
Separate them so they don't
United murder the Richmond
People who are there
Who are the
Root cause of all of their
Right
To say that white people are better
What is a Taurus
White dude
Can say he's better than old
Read people
You and I
These guys are
Banana Republic
Which has its own Iran
There
They have no problem
These people have
Zero issues
They don't have anything to complain about
Is it was a homo
F****** nothing
Every part of their lives is great
They have no issues
But they
On some subconscious
Just level realize that the absence of their issues
Is a byproduct
The fact that
Played the role
Okay I believe that the fact that they have no real issues like
Minorities and women have faced in terms of systemic oppression
Violence directed towards them just for
Speakingout
And stuff like that
I think they start to fear that eventually they will be in the same position that they have put people in historically
Sub sub cons
Consciously
I don't know
Preemptively
Fighting against issues
They've never had to deal
Yes and that's why I think a lot of people in these groups are like eventually will be a minority and that scares them so
To deal with the
Repercussions of Iraq
Actions web we weave
But not weed but like they would
Say I believe that
Eventually we will be on the business end
That which we have done
Again
No on white.
I'm just I'm just starting to lean towards
The ideas
Isn't
This isn't anything
But
I just don't know where to find
Like I'm starting to lean towards
This is the only social group
I'm the same way with Christy
A lot of Christian
Ghibah
Don't give a f*** about the Bible don't care about Christ
They just don't have anything but the
That's all
So to me I'm starting to get the the
Feeling that
None of this is
And all of it is
I depressed
Lonely
White people who feel like they have nothing else going on who feel like their lives there meaning
And this is the only way they can find me
That's that's
You engaging
And some sort of intellectual self-defense
Because the reality is so much
Exterior morphine
Probably
I think that you're rationalizing
Sing for them
Thank you for that
Because you're you're absolutely right. Just a better position to be in
Quite frankly because it's humanizing
You're not to blame this early for your actions just looking for love
You're looking for a you're looking for acceptance you're looking for something that gives your life
A feeling of meaning whereas the reality is
A lot of these people
Legit f****** hate people
I
Can't believe that this many people are true and honest
Psychopath
I got bad news
August
And psychologists said that it's like
What percent of the population of psychopaths
And these people sure make it look like 20% of the population
Pure psychopathy
2hype if you have that 1% within my 1% is going to be I don't know.
20% of the 1% that are
Incredibly charismatic and are able to lure people into their psychopathy
I just buy almost like by proxy
You'll have
Cult leader types within that 1%
And you have people who would otherwise be
Maybe reasonable people baby people who could you do a different path and unfortunately
Workout
Functionally psychopath
Mark Marlowe
That's really what it is like
How did so many Nazis
Just
Watch
People go into an oven
Yeah like that's
That's what these people are
They're good
They're people who are
Pudding
Putting people in
Yeah
I want that to be hyperbole.
To be hyperbole
And it's f****** not
I can move along cuz you
For this long
There was the lady who got killed by a car and 9th
Something people injured
I believe the numbers are a little bit too they very
Based on sources
But Alex
Sort of learned during this next clip
He pretends that he's well aware of it
What
F*** you
They were racist
So you can
Because this is home
I'm projecting again
Wind of these all tonight
Are all these people whenever they beat up people
Soros paid shill
Right
These all these Nazi folks
It's it's not that
Really fighting
Hard
Because
This is
Is the biggest shoe
For Alex
Is that
No longer
Can you say anything
Sing but the
These guys are at
Like before you could say all of their the alt-right Trump directly
Screaming blood
Just out-and-out Nazis
Oh they're all right
F****** Mike cernovich
Light bulb
Tucker Gavin McInnes was light games
So this is
This is his problem is that there's no longer any
There's no longer any
Distance
Between
What
They used to call the alt-right
Nothing very clear what's going on
The conservative movement were
Literal
Which is why I think it's important
To recognize
Appreciate the fact that there are
Reasonable Republican
Conservative-minded citizen
Because otherwise we run the risk
Of conflating
You know like weekly
We run the risk of being as
Intellectually dishonest
Simplistic as Alex
Yeah that I don't want us to ever fall into that Gap
No you're right
There's plenty of room for intellectual and political disagreement
Among adults
There's not room
No I know and I
I
Make
Taking me
Realized
I just
I just wish I could
Tap into their unchecked
Unhinged
Because when I don't feel it but I've got trouble reading all the stuff on these message boards
She like that
It's childish
Like
Like these people like
Here scream all the time
Literal
Murdered
Heather
Hair
Higher
However you pronounce her name I haven't heard it pronounce out loud
That's why I don't
I don't know when
Is her name
She was
Murdered
Literally
A victim of WWII
Like this is the world that were in
Like I don't get to
Experience that level of
Unhinged
No but now we have now
To be the Opera
Yeah exactly
I want to I want to come back
I'm on their level
In the same way that
During the campaign
It's that
During the
Campaign is like when they go low we go high
And it's like
Maybe
We should have been
No
Not not you and I we don't want to start lying
Creating false narratives
No I don't want
We don't want to become propaganda in and of ourselves
But I do agree with you in the sense that I'd like to
Some people
Thought not. But you're engaging in propaganda but like I do I don't
See a lot of problems with beating up now
I feel like at a certain
Point
We are we made
Peace with Germany we didn't make peace
Like we're still at war with Nazi
Weirdly Alex Jones is totally cool with Nazis
I hate Angela Merkel
Terminate Germany Macy's with us
Nazis didn't give up WWII in the same way that the Confederates didn't give up the civil
So let's get to the point where the car murder the people who lost Wars against America
Still trying
Yeah
Winning right now
A Bad season
But be that as it may I hear we're going to get to the point where the car murder actually
Within 30 minutes
Drove through protesters
Tuacahn in Saint Agnes
Josie the antifa
Nope
F*** you
They want to kill Trump
Put in a building
Martial law
Because they're alive
Where the police
Don't trust her
Costco
Designated
Again that goes back to permit
I'd like to get into now this gentleman I was just being way too
Too fair to him by the name of James Alex fields
He is
Has been arrested
Batgirl
Is the guy who murdered Heather
And it's kind of interesting looking at pictures of him
Cuz he was are protesting in the uniform
Vanguard America
And the white polo
Part of their organization
He was also pictured carrying one of their scope
Logo on it
Shield
Tell me what their logo is a lot of Education
Affiliated
Whether or not he was a leader in the group or whatever it's kind of irrelevant
I don't believe that if you're examined Streisand like this you'd be carrying
You're not down with Shield
Around a bunch of people
You're probably a very radical person
Looking into Vanguard America
Parentage testing organization
I mean incredibly boring
A large group of
Because it's elections at Large
Okay fine
Call Griffith
Lookout
Spells let's say in a bunch of
Birthright America
Proud boys
So
Sing that we've been like
We've made this point
In the past that
Isis
Does not scare me at all
It is
White supremacy
Who are
Play couple weeks people ask me a number of times what I think is going to happen
And I
Every indication that I can tell
Seem to be going I think we're going to
Essentially
I'm Isis like Insurgency rise up
You're going to see a lot of this Loosely Affiliated groups
Of Nazis and white nationalists
Are going to start
Bombing South they're going to start
Yeah I think that's what's going to happen I'll be glad to be wrong
Scary part
I don't know
To hide
Military and
National Garden
Are going to be on to hope for the best
The FBI has been
Investigator
All of
The White Knight
Infiltration of our lungs
In the same way that the Scientologist
Angel traded
The
IRS
I think that they're obviously is infiltration but I do believe it
It's not as bad as
We might be afraid it is
I don't know we'll find out
What
You can go to Vanguard America's webs
They have a website
Published a Manifesto
With groups like
To talk about them being alike
Steak and what have you
You got to look at their history
Quite a while and they legit do have a Manifesto of what they believe in
Very publicly available
And there are very strong indication
Convert this James Alex Fields Jr
Was at least in some way
Involved
It is worth our time
To look at the manifesto
Alex Jones
Okay
The Damage Done to this nation and its people will not be fix
If every issue requires a vote
If every Point must be debated disgusting deliberate
Pawn democracy has failed in this once great nation
Now for the time of a new Caesar to revive the American Spirit has.
At the light
Everybody make mistakes
Absorb
Our Caesar
Sort of similar to not quite like on the head it's not it's not a bullseye
In America based on the immutable truths of blood and soil
A multicultural nation is no Nation at all but a collection
Allstate America is to be a nation exclusively for white American people
Who out of the barren Hills empty planes invest Mountain
Forge the most powerful Nation to have ever exist
That's bulshit
That's a historical bulshit
But if it is
Very similar to
Are Prosperity coming and what have you making America great again
The West
Vanguard America stands indomitable opposed
To the tyranny of globalism
Great great
I love it Dan I'm not sure if I actually said this was a Manifesto is titled American fashion
So that's great
The ideal structure of a family is one which is
Working father and nurturing mother in still strong values in the children
This family structure is and it's proven to be the strong foundation for Any Nation
Any assault on the family must be met with Swift and decisive Act
I'll Jones always talk about how people are trying to destroy
The family mother and father boy and girl
Snowflake
Cowards
The Vanguard
Whatever the f*** their goddamn name is
The murderer
The murderers of Heather heyer
Higher
Whichever it is
I love that they don't even have the balls of Isis
They do
They said that he wasn't claim him
Might as well come out and claimed that he was one of them all these terrorists
Exactly
I mean that
That speaks
To the third of cowardly
Hiding of the people
Existed online for a long time and are only now starting to creep their toes
Into actually public because they are
People realize that if he claimed him
And not with his Justice
Department
Yeah I'm glad that
This department is led by
Just sessions did say if they're going to invest
F****** on the case
That ends up Mitch McConnell is on the f****** case
Never a great time when Paul Ryan gets
The sound reasonable
Americans should strive for a truly National economy
That economy that is self-contained and free from the influence of international corporation
Light by rootless groups of international Jews
Which place Prophet beyond the interest of our people or any people
Globulin
The Elders of Zion
The large multinational yeah they are
Be large multinational corporations that have bled this nation dry will not be allowed to
Continue their detrimental efforts unabated
Once they're brought to heel it on the whims of the vestige
Our jobs or industry will not be exported to foreign Nations
And the media Industries will no longer be allowed to poison the minds of our people
Sure
That sounds very
Looks like they guys
I know that Alex would never want to look into this stuff because again it would be terrifying to look into the mirror and realize
That these people who are out there and are Nazis
Believe the song believe the same
That is tough
That's got to be tough
80-in
Wrestling without
Maybe a lot of the stuff I believe is not healthy is not good isn't based on reality
I'm certain that you just like
Oh well the Southern Poverty Law Center evil Fox and all this UPS.
Bring it
Blacklivesmatter website Manifesto
Come on. I'm exhausted already
We have so much to get through
We are
Let's
Six clips in other out of 20
So
I need to be silent for the next eight Clips otherwise we're going to be at 6 hours
Two clips
Another one of our patented
Shot and chaser
The first one
If it's mostly about how antifa sucks
Discusses various City
Costco
Can't come back through here to women children and Anna
Call Edwin
People got pissed
Who made it
That's what happened
Do you watch Game of Thrones
Are they Valyrian steel
Stop
Illegitimate free-speech you can't beat cutting taxes
Sandia prep table
Deep state
Hillary
Yeah yeah
Faucet
In Civil War in civil insurrection
City
Cleveland
Liberal conservative area blue collar
Everybody
So let's ignore the rest of the stuff of the beginning cuz there's a bunch of boring nonsense
What was the Ohio
Why does he think
These are the RNC because it was a
Do it like a Republican
So it wasn't
That's way of the globalist and what have you
Charlottesville in Virginia
Going to be f****** messy
They're going to set you up in Cleveland
Cuz I just want
It's totally fine now listen to this from maybe 10 minutes later
Cleveland
The reason it was different was because it was the same
Does that make sense
Scary just saying nonsense he wants to make our
Even like
I do like the fact that he's got nothing and he has no right
Because unlike these
F******
Tiles of s***
Republican
Paul Ryan rhinos
Who have
The writing staff put together
This well-worded
We we don't believe anything so everybody can believe whatever they want
He has to come out
And late are how much
Nothing he has about how the fact that he's a f****** Nazi
It's it's pretty fascinating on a lot of levels
Like this is exactly if you had
If you had Trump
Or Paul Ryan or Mitch McConnell
Just talk
Reveal exactly how awful and horrible and Races they are
The same white Nashua
Or they just reveal how little they give a s*** about any human being and all they want is f****** tax cuts for the rent
I think that if you had them just
Bitten nonsense for hours on end on a hot bike
One of the things we would reveal as they don't really know any
Now they don't like
Do more than like
I don't know.
10 minutes in a press conference without it being a bandhan Lee clear sayings
You really have a writing staff that's giving you good
You're just saying like
Look up not too long ago there was a lady who had a reporter who asked him what is that
Tomorrow
Yeah
Like before
Like during the bush
The gwu
We were at least a little bit confused as to where we were on the stupid verses
Stupid versus
Lizzie Velasquez
Now we're
Very clear that we are on the stupid
Woodside of evil
Like a
Cuz we're all the way up on stupid and
Evil at the sea
My weird corner
Sure so
Two clips
Contradicts himself
Which is delightful
Navigate to how you got it
Stay out of liberal cities
Any other thoughts about that
He gets into
He's already mentioned it
Boxes of Mac
That's true
Unfortunately I agree with Alex today this is what's going on on Fox
Now that I'm excited
Sure
Nope
Come out
Amazon TV
I want to mention it goes back to what even
About the car is
Is code for
Of course I didn't know about the dog
Megyn Kelly interview when you talkin about how he covered the Manchester bombing
Or you just got on here before he knew any of the facts
These were liberal
You forgot bombed
His f******
That isn't always just let the mouse go really fast
And they never do
And when they don't he just ignores the fact that he was wrong
And pretend like I was kind of right
It doesn't matter
God
I want words to have
Ben White
Everything about
I know nothing about those robber by Muslim
Caesars
Go in South Carolina shooting
Call Izzo whites are all guilty whites are all bad I know you are but what am I know you are but what am I
The white man
What are you talking about
What's the score
Controls
These are Global trying to push this.
So he takes the camera which it obviously is like an iPhone
Recording it attached
Buckley's had B Muffler
Please hadn't just drag them into the roads not Buckley Salazar
But they go into the other room where they have the TV the foxes playing on in the coffee room
I don't know if it's a
Pick up on this
From the audio
But most of the time
The video of it is on the TV
But you can hear cabinets opening and closing I think he wanted a snack
I think he's in the middle of a video and there's also a part where I found
Like you can hear him
To the camera person
It is incredibly lightning Pixies Whispering inaudible
But it's so weird
Opening and closing I got nothing
I'm going to go see what Fox News is doing see if I can get them a bit
All of this goes on for a long time
The audio was really terrible of the TV
Special Report
Especially
So the audio is really terrible at the Fox News people
Keep Coronavirus
It's worth the outside jumping in
This first one is about how everyone wants
Say the name
These groups
He wants that everyone expects him to be really specific in his condemnation
So here we go
It wasn't the alt right
You have to say radical Islamic radical Islamic terrorism
Great
Turn tomato
Immediately
Yeah you got to stay the night
This is Toadette
Again
It's so weird
Revel in not giving a s*** about
You and I
Hair so much
About some sort of ideologically
Idly ideological
Against my will admit that you are right
About some conservative okay I will
Matters
How do you know if I were crazy
Battlefield how do you fight
I don't know but also
Mycallin
Yes I would say that what he's doing in the form of lesser Magic
Where he knows he's contradicting himself and being a complete hypocrite and he's doing it to rub it in your face
Because nothing's real and I can get away with anything
Sarah kendzior like
That's what fascist always want you to do is show you how little they can
Institutional version of game
I I care very much while you're asked
Can't believe that you don't care at all
That's out at Serta
But yeah so that's dumb
Alex
About the Southern Poverty Law Center
Southern Poverty Law Center
Southern Poverty Law Center has been caught running and Tire
Oklahoma City
Swastika
Racist white people but statistically
Bye-bye bye-bye bye-bye
Southern Poverty Law Center with running Elohim City
In the Timothy McVeigh was involved with
Before he ended up Longaberger
But just to re-up on that
Inside the
F****** with you
Supremacist organization
They was giving them information
And because it's important
In a lot of
White nationalism
Malicious for good reason
It's important
And they're not going to unlike Visa Dum Dums in the Vanguard America just going to post it on a website somewhere
Resurrection
Well
I mean sometimes it's a good thing and sometimes they use their plan to murder Fred Hampton
Celebrate
Believe
People because they are
Watching this s***
But it's
You would rather have them watching the knot watch
Complex
And ridiculous time believing that the Southern Poverty Law Center is involved
And I are planning bombings
Some stuff like that
Phone
About 1
Whatever important pieces
World is the southern
Call center
Eskipoo
That shitt
Plus
Plants inside of
Isis
Making sure that they
Wait a second
Have you been listening to Infowars
I'm telling you
I know that sounds very similar
Fighting a lot of free speech issues
You know how that's going
People for like
First Amendment
This is always the first people with a briefcase
Hemet Court
Whenever whenever there is that Muslim ban
Isis being there
Looking up the statutes that keep that from going off
Everybody knows this
I wanted to pull out
I think really important is all these evil whites when in reality white people are
Likely to commit
12 * right is well.
Referent in a real statistic
He doesn't understand that
They're reporting issues and
Crimes against white people
Swept under the rug
And I know from my own
Personal life
There's so many times that if I was black I would have been arrested
Dead as a child
Breaking into places or buildings in
Alex knows that
Alex has pointed out that the reason he hasn't been arrested
It's because of a white nationalist
The cop that pulled over
Bring it up
Cuz if you had any
If you had any inkling of intelligence
You just let that one
Well he knows his audience doesn't
Inclined to pity white people
It doesn't matter if he's already
Negated his own point on his own show that
Still available
Don't matter
Can we burn in as a warlock
Against anybody considered this whether or not Superman
I would love it if it wasn't himself emulated what your sister to protest
Emily flick the cigarette
Goes Up in Flames
Justice weddings for male infertility
I'm so this next clip
Explains
Thank you psychic
But
Please nuts
And also
Strikes me as like
People ask me this that's
Such a f****** b******* thing I've ever listened
The Paul Stanley's album
The lead singer of Kiss about this album
I'm in the past
Course I haven't
He constantly starts things like people come up to be
Stuff like that
He does all this like he just needs an excuse to say what he wants
Give me to a story by pretending people always come up to him and ask
Called you a big dick and I say yes I do if that levels up
When I see that rhetorical trick being used by Alex
You dumbass hole
Anyway I just think that's delightful
I like that that
That's a little fun mixed in with
Does nonsense
Quit
It's more just about the
The car murder
He wants to
Spinach be like
Did you did you read that he's only been charged
Yeah
And a bunch of other charges
But not right
Avery murder
Tourism
Terrorism like this is
There's no
Well then terrorism task force is only about Islam
So great this is one of those things
Like
As as
Disgusted with America's I am
For the first degree
Well to the charges in order to make sure you actually get it
Conviction
That possible
That's sad.
Disgusted
Softener
Here's more disgusting
You showed
A journalist being murdered
Lied
F****** s***
It's a one of the things that he's doing here
Yeah
But also get rid of the conversation is going on in Fox News that he was
Is incredibly scary
Right because
Well
I have some laws for you multiples
About how you should be allowed
With your f****** car because they're blocking
It's not a crime commercial terrorism protesting
Commercial terrorism cuz they're not letting you make your deliveries are getting to your job or whatever
First Amendment rights allow me to
They're being disruptive
What year is it
He knows that the audio is
Go to the Fox News stuff so
He's responding
Something on the Fox News
It's the same thing he does whenever he
Pretend to listen
Stopped
The tub right here I need to get it go back 10 seconds
He's so fattening so ugly look at his f****** face Maddie doesn't
Mr. creeps
Alex
He believes that the I'm letting us run through
Eclipse now.it we got an hour 45 Vero
Alex
Cuz really going
What's
Continue
And go out in public
Live protest
What they were
What they were discussing in the Fox News before he got on his I told you and then tried to do a Ric Flair impression
What is
It becomes an interesting line we're protesting
Start
I am that is a conversation we're going to need to have sooner than later
Because it's going to
Keep happening
The problem
Fun waffles
You can't you can't bring people together if you essentially are trying to start a riot
Expectation that you know you're going to start a riot
Not okay
I know
I don't know how to
I don't know how to engage
I don't either because
Cuz that's been used
Oppressively
Like that is
That is
How many times have you seen right
Take down somebody on arm
Not doing anything
Literally literally
You look at the way that the police
Treated this
Not much
S*** but that's that's why I'm coming to
The point that I am
There is a line
More
Adult reasonable conversation about like what is protest
Testing what is demonstrating a
I think it would serve everyone
Purposes
But because I was dumb conversation
Peabody
Essentially was
What's going on
He pretends I got you
What you doing this you want to ban protest you want to say the conservatives can't have any kind of protest
That's not true
Conservatives have the protest
If they want to have
Or maybe I'm even okay with that uncertain Circle
Dances
Yeah I think it's okay
This is where this is where were
Did the radiological right now
That is true
Know what you're looking at me like you do
Don't like that
But I'm no longer in the
In the I do want to take our guns
Open Karen
Yes responsible gun ownership is something that does exist in
In the country
Population
I don't like
Then there being large militias at
Protests like this
I think the
Elementary
But in terms of
You know
Expressing your political beliefs
So you should be able to have gun
I think that's reasonable I don't take
The only reason that it seems unreasonable because the world we live in right now
Okay okay I'm sorry I don't know I don't mean to cut you off
You know I love you
I don't understand
How you can
Bringing
An
To a protest
Is not
Itself a form
That's why I'm trying to make this line that I don't like it
Here
But in protest that are
Second Amendment
Bass stuff like that it is
Reasonable it's within the law and people
If people are handling themselves responsibly
But if you
Somebody or something like that then that in and of itself is a crime
Protests aspect
How do you take
Make an AR-15
And not eventually wind up
I think that it happens a lot
Turning around
Responsible gun owners always
You're gone at the ground
You always
It's not loaded
Those sorts of things
If if people are tell me those guys I don't have to unload
So it's not fair
You're right
You're right that I don't know
What what what I'm saying is
I would not like to see
Are things that are illegal
And if people are doing well they have a gun at a protest
I think they should be arrested
But if you follow the
Safety protocols
Stuff like that
I don't really think it's it's really that bad
I don't I think it is allowed
Restatement silly part where it is
Don't think it's a problem
I do believe that we have our
Exactly
Stance
All
All reality
Consider this as an intellectual
You have a very cogent
And
Accurate
Point I agree with
We don't live in
We don't live there
Let me flip your laundry
Native American
Holding a bottle of water
That is more
Threatening
Then a white dude that's a massive problem
Is not of holding a gun at a protest
Is an insect
It may be it maybe in your mind but let me flip that
A tiny bit
I don't know giving way too much.
If you say that just the very presence
David Gunn is an incitement when the person
There were hypothetically talking about
Is
Carrying it responsibly it's pointed at the grounds are not threatening anybody
It's your saying it's still inside
I would say there are people who believe it's being two men kissing in public
Isn't in sight
It's something that they are very offended by
And the rubbing it in your face
In in the pride parades people running around with their songs on with their dicks showing
That's an incitement hold on
People who are protesting by blocking traffic
That's an insult
And that makes me very proud
Flexing some sort of muscle you don't have I'm not saying I agree with that but that same logic could be used for
And that's a dangerous path to go down
Has two men kissing ever gone wrong
And killed somebody
Imagine
Misfired
And kill the child
That dude in the street ever
Accidentally overturn and killed somebody had somebody in the street ever
Hit a woman
And then backed up and then hit 10 more people
But that's
Your argument
Understand where you're coming from but within my own argument that's taken care of
Because
Big guns
Be unloaded
So if there's a misfire they're already doing something wrong
So that part of it
Is kind of like
All right within the within the parameters that I'm setting for what I think is
Acceptable
If you want to take
That's right you have
Make it clear that it is unloaded
That
To be done
I don't I don't see a problem with that having some sort of
Station where they check
Exotic erasable
Did this happen
I don't know I but I don't know I don't I don't know nearly enough
You know I know that things weren't checked I believe that that they didn't check each and every one of those
No probably not
There is
In this
Then we have two steps
Further parameters
So that a gun
But even then
You can hit somebody with the butt of a gun you can you can't
Hit somebody with two guys kissing
No but if you have a sign that says I'm super into two guys kissing you could hit somebody with the staff of that
Fair
The fair argue
Disagreeing with you on that do only thing I'm just the only reason I brought those examples
Listen to it was because you were
Hindering your argument on the idea of insight
And just because you have a natural reaction
Come from
Which I believe obviously is probably more reasonable
Then being incited by seeing two dudes kiss
It is
The same
Sort of reaction that you're having within your brain
Now yours
Your reaction is more
Threat Bass
Like this is a threat
But they would think that seeing these two dudes kissing
Inasmuch as they believe that there's a gay agenda and what-have-you they the same
Sort of
Dumb
But there is a dump
A response the people have
And I know that I'm
Being
I don't think it's fair
To paint all gun owners defending
Reasonable conservative
There are a lot of reasonable gun owners
You are not and I don't
Disagree with you on this boy
My point is
If you are taking
10 guns 2
And I'll Stand
Peaceful protest
That is
What else what else is a gun
Hunting
Yeah okay
So take a peaceful protest
What are you hunting
Baby squirrels
Monkey squirrels
You are too because the beginning
Prompted out of nowhere is that
Idle
I don't think it is great to see
These guns in the militias
This sort of protein
Yes but in the context
Second Amendment
Gun oriented protest
I totally
Understand it
Cast
Have a peaceful
Gun oriented protest
Where it is reasonable and
Totally
Responsible to
To have guns
When you inject guns
In places they don't belong
That brings me muddies the water a little bit
I'm not defending
Armed militias with
Semi-automatic weapon showing up
But counter-protest liberal protest
I think that it's helped kind of us
Okay but I died
I don't think the absolute presence of a gun
Contact
In responsible ownership
Is something
Okay that's all the point
And I
I get
I get your point
And I do
But but then you come at me with like
Well a response what's a gun for
For hunting
Event
Or or or Leisure what's an Recreation
AR-15
The argument and I'm not
I'm certainly not making this argue
You're mad but I know that
I have some say in French
Who have large rifles
Stuff like that that are beyond what you need someone
A semiotic
If you have if you brought a semi-automatic
Into this room
Wow
While we are recording
This
We do have a lot of variables
Protest
Situation where
An AR-15
Which is what
They
A f******
They were wearing
Body armor
The real world
And you're taking this into the App Store
And I
I totally
Agree with you
In a vacuum and
We don't live
No vacuum
If we have regulations
Which is what we do
Work permits and stuff like that
Guns you can bring those
Speed zone
They're not
They're inciting violence
No no because because those people took those people in order to be carrying guns in public would have to have a permit
Right every single
I'm doing alright they did
You do
But I don't
Great
I mean I guess I guess we're not going to work we're coming down
To both of us not having the right information
You're right
So we can't we can't really litigate what was going on at this Pacific protest
You are absolutely right and I want to get off this
Ever
Big
People having like these high-powered rifles
Semi-automatic weapon
It is it is
I believe
In terms of
Knowing where these weapons are people having to
What's it called tuna check
It needs to be some sort of
But at the same time the people who have them
I don't think that they have them for
Intrinsically violin
Means
A lot of them
Is reasonable to have a handgun
To protect your house
As it is to have a large rifle
For the same purpose
If you believe that you're going to be
Possibly at some point facing something that is bigger than the pistol can help you with
Yes then
The same argument of self-protection
Does kind of apply
Now because it's so much more dangerous
Especially semi-automatic weapon
I think that
The dangerousness of it needs to be reflected in the regulation
Control mechanisms that we have in place
4 people having
Good protection I don't think
Invalid
Gree with you
We have to be true to principal
If we do live in a f*****-up world
It's not right unless you want to come out and say everyone should have their guns taken away and just breathe
And I understand
I suppose
I suppose again I'm
Taking that
I'm bringing you the real world
Because
Those guys that
We have seen
That wheat
Like Alex
Responsible gun owners
Alex Jones
Has murdered 0pp
Is that guns on his desk
Exactly
Alex Jones
Clearly has self to
So taking it to approach
Tumi
Seems like
Hoping for one of those self-defense
It's possible
I agree with your argument
Because I can't prove that that's why those guys are
Right I can't do
But if they are on
Either side
I'm going to air on don't bring a f******
I would like for that to be the real
I know we're not arguing
The same
I feel like we're not arguing the same
Because I'm writing my
What's agree to disagree I think we both have good points but we're not going to get to the bottom of gun
Write this episode ever
For two people to solve it and it turns out
Over a little bit of wine
I'm hungover as a horse track
Maybe
I believe you real f*****-up place anyway
Okay still reviewing the Fox news coverage I really
I appreciated that
Conversation and sorry I screamed
I understand where you coming from
And I
I get your point
And you've made some good
I I do feel like I think as the world gets more complicated and things get worse
I think it's just going to get worse
Yeah I think we're going to see more and more stuff like this starts
Pop up and start to happen
And I'm really afraid that what's going to happen is we're all going to get distracted by something
On Tuesday
And we won't deal with the fact that
All the time that we ignore it these dudes are organising and still existing online
They are still having their manifestos posted on their website they're still organizing and meeting
And talking about how we need to defend whiteness
Some s*** like that
I'm really scared about that
There aren't but as we move into the future where things are going
To be scarier and weirder
I think that
Be more clear with principles
Understanding of positions that may seem weird to us
Like people having guns I don't have a gun you don't have a gun
Right
It does seem a little bit weird but people who are super interested in guns
And we might disagree on a lot of issues about
Get that
Responsibility
To go halfway
Too reasonable
Because
There's going to be a lot less opportunities for that
Icing
Is
The situation
What we would like to
To see from the other side
Put it
You just kind of got a
Juno quota
Kevin Spacey movie titled you got to pay it forward
Amazon
Or else we're just being the petulant children who are like
You don't do it so we're not going to either
I want reasonable Republicans and
Conservative-minded folks
To come on board and realize that hey there's nothing weird about being gay
Or the trans people are real people
And they're not crazy
I would love for those sort of
Social thing
We firmly believe in
Wheeler I'd love to see it more allies ship from that side
Icing
Right but that doesn't mean we don't still have a responsibility to be bigger
And understand some of the right
Conservatives
Gun ownership is not a right left shoe it's just with the right wing
Definitely seems to be
More vocal and angry about it
Let's put it this
Think that this
Is
A huge conversation
And we are talking
Think about it now for
I don't think that's true
Feels like it
We gotta get back to the school
I understand I understand your point
I do end
I agree with you in effect
I think you are
Hey I think you are upholding ideals
Beauty
And I believe it
Johnny
I think that is exactly why so many people have been murdered in
So and then resolved that the end result
Right well
I was murdered
No
You
If we all must
I let us die with our principals Ann Arbor
Is barefoot
Enjoy
So this next clip Alex is still going over Fox News
They still trying to do some analysis
That's not true
Who's the first guy said ban the First Amendment
Conservatives the first guy on Fox News
Pretending this whole time we've been like
Conservative preachers were on who I like
Blurb
You know that you know that very common
Conservative
Even Fox News
Is essentially
You getting at
Because he goes back
To the f****** coffee room
The break room and the first person who's reasonable
And not saying those things
Intuit order to save face
Because he's built it up as we're going to go back there and I'm going to be able to see this stuff
As opposed to that being all of them
Which item
Which for him is a smart move
Because going further to the right
Ethan Fox News
Exactly what
Want at
This moment you live again
They're all white Nash
Yes
Explain
That's how I have it written down
I guess
Don't breathe
North Korea
Hair
That's the situation
That's where we're at
I love I love the framing of
Military organization order of Alt
Who is going to
Define Free Speech if it isn't the order of
Well they name cereals
This is another one of those times
I wish
I lived it I wish we lived in that world
Because then
You can believe that
The globalist too hard
Instead of
People it's so comforting
For comforting
The globalist or inside
Because in that world.
It is very much like
People Are People
It's not that there's these
Large group
Psychopath
Who have no care for the rest
Because they hate
Are you thinking this world in your life
That's good
What people aren't
These white people not always
Although
I'll leave that alone
These people are good people
They have good hearts
They're just missed
Disregard
They're not
Like these are these are not good
No
These are bad people
Oftentimes
Influence by
The bat
The horrible things that Alec
To say that he's not the only
Call Pez dispenser
Specifically about
Did one of the reasons that we focus on him
A person who espouses this
I firmly believe that
A lot of the narratives that he
Expresses and perpetuate
Are very similar to the narratives that are perpetuated by
In terms of the white nationalism
Supremacy
So if we
Deal with him
And deal with the narratives that are being
Express you can use that
Do understand
The b*******
That those people the hardcore dude
They're spitting
Using right so
Normalizing
Umbrella
In the same way that fox
Snooze is a normalizing
Umbrella for his tie
For storm
Or those
I would argue you
Yeah
More focused on Fox News
Nesting dolls
Is it is it worth
If we are aware to use his terminology and go back to episode 2
Alex wants to give you the big takeaway
The big guys big guys summation unfortunately
He has a big
As is never the case
There's a big takeaway
The secret 2017
Noni
So so bad
That's the worst thing and I can't help but laugh at that sofa
From a performance aspect that's so terrible
But we were laughing over the that when he comes to the at the end of the visit
Much bigger than the media
Why you bringing that up
The other thing is
I mean aside from the car
So much worse
When we went over that back then
Bleeding and we saw the pictures it was just like a lady at a cut on her hand
Scrape
Give me the video of the
These are awful antifa attacks released
What's up
He says that the media didn't report on violence
At the inauguration and II
It's like to explain that
Is Google it
Players in Washington during Trump inauguration
Washington Times Donald Trump inauguration protests 217 arrested
CNN inauguration protests
Police injured more than 200 arrested
Washington Post inauguration protesters vandalized set fires
Try to disrupt
Swearing-in
Photos of the violent protests
Trump's inauguration
New York Times inauguration protesters and police Clash
USA
But what about
The violence that happened
The other day
But what about the violence that happened
Okay but what about the violence
On Tuesday August
Fourth
Cupboard
Table cover
What about the violence that happened
Call man what about the violence that happened after Jesus
It was covered
He's actually saying that because he's lying didn't cover the stuff
I wanted to be covered
Either way I want to be covered is a story of these violent leftist hordes were beating up old women
Now we reported on that Grant
We don't have the video
Rely
The argument they didn't cover stuff is
Very demonstrative liyah Li
It's all there
Just Google it
All the articles in the archives
Eggless
So
Touchdown
Saw on Twitter
I looked at all the real news
And then I
Went to
The Drudge Report
Call great to see what was going on there
They linked to one article
The rest of it
Was
Far away
Yeah and it was like
What what I saw there was them
The Drudge
Report
Masturbated
To how
Equal coverage that
Like that
I like the fact that
What they were doing
Is saying
Look at house
Exactly the type of
That he is
I feel very sad because
Where we were going to do today if
That will begin at episode coming up so I want to put a pin in this state will happen
Matt drudge shows up on Alex Jones
So we're going to
But for now let's
Let's keep trudging forward cuz Alex Jones waffle talk more
That's good
Donuts
Four more days like that
To talk more about you looking
Gamecity
Nope
Hell yeah
Love is hot chicks
Who cares about the rest of the day
What the f***
Is that
Starting to find is a lot of these Bots be Pro Trump
They use
Photos of hot women
Better promotion pictures they are able to photoshop
Something message on there or on a hat
African American lady
The actual person was involved
With the scam or not
But there are a lot of these account
Because all these
F****** fake Twitter account
Huge titted ladies
And they had superimposed on their shirt make America great again
And stuff like that
Oh my God all these hot chicks in super into Trump getting all these
Alex certainly spouts out a lot not dumb people
Just a bunch of dummy dump dumping lesbo feminist
These blonde
Hot big titty girls
They love Trump I got to get on that
Super hot chicks
5 followers
And let me tell you something
If I want to find a hot lady in my area tonight
You got a little tiny URL
Explain half of my experience on Tinder
But
The idea that Alex is even bringing that
Amazon
Talk about your boy let's talk about
Luring in real life
What is the organization
This group
That that Timothy McVeigh was involved
It wasn't that they planned
I don't know I don't know enough about it
I just I researched as much as it its existence
In the 90s
When did the Murrah building
Did they ever
Build the cities like
I don't know when it was
Specifically about whether or not it was run by the Southern Poverty Law Center
Because that's the claim that Alex makes
I'll be the first to admit that I don't know everything about their hair
Whether or not
So yeah
That was a computer sound
So he was expressing
Basically that
I'm so they had to create some
Expound on that a little
Atmore
By being a white supremacist
It's hard to find him though
Studios are
Chalmette
Cuz I didn't have a Sprite I like Gavin beginners
Just to make us look stupid
Wait for it
General officer
This is how they do it
Theater
Computers
Ron
Based on everything Alex believes about
Kratz
Be thrilled at the idea of being able to search faces
That seems like something you be very again
Do you want some light
Right
Control over all of
While presenting it is I'm against all of
What's the government to know exactly who you are where you are and everything that you're doing it all-time database
Why this is a bad thing crazy
Chimeras
Okay
The f****** idea that
Like I have my rallies and then two guys in Klan robes come up to me and they're like we love you Alex Jones
Find out there
I don't believe any of that story except clam people said they loved it
I don't believe it maybe says our class
Doesn't preclude in the wrong way
But
He has one hundred percent right
That makes me more scared that said people are in the clan
Also that the saying that that's the reason he doesn't do more Rally's
And stuff like that I remember him doing was the one where Eric Andre got onstage and clowns on it
I think it's possible
Going to get clean.
O'Reilly Eric Andre Woods
But I think that's more the reason Alex Jones doesn't do more Rally's
He knows that he is
So
Look at it goes back to be talked about 2 hours ago it's now
You be very easy to publicly expose him if he is it in public rally
Cuz there are a growing number of revolts
Such as myself
Who aren't afraid of his Auto
If I were a little bit of would not be afraid
For the opportunity to poke holes in his entire world
Actors but I'm not scared of him beating me up for the opportunity to
Face in public
Through words
Anyway
Words are bullets
Anyway this next clip
Just a bunch of nonsense and it gets back to White ship
Yeah exactly
Liberal
Wait what
He's so upset all my God
I should be clear he's still doing his analysis of Fox News so it sounds like
Audible on the video
It's very shoddy production
Whatever you want whenever nobody knows what you're fighting
Screen shaking his head and being like
Anyway
Other people
Me too
What do you think
Wait is that a life
No
Real quick
When this is over
I will say there is one very funny clip left
Okay
After the special
Does he
First of all
At no point.
I don't even know if I could deal with that.
He does no sim
Anybody who is he
Of course
He doesn't care if it
But if
Still be like
No one cares
He gets off
Discover
The real
The real news
Finishes a sandwich
Yeah
I assume
Delicious Ritz crackers
By the way Ritz
We will advertise a sponsorship
Does he
Feel any
Like
Do you think he
Good luck cuz this is
Is weird
Like this
This bums me out
Exact
That's all like that's all I'm hearing right here anger is I'm afraid that
Established
Bubbly a full-on
Raging narcissist
Maybe on the autism spectrum
Well let me put it to you this
Do you think he was visited by the devil
Every night
The devil is
How how can
Before he goes
Before he goes to bed does he not for
Second
Maybe I'm the bad guy
No cuz you takes knock out of an hour
So now it's no big deal
I remember back when I took sleeping pills
Horrifying
By anxiety did not keep me up at night
That's true. He'll and you're done
Knockout
I mean I guess it's all day
I just
A hard time
With
With this
With the particulars
Sweetheart
Let me distance myself from
I have such a hard time being alive which is
I have a hard time
With how weak
Reconciling that with
How he has
Like he's got f****** nothing
He's got no
He's pulling bulshit out of the air
He's ripping
Throwing up all of his usual waste
So we can tell
That even he knows he's got
Totally
So if even he
He knows you got nothing going on
How is it that he can get off air
And not for a second
Can have any
Introspection
Texas Bank
I think that's how you do it I think he's fine
That's
True thing anybody's ever said
Meanwhile as of Friday
When I got paid
Last week
75 South
Like a good night
So
I'm living in that world
I don't have that to come
For me when we get done record
I have to
We expressed our legitimate feelings
Pointed out where Alex Joseph
Take from it if I was making millions of dollars
I could be like
Holyshit I have so much money
My house
Security I'm sure you
Probably offense
Alligators
Billy gets to go home to essentially a mansion and have no real concerns in the world
Go on errands
MPS concern
I think that's how you do it
F*** you everybody says money can't buy happy
Also money can't buy knockout
I mean I know the truth nobody who's ever said
I know that we
Kind of are coming from a position that he has brain damage any
A little nut
But I also
Do thing in the back of his mind he knows he
He's fighting fake
So when you
Create a fake anime
You're never really scared
Because the people here again
You know they don't exist
He knows that there are globalist
Trying to kill him
Because you made that up
And on some level he knows that
So he can scream about all this stuff
And the only real thing you have to worry about is like antifa coming after him or something like that
So
That's that with basic
Thought I have regarding billionaires
Sword
I have a lot about billionaire
Is that
The reason that they can
Can fund all of these
Is b*******
Nobody can touch
Like imagine if
And I'm not
Advocating this at all
Sounds like you're about that
Right like his
But that's not
Possibility
Like imagine a world where Alex Jones
With Act
Truly afraid
Imagine a world where these white nationalists
These middle-class comfortable
Wearing their f******
Uniform
Imagine if they stop for a second
That they could really be
You know
Vulnerability making them up and they're pretty
Pretending that there
That their aggression
Defensive
When in reality it's b******* like imagine if they were Act
Truly on the defense
These guys
Fry and
Because they're doing that off.
Spanish
V but that's the other thing that's really dangerous is when you have a made-up anime
Defeat them is to
Oppress other people
Then the other people
Your real enemy
Even though
The way you
Express it is directed at a fake
True so
It's not fair of us to say he's making up
Everybody
Disenfranchised groups
Straight
So they're right
He's also weirdly fine with minority women in 100 hot
Then his racism is
Precluded by his boner
But it's
I do not like
I've been wrestling a lot with
Like his is very bizarre version of racism
Because he thinks that he's not a rapist
Cuz he likes Mexican food and stuff like that over and over again
He's like if you make good food I don't care I like your culture
No child version of
I want to talk
You know
This summer again it goes back to that Megan
And if somebody questions I wish you would have asked
That's f****** batten down the
And get through the rest of us
The way that you start a good show at
Let's fuk
Rude
Well I didn't expect us have a half-hour debate about guns
I've edit this f****** show
Are you going to believe this
Cuz you goddamn better I will but let's get through it it's not because I'm like I hate this
It's because like
Looking at the clock
I know I'm not going to bed before midnight
Night tonight
I'm sorry
Tomorrow hoping for tweets from people
Anyway our listeners will think
The cruelest irony
A nextplus
We get to see it like a nice window into Alex Jones
Then how can you generally
Experiences
Peoria news
Asian
YouTube
That's kind of short and really lame but I think it's important
He hears most
Does the people on television
Gore calling
I don't know
Recognition of the nature
Not white people but whiteness
As a social construct
He hears people bringing up the
These points as like white people are inherently evil they should slit their own throats
Pray that goes to this hole I think that we bring up over and over again
Him misunderstanding thing
And then launching off based on the misunderstand
And it's dangerous
That's pretty
Regular for that
Seven and a half hours
We started that
If you are in a place
The idea that
Anybody take
Light little bit
Getting
Some of your
Away from you
But
Getting to the same level you are
Is a threat
It's perceived that way
So how can you do anything but for
Perceive it as
White people should
What's the weather around 3
If if somebody's like
Stop
I don't I don't like you
Presenting it as a rational thought process
VSOP price
It is
Irrational
But that is how it like
If you pretend that human beings are not always irrational
Directions
Yes exactly
Play this clip
You sumbitches made a pretty solid argument over the last hundred episodes
Alex Jones is racist
Yes but unfortunately Ironclad argument I would thought
But I didn't know this
Text clip
Yeah I didn't know that
I might have to revise
Throwing up
Sure
Bunch of racist black people
But
Has anyone ever made an argument against their own argument
Non argue their position
Something cuz we would fight a bunch
Tough one of the fuc
Talking about. I don't care about the most
Hold on
Okay that's on it
But I wanted him in the hospital
Or whatever
Where else would you fight
Where is another Sonic Adventure
You know you're beating each other up and then you get a loaded
Tops nice sour cream on the top
I met him one night at the bar is very nice
Cool dude
Which one is the
Sonic commercial
When
History
Chicago Improv
When we look at like
Alex Jones is negative
Childhood
And how bad
Things were dealing with the reality
The idea that he fought a guy
And put them in the hospital then fought his uncle at a Sonic
But he's rattling it off as like normal
That's not normal
That's
Very weird
I grew up
Not everywhere
Existence in Central Missouri
Missouri
Why do some f*****-up dude
I used to people who are real wild
And if one of my friends was like
Beat up this guy put him in the hospital so now I got to go fight his uncle
You're crazy
Beetlejuice guy
What even
Negotiate where they were going to fight probably was there a want to go to a rally
I don't want a burger I want to get a Coney
I would prefer my home turf and Applebee's
Everybody has their
Everyone has their stuff
Is soccer
Cuz he's Americana and I love the drive-in
Harkens back to the wonderful days of the 50s when you and your special gal
So you can make out point after going to the drive-in
Come up to you and ask for your order Maybe
Flipper a finger
I don't know
Is it good old days
So I wouldn't say is anybody within hillbilly Circle
Then I don't like using that term but whatever
Country for help
Country folk growing up
Yeah
Would be wild
For my experience product I got to beat up the Skype uncle
Yeah
Also is that is that
I beat up this guy
Put him in a Hass
So now I
Have to
Beaded level one right angle is ostensibly the boss movie
The other thing I wanted I want to
Take from this
Is that
Is that the same guy he put in
Nakoma
Because you did that might not be the same guy
And then got food
So maybe he's put multiple people in the hospital and then fought their family members
Still further
Did you put them into the hospital
Like oh he had a stitch
Stitches Hospital
It doesn't sound like you got the
Splint on his hamburger
Any of this b******* real
It feels real
That does feel
Whatever you talk
It's so weird
Because he
Ketosis off so much nonsense
You know like that Hillary killed
Strange though he's like
Everybody we're late
It's to this what's the reason it feels real is
It's bragi
He loves to brag
But that's also why
Just believe it
Because every time you break through
It's gray
Yes I'm not sure but it's funny
Skip this next glucose just about have antifa started
We don't
To hear about this
This is something everybody know so the rest of the video pretty much is Alex Jones
Just reviewing Fox
Experience already
We don't have much more of it would just have one more clip
Then
Comes on and gives his
Of a gives his press
We're not going to listen to that but I do want to deal with it after this clip
Because this is
This is good
This is a
Maybe
Someone expressing something to Alex.
I'd like to say
People shooting on Saturday
It's just I love the resort
I just like the idea of you spending time you like people telling me to shut up.
Bread
Petards
I have
Come to
Deeply loved
The word
Lifespan is cock
It kind of
It's the same thing as fake news
Charter House
Turn off our back Thursday they're like
A little more mad about it
They're more mad about literally every
I sincerely don't care about being called Acora lip tard
Free funny
So what's funny is drunk
Search
Live press conference that he gave about
This distillation
If you guys did not hear it
Petition
Still need to listen to that
There's nothing
No idea the cries violin to bigotry on many side
On many sides
You repeat that twice
Right I saw it and I have yet
Not be
Angry but I didn't I didn't actually
Watch him say these words and cuz I've never
He's been
Percent he's taken office
I have never actively listen
Say a word
Exactly
But that's the point
I've never
Done it
Like I've read his words other people often
Posted it and done all this s***
I've never acted
Sibley said
I'm going to listen to what he has
Because he is
There's has nothing
Does everything
Sweet is a lie
It's made of
It's bulge
Like he has no words
Worth listening to
Is my mind
To listen to him
Even North Korea whenever he says
Oh I'm going to Nuke North Korea even there like
You don't
You say shut up Kim jong-un's emotion
No one should listen to any
He doesn't
I don't I don't disagree with you but at the same time is important to track
Back in many ways on many sides
As it were
Because
Hip Hop
Implies
That what he believes or what he would like to
Express
Mistakes were made on all sides as opposed to
Inspiration
Free murder and Heather
And brother was murdered
The reason that it's important that he
Stuck on Minis
Is you have
Have to think about how the white National
What's the Nazis are going to
That sort of thing
Of course so Andrew Anglin is the name of the guy who runs daily Stormer
His responses
His response to Trump's
Statement that there's trouble on many sides
Batman quotes
Trump's comments were good
He didn't attack us
He just said the nation should come together nothing specific against
He said that we need to study why people are so angry and implied there was hate on both sides
So he implied that Auntie far haters
There was virtually no counter signal no loss at all
He said he loves us all
Also refused to answer a question about white nationalists supporting
No condemnation at all
He just walked out of the room
Really really good
God bless
Why I would care
What do you mean I mean I don't care
If Trump
If Trump said
We hate white National
Who cares
No you don't
He doesn't he could have
Said f***
You could have said that
He is
10 ft tall
Just as much
As if he condemned it
It doesn't mean
It does
The I agree with you that there's a lot of lies ahead
But I think it does matter in this sense because of the apps
Subway
Should have said
You know what I mean like
It's beyond dog whistle to these
Nazis and white supremacist
Do not
The president of the United States
Specifically condemn their hate rhetoric
I have a condemned people filing
Not to condemn
People screaming bloody
Soil
Not to condemn
People
Outright
Being
Publicly
Thrilled to be members of
Of Nazi Oregon
Innovations
To not condemn
Someone who was involved with
Released
Wildly official capacity
Vanguard America directly murdering
Somebody
Is much bigger than anything you could have possibly said
Because it gives them
Tacit acceptance
It tells them
It's okay
In the same way that when David Duke was there
Are you saying
That this were fulfilling the promises of Donald Trump
It's white
I know
And I get that
And if we lived
If Trump was
Anybody else
I would agree with
But
War games
Right comes out
He says
We will not accept white Nash
Write what they were
Is there
Doesn't mean anything
Give me directions because he is
Supporting them
Regard
If you if you say I condemn white Nashua
And you have Jeff
Say we're not going to investigate whitener
Doesn't matter
Whatever it is
F****** says
Based on what he's done
He is supporting
I don't give a s*** if you can or not
He's f******
He's a liar
And he's already said that
We don't need any further proof
I agree
People are surprised at this that boggles my mind
White people cuz you have to imagine
Okay
So
Even worse
Right
Would be if he says
I condemn White
A person
Because then what happens in the Press
Probably gets congratulated
Yep
And he still supports White
Yeah but his daughter said
We don't have any place
It's for white National
Hey Google the fuc what
You piles of garbage
I agree with you
In a broad
But whatever the reason that I'm I'm still
Invite position
Is that
It's not really necessarily about what Trump says or doesn't say or does our dozen
Next to the
Fringe
Radical group
Sure
If you'd come out and said I can dab
Nationalist
The Nazis in this is
Atrocious
We are going to do every
Everything we can to
Make sure that these sorts of things never happen
Run again they could say he needed to do that cuz
The Jew media
Is on his tail or something like that
They could say that
They would say right but that doesn't matter
Has much as
He didn't
Say those things
And they don't have
They don't have
They got
What they wanted
They are
Accepted they are
Safe
In a lot of ways
It's like I'm trying to say
It's less about Trump
It's more about the fact that we now live in a world
Where
Our president doesn't
Stuff like this
And we live in a world where
These this group
I get to operate
In sunlight
They don't have to be afraid
I get you
And
This is it
This is again one of those things where they don't they don't have to stretch
In a vacuum
I agree
But if Obama came out and said while he was president
The Great
That wouldn't matter to them
That's interesting
Probably not
I think some of them probably would have been like Obama is a sleeper Patriot at that point
Lichen
Trump is a white National
He was before today
He will be
Tomorrow
He could have said
I will
Pee on the face of Richard Spencer
Doesn't matter
We know that
In the same way that Alex Jones
Conseil
I don't support
David Duke
It doesn't matter
Like we already lived in that world yes
We did
Because
Right
He didn't need to condemn white nationalism 2 days ago
No but no but the point isn't still did their b******* right
They were going to do it
They were going to do it tomorrow then
Today it doesn't matter what Trump says
They're going to keep doing
I agree that it doesn't matter necessarily what Trump says in terms of their Acts
I would argue
This organization
This
Protab
Castration
This Nazi Gathering as it were
Is a trial balloon
And sometimes
I don't think they necessarily
Look at the beginning of it it was planned we're going to run people over with a car
I don't think I think that's probably a game-time decision
And probably
Wasn't
A lot of the ugliest Lee the out-and-out bigotry
The screaming that we will not be replaced
As white people
With the Jews won't replace us
That sort of
Then that is
Kind of
Again a little heady
A little bit
Not dealing with
The fact that the reality is what it is but it's a trial balloon to see how
People react
It's a problem if you watch it
Acceptable where is the line
And what they learned
I believe what white nationalists and Nazis
The supreme authority the commander-in-chief of our country
He's not going to be all that bothered by the fact we did this s***
And
You going to actually say that the people who were trying to stand up against just as bad as
And I know
That your argument is sound
That
The key
Was that person
Three days ago week ago he was that person when he was being raised by his kkkk
I organized going to meetings father
Like that is
That's always been there
3 days ago we didn't have
A situation like this happen
And
Oh Dad not going to punish
Or something like that
Launch
And a lot of weight
And I think
That what we're going to see is more trial balloon
Because there's emboldened
Bolden
From the jump
But
There's concrete evidence
But nothing's going to be done
But
Maybe not as over
Not as
Extreme
I guess I guess my issue with this
Is that
This still doesn't matter
No
He's going to do any
You might as well
Might as well get off
I don't care
Bare minimum he got arrested
This is
I I don't
I don't think
This matter
I don't think it matter
If if it mattered
But if this was
Something important
Then you would have done something about guns after
Vision
Is Ben going
This ship will be going on
And it doesn't matter what
Matter after Ferguson what Obama
This s*** continues to go on
Until anybody
Do anybody actually f****** does
Goddamn thing about it
I don't even care what Obama says about Ferguson they didn't do anything about it
What are you going to
If you don't
Who the f***
Gives a s*** what you say
I get what you're saying
I agree
Okay well then we're done
I also agree with my position though.
I know and I understand and because this
This is a position that
I have heard
Continuously
Throughout
Is that
Symbolism
Isn't
And this is a symbolic
I don't
Daycare
I don't what does that mean
I I mean I don't think they cared when I don't think gun rights at the NRA didn't give a s*** whenever
Obama said that we shouldn't have any more Sandy Hooks
Give us Whenever there was that other mess
Or another mass shooting
Dylann roof
Murdered
They don't care about what the government says
Or what the presidency
Already got
Approval to do whatever they
And they've had it for the past
Goddamn here
I don't know what else
There is to say about
Who gives a f*** what the President says
Because nothing is f******
You changed
Yeah you're right
You're right
What is it going to get worse
Exactly anyone's going to get worse
Regardless of what he said today
Flower
Really
Do you do you really believe
Well the way I look at it essentially is
It's like a bunch of rebellious dumb children
Steal cookie
4 x 9
Maybe your sister is trying to stop you from stealing the cookie
On your break a jar
Or something like that
When you were trying to steal cookies
Which is against the rules
Your sister was trying
You are as the
Cookie stealer
The fact that you're the fact that you're both being punished or both being castigated because
Of what ended up happening
AB IV
Authority figure
It makes you feel like maybe stealing cookies isn't that big a deal maybe it's not going to be taken seriously around these parts anymore
Eva is a problem
Although I do 100% recognize what you're saying
Of course they already
Information
For a long time allowed to
Continue being a
The boy
I just and frankly I guess I guess
It's more just coming from my
Cynical definition
Like I'm more into
Just get it over with all the
If your murderous all
Then just f****** do it
Pic of
Like this nuclear war bulshit with North Korea
Do it I'm done
Of course
These guys are f******
Idiot
But the point is
That's why I have no issue with
Being discovered by the info Warriors
I have no issue with getting death
Tired of waiting
I'm tired of having to pull this b*******
It's 8 either do it or f****** don't do it
Before we get
Like
Entirely nihilistic
And the GOP has a gun to my head and I'm just saying do it or don't
They refuse to
You know what doesn't feel like having a gun to your
Going to knowledge by car
God I love her
Got buttons
Available on the website
You can buy button
Separately
Get yourself
The button
Listen
This first button is very bare-bones it's very simple but we'll have some
Real
Exciting stuff
Mayaro
It says knowledge fight with Jordan
Burien
Inappropriate
I'm very humble
You can also follow us at knowledge underscore fight
Controls that Twitter account so you won't be
On Facebook
You can find us at
Just add knowledge fight on there I listen to you and metrics and
I was really hoping that
Without me there you
But you did it
Did it there for life
Please
Tell everybody you know about us literally everybody
Literally everybody sooner or later they're going to find a way to Aurora
You can leave a review iTunes and help source
Who knows
Anyway
Glad you're back Jordan
It was nice it was
It's not nearly as insane as a casita
He's not tapped into how crazy all this s*** is
Replacement
You have been I've been quite willing to
It's freeing to just be able to have shorthanded dive into stuff than I appreciate it
But
We love you guys so very much Dan
Is there somebody
Are we never going to do that
It's about so I was Googling in trying to research this Elohim City stop
Exactly where a lot of these ideas about
Timothy McVeigh
Being a patsy came from
Alexandra Thurston color