Damn important
I have great respect for Tenaya Lodge babe I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Alex Jones
Jordan Jordan
My bright spot today is the Turning of a season that turning of the sea
Wrong or how everybody
Sure and it's getting a little chillier
Right maybe
I think it's a little chilly here in my apartment than it is even outside with ugly
That is true
But I don't mind
I like I run hot generally Sotomayor
The cool weather
In the past
The Cult
As always signified one thing for me
That cranberry splash Sierra Mist is right around the corner
I did not know that that was a cold base
Sierra Mist cranberry
I don't know I think it probably will be sometime like closer to December
I've realized there's a new thing that's been Incorporated
But it is an indication that I think I'm getting old
And that is I got
Excited as at the Walgreens and I saw that they had
The soft Werther's Originals
Candy apple
Variety
Excited that you get it goes.
Didn't immediately like give it to a child with a little piece of wisdom as you walked out
I'm eating them all
Games of all of them
There's a couple other flavors to that I may try there's a maple and a cinnamon
I want
That I may try there's also pumpkin but I'm not into that so
Considering they're clearly not
Original
The karbala
What exactly
I mean those you can call where there's originals but what do you call the maple one
Werther's innovative
Innovative Innovative I like that I don't know
It's great
Congratulation
Derivatives would be a little bit more
Yeah
Play can go three Mount Telegram
My partner and I have we've been on a fitness week
We've been no we've been exercising going to yoga class everyday doing the whole thing and
It feels good
Feel you know you sure like to exercise
Did you get your heart rate moving definitely yeah it is it is like there's
There's certain
Spots you know you I'm not like all I'm an old man I'm 30
There are certain spots in my body that are not Werther's original
Butler
Thereby many is 68
Like it's that kind of
That kind of situation
It's it's good and also very difficult
Do I do one of these with my shoulder hurts a lot
These are things that take a little bit of a hit
There's more where on that been on some of the other parts of the body
Well I forgot
That's good
I wish you the best that I don't know what that feels like at all no memory of motion
To Jordan today we have an episode to go over
I decided after our last step
Episode where we talked about Alex's weekend
Excursion
With a Robert Barnes
Where Barnes committed
The crimes I decided I wanted to put Alex on timeout I don't want it
Here's the thing you know we've been watching the trial as a
Progressed over the week and this week has been a lot of family
People telling
Moving and difficult stories of their
Hear their loved ones some some very heartening and bright stories about their lives
Eminem
Terrific
Tales of the abuse they suffered
I mean yeah it is
It is a
Emotional rollercoaster that is is like
So extreme you know you you see them cry and in with with smiling happy
Happy tears at the at these joyful memories and then you are and then it's it's just
Voice in pets
What are the things that I keep hearing a bit too like that just
I don't know maybe will haunt me
Is the
Consistency that you hear people
Describe one of the effects of the abuse that they get as like almost
The denial of their self
Do you know like yeah
Being asked
Are you related to this person who died at Sandy nope that's not me right y'all having to deny your sibling or
You know your child just for the sake of like I don't want to deal with
The possibility that they're one of those people who wants to yell at me
It's just
It's dark and
I am challenging I appreciate
That
These people are getting this opportunity
But
I don't
Waktu cover Alex
This stuff
Right now
You know like he did as bad of a
Thing is he
Could do on Saturday
I can't
Think of much more disrespect
That he could give
And
I don't want
To be at like we talked about this I don't want to be an Alex Jones Chris Hardwick show
Talking Alex
Mohican go on timeout
So we're going back to the past
Yeah I don't know if he could get worse but I don't think I'm interested in seeing him try
I will where we he did and he in Barns
Stepped
To cross that line
Last episode to a point where I'm like
Why aren't we all suing them as a
Country
As as a as a species
We should get
Together and like
Include talking rhesus monkeys because he probably defamed them to like we should be all sewage
Him and barns for what they did
Class-action human sonrisa
Yeah and I totally would not talk will not talk about like Alex at all
Trial progresses or anything or his present pay stub
It's too much
Yeah we can go sit over there
And we'll talk about the past
So we're going to talk about August
12 2003
Continuing or pass through 2003
It's just what the doctor ordered
It I don't want to say okay to say we got a bye
Right okay okay alright
Was
There are two things that happened
Aha that are just
Man there restorative
Okay alright if you're listening to Alex Jones stuff this is the kind of episode that you need
To be like
Oh you idiot
So I'm going to be able to provide that and I'll get to that in just one moment before we do
Let's say hello to the new Wok
Could you very much
I listened to your backlog on a drive from California to Minnesota and only made it through 10 episodes
Country
Conquest thank you so much
Thank you very much near and dear to my heart
Your
Yeah that sounds about right and I'm going to ride that
Snake around all the time
About to run
Spider-Man
Sucks going to get ostrich espresso
T-rob loves hot sauce thank you so much and I hope all is well
Next
The treasure Yeti
And Sidney Powell cheetah print cardigan thank you so much going on Iowa technocrat
Start until you're brilliant someone sodomite
Jesus Christ very much
Before we dive into this episode here's a fun out of context
Today Show
Just so happened
Just so happens if you wonder what kind of
Apropos of nothing I look like a potato
I look like a potato
It really is a non-sequitur that drives you insane
Is it reminds me of Lewis Black
If it weren't for the horse I never would have spent that year in college
I need so much more information than that
Well you'll get none.
So here is where we start Alex is in the mood where you want
Talk about big stories but a cat
Battenkill
Grenada
In their barracks
Iraq
Dying
World War
Governor of
And I know
Play the dark
Hercules
Kent Chevrolet
Okay
So I think it literally everyone knows that Arnold was a powerlifting guy that's what he is
Mr. universe
Also Arnold represent Austria
It's a small point
Different countries did you know that Dad
That's true Alex's nah
Also Arnold is not an atheist he's a very public
Catholic
You may remember that his daughter Katherine married Chris Pratt couple years back there was a bit of a public Reckoning with
The notion that. Only Pratt but also Arnold's daughter
We're pretty traditionalist Catholic vote remember that Arnold is married to Maria Shriver
Famously a member of the
The Kennedy family notable for the fact that JFK was the first Catholic President of the United States are is that
A mother Eunice was JFK's sister I also have no idea what kind of books
Books Arnold was right before 2003 but looking mostly bodybuilding Memoirs with checks out
I'm actually Alex does touch on this later that is what he's talking
About bodybuilding books
God is bodybuilders book
Weights as well as if I can Arnold tan we know this I guess
Come on so there's a really fun
Thread that goes throughout this entire episode that is like Alex there's so many big stories to cover but I do know I got it.
Talk about Arnold
I did
Is making really
Very
Put a part that he has to talk about Arnold Schwarzenegger
No
Okay
President
National
Police horse
Right
Dress
Arnold
Okay
Korean
A little bit in the shower
Well it looks like Alex is a bit off on his prediction there about Arnold haha like he was just governor of California for a bit
And now he makes videos with animals in his kitchen about Trump is bad news and how he loves
The people of Ukraine and the people of Russia yeah he seems like he's having a way better
2020 life
Another point
Alex is totally wrong about the etymology of Schwarzenegger
He's assuming that Schwartz
What's means black
Jack and the second half of his name well you can guess where Alex
Popular piece of incorrect information that was flying around at this time and Alex
Probably in a meme or some dumb blog and then just decided to pass it along
Who is audience of gospel
Do chit had stuff right there
In reality the name comes from his ancestors being from a place called Schwarzenegger
Which is in modern-day Austria
Does being black in this case and egg is derived from the word meaning Ridge
Schwarzenegger's name memes
Person from the Black Ridge
Here is Alex's stupid in most of the things that he says mean absolutely nothing
He's playing this kind of like
Expertise are like this
This depth of knowledge that he has really just like
It's nothing it's the confidence with which is delivered by absolute
Made-up nonsense then just
No matter how many times it happens there is a reason Khan
Men have confidence in the name like
Let's just rags
Like I don't even think Alex probably thinks this is dumb
Yeah of course
Because he never takes time to look into anything so
Is like 50% is
Is like
Well I did that
That's fair
Who got we are Arnold on the docket
Is very important
Yep that's running for governor
But Alex needs to take some calls
Because if you were if you remember on our last episode he was in Johnston at Miller's Studio it's we couldn't take
Call
So now we got to get to these calls
This is very important
I'm also movies are real
Call
Dory
Lumos
Sprint
If you want to come
We want to spend the night
Confirm
Abortion
Falcons
That's the way to disagree with you
I can't be like hey maybe you're just the wrong about stuff
Strawman
I'm I'm
I'm going to guess based upon the
Length of time he's drawing out
Call Me Maybe
The show isn't as busy today as he might have you believe so much she has to talk about like I'm starting to think
I think that maybe he doesn't have that much to talk about I really don't think I would be
Here's all the stuff he's not going to talk about today
I will talk about Arnold
Why not
Make
Smallpox
Showtime
No time
McDonald's
What if I call in and talk about this
Feel like he's drawing you out
Could be talking about it now in this space
Oregon
I've been called
Pneumonia
The UN organization
Quote no time
Sounds like you got a busy show is he can't talk about all this
Talking about what
When you're too
Over a5000
So
I'm talking about who put those spikes
To the bottom of that ravine
Play Mortal Kombat
Yes on the GLK
It's down there
Tow truck
All Alex's choice
What you cover if he's so mad that he's like
Arnold Schwarzenegger
He should have
Just like chosen to cover what he wants like
His audience is clearly captured in the sense that they are going to leave him if he decides not to cover celebrity stories
Explicitly believes
Are beneath him
They'd stick around whatever
Purely his choice
Something that he wants
Talk about
He wants to talk about this because it's easy
The pontificate about like celebrity type gossip style stories
Yeah and Egger is easier than
You know like what he just did there he's covering these stories for him right
It's touching the surface of it and what is story
So just touch on it and move on your above
I have to talk about Arnold Schwarzenegger but the people demand that I do it I mean
Love the idea I'd like in a tragic sense this is that that almost
Twilight Zone and you know like
The TV journalist who's always stuck talking about I don't want to talk about the cat stuck in the tree you know
I want to be a real journalist and then they capture the audience
So they can finally talk about what they want to talk
Talk about But realize that all they're capable of talking about
Is that cat suck
In the tree you don't like it the tragic situation and ultimately that is what they talked about today
Hello this is Alex's Black Mirror
So
I was actually with Arnold Schwarzenegger
It's called from a guy's been giving out a bunch of his tape
Now I know that we know from listening to Alex the show that the success rate
With those tape
90 + 40
Covid-19
Giving out hundreds of your cakes
50% of
The people are left
They just don't even
And they don't have any
Carmen
The second thing I do
That's true
Usher videos
Videos
Scared to death
And I think they're sitting on the parents they don't know
Okay your tongue is a little different now
We only need four
Like we're happy you that 90% happens first point those 50% aren't lethargy
They're polite
That's number one sleepy they don't have the energy to fight
Actually maybe there to fight you
They can take the test
Yeah
I noticed second things that Alex
Is doing here he's like those people aren't even in the game
I wonder if
Alex is 90%
Excludes people who just like don't even want to bother
This but I don't want to talk about it I want to fight you on this
Those people are removed then you're artificially creating these imaginary 90% by excluding all of
The people who don't even want to talk to you right right okay if you were saying
You know hanging out your mixtape
Trying to get people to listen to your demo 95% of people don't even want it don't even take
Right
But some people do ticket
And the one person who comes back to you eventually was like a man that was really good
That's 95% of the people that have listened to it
Probably so you got a 95% success rate
If two people take your tape
Right and we'll Boy 2 is too small it's good
But you've
Approached
1000 people
It's 50% success rate
I deducted right to be
Something like that
Surly reset the movies are real and film is real and all this stuff
And you wanted people to call in
And if they've seen if you see something
Say something Cena movie that tells me a secret about the
The globalist that I can
Can pretend to know about I need to hear about it right
Alex is mad about
Dynamic
Because
He has to watch
TV to get the
These messages
He doesn't want to watch it no fever
Exactly how they send message
He can't rely on the audience to constantly tell him everything
All these messages that they're speaking in the television
If Alex
Doesn't watch TV
Are they still sending out
Text message
Why hasn't Alex made this like
Real attempt
Tina like let's try and change the globalists behavior
Right so I won't watch TV or talk about TV or let my audience talk about TV and if they still
Want to get messages to me
They will have to send them through a different media
Well here's
Here's the actual answers that
It's not
Just messages that they're sending to Alex also like
You know
Demoralizing the public through the messages and stuff so
Even if Alex isn't watching the global has to have every reason to still do the same
Demoralizing
Bonus bonus game that we can f*** with Alex and demoralize a bunch of
Rising things which Alex experiment
Experiences as them taunting him gacha so there is that
That that two-way communication
Anyway we can talk more about that episode of Frasier that's a good
I want videos
Reading
Again
Call Peewee
Kerala house or whatever
Television
We talked about
And
We're building
Group
And
Is dangerous
Commercial
Dan
Everything must be made with my
Particular trigger warning
Alerted to me in advance he does frankly
Edo sound
A little Center
He sounds a little bit like he's triggered
Well look Alex hasn't seen this Frasier episode
He's just taking a little misrepresented
Details
Paul Joseph Watson interview on yesterday's show details
To create a better story out of
He has really basic plot points wrong like how it was Niall's not Fraser who got into guns
Importantly that it wasn't a gun club
He was at Niles and his dad went to a shooting range
The bigger aspect that I was really messing with this episode is that the shooting range and guns are treated as totally normal safe
And actually fun
Brazzers dad has a routine of going shooting at Niles is a stick-in-the-mud but after firing a gun he realizes that it's
Really enjoyable and not that scary
Nothing about guns are even an issue that the episode makes look bad
It's the p
People that he met at the shooting range of their weirdo New World Order dude and that wouldn't even really been a problem except
They were trying to get Niles to come to their compound in Idaho
Which is why Frasier's dad was worried in the first place
The compounded Idaho that's suspicious
Not the gun
Freezer is
Portraying guns as a legitimate way for a father and son to bond
Definitely that's like a real thing like I was to be fixated on that saying like look look the New World Order
Even the New World Order is like dieta for like fine recreational activity
What you want people to think guns are
I mean at best Maybe
Making a machine to fight the new world order it was in a basement
They were at the gun show and the dudes were looking at blueprints for a generator that they were going to need once the New World Order
Took over which is what clued Niles in
But he's shooting
Go to Idaho with them
Anyway the point is that Alex doesn't even watch
TV to find these evil hidden globalist messages
You just hear secondhand retellings of
Plots and then makes up stuff so we can ramble to his listeners about evil hidden globalist messages
That aren't real
Yeah they're not real
I mean I think what's funny is that now that you know back then if I saw that episode of be like yeah it's because those
Guys in Idaho
Be crazy you know that kind of thing
And now it's like I would run away from them
It just because their stories are really boring
They're just B they're made of
They don't think you weren't actually in the war
Whichever one you're pretending to be now you're imagining details into this episode of Frasier
Nice guys
Feature heavily in a Frasier episode now
Would have been a true prediction
So Alex takes takes another call
And this person also want
Wants to talk about his film and this is kind of frustrating
This point
Which would be your choice
Probably 911 Road
9/11 the road to tyranny
Police state
Tremendous
Your ear singing
Let's crepe
Maybe somebody wants
I thought you were the one
Oh my God
See you are still what's going on here
About how I got all these big things we got to talk about Arnold
Justify his like I've got to talk about this I would love to
Talk about these important issues but then the colors are going
He's frustrated that they are analyzing goddamnit
Back from break and his audience into telling about Artemis just
Little bit frustrated
Literally nobody wants to
What are you doing
The only thing I kept thinking I was going on was like well this
Pageant is not working
Play is just
Completely laid bare in front of everybody
Oh that's the fault of mine
Yep just delicious this is a fantastic tripping up the stairs and falling onto a Paisa
Situation
Alex has some other news not in my laundry list of things
This is true
Because it's not
Last week
Lion
Noticed
Bet your lawyer
This is that isn't true
That sounds that
That's such a great like
If This Were happening I be
Furious right now no I agree
I imagine this has something to do with there being some exceptions
If you're trying to witness tamper or like destroy evidence
You want to commit a murder with me later your attorney doesn't have to maintain privilege if there
They're trying to be involved in a crime with you
The crime-fraud
Provisions
Allow for that to be
Be breached fireman
Live for me I can't
Do that that mean I have to tell people that you said that
Sorry man you could just remove yourself as you can break the
I don't know
Anyway there's other news
Level four
Work
Smallpox
A level 4 in
This is why I'm saying you just
When are you list off the things
And also
What you just said is so not true
If I was actually thinks that level for labs are for weaponized things that explains a lot of his dumb ideas
But he's just making that up
The distinction between level three and four are the things that are studying level for labs are quote infectious agents
Toxins that pose a high risk
Have aerosol transmitted laboratory infections and life-threatening diseases for which no vaccine or therapy is available
Both use very high levels of safety protocols but understandably for things that are Aquino
Start even level forward they need
Greater controls
Smallpox and Ebola are absolutely not level three pathogens
Third studied in level for labs
I am in and I'm just going to throw this out there I'm the globalist
I'm trying to figure out where to put my weaponized
I'm not just going to give it a blanket late level
I'm not going to be like oh by the way
To the whole world in case you're wondering all of my level 4 Laboratories
That's where I weaponize thing
Take a swing at this Apple ID
Level five
Is there any of this it's all clandestine make it a secret level was a weaponized
Lab level
I wouldn't tell people about a secret
The slam dunk
Yeah
Do better
So look
There's another really fun thing that have
Office episode the first thing is that Arnold
Charade falling apart
Delightful
First hour of the show
Just what
Absolutely there's another really fun thing that happens
For the net
If eyeglass hours
I wish it's so different
Unfortunately
There's many semitism we got to get through on the way there
This is weird
Alex is upset that people are mad at The Passion of Christ still
Fisher
And he said something strange Hawkeye
Is the passionate person
Because
Corrupt
IC
Yeah
Not
It wasn't talking about Jews just the specific subset of Jews that don't agree with him
The setting off at ability for us to hate them for the rest of our lives I don't understand what that is
Problem there hahaha no big deal
What
No he just chooses to hate every juzt
Oh no now I'm getting it
Already about The Passion of the Christ and the the problems with it and Mel Gibson's dad
Problems with almond problems Holocaust
Denial and such and he still allowed to be in movies
The way I was just framing that there at the end
Is bizarre
Is
I I just I don't understand how these things can just they can come out of his mouth and he doesn't recognize what I'm saying
Cannot say that
Yeah there are things you can
Choose not
One more click before we get to the really fun thing and it's Alex reporting on a story that is not
Wonder Channel
Ford
Over in
And that's normal
Carnival
Sure would be
That's absolutely horrible
Scotland yard's diversity unit is going to come after you if you criticize an alleged show where they put
10 year olds in a house to have sex
I do appreciate that that is kind of the bread-and-butter of radio though there's a little bit of like
Did you hear this did you hear this in the news
I read recently don't quote me on this I read that somebody somewhere in some
Government said that they were going to replace the sugar in ice cream
With bird feces why did you believe this
Out of control
They brought him back
I will say though I recently went back
And I was watching
All of the egg
The Christie Poirot
And there was one where Paro and Colonel Hastings
Things were sitting around having a conversation
And Chief Inspector shop came in and he was just
Complaining, hard day of arresting people for crystallization
This is just
He's not Fred she is Belle dress
We get to this
Out of the guest
Naomi is really giving an interview and play
I wish man that be great
Yeah that would be great
It's a guy named Paul Revere
Not real name
Really quick
Alex Jones I'm not accepting bookings for people with aliases
No fear
Can't trust you come on man do Paul Revere more than somebody who changes
Is Dave de Paul Revere you're a liar
The pastor of sorts sure
And Alex recently heard him on another guy's show this guy named John Andre
Jose
A guy I think he has a voice of ministry or voice of
The truth is another show on Genesis what are those
Answer Paul Revere
Had some thoughts about Roman
What's 13
Now as we know Roma
113 is one of the things that
Christian
Folk like Alex are really mad about
Right because it's it's the scripture that
They think is
Going to be used by the new world order to
Convince everyone that Christians need to submit to Authority and right have you sold
They believe that this is a twisting of scripture on there
Very very upset about real mad about something in their butt
So this is what
Paul Revere's bread-and-butter is Alex to give an introduction
And then I have a fun
Story to tell you
Is
Minister
Romans 13
All orders of the government
Promoting
The new Bible
Getting off
About
Mister
About his comment
Put a pin in Alex's disagreement
About eschatology
Might come up later
I meant you know
You know if your book can just like
Edited
And then that's it
Then it wasn't that Holy of a book in the first place
You know
There are some
Arguments you can make on that front
I would rather focus on the fact that
You have
Priam post-trib Rapture ideas
And people who believe different things about that 10 to fight with each other real mad because Alex is not a pre-trip guy
You got to go through it
To do it
This
Might,
I want talk about Paul Revere okay
Alright here we go he was on John Anderson show talking about how
Yeah that's fine I don't care what is the scam that
Working that he doesn't bring up
At all on this show
I don't know if he thinks it's a scam I think he does not poke
Part of Paul Revere's philosophy is that you are a citizen of the country that you're born in
And when your reborn in Christ
You are now a citizen of Heaven
That's something I can go along with as a metaphor but I need to make it clear to you that Revere means this literally
Are you going to tell me that he is going to sell some sort of citizenship passes
He runs a church called the embassy of heaven and there's a reason
It's called the embassy he gives
These people pass
Exports to Heaven through his website
US Government document like a passport a driver's license to be a citizen of Heaven
Mutual Assurance which appears to be some kind of fake insurance
Alright also there's business licenses
It's creating an alternative government and just calling it happened
At least be like documents office of it yes
Appreciate that
Beyond selling fake official documents probably illegal
1 Civic information about the country of Heaven
For instance
He takes things that are mentioned in the Bible and then uses them as official symbols of the country
4 things
Okay that I'm going to ask you when you have to guess what they are okay
What is the national musical instrument of Heaven
Finish be able to get I mean
You know you could go with the liar
Right
Because it sounds too much like liar
I think there's probably a number of options on this could also go harp
That's not good
Draw people into your Embassy of Heaven everybody already thinks the harp
So it's a lot of trumpets in the Bible
What to eat
Be national animal
Of Heaven
No that's the national bird
National animal
That's enough
I think of you
Why is a bird at lion
No
Lamb of God
Breaking me shut up
Next one third Euro 42 so far
The national dance
The Lambada
Leaping for joy
The Dead Sea
Okay alright last one
Leaping for joy
National song of Heaven
What Okoye Ode to Joy
It'll be it'll be an interesting choice traditional
My Country Tis of Thee
Explain to me how that is
Possibly
First it doesn't even fit the pattern
My Country Tis of Thee America
And the dude who wrote it just stole the tune from God Save the Queen
Boy
This guy's got a website called the embassy of heaven and
It's
A lot
He has a whole section about his encounters with police
Is the type of
Something that you would experience a lot if this was your church
He's driving around 1 BC some cops
And so he pulls over it isn't after he'd gone to the post office cuz he had to do some official business
The
White guy
I think so I only seen a small picture of him
I would guess
So sweet
He goes down down the street
At the same time quit a city of Slaton police officer was traveling north on Center Street in
Recognize the embassy of Heaven vehicle
A SEPTA
After circling the block he realize that we were headed out of town toward the embassy
We were about three blocks ahead of him and he traveled at a high rate of speed to catch up with us
After leaving the city limits I turned onto the long driveway of our friends place
Quinn also entered the private property and turned on his overhead lights.
Pulled up behind us
I open my door and started to exit the car
Quinn stepped out of his car and yelled for me to remain in the car
Remain seated in the car and close the door on the radio I asked
How to handle the situation
She had no answer
We both realize that it has been five years since being stopped and I was pretty Rusty
Do unmarked cars arrive within bone
One of the persons in the first car was the chief of police
Clean approach this my side of the car and stood slightly behind me
He has to see my driver's license and registration
I asked if he was tape recording and he said he was not
Rather than answer his question I stated I am an ambassador of Jesus Christ for the kingdom of heaven
I'm using the highways in the Kingdom of Heaven in the performance of my official duties to evangelize the Kingdom of Heaven according to the Great
Commission
Alright sir I'm going to have to ask you to step out of
I declared my intent which showed I was operating under the highest Authority
And ignored my statement and repeated his question
May I see your driver's license
I want more I want more info about how he rates a chief of police stop as well
Like the chief of police is also in the call town or not actually that fair enough
I was not quite sure how to handle the situation
So I said that I needed some time to think about
Quinn said he would give me a few minutes and he returned to his car and talked with
The undercover people
If I was Paul Revere
I responded by saying yes I am Paul Revere
The moment
Paul Revere
Everything I've ever work for just paid off in that moment when the cop goes
Are you Paul Revere yes you better believe it's there for a third time
May I see your driver's license and registration
Probably a little bit slower this time I have responded I have documents at the embassy of Heaven that I also have document
If I give you these documents will you what will you do with them
I responded if if
It is those Church documents I will not recognize up
Okay well I guess that settles it
You're under arrest
Running to police
About this story because of the pulled over in the first place
Emily scroll down a little bit further and there's a section here and the title the section is
Heaven plates removed that's kind of what I was waiting for some sort of Heaven reason
Dude you a you lit your own lights up with handles that's not how cars work
He made his own Embassy of Heaven license plate switch is going to get you pulled over
I'm amazed you made it a couple years without getting pulled over
Yes I got it
Are you Paul Revere item at maybe there's like
Let him go
There's absolutely there's no doubt in my mind that he gets away with that just because the more you the more you bought
Bother him the more he's going to bother you again like more proof of his own persecution complex and
I don't know what you do all of these loads are fake and made up in her only enforce baster
Upon the willingness of the law to enforce itself upon us
Dad
You could just say no to the cop I wouldn't do it
Well they're having conversation
What's 13
Everything is going good
And Alex believes that these are smart smart people
You're both very intelligent men
Then what we hear
Hell yeah
Let's think
I don't
I'm thinking about some stuff
Yeah are you
I'm thinking about
Alright
Secure
We have this guy Paul Revere
Right and he's on with John Anderson that they're clearly associates they seem to like each other he's been on Anderson's
Paul Revere believes
That
The United States doesn't exist
Or at least
He's not beholden to any of these laws cuz he's a citizen of heaven and everybody's born
He doesn't really care too much
About
America
Right brother and founding fathers Constitution
And maybe this comes up
About Roman
The king version
Okay here's an example
Alex
Served
To the point
If I ask you
Father Fredo
Jefferson Georgia
Archaic
What if I name
Peter
John
Going in
When we read the Bible with the freak
These ideas
We come up with
Yeah man your small-minded thinking about America Nonono the country was founded by the apostles
That is such
Verbs of hooking Eckhart Tolle like
Giving a speech
Let me ask you a question
Who are your
3 best
Businessman
Oh yeah I'll tell you who mine are Jesus
Bryce
Himself
Okay alright bad alright okay
Yeah
Pretty good
So this is where things started to feel like
This could get
This could get messy
I'm not sure where this is going to go
Quicker than I imagined
It did get into ideas about the Rapture they are not on the same page
For just a moment
As far as
Eschatology or last night
Book of Revelation
The Jets be fulfilled
Paul Revere
So here's the thing to understand
This is not even an issue of post or pre-trib rapture
He's denying that the Rapture even happen
Because he's saying that the Book of Revelations was already fulfilled
Jesus is coming the entirety of of the
Is gone
Now we're now we're
We're waiting to get our passports
To get into the Coney Island of habit
Get a Gray's Papaya of Heaven
Yep
Alex can't handle this
The reasons that I really feel coming through strongly
Is that Alex
Needs
The devil
And
Yeah this will put to bed very officially whether or not Alex believes in a literal devil of 2003
I like it definitely does
And there is such an aversion on his part
To living in a world without the devil the devil
I mean once again reinforcing my belief that he is the actual Satan worship are you know based upon what he
Describe Satan worshipping people the noises they make are the noises he makes
Bullseye no
The way works
I think it's not worshipping the devil on Alex's bar
Just very weird somebody else's fault
We attract here
But
I heard about Roman
And
Grand Furniture
Nu Look
How do you say but hey
The government
Following orgasm
Look at that slave Bible
Twerking
BigCharts
My Bible says
They're not disputing that really right
There's still bad it's just bad people who doing bad things
Who are outside of this Kingdom of Heaven that exist on Earth
Like they're still like an obligation to be a good person and be opposed to bad things
Apple doesn't go away if Romans I mean yeah
It's interesting and then Alex is trying to twist it
Now to be the poster
Pre-trip
Ikea there without these churches that are saying that
We're at we're taking out to get that's not with these guys are
Trailer difference
This is the type of s*** that makes me want to like really get people to understand why Christian Nash
Nationalism is bad
You know like phone
You say you want a Christian Nation
But are you a futurist interpreter is do you know like what are we what are we doing here because you do
Don't f****** know what Christianity f****** is the breakdowns of like
Really really aggressive disagreements
Same thing with like alright I want
Statehood and state sovereignty
Well now I don't know if I want that
Oh I didn't think about how this could go wrong
Inconsequential
Yeah
But yeah it's
Just I think that Alex has an idea
Of how things operate in the way here
Mythology and the cosmos to him
It requires
Cosmic
Evil
It requires
The bad guys on his side not
Be bad people doing bad things
People who are parts of bad systems or neutral
It has to be
Something of this
Mythological Good vs Evil struggle
You can really decide that's what I feel coming through and I in his opposition
Problem
Because
Calling Christians
And we are
I was just confusing himself
Yeah
Cuz if they're not
Saying you shouldn't talk about
Or talk out about any of those things
Maybe the New World Order isn't the devil
Right right
I think I mean like
We ghetto
Deep down
My fear my feeling on it is
Alex finds it very very
Comforting
To think that there are people
That can override
You know what I'm saying so like
No matter what
At the end of the day you've got a I don't need to take responsibility for my actions card
You know what I'm saying like that's why the Devil exist is because
At the end of the day
I am in there
You know sway I'm just part of their little struggle or whatever it is you know sure you don't have to look at
Myself in the mirror and say I'm responsible for every single thing I've ever done I'm in the arena but it's there
Are Arena
I think there's something to that
And then I also think
That because Alex is so obsessed with this idea of this tyrannical One World Government
It's the entire world
Alright what's above the world while it's got to be causing it
What president of the world is a human
So then there's the other aspect to that I think
That is narcissism
And that is
Alex sees himself as such
The Conquering Hero
He must be up against the great evil in the entire universe
Hubris
The thinks he can actually defeat
With Depo
And I think it'll be unsatisfying for him to just
Be like
Somebody who's like okay I see a problem I'm going to work towards an actual solution to it
Yeah okay yeah you
Denovo
You rebuilt someone's house after a natural disaster or something will they fight somebody
I mean there's Livia devils
22 like
Sort of ba
Part of working
Towards helping and solving real issues it is gratifying to imagine
Everything you do whether it is
Productive or a mistake
Or stupid
All of those things are
Part or you're misinterpreting a Frasier episode there is that all of that is
Fighting the
F****** devil
Grandiose way to live your life
And I
Imagine
Empty
I'm with with that kind of narcissism you know if the devil is his nemesis
It's not as archenemy
You know like the arch enemy you would be fine defeating Nemesis you would feel exactly
If you defeated you
He be like grey we defeated
Damn you know like we got him
But if he defeats the Devil he's like well then who's going to push
You know who's going to make me more holy
That kind of feeling it does not
That's not nice.
And also there isn't a second
Imaginary
I don't know
This
This aspect will come up more later this absence of the devil in their world you and how's this is like
Incompatible
But
The not liking America thing
Is
Great
This is so fun here we go
Where do you stand man
Because
Well it's real simple
Alex
If you take a look
Jesus
Ritchie producer
Bad seed
I don't like
Bad bad cannot
Produce
Good
Gregor Mendel with music
What did
Stage the people
Fathers of the
America
Where did these people
Majority of them were.
Can I come from Pat
And he elaborates on that here
They came from England
The teenager who had grown up in
I want
Piece of the action
I don't want the mother
Country rulers we want to rule ourselves
That's really work
Came from
Eating their own skin
They were fighting
But they wanted they wanted to be a teenager that grow up
Did it come out
Come out of
The kingdom of God
Possibly have
It came out of
The world
And they even in their own declaration
Declared
We take equals
Powers of the Earth
How we don't know that
Come on
Paul Revere
You're even nine.
Wouldn't
We wouldn't exist
They did it
He did
In fact at one point
Candidate even made
Man
Troy the whole world
Ghetto Barbie worshiping that guy
Real quick real quick
You said your God was like all I should have killed everybody I don't want to work with that guy
Wow I mean he does make a good point to Alex's you know it's over bottle
Yeah apparently too obviously
If you could understand anything about what these people actually believe
You would know that they
Can't possibly be in favor
Of the United States
The founding document
The founding fathers
All of that stuff
Here's what's interesting about this
A lot of the beliefs that you have
Could still overlap
According to Alex so many of these things that are in the Constitution
The tution are actually god-given right
That's so they preclude or are they predict the brat the Constitution
Those are things that the government cannot
Do to you as opposed to write that they give you
So coincidentally
He believes by Paul Revere and John Anderson both are like
Everybody should have all the guns
They could still believe that with or without a belief in the Constitution
Rye Rye
But
I don't think Alex would ever let the conversation get there
Because
It's so much
He means the Constitution
In the same way that he needs the devil
Memes that in order to
Have his god-given right or whatever
He doesn't actually care about the cons
Institutional cares about that
D of the Constitution that he's created like he doesn't like all of the Constitution and if he answers
Scratch him out of a couple of
It is if stupid stupid conversation whenever he's like
The Constitution is inviolate
I mean I would get rid of this amendment I would get rid of this part I don't want to deal with this freedom of religion get that out of here also
Outlaw the Democratic party you and okay so why are you arguing with him about whether or not the founding fathers were
Hundred percent right about everything cuz he's doing
Do so stupid so look there's no devil
But
What do you mean do you know that
Okay there's no devil
Why do people worship the
That is according to
Scripture.
Why did the world leaders
I want to talk about
5 years of my life
Nonsense
I came but the truth
Chrysler January 9th
70 nights
Alex
Spectre Channel
People have a lot of
I found myself in a very bizarre position where
I am laughing my ass off
Paul Revere believing that he's a citizen of the kingdom of heaven and laws don't apply
But he and John Anderson make a lot more sense than Alex in this interview I know I really
Do I really do want to fight him I really do want to throw a rock out face while so people talk to him
Hey listen
I've seen people do all kinds of weird s*** like fruits
One time I got pulled over by a cop
Cuz I believe it's some weird stuff I started talking to him to be fair this is John talking
Anyways
Vivi
The question
If the devil doesn't exist why do people worship Him and the interbeing
People do a lot of weird s***
Is like well I don't have a rebuttal to that that is true
You do a lot of weird s*** God dammit
I'm pretty sure that if I knew more about
Either Paul Revere or John Anderson would not think they come off as rational at all and obviously
Even just from this website I don't think Paul's got a good head on his shoulders
B
Alex cannot handle very basic things with John Anderson is throwing at him
Yeah it's
Pretty not good
But
John
That he used to be involved in the occult
And this is going to be good way for Alex to try and be like maybe you are the Dead
Oh no they can't bond over his previous being in the occult
Maybe is just like her back right now
Are you into
Involved in love
Call Linda
We believe the base
Ecclesia
The great white Brotherhood
What
Predictions
Georgia
Call a lucky guesser
Damn
Alexina understand that the point of this story is
I no longer believe I was psychic
Alex you realize the point of this story is that I am telling you I am not actually psychic
I do not have the powers of a psychic I believe that back then
Didn't do it
The thing I said I died
Didn't I wasn't a psychic
So
Again
That's delightful Alex who lies about his predictions
Order to appear prophetic in driveways right I didn't look into this so I don't know John Anderson actually did make his money
He did
She's disowning it as
Some kind of a
Like feet of His Brilliant oh yeah as a lucky guess
Kind of like
It's refreshing supposition to Alex
Although I'm sure John Anderson is
Play Wildwood
No Doubt
Hades it is fantastic
Did you tell Larry Flynt
What's going on here
I don't know what I don't know what time
It does feel like maybe we're in different
Like spots of the like on about your predictions like he's like
I do know that was my old Griff
Like maybe Alex we see him in 10 years on somebody else's show like Adam prediction anymore
I used to lie about you know like where are we in this grip
This guy probably isn't saying that it was a lie that it was some kind of a psychic prediction MIDI
Felt like it to him then
But he got lucky really
If you think
I would see it that way disowning necessarily the fact that he did say this and it
It came true
Just if there's any meaning to it
No Lie
No
I mean
Did he get paid for it
Who made the national news
So look
There's another problem that Alex has was that all right
Fine
Is this all happened in the past
Why isn't the devil in a cage
Troydan
He would do
He overcame
Okay first of all your daughter revelation
20 and your
Taking the
+ 1
Circles
It's almost like we're both walking in mud
Going on that you're arguing about imaginary dog sheds
That is very silly
Are we just keep going back and forth cuz there's no way to settle this argument based upon made-up nonsense from thousands of years
I would I would say I don't want to believe it either of these people's ideas
Sad
Forced to choose between the two and we grade on a curve because this is Alice
You know Alex you know all the s*** that he believes
Good person comes off looking pretty good just
Based on not being the
A wild liar on the lake in his passports idea
Ringo also somewhere
All things
Being equal
I'll take a world where there isn't it
The devil running
As opposed to one where there is
Answer already John's idea in his world is far more appealing
It seems bizarre to wants to hold onto the idea that there is a devil
Yeah but unless you need it
It does it does seem like something he needs
That he absolutely could never be able to
To process
And I can understand a like he can't understand
No I don't want
The Devil Inside know you do
You do
But you can't process
But you just can't understand it
Deal with the idea that they're the devil's dead
Zuckerberg
It's not what I'm
Scriptures
Teaches the problem is
Really good
Christians don't have a clue
Okay
Hebrews 2:14
Portsmouth Spanish the children are protected
Play Sheboygan
For Christ
Destroy him that had the power of death
Did he
Walkabout
Is this an immigration hearing for the heaven country what's happening
Before the courts of Heaven before the courts of Heaven shows
Yeah I wonder if they're integrated those courts are part of the empathy of had a right
Notarized
All of the documentation to get into heaven
These are not notarized on argument
There have to be a notary
Not public Define notary Devine
Why do I know which is third search
Is great
Alex has no rebuttal to this because it is
Okay
Scripture tells us
Did you fail
Right
He's he's introduced the thing into a religious argument that you just can't
Can't do which is a yes or no question about Uptown question cannot happen in a religious argument
You answer yet
Screwed your position and answers
The only way to answer that question is to not answer the
But it's bizarre that I mean like at this point in his career
It's so weird that I like
Looks just like
Does this
Yeah like
He doesn't hang up on them he doesn't
End the interview he just gets kind of
Petty and childlike a little like
I don't know yeah
The lawyer trick
Or something
And I think
There is a desire
That he has to be seen as strong
In these settings
To his listeners
This looks very weak
Right he doesn't come off like somebody who can defend his position
Yeah
He reminds me I mean this is fairly early on liking this reminds me a little bit of those early debate Bros
Online
The twitch platforms or whatever the the debate brothers who would go in there with a
Freshman-level philosophy
Audit
To their name and and like
Just try and argue with people about religion for a while and it didn't matter if they're
Obviously stupid argue
It's look stupid they just
Clowned on them or
The stand-ups who were like pretty early on wanting to tangle with hecklers or something you know like man
There is a there's a desire to like
Appear
Above or like having like
Like stood up
2 something medium destroys Heckler like
In order to
Counter the things that this guy believes
You need to personal understand what he believes
And then second you're going to need to unpack this entire idea of Heaven being the country
And you don't want to do that
No cuz it's way too complicated
Your audience is going to you're going to lose some of them
You're going to reveal the
Those are the sorts of people you're going to take seriously on your show
And that kind of
I don't know
Demand the entire show
Yeah and I think if you're interviewing and taking seriously a guy who calls himself Paul Revere
Embassy of heaven and sells fraudulent documents to people like passports
You kind of
Take yourself that seriously and you would need to reveal that in order to actually have the Conn
Conversation that Alex is wanting to have
And
Yeah you just stuck in the end because of that you just has John Anderson ask him these
Crap questions
That's why I that's why I later on he's like I'm not doing that anymore I will hang up
Are you if you challenge me
So weirdly later on as the Tea Party grew
Revere would come back up
As somebody who
Work for FEMA
Paul Revere works for FEMA he was he was like
The pastor that was recruited by FEMA
In order to get them to preach Romans 13 how am I going to everybody
Mysteriously isn't in his backstory here I would have to assume based on
His lack of
Any
Documents
Clearly Froedtert
I don't think
FEMA's going to be
It recruiting him into any
Kind of Pastor initiative I'm interested to know about a conversation that happened what meeting room did it have
Happen where they're like man
We cannot find anybody to preach the correct interpretation of Romans 13 and our Felix
Nobody will do it
There's nobody that we can get
To preach
Romans 13 as a means of submitting to the FEMA camp
A guy who's made his entire career preaching the opposite of it and selling people fake passports
Yep
Yep yep
One passport if you want to enter my land
Two passports if you want to enter by sea
Show me one last clip here
Outsourcing
Program and I.
Is big news
Big news so we have all those stories that Alex didn't cover price
I want to talk about Arnold's
How do you spends like over an hour talking with these dudes because the real big news apparently is that Romans
13 is been twisted
Yeah
What that is
That is a curveball it is but there's one thing that's important to remember that
You're not
This is not a religious show is not a religious show
Over an hour talking to a weirdo Pastor who calls himself Paul Revere bleezy
Head of the embassy of Heaven
Yeah
But it's not a religion
Touches on religious
Topix
Okay from
Time to time
Has transformed the mythology of
The United States into its own smaller version of Christianity itself
That's making my belief in the country of religion
Along with my belief in this state is a religion
Along with my believe in this house being really like he's a religious man
This this is not a religious show
All right we will spend
Over an hour discussing religious stuff for me to cling to my belief in the devil
And then
Here's what you don't understand
This affects
It it made me laugh
In the literal definition of the word
Yeah
And I think it was a nice reprieve as it were from present a b*******
This smell good
Little bit of maybe that shoulders feeling a little looser now Georgia
If you were watching
Alex's trial Indiana
Do you know
Thinking that he's onto something
Remember that his career is meaningless
Lake Jordan will be back probably check back in on the present day on Monday
Perhaps
Yeah
But until then indeed we do it is now
We're also on Twitter
Dzx Clark I am Wilfred Snapple Snapple of the Gravel Pit Bull
And now here comes
The sex robot