Damn important swetik
I have great respect for knowledge B. I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
Need money
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Acknowledge
Worship at the altar of Selena little bit about Alex
Jules Jordan
What's up
Furious Furious spot
Nobody tell me
That guy
Here's a couple years ago alright alright
There was a movie version of the color out of space
Not my favorite HP Lovecraft story but it is a a lovecraftian tale okay
Nicolas Cage
Play what's it called
The Colorado
How is it called that
Webkinz lamb the story I know that but I mean like I feel like if it was the name of an HP Lovecraft property
I would have at least known it existed
You mean like the story itself one of the better
Lovecraft stories
All things
Inconsiderate
Nicolas Cage
Starring in a weird craft movie did you see it no
No one told me
I mean
Look
Clearly
Dicey in their own ways
A match made in regular space
Yes
Strike me as a
Is an arena where cage could really tee-off
Make a really bizarre performance
Cuz like you know all look nice in protagonist or sexually losing their mind
I'm going crazy to play
Yeah especially as time goes on they don't get better and not like a uplifting tale I'm sure it sucks
Good movies bad but I'm going to watch Adventureland on Madden 12
Anyway what's your spot is my partner and I we finally got into succession
That HBO show about the rich people
Battling Nicolas Cage
That'd be great I've heard a lot about that
I thought it said I think what's interesting about it is they're trying a thing I'm going to do like
Play if you think about the office
It's that kind of workplace
Please, do you know what's what's fun about it is that you have paid those for all the
The awkward situations only like affect you because you're like I care about that person
Like they're playing is
Game of Auntie pesos where you're really here like
You watch something terrible happening to your like
That's pretty funny
All right you know but they're not falling down and said they're like losing money
Okay you know what I'm saying it's good clean fun
Volume
It's like all he lost a million dollars I f*** you
But I'm glad you're enjoying it
So Jordan today we have a situation that may lead to someone else losing
Million or so dollars or
Talking about the end of last week Thursday and Friday September 29th and 3rd
30th 2022
Sure
Man
Big something big happened
On Thursday
It's it's it's not he's at he is a lunatic
I don't know why
I can build this up
A hundred times over and it is still unbelievable vampire
Amanda Friday
That is what it is
It's a little bigoted but hate look Thursday wouldn't be enough to talk about so
Attack on Friday
Monumental Monumental thing happens and then it's just a waste line
I want
I want to f****** AAA Jimmy Kimmel to walk out me like less
We got one really good guessing that we had to pad out the show I'm sorry I look tonight
You know it and I know it
I feel
I don't know why you're so surprised I feel like I've said this many times before like
Most important surprise I enjoy it
Before we do Jordan let's say hello to the new one
The first Jordans
Play the show you how far back we are
Not great
So next to Becky I told you I would make you a supporter three exclamation points in a policy wonk
Text Mark Moran PhD
Congrats the Hunter and his fiance Stacey on there earlier
October nuptials
That message was sent
Do you have game to the systems perfectly okay
Next Rick Deckard and general veers love Kylie Minogue
Thank you very much next roast beef with Anthony Hopkins
Thank you very much
Jordin so get well soon as you are
Recovering from surgery
Like this much
You and I are attacked
I have
Risen above
Go take a little break you down
A little breaking for me
And then we're going to
Comeback
And I'm going to start the show over
F*** you
At the end of the day
F*** you and your new world order
And f****** horse you rode in on
All your s***
Maybe today
Check out of here tomorrow
And you never see me again
I never want to come back
Apologize
Yesterday that I
Was legitimately having break
Bounce on air
Better tomorrow he's not
Bono's real bad
So Jordan restart off on the Thursday show
Responding to
Some of the big news of the day obviously hurricane Ian
What is an implied right and also Kamala Harris
Made some
Mistake
Images of shark swimming down the highways
Water flooding into the second
Floor
Hotels is
Dramatic
We will be
Going over
Eventbrite
In Florida and then looking at
Like The View
Saying that this happened because the Santos was elected
Now do you think that idiocy
Cannot be taught
Kamala Harris
Not.
Later on
Set of
Dementia
Complete
Puppet
Has come out
I said that the United States relationship
With an alliance
Republic of North Korea
We are currently
War with North Korea
Since the armistice
The ceasefire
Back in the nineteen
50s
Are we still at war with North Korea
Congratulations you just learned something I'm not sure if anyone
In the world let alone The View are blaming DeSantis for the hurricane
If you want to hear something crazy
Go back in time and listen to what dr. James Dobson thinks about what year was Hurricane Alex actually plays the clip
Map of The View later they're just
Saying that
He doesn't believe in climate change right Auntie is the governor of a state
It's just a b track hurricane not mean that he's blaming
Now he's being blamed
For it now
I wouldn't be too surprised it too it's like people were curious because going to continue kidnapping emigrants and stranding them in various parts
Parts of the country to own the libs during the storm or if you would wait until it it
To do another publicity
We stopped at Mox
Human rights
It's fun at all to point out that the Harris misspoke in his speech and I'm glad Alex can have fun pretending it was a sincere
Statement
I would just like to remind everyone how pumped Alex was when Trump went to North Korea and prowled around with Kim Jeong Hoon
House didn't seem to have a problem with Trump when he's
This about Kim Jeong Hoon at O'Reilly in 2018
Quote we went back and forth
When we fell in love
He wrote me beautiful letters and they were great letters we fell in love
Yep
I remember that
Every time you think about those years that 2016 to 2020 and people tell you a thing that happened in Hugo
No it did this is maybe just maybe complete bulshit manufacture
Outrage on Alex's part about this
It is a really easy strawman for him to tee off against which is easier than him trying
How to do his actual job
I'm better off for him
I mean
She was in the DMZ three misspoke
I made it sucks yeah you'd rather someone not make a mistake but pretending that she actually thinks we're in a f****** alliance with no
North Korea's meticulous
Ed
Is it that
That's absurd
I don't even know how to begin to like
Oh man look at that idiot I mean that's too obvious
Yeah man we're in alliance against the death robots from
Times that I could waste our time with like Alex misspoke
And like I just
I would feel bad
The level of Lake
Point that you're making
Early days he had that clip that he would play that bad
Nancy Pelosi Miss speaking like a like a ray of stuff you could do that in a heartbeat
4 hours
I just like I hear it
Say stuff it's like oh I know what he meant he just said the wrong thing
Bright and I don't even cut those clips
What is the time
Zacks wasting time
Grayson Arts
Has big news also of
Non misspeaking
Types and that is pipeline news
That's happening every front now with the Nordstrom one and Nordstrom
To pipeline
Confirm to be attacked
Western control sectors Russian government
We sang
The I even had
Rusev
Ion
Commodus Russian anthem
Russian
Peter Gracie analysis
Clear
The New World Order blew up
Looks like northstream to they're saying can never be repaired
Economically to Europe will be Beyond devastating
It'll be felt here in a big way
Joel skousen doesn't like Russia that is true but he's also cripplingly addicted to calling everything that happens in the world
False flag so I really don't see how this is a meaning.
From Alex
We're from scouts and it's exactly what you would expect
Now the situation with the pipelines is an interesting one and it's something to keep an eye on but it would be unwise to fully jump to
Conclusion about it immediately
Which is what Alex and skousen
Clearly.
And always
There were three leaks which were clearly not the product of an accident or coincidence
The odds of three independent incidents happening around the same time or astronomical so it's just
You know it it's not just Russia but saying
Probably isn't intentional act and NATO are also saying
Wow I mean one of the
Leaks was in the shape of
The Batman logo
Rapoport
It was done by someone for some reason
But it's not really clear right now who it was or why
Most people think it was Russia for a number of
The first is that they have the capability and
Capacity to do it from a technological
Call Stan point
The second is that they would lose essentially nothing
And given that their oil companies are sanctioned in these pipelines are all but shut down curve
The third is that
Kind of gesture would send a strong message to the whole of Europe that they're not going to be getting Russia's oil in the future
Even if the war ends there at the mercy of Russia's energy
Bee supplies
This is in line with act that Russia has carried out in the past using energy as a tool to apply pressure on Europe
To sway policy
Give me a minute this isn't going to make things that much worse it all per Europe in terms of energy supplies
Nordstream2 was never open so it doesn't really factor into things
Russia cut off Nordstrom lawn over the course of the war
Can you cry
This is more of an omen than anything else in there were very few parties you could imagine having a reason to do this
Other than Rush
Right right it is possible that this is the result of a wild coincidence
Or even a rogue actor that we haven't identified could be behind it but
The smart money
It's pretty clear well I will say that
My bachelor party got out of control and so we went
And I know
Sometimes you're you're out you're having a nice little walk with your buddies you see a pipeline
You're like I got to pee and then you poke at it cuz you're just f****** around and then bam
Sometimes your friends are like let's go to the strip club and it's sometimes friends are like let's go to the casino
Standard
Strip clubs name was pipeline
Plot of Hangover for I believe
Global global relations
But here's the problem like when
Start thinking about things being
False Flags
By the way Alex and skousen
From a neutral perspective you would have a hard time figuring out why the us or NATO would want to do
Something like a taxi pipeline
There really isn't a reason for them to do it
But Russia does have some potential reasons to
Carry this out
And now if you
You're addicted to false Flags you found a reason for the US tornado to do it
They have no reason to do it but Russia does and now they have a reason
Which is the frame Russia
This is tortured reasoning and it's based on Alex
Thousands intense hatred of our government because they think it's controlled by evil communist globalist
You know did they
And into these pretzels in order to create motive out of absence of motive
They create motive for party a even though party B has more poker
Just that it's torture
I made for their there they're like all argument for the globalist
This is like essentially cui Bono you know just like
Follow the money and it's like well the money points to Russia
That's how you know that it wasn't that because
Is benefiting Russia to trick them into thinking that
Classic
Maybe don did it
Somebody did it
So why Biden
Also sucks
And everyone wants you to eat bugs
And we have a president
The month ago
Look like he had
Leave
Second phase
Planet Nissan
But don't worry he's got control of nuclear weapons
This is where we live this is what's happening
And now there are
Government
In the UK
Australia Germany
And now the US government
Is promising to put bugs in the schoolchildren food oh
You don't want to bug as an adult was a child you'll be made to eat it
Sheraton or the shell
There there there there there
Shell
The
Bob
Extremely toxic
Extremely bad for you and causes liver failure
Amongst all the other wonderful things
There's a Washington Post insects a nutritious ingredients
Rolled out
Eat the bugs UK school children fed insects to encourage
Nobility is for the Earth
Has bugs and insects
Horsefeathers children
1000 Australian Public Schools
The article that Alex's siding with the headline insect
What's a nutritious ingredient for school lunches is from the washer
Canton post
But it's also from May 13th 2013 so close
It also ends with a?
It's just a write-up about a report released by the UN food and agriculture organization that looked at Edible insects around the world
World and what potential existed from exploring insect agriculture
It wasn't about feeding kids
The bugs a large portion of it is about raising bugs
To use as feed for livestock but as a headline
Provide a decade ago and he's using it to make s*** up to freak out izadi
Yeah
The headline about u.k. school children is from a May 2022 article on Breitbart that Miss reports on a study that
Researchers were carrying out
To see if primary school children would change their opinions on alternative proteins
If they were given
Accurate information
About them
No one's being forced to eat bugs
Isn't there School lunch
What if we didn't lie to children
The wef headline Alex reads is even weaker
This is a newspunch article just trying to report to Their audience the class guava wfr tricking kids in Australia
Schools that enforce feeding them bugs
You can hear how Alex is reporting this story which is how the article wants the reader to experience
In the real world what's happened is that there's a brand of chips and snacks called
Circle Harvey
And they use Cricket protein
In there
It's very prominently displayed on the packaging with the name of the product being
Cricket
Chips
Circle Harvest has been holding presentations at school since 2000
7 about their intake protein business and their insect farming which
Weirdly is only now becoming an issue for Alex and all these other idiots on the right
This year they began selling their corn chips as an option in about 1,000 Australian schools at the canteen
Two kids want to eat them
Cam
They don't have to
Start a product they can choose to buy or not like Doritos
Sortino's
Feels to me like Alex is afraid of losing to bugs on the free market
You know
I just wish it's I think it's time I think we're grown-up enough
For everybody to just like come out be like listen
Eventually we're eating bug
Climate changes destroyed your food supply you f***** up
We've got nothing
But there's a lot of bugs
Just deal with it and also like
I mean not for nothing
A lot of these particles you can find make a point
You're already
Just based on how processing works
How big agriculture works
How
Packaging works
There are
Regulations in place yet but their regulations that are like
Sorry, few but
It lives under the water a lot of stuff is culturally dictated please taboos and what have you
Bug you're going
Now as far as keratin goes Alex's confusing the bug related form of that and
Keratin
That's what prior is a food source
It's not toxic but the latter is a
The cosmological
Treatment that uses
The cream containing formaldehyde
Which can be toxic
60 people
Her cause negative
It's not the Keratin itself it's toxic it's the formaldehyde cream that's being used to treat
Human keratin like
A person's hair
There's been a lot of misinformation flying around about chitin
The polysaccharide founded bug exoskeleton
It's mostly about how it's undigested bull by humans and talk
It's not toxic but it is true that chitin
And itself may not be
Be fully digestible
What's so cellular
Switch doesn't stop people from eating celery
You can still get nutritional value out of eating something that contains parts that can't be fully digested and then you just passed those parts
It's actually good
For you like how people need fiber
Just a regular
Yeah what would you rather like have to swallow Rock
And have
Them like deal with the food inside you and then
Speed up the Rock's like
Depends on if crazy right-wing people got into rocks
Yeah it's kind of hilarious to me they were in 2022 is becoming a core part of some people's identity and political ideology
They're mad about the idea of
Bugs being edible
Ridiculous
Children
You're going to eat
You're just gonna
Whip whip
Is it in 20 minutes you only bug
Y'all. Lamented diets to the pills
And we'll just have two or three pills and will
Bring it to me
I will say though that
I'm a picky
You are and I don't eat fish now right
I'm opposed to eating bugs for a completely different reason
Mostly just eat chicken
Looking down the barrel of a bug
You're going to you're going to have different feelings
I guess actually if you
Just ground up bugs
And stuff like that the cricket is used in cricket corn chips
Flour substitute
Yeah I just feel like
I think the problem is
Give the problem is you can't
Like
For most people psychologically it's a difficult thing to get over the idea of
Eating a bug
So the knowledge of eating the bug will influence the taste that you are experienced roof
When you're eating like a whole bug
Of course that's not great not appealing to
What if you were just to bite a chicken
Look like
It would believe you
That would be on Advertising to
Sure
Prosthetic lie like a real bunch of
Cockroaches are the table there like a high these have been
Butchered correctly
That's true
PewDiePie
That's coming that is what they listen you're going to eat bugs you're going to have tiny hands
That's what's going to happen
Evolution will dictate that this is where we're going
That works
So we got the covid headline other day baby
I'm continuing
Massive
Poison shot down as the coven
Unbelievably powerful
I am more than 15 new studies
And match reports
Popsockets going public
I'm going to give you those headlines here's the first one
Increases infection Risk by 44% Oxford
Study
Do that but it gets worse
Oh man
Does a dumb blog headline that Alex's reading it isn't accurate at all
The actual study that's behind this is titled
Associations of BMI with covid-19 vaccine uptake vaccine Effectiveness and risk of severe covid-19
How comes after vaccination in England
A population-based cohort study
If you understand the title you'll probably realize that this study would never be able to be used
To make a kind of claims Alex's reporting it
It's just not something they're looking
Lead stories reached out to the study's co-author and they explained that this interpretation of their data is irresponsible and in
There's one databox in the study that's being used to argue that vaccines
He's caused a 44% increased risk of
Infection and if you only look at the numbers and isolation and create your own interpretation you could
Maybe come away with that conclusion but it's totally out of context and wrong
This was an observational study which is to say it depends entirely on test
That I've already been taken
As explained by lead stories
Quote their data was depended on covid test
That were available to them and the people who chose to take them
In other words
A person who did
Didn't feel sick and didn't take a test wouldn't be able to
Provide with them with a negative test result
So the data is
Yulieski that is an issue
As we see everyday Alex has a new covid vaccine narrative that's easily dismissed
Innovative digging
He never looked for any explanation or context
Because he doesn't want it
That would ruin his ability to keep throwing out these vaccine narratives of the day which he needs
Skip his audience
In a focused
Scared stage
Constantly seeing new classy headlines scroll past them
It'll be forgotten tomorrow the next day that'll be something new
Imagine all the scientist get-together at
My conferences
Just kind of like
Start conversation with
How they lie about your work
What were the Levites Ally on this one all they couldn't read numbers yeah yeah yeah
Good read numbers how many times have you tried to operate in good faith and explain the people are wrong
Only for them to not listen and continue creating computers and theories out of your life's work
You know what I miss
Blow your mind
I thought if I
Explained it they would hear me
Hahaha what a fool I was
We were all young once
We got the pipeline
But there's
There's always time for a PS
Golf Course
Good clean protein and good clean fat
So good for every cell in your body
If your arteries
Chugging for your heart
Artificial fats
Boiled
Fast
Cook
That are
Deadly
Lynx don't have any lights
Lean chicken is incredibly good
Bob's
What is that
There are some things that are
What you say
Fast cook bacon is a
To the heart attack
What are we doing better
Whiskey Barn bacon
Cookie
Onions lettuce
Chisme
My goodness
Fried egg sandwich
5 minutes
I cook it for
20in even taste better
Just don't be lazy what happened
Everything else they tell you is a lie
What
What's hookah
Confirm that Alex Jones is paid off by the slow bacon
Cooking lava
NY that just at Barney bacon Gifford has like now
What I what I started doing
Have you tried that Lissa
The hot oil is what's the problem is that hot oil you want to bake it
And then you'll be healthy
You can eat your bacon
And be healthy if you bake
Yeah that was a little weird
Strange strange diversion but back to complaining about the
Love you Alex has some pretty
Yes I got some nerve on this one
Wake up the station
A tsunami style floods killed hundreds
As50 National Guard Choppers begin search
And Rescue
Operation
Meanwhile
Piling onto this tragedy
Are the disgusting line
Anti-gun anti-family anti-america in
At The View
And what are they said here's a quote
Just getting hit
One of the worst hurricane
Thanks to hurricane
Exxon climate change
This is superstition this is this is
That's why they've dumb people down the school system by Design it's in the garbage documents
Batman
I just I like
Be idea that Alex is trying to take some moral High Ground over alleged Superstition and hoodoo
Is misrepresenting what they even said on this
Idiots who would think that his beliefs on climate change are causing this
Weather weapons morons least weather weapons have a cause-and-effect
Relationship is supposed to his belief that God has doomed our planet because of abortion
Well you did
Remove his protection get a reprieve for a while I think that's over though maybe mother
Forever moved her protection from Florida because
Do scientists believe climate change the same thing
Do God and Mother Earth have different protections as they can
Are they like company
I'm just saying that I would screens don't spiritual cause and effect nonsense all the time
All ridiculous
Ridiculous
At this point Alex does devolve
Into a condescending lecture about weather
I'm not going to play it
Idaho
Feel like he understands weather
Did you know that a typhoon is the same thing as a hurricane in another place
It's basically just that
He's as this which I thought was
Time lapse of storms on Jupiter
Are storms maximum speed is about 170 miles an hour
The storms on Jupiter
Get up to several thousand miles an hour
Boy you would want to be in one of those
A lot of reasons I would want to be on the store and then to putter
I have not heard that
I have not heard the snow like a bit back in my day we just have to walk 5 miles at every
Directions to the Moon
With your climate change making storms worse nonsense you see Jupiter
Crazy God 11
Cool
No I've no I would
What about Alex's big
Covid
Sources
One of those big things of course
Operation lockstep
Real
Document that sometimes
It's just makeup wild s*** about it this is the the sparse document
In the Pentagon John Hopkins develop war game
I'm plan
About two years before they want
Covid-19
Impala 2017
Sparse 2023
20/20 2023 is when they ask
The document called
Bars 2025
How many numbers
The entire document
Love you.
The same days
Put out the real world in 2000
2001 at goes in a 2000
They just changed
In 2001
What to do in real time
They got caught
With the battle plan it wouldn't be a plan for a biological attack on America
Virus and then through the back
Maxine
It would just be a drill
Emergency Saturday broadcast
Shocked by sparse 125
2028 doctor
Posted
Infowars.com front page
Are the live
Show
Speed
Today
Very very important her by to get that
Ensure that because we're living
Describe the opposition to the shot
Start coming out
Give you the disease
Describe
Respiratory disease
Describe about a year into it
They would start having people from the health services defect
That was wrong to do
Animal into years of releasing the deadly vaccine
Admit
That it didn't work
They would remove the heads of big Pharma
Punishment
But that there wasn't be a biomedical State brought in
Two basic
We oversee all a big Pharma
Play describe the whole process and how they're going to hit us
Either going to kill us
Away with it
None of that is at all accurate about the sparse scenario exercise
How to just making up pretty much everything you saying about it there's a good reason why
He needs this document to be prophetic but more importantly he needs to be prophetic for his
Fake reality
But he's constructed for his body
The document doesn't say any of that stuff but these are the narratives that have gained prominence in Alex's world
So they're the things that he needs to retroactively applied to this scenario exercise
Roset doesn't really have that much use for him
Bars much like lockstep isn't actually useful
For Alex if you read them and understand what they are
They only have utility as ideas
Skeletons that he can build a body onto himself
It's one of the reasons that scenario exercises as a whole
Super popular among conspiracy theorists like Alex
They portray imagined
Future events
Explain the scenario using a narrative
These are things that Alex can exploit
He can take the actual document and lie about the Imagine future events and how they line up with
Current real event
He can write his own narrative to replace the one that actually exists in the document pretty safe in the knowledge that if anyone called
I'm out about it
It's just a matter of Storytelling to convince them that his narrative is secretly with the document is at
Chili about
None of this is real and it doesn't even match past versions of the sparse document conspiracy Alex's spread
Google just meaningless s*** whose end result is really just
Getting people hurt
Yeah if I was one of those secret agents or whatever
If I was one of those operatives who got caught with the plan
Right
I would be like
Isn't this plan so terrible no one would try it what a funny plan this is
What's a duck idiot would make this
Dumb
F****** plan-b standard conspiracy theorists
Scenario
Exercise kind of
Drill
Bass
The explanation the real Attack
Right right right
It's. So have you considered
The idea that this organization
Were they real would want to plan that work
Would have you would now
It does listen to me
Follow me on this
Maybe if after these
Decades
I suppose
Millennia it Alex's world
Of failures
They be like let's hire
Some Consulting
I'm just really streamline this process perfect
Perfect answer
They didn't count on Alex
Really don't think that's the case Alex has been too successful
I tried to recruit him when he was younger behind the devil can see the future in knew that Alex
Is going to be super successful
See if I'm the devil
With my plan
Aibeile
I've been working on this
Spore but I got to go
Classic Disney's Hercules Hades had a problem with
What's Hercules didn't didn't die you just f******
Bail on your plant you already know you lost
Tom the fucken devil I can try again
I'll wait him out he will be dead soon Alex f****** my plans up I'm not going to keep it going with him
Stupid
The terrible idea
So Alex
Some calls
And one of them has a pretty interesting point that Alex.
Does not like
Hey what's up Alex
Brother
They didn't she get in trouble two weeks you're still promoting the big vaccine salesman the guy that fluent
Explain why you doing that
Oh yeah
And I've been really against Trump on that
He flew on a flight from New York to Florida
On a chartered flight with Epstein
He never flew
Whoa whoa whoa
Disagree
But I'm not going to
So you can talk
Cal flies you do through them
Trump did not ever fly Lolita Express
The little Saint Johns Island
He did fly
Once
In the 90s
On MCS plane from New York
People
To Florida
A lot more than that yes I was up staying
K baby there is no record of him going to the island that's entirely possible
But like Alex
Can't handle
Like anything
Annie push play
See the way that uses these cheap tricks to control the conversation
Pictures of the guy allying
Put them on hold it's just all the
Yeah it's a
The flexing of a guy who can't handle
Hold his own
Yeah you know I feel like I have the only really unassailable position on this
Which is that
If we got rid of everybody who was on the plane
At least one
Or above
We'd be better off
We be fine
And let me tell you something
No false
Interstate let me know let me know if your language just a tiny bit
It took them out of the public
The power
I'm not in the mafia
If people who are new to the standard that you're describing face
Consequences
Yes
I think that as long as we got to hit him
I would even go so far as to say
Ninety-nine percent of the people have never been on the plane and every one of them who was vast majority of the population has not been
If you're on the plane one-time get the f*** out of here unless you were on the plane and it wasn't your choice
Did another call here
Well
This caller believes that a better version of The Alex Jones was right meme
Alex Jones
Which
If I take issue could be an issue
Because where this goes
Bad time
So I think that
The meaning of house
I think that
There's a wonderful man but I see
Alex Jones
Who's telling the truth
Because if
Wrong in something
Apologize first
Or you can write
Or more stuff
Using wrong
And I see
To say
He was just telling the truth he was just reading the news
Telling the truth
And then later I said okay it happened
Now that I've seen the
The trials rigged
And how it all looks
I mean
It's definitely the whole thing's deep
That's all I can say
Publix original Instinct about it
What's rights
But it is
It is synthetic as hell
And I think that you're right.
Creeper
I just want to say thank you
For everything you've done
My God
What is
What is happening at legit want a personal apology
I want a personal apology from all of the media
S*** about how they've
Alex finally admitted something Alex finally apologized personal f****** apology
Remember God damn one of you got to get you back on Twitter if that right is outraged go
Yeah
This is
Bad
For Alex
Okay
So let's break down a couple
Dino Alex's language
And what things mean
Yes him saying that this is synthetic
Is very bad
Immediately after saying that the trial was rigged
Well but that's kind of normal for him
That my life at this point
Synthetic is a way that he described the event
When he was saying that everyone is actor
This is harkening back to that line
Now to make things even worse
When he says
The people
Instinct originally were right
Yep that is him saying that they were at
Yep that is
There's no way he describes
The theories that he just started to look at he was just looking at the suspicions that people had
When he uses that kind of language
He is
Definitely
Whether or not he actually believes anything he is definitely giving voice
Do this was all fake
This is
And I think
If I had to guess
It's based on anger
Well yeah Mark Bankston was first on the show
First time
He speculated that one of the things that drove Alex
Is anger at the end
Yeah
Really
Necessarily agree I thought it was an interesting perspective but it wasn't the way I
Necessarily looked at
Wright-brown
I'm coming more along to that
Because he has said things that were so
Disrespectful to the idea that there are grieving parents
Crying in court than you know
I I think there is like a just how dare you make me feel by
Right
I am dumb
One of the things that I think is really telling about this
Is that Alex knows he f*****
Cuz here's the version of this that appears
On his own website
So I think that the
The meaning of Alex Jones was right I think that
Wonderful man but I think what would be more powerfully to me with these
Alex Jones was telling the truth
Because it's
You've been wrong in some things but can't even apologize for those things
Are you can write on far more stuff
Using wrong
And I think it's much more powerful
To say
She was just telling the truth he was just reading the news and he was telling the truth
Purslane
I just want to say thank you for everything you've done
He entirely cut it out every part of the
Yep you know if you talked up what he said if words mean things which I don't know if they do
If words mean things
Kingston what he said was
This happened
Didn't defame the families
Then
They sued me and now that I've seen the trial is rigged and all of that stuff
First I said it happened I said sure it happened
And then he said but now the whole thing
Is deep State that's all I can say and I'll hold things
Totally synthetic and you're like so you just talked yourself into
Defaming the parents of again
Yep.
Santino's he f***** up
He edited it out for a reason
And the reason is because you was hoping
But unfortunately he's still like he did this on his show
And
It is on the
Diversion
Radio affiliates
Yolanda gcn feed of his show
And certainly this next week I believe this will be a problem in court
Texas
This
Is
About as bad of a thing as he could do
In the middle of this case
He
I was text
Sing you about this
You know cuz it's
Like I was
Flabbergast
Of course
One of the things that this does
Is it hands to the plaintiffs attorneys
Concrete evidence
Will never change
You can't learn lessons
There is nothing that will
Stop him from doing things
Like this
The very thing that he is in court
The very thing
This trial in this jury is trying to determine
The penalty of
He will not ever
Stop
And that is very valuable thing
For the
The plaintiffs attorneys
Well
It's
It's on a platter I mean you remember both of their opener
Statements you remember Maddie
Saying you know like
We got to we have to stop him
It obeys
We have to stop
The only way to do that is
Is to take them off the air
And the only way to do that is to take all of the money away
You know and then normal
Was like that's
That's not how you should work
You know you shouldn't just
Do that you should punish him and then he should be allowed to go on his deck
But this is just
Every bit of why
You know because the jury didn't really know why
That he has
To be stopped
You know they've gotten all the shity
Done
And you can punish him for the shity
He's done and then say okay
Now that you've been punished
You know not to do this again
But he's already been punished he's already lost a lawsuit and comes into court and does like this defiant
Pendleton Act
You know I question some things and my right to be able to question things
Like you did
This is
Why so in the face of any kind of presentation he wants to make
Kill himself
I in court I think that did himself in
Write a book
The service
I am like I think Norm sucks I got no sympathy for him
Having to deal with this
Is like
How do you not
Beg the court to put a gag order on him
He can't stop himself from
Blowing up his own spot
I am
Play amazing I mean
Oh man
I don't know man
Pretty bad
Honestly
I think it's going to play you who works in court that he cut it out of the episode it's not going to be good
We're wearing its of what you did
Yep
Sunright good luck
You deserve every bit of what's about to fall on your face
S'more calls
This guy decides he's going to insult Chris Mattie
And then they
Balsam conspiracy
Not about the case
About smart
About the pipeline
Drawing the book
Loving the supplement
Love the way you handle that pencil neck
Connecticut
They're not getting any money on their asses
Questions about the pipeline
They're saying that it's not being used
Gas
Escaping
Nordstrom 21 open
They blew it up was it damaged so much gastro
On the mainstream ever makes it easier
They opened up that new pipeline
Who owns that fireplace
That's a good question
I would like to know who owns that
United States
Clothes never open
Gas in it why would it blew up
Gas
If nordstream2 didn't have gas in it
Why when it blew up all that gas in it
Nothing makes sense when you don't look into the things that are confusing you
Like if you have questions and their sincere questions
Find the answer to that
But they don't care
Question they don't care about the answer the
Is a prop
It's being used to justify their
Disregard of any and all possible by actual reality
To prop up and
Decorate
Their predetermined conclusion
Nordstrom pipelines are closed
No flow through them but they're still full of gas
Estimated to be about 90% methane
That's why the pictures that you see are of gas roiling to the surface as opposed to the classic image of an oil spill
I could have found that out
Within
A minute
I do appreciate the idea of being like
I'd like to know who owns that pipeline
We going to turn up volume
Midstates need to look it up anymore I just decided
Worry about it I won't but no
Draw my question
Answer for the answer is two up
Sure
Pipeline, the US
Altec pipe which opened around the same time as the other ones began leaking
This is of course
That everything all of these are connected
The pipeline is not owned by the United States it's a joint venture operated by the Danish company
Danette
And the Polish Oil Company gas
System
Since 2001 with long periods of dormancy but it's always been an attempt
Decrease your abs
Dependence on Russian oil
As far back as the beginning of the year they were estimating October 1st as their partial opening date with a full capacity
Be possible Bible
Beginning of 2023
Maybe interesting that this pipeline opened around the same time as those other ones were possibly sabotage but that alone is
Not enough
To prove that these events are connect
It's enough to prove that an Infowars Lambo because truth is not a solid object there
Well I mean it's understand the coincidental timing right but it is it is like
Okay
You made a pipe
That nobody was getting oil from leak
And this one's fine
So
What's the conspiracy there
Like who
Who benefits from this
NATO
Oh s***
Yeah
Just a tease
Dumb
Okay now it looks like
It couldn't have been
Accidental
But have we
Giant spiders
Those big
Does big night and there's water spiders
That sounds
Good enough for me we have not accounted for we have not accounted for giant spiders
Alex
Russian spiders now we're in real trouble
So we jump to Friday the 30th
And here Alex is in
Quite a mood
At the beginning of the show
When I come in here very frustrated
Instrumental ability
Because there's no way to cut
Elijah Told part of the human process and all part of Cycles
We go through and we're entering the bottom
I want the most
The most deadly
Goodbye techno
Ron
Service of this planet
In the air
What
But why
Get focused
Find a place
Clarity
Standing
Why the enemies
Stop them
The right now in one of those Focus places
We'll see if I can stay there
Call me over this because the gravity of all of this
Is so unbelievably important
I love
First of all
Set mistakes real high
Undercutting the stakes by saying if I can even stay in this place it is kind of interesting
Articulated so clearly
How long could probably not going to make it to the commercial break I am not good
Playing in this like
So this isn't good it's
Mostly the the argument here is that
Demons
Take children
And then they messed them up
And
You know
Some of it is keep going I'm going to give you a little bit of background music to really help you
Some some of it ends up in Murder
And some ends up with these kids to go and like
I recruit more folk share
Panties
Baeza demonz
Get the kids
Through like the CPS
Okay what have you drowsy
In order to destroy the family
And has to do without
What does transphobia
And that's basically how the globe.
Yes that
Unfortunately sounds like how the globalist do operate based upon what I know of the globalist
They're not real
Mostly this is going to end up being a bit of a transphobic
Display
Funny parts
Long way and that is
The first part at least okay
Alex is determined
That some people identify as alien
It doesn't get much more evil than this
And then you see that
Showing the abject
Freak Show
Where
There's this big moment our they go I'm not even a human I'm not a dog I'm not a cat
I'm an alien
One of my good friends
Tonight's ago
And they went down
Wife
Criminal
All these creatures
White wine in Spanish
They couldn't tell what they were but they look like
Weird green eyeshadow
Clownfish looks
Just like drag queen story time
I said that
Within 10 seconds they pulled up
Instagram Facebook Twitter
British groups go on together
And they all
Look completely like aliens they're into how they lost her
Humanity
Sexless
This is what the globalist plan in Brave New World
Publishing 1931
I was out on the streets of Chicago and I have to report to you that
There are large groups of people who identify as Santa
Drunk people out
He's like in Alex's world no one ever just gets f*****
Can high for a night you act like nobody's ever just f***** up tonight like I got f*****
Yep I did a little of MDMA and now I'm going to hit you like that might be fun
Tonight or if like
Some people on like an alien bar crawl or something like that
Having some food right
Like if he saw the Santa bar crawl or the zombie Bar Crawl The Flaming Lips still touring they could have been
Go to Flaming Lips
There's a number of possibilities but apparently this
Is terrified I just wish that his
Where's worldview doesn't ever encapsulate somebody just being really f***** up and having a good night
Insane weird s***
You know it's always got to be like an ongoing thing
So
Alex
One of the things we know from watching his show and paying attention to a lot of the stuff
These dates
We
Look at
The satanic Panic that's going on now and the satanic Panic of the 80s is kind of
Separate insensitive
Sprite there was a flare-up
And then it went below right and that's coming back as opposed to one giant long into
And Alec believes
I believe it's one of course and it's all real
Bright sand
The devil just was getting a guess
Active
The devil's a little bit like
Earth
Herpes you know it shows up every now and again and then it's like I haven't had an outbreak for a while
Yeah
So hard they possess
Everybody energy
Eons old
True you know
Yeah I mean I'm pushing 40 and I'm tired as hell
All of the red horns and the tail doll that is more like an ENT
From Lord of the Rings that you just like
I got to go
Satan
Sai maybe that's
That's why is gone from the 80s present
So what are the things that feature of that is of course the McMartin School case
Ted gunderson's involvement
Alex
Imagine being the first person to expose this
And people think you're crazy
Yeah that be crazy
He left
Expose this
He discovered whole towns
Run by devil worshiper
Hiding behind science hiding behind
Science
Psychology and psychiatry
So I have this
I said I'll get to it later
Remember when we're covering all this other
Information
That witches are real
When you see these three judges and he's Democrat lawyers
Like yours
They are devil
Worshipping
.
That's why they look like vampires
They're all these types
You learn the look of them and then you see
Policies
Sexualization of children
Chemical castration of children
Bizzle castration children
Because they want the spiritual app
I'm destroying innocence and the future
But when you ask
These people you see the deadness in their eyes
You see what the other like race
And a no
What
Are doing
So everybody is against Alex or Alex
Against
Is a knowing
Pedophile
No way they're doing yeah
No no that's how you demonize the entire group and that's really bad
It's not even entire group
Everyone here again everybody's anybody I decide today
I like 9 times out of 10 though like
What's the other person doing what's Alex's lawyer
They going down like an office setting and they're all sitting around and he's like
I hope they don't know that I'm the only one who's not a knowing pedophile here worship safe
Ford Hayward
Thankfully dissolving Alex's hat
Alex sides to take
EBenefits
To describe
The taxonomy of Diva
Kingdom phylum
Hierarchy okay alright here we go
Show me different classes of those that have fallen the evil
I put a handbook out on it
Yes you should
Monstercat radio
Webster in a trance
Just watch TV online all day and
Corsage
Glow-in-the-dark
Translucent
Jeff
The General Public
Years ago or 20 years ago
Daydream
Waking sleeping
Sleepwalking state
So you got the zombies
And
Technical term
Evergage color racer
They're everywhere.
Then you've got people that
Trying to become
More like
Gremlin way
Gremlin
System of corruption
Hey for the family and they love story
GMOs and they love whatever the system
Worship the system
Avant-garde Rebels when they're totally backed by the New World Order in the system says
Get rid of their Humanity anyway they
I can
To make themselves look as ugly as possible
And I acted big groups and incoordination
Zombies don't so much
Incoordination
Smell around my nose
Mitsubishi
Equal
Globalist New World Order say
What are the new saying is
They're the
Mpc's over-the-limit admission
So what we got the zombos and the gremlin race
I was kind of hoping we would get a lot more the
Okay good cuz I feel like I'm writing down everything
Need to break the cycle and I want his monsters
What's your what do you see when you hear gremlin
I see Alex not preparing
If you wasn't just covered up with this off lock
Pizza.
I don't see so Gremlin I see the I mean forget
Do you see Gizmo
You sit your Gizmo guy
Imma get smoked okay
So we'll go with that
Alright
And then the rate fight so it's
It's Gizmo wearing a row
Sure
I guess I'll take that
I want to join
Make some make some
Stir fry I got some little nugget I prefer oat milk to soy milk myself
Hanger-on with the soy sauce
I think everybody kind of likes it not right
All right look I say on fleek
As a joke about how out-of-the-loop I am
Alex I think it's sincere out of the Lupi as wealthy
The right-wing talk
Maybe maybe you guys didn't like sorry cuz you just didn't know how to
A parrot
So
Zambo
Pretty much everybody share that Alex doesn't like TV
Unusual thing people do like Alex does all the f****** time
Head start on the view all the time how much I don't matter Bill Maher
They just waddle around
They Mi about 10 or the Gathering group no
Big groups
I think that's the protesters basically on our end of the
Visual that Alex doesn't like
Then the gremlin race
Are like protesters
Organized
Things that Alex doesn't like
Right right but there's another level above that
Involves
The CPS
Yes I believe
I think they're the next level
You have the zombies you have
The gremlin
Sherman
And then you have the renfield's attacks
Sure
And there's a hierarchy in those
There's 100 babies
To Dracula who then gives it to his brood of women
When he has sex
Archives
Wingfield's are
Your corrupt CPS workers
Winfield your threat Family Court judges
Renfield's are
The people in Germany in the US
The orphanages that deliver children
Pedophile
Levels
Low-level Renfield
Grooming deliver show
Then you'll have renfield's that keep children ready and
And they're trying to transition
Is Renfield his in the book Dracula
Children
And they're always bringing Dracula can we
Can I take part in killing them
Anna Dracula
You got to really work hard and beg
To get to the point where actually
Wow okay
So what are you
Wow I mean we've jumped
Pretty far from love soy and yes
Kidnap babies that happened so fast to drink their blood
Middle level in between there their well I mean I think if you're talkin about a hierarchy of demons essentially
How to be a benign boring.
Zombie has like some awesome regular
A bureaucrat like a you know something might be in the hierarchy of vampires
Dagwood's
Steal your your blood
Except they have to be worse than the Renfield
Cuz they're higher up on the ship
Well they don't have to be worse
No no
You're getting this backward
They're higher up
So they don't have to
The Dirty Work
Be bringing John if it weren't for them their demands I mean they just say things and then they appeared
Are you making any hard demands
It Dracula's not making hard demands of Renfield Alright good idea
We we have an identification of Dracula Netflix
Oh there's only one Jack yes okay
Gotcha Covered already know who it is
It's got to be
Stelter
Notes King Charles
Zombie
Gremlin
And then you get
Your low-level Renfield
Mid-level Renfield Jairo rentals like five or six levels of Winfield
Sure
Why
Justify the 4th level
Get the king of England at the top
Count Dracula
So
Researcher
But it's wrong will
I am
Take these guys on
And once you know they're sure I know there's a Renfield
They're weak to Bo's
CC
Vampire
Melee weapons only
When you see a Prince Charles
People that's who they are
Get it
This is how things work
And that's just how it is nice to know we've got some bows I got Gremlin race we've got the
And then we've got
Regular vampires right Hillary Hillary and then
The top
King Charles
The guy who is been essentially ignored for the past 70 years and clowned on largely
Dislike
Postpone
That's Drac
Zoe so he was behind like you don't understand Dracula myths
One of the essential features as the Dracula had a wife that everyone like way more who died
Regularly
Okay so what was the queen doing did she know was Dracula previously
You can't just pretend I think
You can when you die
Charles Baker
Write imagine
I think they would Alex is saying is the station of the king of England is the
Is the the dragon dragon
That Prince Charles at talked about how you like
Transylvania Heritage Railway
Huh
So yeah
So
I mean it all makes sense now I'm glad that he was so Focus
I'm still stuck on the gremlin right
Because I just see a little Gizmo where the black robe
Okay
Highest ranking Gremlin Wraith
Is that
Equivalent to the lowest-ranking rent
Prince Fielder always above fields are the Servants of the Dracula's in the vampire
The gremlin race
Not really
Maybe that maybe nobody gives them commit chaotic
They're like the Goths just Roman about
Tearing down Rome whatever they cry
No.
Yeah
Yeah so unfortunately there's ways we can end up becoming a vampire
Do I hate somebody that is
Is gay better be my dad
The Gateway
Into this whole thing and it's heterosexuals are pedophiles as well
Lgbtq P mobile
Opera
Damn
What a load of s***
Show me the makes it less fun right I mean
It's it's a lot of fun to hear Alex rambling about the hierarchy of demons in the world
It's silly and stupid but then you realize
Kind of at the end of the day that this is all
Just
Lgbtq plus narrative
Vapes
I mean it
It is implied violence
Absolutely
Well your
If maligning
Anybody
Essentially arguing that being gay can be a
Gateway drug
Or being a pedophile
Of course heterosexual people can be pedophiles too
Naturally anyone I disagree with
Also a pedophile
Regardless of what their sexual orientation may or may not be
So basically everyone but Alex f***
Kids
According to Alex
Yeah that's true
Allegedly
Perfect way of describing something I mean he does Amazon
I'm a predator example
I was trying to do it upon like
But yeah
So Alex
I need money
Cuz he's Van Helsing
Right he's been he'll singing
Nugent van Hellsing right yeah
Alex
And he'll grouse
You want to fight you want to try to stand up the New World Order
Broadcast
Celtic runes
An hour in the main battle
Really a simple equation
God keeps me humble
But I'm going to tell you right now
I barely have the money to pay my lawyers I barely have the money to travel connect
Bankruptcy Court
Me personally paying for my travel everything up there
Whatever great
I'm almost out of money
Go to save infowars.com that's the URL to make
Personal donation Infowars
Legal in our travel we need your help
We're in the fight Rocky Alamo sending a letter out ask
Whatever happened
It's up to you
Is that a colonel Travis sending out a letter that I need $80,000 to get a private jet to go to Connecticut
F****** a****** it is like listen
Can I get it
I get it
You you realize that you can't just booked a Southwest
Flight
If I'm standing
In f****** boarding Group C
And I see Alex Jones in front
I get it man
That can't have
But you could fly first class
Gary Kirby you do you get your own little view get to show up earlier whatever the f*** it is really like 10
People in their wig absolutely probably not get to harass
You could go as
Well I wouldn't recommend it
Now that I think about it
If he tried to do Madea it could be
There is also probably a cheaper way to Charter travel
You know like
Even if he had to do that I think it'd probably be a cheaper option
Hey somebody's flying Subway you know rich people really hate wait
Play real quick take
I like it's going to be a long trip it'll be a lot more than $80,000 to drive that take from
Rally's along the way Owen pave the path I like
So we got a headline here
Just came out last week was interspeed goals in the German news
This is what the great reset
Looks like
Germany's greens plan to ban native Germans
Assertive jobs remote diversity
It'll just bring it outside populations they then don't let you have a job
German greens plan to ban Germans from a third of jobs for meth diversity
This isn't true
Member of the greens parliamentary group recently said quote by the end of 2026 a third of all
All newly advertised positions in the city should be filled by applicant
With a migration back
This is a headline that I was reading from Summit.
Paul Joseph Watson site
The way this is being reported as convoluted
Here's how the article star
In the name of promoting diversity ruling Greens in the German in the German city of Hanover
Citizens for applying for government jobs
So they can be given to Mike
Yes really wow
How is
City jobs ideally being filled by non german-born citizens the equivalent of banning a third of native
Citizens from applying for those jobs
That's just nonsense and Les Paul somehow believes that the only jobs available in Hanover are from the city
They reported this way because it's too much more flashy headline then City aims for 30% immigrant
Workforce
Paul's version is easier for Alex to yell about get his audience nice and scared
That's why he writes these completely nonsensical and dishonest title that he does
It's because Paul's role is to
Saturn outrage bait the demagogues like Alex can then used inside their audio
Here's the part of the story that Paul doesn't
Want to bring
Nothing neither does that
Hanover population is only 78% German
Even for a city Workforce of approximately 30%. German-born individuals is really not too far off from Acura
Currently reflecting the city's demographic makeup
Considering that the 30% that they're talking about is a goal not Amanda
It's likely that they'll fall short of that number and maybe
Maybe they'll hit 22% immigrant hires
Which would be exactly representational of the city as a whole
This is outrageous based on.
Actually based on less than
Willful ignorance of Base
Reality because that reality would get in the way of being able to add jatate against groups of people
You don't like
And you want your audience
What's not to like
Puritan
You know it is it is that classic
Race
Saying though it is at Classic
Just you know like if their lives get better
That means your life
Has to get worse
And it's always that argument you know it's been that way for
For so long
It's been that way it's why you know that that unions couldn't integrate
You know 100 years ago
Edit always that like
Nobody can really
Drake through the
Skulls of so many people
That if everybody's life gets better
Everybody's life gets better
Every but that includes you
It includes you
Right you are also everybody
Yeah but I think I think there's some people
Who want other people's life not to be badass names are Paul and Alex
And many others
And this is weird
And a John Birch
Society was founded
More than
60 plus years ago
When an army officer John Birch
Along with the CIA in 1949
Canning all the power to mousy tongue
Shanghai Shack
He was tortured to death
And so the term the John Birch
But my dad read the writings that woke up when he was young my grandfather his father was aware of it
Radio broadcast
Dallas
Drive up on my Ranch
Read the books
Interviews of the speeches
It all was right it all came true
Show
Alex Jones
Tomorrow's news today
Well
50 years news today
Is the John Birch Society in Robert Owens join Judas
The bouncy our national council members
Holyshit me on there to say the N word a lot to remind people of the John Birch Society
I mean eventually they will get there
Yeah
So Alex is having a representative from the John Birch Society
Thing and they're so great and apparently
Not only was Alex's dad super into the cupboards
Radio show ever at the problem
I got some Flack a little bit
After the
We put out the Alex's War episode
There was a part that Alex was
Downplaying is
Families Gilbert Society connection
I think maybe had read a book but yourself
Come the f*** off
Alex selectively deploys
Information about what his ideological background is because it's
Advantageous like that f****** dumbass documentary
It's not advantageous for him to
Be like the John Birch Society or profit to the best ever
He knows that he knows how to make it look bad
Yeah Alex is back story is I think similar to a like
Dark Knight when the Joker was describing how he got scars
Any change
Change the story every time
Cuz that's the joke
You shouldn't believe what he says
Remind me about
Alex
Which is weird
Why isn't
Say the John Birch Society your founder have been Vindicated
My friend
Robert Owens is an understatement
Why don't you start with history
The JBS
The original Alex Jones
Why thank you I thank you so much I Alex for having me on the show
And I wouldn't be much of a Berkshire if I didn't Begin by saying
Edwards
Let me invite you to join the John Birch Society
Why won't
I don't know maybe it would
Make him sound f****** crazy because
If you was a proud member of the John Birch Society
Maybe that would come up when he's on Rogue you think you're maybe when he's trying to pass himself off as some kind of
Crazy John Birch Society extreme right-wing
F****** fanatic
Then it will play against
I remember him being above it
I remember him being above that left-right paradigm
Well you can make an argument that
The
But
Fascist leaning
In service of large corporations right
Rooted in the National Association of Manufacturers
Anti-communism because we all have huge corporations that would suffer
Financially by workers having rights
Terrible
It is it is maybe a different Paradigm that they have
Chopped out of a magazine and then put on top of ours
Maybe it is above it all to be like the Civil Rights Movement with a communist conspiracy and I wish Rhodesia still existed
A worm
Either way Alex loves this dude
This this Owens guy
Power
Robert Owen
How much what you house arrest
Don't you knock it out the park
Robert Welsh
Talk about the best serious
Holyshit
He doesn't actually hand off the show but this is some of the most glowing praise I have
I heard him
Publicly make four
The Robert wealth admitting that he's aware who Robert Welch is
Is wild
No it's not
Good on some fronts cuz at least it's
F****** forthright yeah that's true I'm not playing some kind of a peekaboo mask
The games the most I've heard anybody phrase
The John Birch Society
In public that's not going to be easy love.
Oh man
He's basically work
That's why he's our miracle
They have some by candidates they're really excited about this I have to JBS
Hey you can go to college
But here's the exciting part
Unbelievable Warriors I'm going to give you a name Jr Majewski
Marcy kaptur
Congress
He is killing it
Kids on the Warfare fighting and battling an
Taking the
The stabs
And the worst abs are from The Establishment Republicans Alex stabbed
Republican
You might recognize that dude's name cuz he's the guy who's been accused recently of Stolen Valor for misrepresenting
Get service record in combat in Afghanistan but there are no records of that and his claim that his
Deployment was classified has been questioned by experts
Even if it were classified what he was doing there still waiting
You could corroborate that deployment with cheese
He's failed to do
Also turns out he was dishonest about why you couldn't reenlist after his first stretch in the Air Force
You probably was stationed at a base in Okinawa and got popped for drunk driving beer days before 9/11
Which led to him being demoted from Airman First Class to basic Airman
This message resulted in the GOP not being really hot on him anymore as you know
The stab
From the Republican
Yeah bye.
He's running against Marcy kaptur who's been in office since 1983 so I don't know if I'm going to put too much of
Money on Jr here
The district that was widely read
In 2020 which led to a much higher GOP voting
Percentage
But it might not be enough I'm not entirely sure
You know it went from a heavily pro Democrat
District
In the cook
Partisan index
Slightly Republican won
It's it's atossa
So yeah so
I wouldn't put my money on
This level of a candidate with atossa
You seems like you suck
Fox yeah
He was there
Is it give you do that
Olivia like you
No
No so like I said I
Rarely heard Alex have like specific awareness about things in the JBS because
Play fast and loose about my other ideas
Right where I said something but not the Robert Welsh
Grambling sexual Rim at Robert Wallace was just a Super Genius
Well he he really was this was a guy that age 16 graduated from college by the time he was 20 in bed
Send to the
U.s. Naval Academy in Harvard Law School
It was pretty accomplished but also he was a Candyman
In the free market economy
To cover the hole
Candy mark
He invented things like the the Sugar Daddy Junior men's
So the company that well she was at invented those candies but without saying isn't really true
Welch's business Oxford candy company went out of business
His brother James also ran a candy company called the James o Welch Company which survives and after Oxford claps
James hired Robbie
He was the best business man ever any took over the candy Market single-handedly
What was it what was the one we created it behind the bastards
What was just the fuk stick is that
Yeah probably
That is there
Look at what my squad. It's because I'm not interested in hearing this
Goddamn recruiter for the John Birch Society on Alex's show
It is
Relevant to bring up
Recruitment
That is what they say
And you can hear it pretty clearly
What's Explorer Liberty
So here's the thing
What what
My recommendation is if you mean business if you want to be part of
An organization
It is going to give you the absolute best information going
Go to jbs.org and sign up
They will put you in touch with a local field office or guys like me all over the country we have some with most
Google men and women
Professional
In a specific action agenda chapter you're going to be doing things
We are actually going to be
Making
Indifference
Bushing
Purpose of Liberty not Justin as an academic X
Exercise
What is a specific
Wilbur soot
This is kind of an interesting development in Alex's path
Whatever the f*** he's doing now
You have a
JBS recruiter who's coming in
Alex's showing more awareness
Forgiving effusive praise
About Robert
Everything
He's
Insinuating himself and involvement the JBS far more than he usually does if anything's service
Of leading to this guy pitching
If you're serious you should join
The John Birch Society
I think it's weird
It sound
Like broker broker
Yeah honest
Now it sounds like a multi-level marketing scheme getting a an hour on a free Ricky
There are
Feelings like
I know that Alex
Like from everything that I understand from listening to as much of him as I have
I don't think this is out of line with his
No not exactly that he will take money
He has been
Far more cautious
About
Given too much public
Airing
To his love of the John Birch Society
Yeah he has in the past
Obviously
Made some
Overtures
More
And
Impasse
It was not always
In the context of
Interviewing a recruiter
Yeah who's trying to funnel listeners to the recruitment phone line
Yeah that one stuff that one stuff
I wouldn't
I wouldn't want to
Maybe it's just that the ghetto I don't think the JBS
Guys really known that well anymore right what stands for is in the little from Publix
Yeah yeah I think it's I think it is more like
You know you can say it now because
Most people don't even f****** know what you're talkin about
Yeah also absent in their discussion of the the past of the
The baby I said don't talk about Fred Koch talk about reveal Opie Oliver
Don't talk about the universe
The connections
Do you like
Slightly different name at the National Alliance
Yeah I found I found that to be troubling
They also didn't talk about how the mythology behind the John Birch
Yeah it not true
People who knew the actual John Birch
Say that he would not be in support of his name being attacked
Maps to this organization
Because why why ruin a good time
Yeah you know
What is it just disrespect
Be a person were claiming into the inspiration
You don't care
Well I couldn't do that
It's so important to do with the first casualties help
Anyway
Look there's some stuff to Tappan that is suck
Yep put man
There is nothing more like
Him calling it a synthetic event
Again I can't
I can't can't believe it
I can't even put into words how much I can't believe how stupid he
I just I mean
It is
Eventually I mean it's just
It's not even stupid
He just cannot stop him
Jazz no self
Control whatsoever
You want him to stop saying or doing something
Either
His entire audience
Has to not pay attention
Or stop giving him money for it
Or you have to shut it you have to shut him down I guess I was going to say that it's kind of stupid to have no self-control
And not work on
Right
I kind of
You know if you think about it a little bit more
That lack of self-control is essential to him being able to put on the show that he does
He's made of half a billion dollars not having a lack of control and self-control
And practice Atwood
Probably hurt him more oh yeah
Him just being like
F***
Ida saying these people again
Totally
But
He's not so dumb that he leaves it doesn't matter that out
Yeah you know it is I can help just like there is an entire
Structure
Based around making
I'm sure Alex
Continues to behave the way
Weather weather the pressure is like
All him
Right but I don't think the pressure is direct
It's like oh Alex you need to keep doing the Alex you need to do this or anyting
Just so much as it is like
Hey man if I stop for a second
All of these people are going to
Lose all of their money or whatever her job yeah
Every photo Owen Shroyer I'll be out of work I mean I think his family in that
Yeah we wear whatever
Totally
If you will
I am interested to see how the aftermath of this plays out in the real world in a courtroom
Yeah and we'll see you there at court starts back on Tuesday so we'll see what we'll see
Probably won't
Be good
We will be back but until then
I'm Neo I'm Leo and bcx Clark I am Wilfred Snapple Snapple at the Gravel Pit Bull
The sex robot
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color