I have great respect for knowledge by now I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
Need
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Worship at the altar
Alex drew
Indeed we are.
What's up
Is
This this button stuff is
Going along I have a prediction that I think it'll probably
Every button will be out by the end of the year
I'm giving myself that kind of sort of
Window
Yeah but it's really fun I mean one of the things that's really nice is a going through and
Addressing the envelopes
Some stuff that I see a lot of names that are like
People from way back yeah you know and it's really nice to know that these people like a lot of people are still with us
You know that's that's really
Exciting
And then the other thing
The second Wonka button is in the mail
Brightspot Willy Wonka button
Somewhere
Yeah
As luck may have it
This is an international button
This one is going out of the United States
So someone
Modern America Patriot fans are not going to like that I'll be looking out
As eyes look as long as it didn't go to the queen landed in the United
Sure that's true I knew it I knew she was going to ask for one and then she died
Well thanks for going to Queen Beatrix
Whatsyourprice
My bright spot is I started watching the show called Welcome to wrexham
Apparently Rob mcelhenney from It's Always Sunny and then Ryan
Reynolds from being a dick and movies
Body like
Zoo second-tier
Football Club
In wrexham
In Wales
Which is like the old estate site it's really cool story about the backstory of the town and it's got the oldest International
Stadium
At anywhere at all this cool stuff
And then they turned them into like the Mighty Ducks
Right and that's really cool
But then because Ryan Reynolds and Rob mcelhenney or riches s*** and they can get all these sponsorship deals
Now they're in a league where they are getting ice
Huge budget
Compared to everybody else so they're like the bad guys
The same time because of the way football works
They're in a little early so what they're really trying to do
Is get out of that League to be the underdog in the higher League
But there's another errand over dog Underdog
Kind of situation
And it's really cool
Cuz it talks about the town which
Is more interesting then tonight
The corrupting influence of money
They like if you have too much resources you can't even be the thing you walk away weed which is the underdog
They're not they're they're buying people from the upper League
That's because
You know like it's it's difficult
Difficult
Sure and they're trying their best
And there's all that fun stuff but it's amazing really good documentary in its its Mighty Ducks ass
While you're on the subject shows
Contraption master I finished a couple episodes
I believe you well
And then I've been needing another show cuz I watched all the survivors
Making the buttons right towards shows that are about people surviving
And then
I tried to Naked and Afraid but as I told you
Play maked Hermosa tomorrow that afraid
The Show recently called alone
And it's they are straight-up alone my partner loves
I am I'm into it I watch the first season
And I think it's great
Cuz it's 10 people they have to record
Themselves in the first episode of the first season
What cables got eaten by a bear
I was thinking
How would they stop that
No
Evacuate somebody who is worried that there were like
Big cats
Around
3 hour drive away
That's a lot of time for a big cat
They're quick
Yeah it's like right there I've always thought like the survival shows often don't have enough serve
Survival aspects
This gives that
Something bad could happen here
Appreciate
And then the second thing
Is head
There is no end date
Nope they just are out whoever goes login
They might as well have their hand on a car for a year
Yeah I don't want to like spoil anything about it or anything but like in the first season
The beginning of it it's really survival base traveling make fire
I have to survive because they figured out like
Okay I can get to
Some food here
I have a 10
I made a guitar and a boat yet totally totally just so bored
Just like I have
I have defeated existing but now existing
Is impossible to do that conversation of like
Am I proof
Who came in second cuz I watch the first season the guy who came in second and it was after like 3
Three or four months
And it was
Like you were just hearing him talk to a camera and you feel like he's talking
To you and then you stopped and you realized
He hasn't spoken to another human being from
The other guy is just like quoting Edgar Allan Poe
Georgia vaguely hillbilly
Or at least has a little bit of that
Deeply philosophical hillbilly
I like it
Fall off my big difference between alone and Naked and Afraid
I loved alone because they keep
Building their shelters until it looks
Cool enough for me to live it like that one play of months I know that would have build a shelter and I was like man
I kind of wish I was living there
Call the guy who made a guitar and
His mind before he decided to leave he was like
Think about make a sauna neck
You couldn't also
You got to go you got to go bad
I was talking to my friend Angela cuz I really enjoyed
I didn't know if
How it works
Like the only complaints
The only complaint in this is
This goes to what we were talking about
They should not tell the person who survived the longest that the second-to-last person has quit
They should see how long I had that thought
Someone's just out there for like six extra mods
$500,000 a lot of money that's 6 months worth of work let him stay out there
What is that hourly
They have no ability to gauge
How long other people have stayed
One guy who's the third to quit was like I'm definitely first
Totally
You just be like okay
4 month
There's a couple people still out there meanwhile two months ago everyone's gone it is a sort of prisoner's dilemma ask
Back to because you have to be in your head like well I'm a great Survivor obvious
Because I'm 4 months into this
Is the TV show man
There's got to be
9 other great survivors on the show they could be
Pick up beer for a year if you know that they're going to come and tell you when you've won then that takes away that meant
Light app
F****** with your head like maybe I want
You know it should be a surprise if you win you are alone
I'm going to watch
Sounds good
Took Jordan today we have episode to go over and what I thought we
Might do
He's talking about the trial court
Discuss Alex's press conference
But he gave on the steps
Of the courthouse
I think that there's there's a
The points that I want to make
And
Probably merits Focus
Okay
In This Moment before we do
What the hell
The first
Basket of muffins
Thank you very much
Box thank you so much and I'll probably walk
Next, Ohio thank you so much
Thank you very much room temperature
Level above that one up to the front because it's so important people know about
Relevant you're going to get pushed up and if it's
Such an important social message
It's a PS4
Feral swine
Ted Cruz is a spineless sack of jelly thank you so much
I have
Risen above
Miami
And then we're going
To come back
And I'm going to start the show over
F*** you
At the end of the day
F*** you and your new world order
She wrote in on
All your s***
Maybe today
Maybe I'll just be gone a month baby
Tomorrow
And you never see me again
What I want to do
I never want to come back
Apologize to
To the crew in the listener's yesterday that
Was legitimately have
Better tomorrow
He's not
Is that
He sucks sounds
So we recording this on Thursday evening closing arguments
Today and so when this comes out every Friday
You're listening to this there may be a verdict
For tomorrow who knows how long the jury will deliberate on this could be till next week
But I think
That's of the
Course of the content of this trial and the
Testimony that we heard was
Something with the stuff that you hear about Alex
Whether it be the business
Practices or the
Yeah I think that's a guy for the Super Bowl the Matt Miller guy was a
You know certainly that
It's not like
The biggest thing in the world champ
Crippling to Alex Azar
The lot of that stuff is there and then
I to the side of that all of the
Humanizing
And the flushing out of the people's
Experiences
Other than that
The sort of
Discussion of their loved ones yet
Enough to
Yeah to wrestle with
Yeah it is it is very much like I feel like
Everybody who wanted their say
Got there safe
And they got
To tell their story and their story was
Very very
Variant
Emotionally affecting
Powerful
And the way that they have
All
Turned their lives
Listen to something
That is
I mean just
You know it is it something that's stronger than I think I could ever
Accomplished you know like it is that kind of
God will never have to find out
Just
Yeah words almost fail me in terms of the process of this
Blast
Until we reach the end of the the trial in the testimony and closing arguments
End up with the plaintiffs lawyers
Laying out really
Concise argument about what they have discussed
There's like the appeal
To the emotions of the case scores respect for that but also the cause and effect
Alex's behavior and
The grief that was caused to these people
Then then
Norm
Paris
For the defense
Scientist going to play a 20-minute video
His own show
I thought that was strange
I mean I heard him I mean I watched the video and was
Focused on it because for some reason I thought there must be some sort of
Content reason
That he would play this video
And when you watch it you're like
I think you just didn't want to do 20 minutes of his closing argument I think it was Alex said play this or you're fired
That's my argument that Alex in Norman wanted to make this whole
Full-time is that the video the plaintiffs are showing of been taken out of context
And understand
What they're playing
So now in the closing statement
That's when Norm has disability
Need to do that
But this is kind of b******* because the exact same argument
That they use applies here
This is just like a 19-minute video from a larger show
The context of this video shouldn't be insisting you have to watch the whole show
And to be honest Alex's shows are generally emotional outburst
That are the result of some other stimulus so in order to understand the whole show you kind of need to watch the day before
The day before showing
Contact
You can see how this argument spirals out of hand easily because it's
Meaningless
Alex defends himself by saying the things are out of context if you need to see the whole clip because
He wants to be able to set the arbitrary parameter for what you need to see in order to be qualified to judge
Hate b*******
Also there's at least one added in the video that Norm plays so even that doesn't even
Hold up I'm not just that but what Norm did
In his closing argument I felt like was essentially flat
Every rule has been made so far up yet
The video
Had like five claims that you could not make in that courtroom will get to that
It it was
Explain saying that Norm had at least six or seven
Out-and-out lies that I know he knows our troop that's like physically speaking in the world we can't have
But I know Norm pattis
Note that is not true and he saying it in front of a
Judge you know so I don't think the video did as much to help Alex's cases he might have thought it would
Beyond sounding completely insane rambling about how Megyn Kelly totally wanted to f*** him and he could prove it if
He was recording at the right time
Yo man Alex also touches on a number of
F*****-up claim
He says that it's proven that the Wikileaks releases couldn't
Have been hacked and where the result of someone on-site download in the files
This is part of his Seth rich
Conspiracies and it's based on
The comments made by his buddy William Binney
It was shown
Benny that you was totally wrong and that the documents could have
Easily been downloaded remotely and Bingham
Chanted his claim
But Alex is never corrected himself or updated his talking point
So just off the bat in this closing statement Alex's reaffirming his belief that Hillary Clinton had Seth Rich killed for
Releasing the WikiLeaks
Purchase family has successfully sue people for claiming I was going to say in court he did a thing that
Gets people put in court
2 oz repeats completely false conspiracy claims about Hillary selling uranium to Russia
Forgive my language but Alex call Sandy Hook a Tar-Baby
Pete's conspiracies about Sandy Hook
Direct
Yeah he said that it's a plaintiff video where he said that and and they were like
That's going to do it
For Alex demonstrable lies about what he said about Sandy Hook
He directly contradicts videos that have already been shown in court
If this video shows anything it's completely untrustworthy source
Particularly about his own action
Five Alex claims that the Syrian gas attacks or false
In this clip Alex says that he got a cease-and-desist / retraction request about Sandy Hook that gave him a month to
And he didn't
Because he felt like he had done anything wrong
That's in the
Play I was insane
IFixit Alex severely overestimate his own ability to make a point
He's playing his video because the underlying point
He's trying to make is that he's totally cool did nothing wrong in the media is attacking them
Sandy Hook because he composes things at the
The media doesn't want the public to know
Like how asada super cool right
The thing is though that
He makes no sense
I don't see him lay out his defense
Then they would get it and it'll be game over for the plaintiff's but this video is uncompelling to anyone who doesn't already believe Alex
The s***
It's particularly useless to show people who have already seen evidence that the things he's saying in this video are b*******
If the jury already has
I get the impulse on Alex's bar
I think but in this setting it actually kind of makes his image look much worse
It is
I think
It's the wet cement
Problem
You know like if he'd gotten to play that video right
Color the jury's perception
With that video at least a little bit
You know maybe that does something
Because the cement is dry as f***
His video bounces off of it and you can
Can see every
F****** problem I'm not sure if that would
Fully work
But that Dynamic is
Very much real big
You show this video in advance and then maybe you'll have a kernel of Doubt whenever you hear him say these people are actor
Yeah yeah
Free streaming that like
Like everything is out of context that's what he does free frames events that you don't know the
Complete details about
So he's trying to do the exact same thing here the only problem is
He's not allowed to talk by him
To get to play this
Troubling clip full of b*******
Alex's used to facing no consequences being surrounded by losers on his payroll who know their unemployable anywhere else
Interviewing con artists who are financially and professionally invested in maintaining the illusion that Alex is right
And being able to hang up on or bully any callers who disagree with him in any meaningful way
He's used to his explanations for things working because the people he's explaining things to her already in his camp
The uninitiated here Resort
People who seen evidence
The contrary
This video just seems insane
What would have been useful for Norm to do would be to take
The clips of Alex saying that Sandy Hook was fake with actors that were played in court and then show the full video that the clip
From which of them reveal that the original clip
Was taken out of context
Alex is actually just asking questions or Playing devil's advocate
Absolutely can't do that though because those clips are out of context the problem
Old Norm can do is insinuate that the larger context completely absolves Alex
But it's b*******
Norm's other arguments that Alex's actions were driven by a fear that the government was going to take the gun
It's not by a desire to endanger
Grieving parents for money
But
The reality is that I was in danger grieving parents in order to push his narrative surrounding the fears about the government take
Which is something he embellishes exaggerated sin sensational izes
In order to make money
It's not one thing or the other is Norma's pretending it's
Dynamic system that Alex uses
Don't understand this he's been a guest on the show numerous times
If you watch this
How to get the sense that Norm doesn't believe a goddamn word he's saying
It's just that there's no other real way to argue this
And the bravado that he had about
The families
Exaggerating their grief
Probably
That's the sort of
Talking isn't going to play too well with a jury after days of hearing from said family members about the pain they've been doing
Yeah he tried to bring that exaggeration Point backup
But you heard how much more apologetic and careful he was about it
As opposed to the sort of cocky swinging Dickie had in the open
I was trying
Nor was desperate to try and make this
Lytical in his closing
Trying to shoehorn in references to Trump
And getting shot down with objections along the way
He also tried to make a mockery of the idea that the plaintiff's who testified and said that they didn't know what Alex's
Positions on guns
Where they they didn't notice position
I don't want to
Touch on this for a second
When you live by the sword it's not a certainty that you're going to die by the sword
If you do
You have an obligation to accept your death by the sword
Alex is most consistent defensive himself is that he's being taken out of context and that you can't understand what he saying
Short clips
I think this is bulshit but it's the foundation of norms defense
And their position
So he has to accept
It's all good fun for him when he wants to claim that Alex mocking Robbie Parker was out of context
It's so weird how he doesn't realize that this Cuts both ways
He can show the jury a clip of Alex saying they're coming for our guns or they're staging shootings to take our guns and
If he's being intellectually consistent he should know that the jury camp
Possibly know what Alex's position on guns is
Without watching the whole video
Innocent
Norm's underlying defense strategy precludes him from being able to expect that he's able to
Approve anything
This is also a corollary of one of Alex's other defense
What he's accused of anything and then shown video with him doing or saying the thing he's accused of his contacts.
Satire
If that is what I want to say
And if the entirety of his on-air career isn't allowed
Be shown in his custody hearing because he's putting on a performance
Then why should the plaintiffs in this case take him at his word
Bernie says something on air
He could lay out his entire philosophy on guns
Succinctly on his show and the plaintiffs would have every right to say
The wealthy did say
See things on are they have no way of knowing what Alex's sincere positions are
How to get a lot of mileage out of people knowing he's a fraud and
McGuire's where you can wiggle out of trouble by disowning the things he says on Erin's being Seattle
Satire
But the other side of this
Is this
If you want Norm to insist that the Sandy Hook families are suing them because of their opposition to his position on guns
You have no right to claim that they even know what those positions are
It's called being hoisted on your own petard
There is bad
Told you can't understand what I'm saying on air
Expected you get to use that other opposite for your own purposes
It was a bad closing
Statement describes full all around
And f******
Yeah yeah the moment where Norm
I mean I really thought the
Set Norm should have been packed
Buy likes
Deal of law because the moment he was like full from Night Court
What attacks them
Cuz he was playing the video
And the norm said he was trying to insinuate the thing that he's been trying to insinuate the entire f****** time and
Everyone has stopped him and they still let him do it and then the objection was sustained but it doesn't f****** matter cuz again
He got to say
Why did they come with this
Ed with this lawsuit
It's because of the guy who said good job Alex right instead of saying cuz he can't say it's Trump
Yeah he can't say they're coming after Trump but it can't play a video where Alex references Trump and then references
Maybe he was referencing
Pronoun still refer to a thing
I think I was painfully obvious
I don't think the jury's dumb
I think that they get that too
To the extent
They have any awareness
Of
Why
It's inappropriate
This Behavior understand like
This is this guy's trying to do something he's not allowed to do
Yeah and I already have faith that those bill
Sucks that out I don't think it's too hard after a like eventually
No matter what you're like oh this kid is trying to break into
Do the cookie jar
I get it then and then
Dude with the
Attorney prayer or whatever the f*** f*** that was rough what the fuk was that was embarrassing
Corroborated that that an attorney's prayer
Has anybody said that attorneys pray like that is any attorney ever prayed like that I could see it being like
Placemat
Grandma your lawyer grandma gets it for you
Circle these words of the prayer
That was tough
Yeah and then
Nor might have protested a little too much about how proud he is to keep
He kept saying like I'm exactly where I live. So proud of you
Felt a little bit like somebody
Talking themselves up of
Like no no no I am not ashamed to be here it was it was a little bit like a shirtless
Naked man walking into Congress being like all I'm so mister
Chris Smith I am going to f******
Filibuster this s*** everyone's going to be like look at this
Genius
I think we
Are foolish for except expecting more
From a guy who drops
Does pancit has the underwear course we are of course we are
Norm's Behavior throughout the entirety of this proceeding has been
Shameful
I hope you enjoyed
Being second banana on Infowars to Barnstead a lawyer
Yeah I don't know I don't know really what
I can't I find it difficult to imagine he'll
I have too much cash I wouldn't
I wouldn't hire him
It's just been bad
But
I think there's something else that is
And that is Alex
So he went
To Connecticut
Little bit back
Justified
Add a little bit of a meltdown
Had to get away from The Buttery
Right went back to Austin to do his bulshit with Barnes say the same thing as fake again
Flew back to Connecticut
Right
And then the idea was that
Nor was going to call him as a witness for the defense
The only Witness
Yeah
And this game was being played
And Alex came back
And now that both sides have rested the closing documents have been made
We know that he did not testify
Like Brave sir Robin he ran away
It's
He went to Connecticut for
Essentially no reason
Except
Well
Promotion
He went
Publicity
He went to get attention
And
It is my firm contention that
He never
Even considered
Testifying again
He went
Specifically to get as much attention as he could
With the
Pretense
That maybe I'll testify
Or maybe I will
He went there because he knew he was going to get that press conference right outside the court
Always gets it because
Everybody who works in the media is fuc
Here a little bit adapter
This press conference
Because I found it
Tubi
Great
The best quotes
None of those things
Here's where we start off
And I should give you a little bit of a sort of tableau
Alex & Barnes
AR
Standing behind so camera
Now little bit later Alex Alex
Stowaway well
We'll actually find out why Barnes is there a little bit later and it's very sad
A little bit later Alex is talking to some people and Fielding questions
And he's holding up a copy of his book
So obviously like this is all this
Getting your your product
On the news
This is the game that's being played
Bruce standing there with Bart
I really
For being here today
Alex said f*** you at that point
Constitutional
First Amendment
Criminal lawyer who also worked on
For several years he can give you documented evidence
We gave them all the
Discovery
Case
The Poltergeist
Because I'm the villain
That deserves
To be found guilty by the
Kangaroo court
So yeah Barnes was working on the case
If you have heard the deposition episodes that you'll know this but just to revisit
This is Brittany Paws testifying under oath
That they're considering suing Barnes
I went over this a little bit with me
The kind of company decided one way
Play or another
We have not decided
They're considering suing their previous lawyers for malpractice
Sprite
Justin Bieber
Totally clear
They also discuss which lawyers there was a problem with
I'm not sure about
Barnes
Bobby bonds
You can tell there is a heavy bar
Barnes and then exhale
I got some issues with bar
That's a
Personal Excel that is a woman who is talk to Barnes and when I do not like
Conversely someone who has is a lawyer and is looked
What happened except is like
This is exasperatingly
I can't get into any of this but
I have an issue with Barnes
Good good guy too
Explain how you
Did this case by the book
Good guy to bring with you for your dumb publicity stunt in front of the courthouse
Keep in mind
The people in the court
House
Are having their day in court
They're doing something
Incredibly difficult
They're being disrespected by Norm routinely
And
This is what Alex is doing
Wow that's going on
Operate II
I need I need
This to be hammered into the head of every journalist alive
Like with a
F****** hammer
When you give Alex that prescon
Outside of the Court
There's two things you're showing your showing the difference between what you're allowed to do inside the cork
88 a wall separate
Being allowed to lie
To the entire world and being allowed to f****** lie to a judge
Right
And then second
If you are giving him that press
You're the editor forcing somebody to go give him that press conference
Who are you doing this for
You're not doing it for you're not helping the families at all
But you're not helping measuring officers it
You're not helping
Anybody
But Alex
And I guess
The corporation you f***
King work for
Yeah those are the people that you care about if that's what you're going to do
Those are the people you care about
Give up any other
F******
Argue many give them a little bit less of a hard time because
Some of them were probably
On the beach
I know that you're a better person that I assure
One thing that sticks out to me about what you're saying is he does highlight the difference between what you could say in court
You can say it outside on the steps
And
I think
That imbalance
Should be
Chao 2 hour
What's your first amendment right that's kind of why I think
You know I get a little uncomfortable with your instinct to Barca
Two people in
You know whatever
That is why someone like you should actually have to be there for all the press conferences
What in the courtroom people ask you polite question
Be a piece of s*** because nobody else will be and he's going to be
You want it only exists in the wilderness of these steps totally
Then I will be a bear or whatever because the bailiff
Will come and stop me from interrupt
Sing him
That's f*****
Yeah I'm protect
Hemet
Make sure he's okay and nobody's mean to him difference I suppose
Is that like
You have the awareness that you yelling at him is disrespectful to the court itself as well
Disrespectful to what the families and all them are doing
I think that's another thing that Alex weaponizes got like people of good heart and good conscience went to make a scene
And treat him the way he deserves to be treated on the staff
And this is a result
This is why you I do need to be there is because I was in if you recall I went to the f***
King Lou
And there was a kid who stepped over a kid
French
Not my child obviously parents nowhere to be found in the kid was like
Taking picture and was getting too close and I was like hey
Get the f*** out of here
Real loud and everybody was like
Good call that kid needs to get the f*** out of here so that's what I'm here for
That's my job
Trey Mall
Nebraska
Justice
Itself is on
America
Injustice
On trial
Even the worst
People in the world
Which I'm not
A bad person
Some say
I deserve my day
Newspaper
I'm not allowed
Defend myself
Nautical publish Esther
Alex Jones
Star Supply
Here's what we know
Himself
They had three weeks of
People up there lying about me
Twisting what I said
Memorial
Kill
This article in the current doesn't say this
It says quote
Johnson his company Free Speech systems have been prohibited from defending themselves under the default
But
Kim try to minimize what they have to pay
Incapacity and punitive damages
Alex campus and himself under the
The default
That's an important distinction because
Get every opportunity to defend himself when that was appropriate but
He didn't he was so abusive of the process that he was defaulted
He can't now take this damage is hearing as an opportunity to try and undo the default or
As if he hadn't been defaulted
He f*****
Himself over in this is a consequence of that
Yes every
Ability to defend himself in the context of this damages
Which is the second part of the sentence
In that current article that
But he's ignoring
He can try to minimize the damages
That's the damages hearing equivalent of defending him
Boy being out to the f******
Baby and Barnes is tag-along to Connecticut with him because Barnes
He just loves the public
A problem being a disrespectful s*******
It get some attention
Maybe drives a couple more people into his revenue streams like on that patreon clone at unhinged
Assholes
Span I beam the the f****** cycle the psychopathy of doing that
You know like that's not
I wouldn't I would up I mean I guess
Separated from Humanity you know you're in a studio
It's just you and Alex he's easier to step into the world where you can be a piece of s*** to be a psycho and
To go and stand on the steps
And watch
Alex do that s*** all the steps that are required
Get you there yet the plan
Got to get lodging and insecurity
Knowing that what you're doing is just
Traveling to another city to disrespect
F****** people that you've hurt
Yep that's what you're doing
Yeah but like later he is just holding up a copy of his
This is a publicity stunt for Alex
Pure and simple
That's why he went to Connecticut
Give no intention of ever testifying but
Since the bankruptcy court has taken over his business as finances
I bet he had to pretend that he was going to testify in order to rationalize the expense of his travel
Who probably not fly as business
Transfer Company in bankruptcy to say hey I want to go across the country with my s******* lawyer friend so I can promote my book
On the steps of the courthouse
Swear I'm avoiding testifying cuz I'm
Scared I bet the bankruptcy court would be like yeah
No
I'm in the back and it's not going to be in
Expect
Going to fly
Yeah I got it
I got a charter a plane so I can
Try and get some attention I'm going to throw this out at you how do you feel about an aisle seat
I went to the tremendous peace of s*** in this press conference is a new level of inexcusable act on his part
He could have stayed the f****** Texas
There was no need for him to go to Connecticut just so he could siphon off some of the attention from this trial in order to Grant
Stand in front of
The court with barn
Instatrim promote is stupid
It's honestly difficult to think of a way he could have been more disrespectful to the families inside just trying to get there.
In court
It's one thing for him to be afraid to sincerely face them and accept responsibility for his part and everything that's happened
Entirely another thing to do this
Stop it
I don't know man
I have I have a lot of words for him and I don't know
Can't blame Alex for this I mean true
He's discussed
He's a monster
But I wouldn't want to go back and absolutely
The worst thing for your defense
If cowardice is a given
Of course yes
The problem I have is
When we talked about enablers
We do not often talk about ourselves
You know like
No not us
Obviously if it's
If he ever mentioned our name maybe we could talk about us being enablers but
Kaiser of knowledge first
It does feel like everyone is in a attempt
To keep us from doing that
Who is enabling him
Who is enabling him to do that he's not going out there
Thinking
But he's not going to get oppressed
There are people in neighboring him
Who are making money off of letting Alex make money off of abusing these people and I do
Don't find it acceptable behavior I don't I don't find it acceptable honestly don't understand another
It would go without like a gag order
Understand
I don't
Think that anybody is making
Like
Super wrong
Choices given the
The circumstance
I think that local news it makes sense that they would be there here Alex is giving a statement
It makes sense to document it
I don't
I don't know
Is this is different to me than somebody like
Alex Lee boilermaking that documentary you know what
There's a series of decisions that don't need to be made
That led to that
Where is Alex speaking out
In front of the court and people recording it
I hate that it's happening
I hate that this
Do something that happened
But
I mean I'm not arguing for the world that we currently exist in
That they should be somehow like
Punisher
Prayer Behavior that's terrible what I'm arguing is that
The current world that we existed is not capable of
Handling this
In any responsible way exacerbating it as time goes on
Man so I mean my argument is
All of society is bad
Your first thoughts about the judge
This is not a trial
Testify two weeks ago
I came here this time.
Today
But she will hold me
Did I say I'm bankrupt
First person to climb
Sandy Hook
Andover 10 other things
Has ever told somebody
What they can and can't say
That doesn't sound true at all
Ask me question
Or I'll be arrested
If I tell
The truth
This is outrageous
You're all having
More freedom
Going to be held in contempt because
If you did any of that stuff he be acting in ways that are contemptuous to the Core
He's not allowed to train re-litigate his default in this setting because to do so would run a very high risk of poisoning the
Jewelry
The jury isn't there to determine Alex's culpability that's been
Decided so for him to rant about this irrelevant nonsense
He's an act of contempt of the Court
Judges very regularly hold people in contempt if you don't stop yelling about things that aren't germane to the matter at hand
You will be held in contempt
It happens all the time
I was just doesn't want to accept that he's a petulant child who can't allow for their being rules that he's subject to
He's trying to turn it into a constitutional issue
Don't b*******
Legit
What am I mean that's kind of what I was watching during that closing
Whenever they played the clip
Is that like
He would have been held in criminal contempt
If he had said those
So why in God's name are you allowing him to say those things
The Thriller video
He should still be held in criminal contempt for that
A norm should be as well for or some of that like
I
I don't know how courts work
Me neither I would have probably stop that video
Yeah totally
I said the stuff that we said he can't say if he must hear
He would be going to jail maybe there's a different way that things work in terms of like the closing statement
What's an opening statement
It's there not evidentiary that's possible
Still
Don't ask me
But also Alex wouldn't be perjuring himself if he told the truth
He wouldn't
He wouldn't have to perjure himself to answer any of those questions
He would have to purge or what
He believes of himself
You'd have to
Encroach upon his self perception
And that is something that he
Is too afraid to do
Yeah it is it is a moment for Alex that is change or die
And he can't change
But he's probably not going to die either
Cuz I'm at metaphor
Sure
So you asked why Barnes is there
I am interested Piazza new position at Infowars I got no
Robert Barnes
First person
That is
American just
Itself on trial
So this raises the issue of whether or not Barnes is an official spokesperson is he on the payroll again now
And if so is this just a way for Alex
It's to try to rationalize the bankruptcy court to pay for Barnes to travel
To Connecticut for their stupid publicity stock
Does a
It's a question worth asking
Yeah
Man
They're just
It should be harder to be
Sneaky
Hanging out it should be harder to trick a bankruptcy court I would suggest that this is evidence that it is very hard to
Be sneaky very sneaky
That is true
I think we're talkin about this from different directions
If there was anybody
But Alex
Who determined whether or not he test
Then I be like well you know maybe he went there expecting that he might testify and then he just didn't write
But in this case
It's all out
Well you made the decision and I
Guarantee
T he made it before he left office
Well I can say that of all of the corporate Representatives
Who has been asked the
Bastion of
Can anyone tell Alex what to do
Not one of them has said anything other than
Nope no absolutely not nobody can tell us what to do when you make all the decisions completely by himself represented
Employees consistent
Alex
It's just does whatever the f*** he wants to do
To look it's a bad times if Alex testify
Because
He's going to get locked up
Everybody knows
You're the one person who is
Any day Inn
In court is Alex
To such a degree in a car for a month and he was already in there once
Testifies
Honestly
Justified truth
But have you answered
The questions in the way the planets
Lawyers one
Also go to J
No matter what he does he goes
J lift
Testify in his own behalf
In his own.
How
It doesn't make sense now he'll go to jail I understand this fantasy about it being locked up for 6 months for criminal contempt
You know if you need a ride
Okay what's my agenda scenario where they ask like did you say that the Sandy Hook families were actor
Yes how's that going to bring him to jail
No Doubt
This is bulshit
This is so stupid
Barnes
Come on man
Alex lies in court
Enough
Sooner or later
Someone will do something to stop him
And if whatever it is that it takes eventually wind up being prison it's going to be a long
Long way away
Imagine a world where they ask him all these questions that are like did you do this
Did you do this
Yes he says ever
In a way that is advantageous to the plaintiffs attorneys
How does he go to jail
Trial know it'll happen is
The walls will suddenly fall down the trunk realize that we're all already in jail
Exactly see that
That's the twist right Alex says I did it and then black doors
Do you know a lot of smoke
So ridiculous
As we know from listening to Alex's show Barnes has his own little pet conspiracy about Saint
Sandy Hook
The store they told about
Was not true
In the sense that they blame
Gun owners
Blamed Alex
It's going for what happened
When the reality is
Is it school safety was not up
Democratic College
Decided the pocket money method
Supertech little kids lives
And little kids died
Didn't mean to.
Does politician
That's the real
But they can't have any of that
Holyshit hay barns
I know a school safety officer you should talk to
Used to be a freak
Cast on Alex's show
Wolfgang halbig
Kim
Buddy
This isn't good I mean I
Need to keep clarifying this
This is sad on the steps
This is bulshit
I'm writing up
Los
Stuff
If I hear him well.
If I hear him say that outside of a courtroom I'm like blah stuff needs to happen to stop this already
I don't know what law stuff needs to happen but I know it does
Yeah yeah
I just
Play words fail you know we we talked about this in the days coming up to the
The trial
That kind of idea of like
If he gets a judgement
What is going to make him stop
And if Barnes is outside of the courthouse
Outside of the courthouse
Days before they go to deliberation
Making vague insinuations about
What he's doing
Vague claims about
Various
Democrat politician
Right
Reticular in a different context
That is
Fine but in this context
You are denying Sandy
In an accounting office or something like that maybe put the water cooler
This is not
Number one
Relevant
Number to Noland blamed Alex
Sandy Hook
Bill
This
Outrageous
Unacceptable
Anyway this is.
Why are they so scared and terrified
The truth why are they so afraid of
What they say about Alex Jones
True why are they willing to allow Alex Jones to have his day in court
These are questions every American
Everyone was so willing to let him have his
Fucken are you going to show up to
Ben said I've been involved
With the plaintiffs attorneys in Texas course
I know from
Conversations with them
Very
Willing
Quite a surprise
When there was a default
And
That
Would have been fine
Done what he was supposed to do
Send
Competent
Corporate represent totally allowed to
Disclosure things to happen with
Discovery
They were perfectly happy to let him have his day in court every opportunity
We could have had this thing wrapped up in
In f****** 26
Yeah you didn't want his day in court
Maybe a little after that but yeah
Barnes
Feel like he's
Getting dangerously close
Climbing 12 saying some things that aren't
Appropriate about some one of the plaintiff all my stuff on Alex's show already
What is dislike
Tell if they were working out their talking points working out their B
On his show and then now they're just doing it in front of the court
Here you have a case
FBI agent
Are our current FBI
Lawyers
Don't know anybody who died in
I mean
What is FBI agent
Canal sue people
For raising Quest
About what took place
Various cases
Everybody who Quest
The government now go to jail
Testify truthfully in their own defense
Do they all go
Get bankrupt
Into Oblivion
Because that is a
Future we face if we allow Presa
Didn't like this.
Such an abusive of
Logic it's pretty ridiculous
It's a disgrace
For Barnes to pretend that bill Altenburg is just an FBI
Agent or FBI lawyer he knows better he knows exactly why he's one of the plaintiff
This is bulshit I mean
You compare that
And this was a good one of the more powerful things
That you could hear is that
The FBI agent
Himself bill
Testifying
I wish I'd worn a different jacket
Maybe that would have
To change something
Can you add like
That kind of
That kind of weird Gill
That should never have even a
Existed
Just like man if I'd worn a different shirt
For ten years these people would have been a
You know
Saying that level of irrational guilt he knows if they're rational man's gone to therapy for years you know like
You can never
It's just f***** up man
That is plucked
And Barnes is a disrespectful
Yeah
I'm not Adam Lanza
I didn't kill those kids
But people don't know
We'll take a few questions
Animal going to come back later obviously
Listen close
Considering tomorrow
When I get put on the stand
Looking at the judge
Just saying you Barbie
Medicine
This isn't a real Court
Amendment
I was just never considering pleading the fifth because he was never going back into that Court
He was only going to testify if Norm
Called him and he knew normal isn't going to
He pays Norm
This is all just artificial bravado and it
Alex is Bart to get headlines written about
Speculation about him
This is desperate
Pathetic
To use the trial is a promotional event
Also more people know who Alex has been Adam Lanza because Alex is a giant media celebrity with an audience of millions of people
Lenses a notable name
He's a murderer from about a decade ago so maybe his name recognition isn't the same as a giant media
Celebrity who's the textbook
Definition of a f******
Attention w****
Get out of your Alex Adam Lanza's name is in the first
Who gives a f***
This charade that Alex is using about like everyone thinks that I did this or
They don't know who Adam Lanza's we know who I am is is
Is just
Yeah you're living in f***
In Candyland
Infuriate
Yep
Pleading the fifth
Yeah
So I take the
Guilty
She says
The truth shall put
In the Waterbury jail
6 months
That doesn't make sense
Never before in a Civil Trial is the Fifth Amendment needed
Top lawyers
It looked at it
And say no
She wants to put you
Drudge
And you are guilty of
So I guess the judges part of the new world order now
Many
People
Use the fifth in
In civil cases
That's not
Titan of men
Yeah that not like I sometimes outrageously
False
Standing there is embarrassing
Constitutional lawyer in no one's ever used the 5th before civil case
But Alex says top lawyers
He's just talking
And maybe Norma consultation
Anymore he probably wants to forget his
So yeah he's going to take some questions but we know Alex there something that comes for
You have heard
Little America
You're going to sell something
Yeah right to say he was in
Think about
You're being robbed
Process
Stanford
Dot-com
Yourself
Walmart books for the world
The War of the Worlds
Papa film
I barely covered
That's a lie
And I did
Warren Police
Apologize
Years and years before I was too
Cannot send
Do you notice here that I can't even bring himself to admit that he called them actors when he's explaining what
He did wrong that he claims he's apologized
S4
You can only use these vague terms like that he called it staged
He's doing this because even he knows that his real actions are indefensible but if he lies about what he actually did
Becomes a little bit more understandable how we could make these mistakes and such
He's doing this because he's a coward and a liar
Simple
And nobody's challenging
He gets old sad and predictable that's like a plug is going to come in here
You're doing this
Bulshit disrespectful act on the courts
Have to plug
Yeah
Yeah Heil Darvish this is just like that
What I'm for is when he's about to say
Infowars I buy just go airhorn yeah absolutely
Bring back the who's Allah
Media dum-dums
You're here
You don't know when he's going to do a f****** ad pissed but even they kind of felt
I'm sure Liz was like a f******
He's going to do it
Shitzo know is the name of his book going to no kidding
So you take some Quest
And you know I think
I think actually some of the
Some of the people if they were asked
Questions for rational people they would be fine question
Alex they don't know like
Right you're not going
How to get to know what you think you're you think you're going to get something you are not going to
The first question is what do you say to the harasser
The original people
Professors
Opera
And they never told
Anybody to go rest
If you mentally ill people get harassed
Family
Add Alexa
I put the
People that are
Public figures
And met with Obama
10TV
You do a lot of folks are pro-gun
Didn't like those
Family
Not sure anybody
Able to do that
There's tons about
That part where you said release the Kraken is a real issue
Instant promotion of Wolfgang halbig another very big piece of it
Jail time
Yeah man I mean this is
Just you know you can just say these things and
Just bullshittin then they'll write it down and put it out there
You know this is a local news peace and maybe they would play this and
And then be like
Not back in the studio sounds like this is totally me
I imagine you know I didn't see the local news peace imagine if you're watching local news in Connecticut
Probably not going to be
Probably not
I mean I certainly wouldn't be if I knew that he was coming to disrespect your f****** town like this
Make a mockery of the proceedings and
Try and sell books on the courtrooms better Community is gone
Through
Together
Yeah so
Also ask the question there's like
There is
Tomorrow that's something you're really considering
I'm not going
I don't recall teleprompters I don't give
Scripps
Go to jail tomorrow
If I get any other answer
I don't know
Isn't it true you make money off
No
The judge says I'll go to jail
She says I did it's a lie
But you didn't give us a banana
You're guilty
Do you understand
The kangaroo trial
This is a fraud
Pictures of danger
Alright
Find the truth
Infowars.com
God bless
Yes I mean he only took a few classes mostly just needed Barnes ranting about bulshit
Yep that sounds about right
He didn't end up also answering some other questions from people this is not
On the video that he put out on his own website
Interesting yeah it's
Stream because some of it
I mean it sounds bad
They're going to be snowing
A Thousand Years
Name a whole planet
Okay
This is a damn
Oaxaca
What about it
I don't have to
$2000000
I don't have all the
Put money in crap they talked about so they can
Billion dollar verdict they're going to get anything
Charities
Cash machine
Is
Unaccepted
Stephen knows that like
Let's not play that part on info
Pretend that didn't happen
Where I'm laughing about they're not going to get in my money because I don't have any haha the joke's on them and
Calling the
This trial a publicity stunt while he publicity stunt
Call Nieves tabs
I think I think saying that they're squeezing money out of the dead kids is
Pretty grotesque f****** thing for him to say
Yeah you know when people are like he should have gotten his ass kicked when he was younger like
We're leaving out the many people get serious head injury
Like Alex got his ass kicked enough but I think he's
F***** in the head
Maybe we maybe we need to talk more about that
I mean
There's an inability to control himself it is absolutely true
But he can control himself enough
Navigate
Doing s*** like this
Yeah
Mr. Magoo like right
F****** around and everything just falls into place for him
Magoo was like deeply malicious
Yeah
So I wanted to
Take this
Episode
To Alex's been in Connecticut has been hosting the show
Mohammed Barnesville still pop in
Here in there
But like I wanted to take
An opportunity to really look at like
This is this man
That's is what he's doing
I think
In terms of
His behavior
Obviously
He could do what he wants on his show
And there's a level of that that is disgusting
Toxic and I
Jenna Dewan ignore it totally
But
The idea of it
He would
Take the time
To go to Connecticut
To do
Who's this
Is
Hey baby paint
It paints a picture of a real piece of s***
Yeah and and again
This is outside the walls
Like
The families could have been in the hallway and
Turned around
And heard this
Like how it's supposed modest earlier for doing this s*** expect like do your own research
I would tell the jury
Chance of a jury could have heard
And that's legal
Alex has no way of knowing
Like if the families were outside
Within earshot
Just just a f****** psycho
Yep yep
Jesus
I'm sorry to make
This the episode where we're going to launch it to the weekend
Things on like a easy breezy kind of place
But who knows maybe there'll be a verdict in little
Do you know
Be high I'll tell you if if half a billion-dollar judge week is handed down what's going to be a good week
It'll make it'll take a little bit of a bomb on this it'll be nice
Of Alex's bullshittin yep
Anyway we'll be back on Monday with another episode
Not about
Adult publicity stunt press conference
Ross on Twitter
Slip will be back
But until then
Amigo
DCs
Text Clark
I'm Wilford Sanibel Snapple of the Gravel Pit
What the sex robe
Holding
Alex