Damned important
I have great respect for knowledge by knowledge I'm sick of them posing as you're through the good guy
We are the bad guy
Need
Knowledge fight
The altar of saline and talk a little bit about
Alex Jones
My Brightspot Jordan spoiler alert
Extreme Rules WWE pay-per-view
It was fine
Fine
And then at the end
I got it
Lights went out okay
He's got the whole world
Everywhere
Very exciting
Scott is Lantern
He's doing the whole thing
I don't know I wouldn't say it didn't look exactly like he was back to swamp hillbilly Hawaiian shirt Brea
Gotcha okay
And I think today would be
Take to go back to
I think the Hawaiian shirt is always at
Personally I think that
He has grown past that stage that character is coming to gone and evolved into the fiend
Right + Erick Rowan
One of his guys isn't there anymore and Luke Harper the other guy who was in his
Wyatt Family
His now passed away yeah and so it would be
Kind of tough
To recapture
Some of what the Wyatt family was
I think it wouldn't be worth to
We going back to that but I also think going back to the fiend thing
Might be a mistake at this point too so I'm glad that he had his mask
Right
I am so like
It's not
I don't think it's going to be horror supervillain anything but
I'm so excited
Did you see your back
I don't even watch wrestling that much and I'm very excited for him
He's a he's a
There's something about that Bray Wyatt fella it is it is really interesting because we've talked about him
Extensively despite the fact that I never watch
Wrestling interested in the character was interesting is that it seems like
That's a character that is great
For wrestling that they really don't know how to make
Work you know they're like
This character is great
Let's try putting him places and then I got all know that's not where it goes like the Undertaker
This guy who's
Supernatural powers
Right kind of busy come back from the dead repeatedly kind of
It's fine don't worry about it
Far
With some of the Bray Wyatt stuff
That's true that's okay
Immoral sister powers
Like Firefly fun house thing I think it's
Fine because
If you really think about
Bray Wyatt
He had a superpower when he was a swamp hillbilly called later and that was largely manipulation
You was really good at manipulating people which is
Is the human superpower that people can have
You cannot see the the purerb
Bug eyes of delight that huh
You can see
Going into people's heads extension of that already.
Power
They're like the battle within their mind
Is kind of an artistic expression of what
The person is going through wow they're being manipulated or whatever
You could see that being okay sure
Once you've got like
Indestructibility
Your presence in a fighting League
The cruel The crucial part of a fighting league is the possibility of lost right so I hope I hope
Interesting will happen
Some face
And fingers crossed
What's a yurt
My bright spot is dead
I know it is that
Rcap
Garbage
Garbage couch we've had it's been torn up it's time to get rid of the couch
A little bit
Little bit
My wife comes up with the brilliant idea
It's her birthday
Play weekend as well
Replace everything
With a giant bean bag chair
And my friend
Brilliant idea that's an interesting gamble genius idea we got it it's eight feet long
Several hundred pounds wow
Long beam man it's the size of your couch Tire bean bag
Multiple people can sleep on in the whole thing
Incredible
I'm telling you I fell asleep on it last night
And I didn't mean to I looked over I was like
And then I was gone it was 7 a.m. this morning
Is that
It's like a cloud
It's the new water bat
She she wins
Forever cuz that thing is incredible
Balter birthday weekend
Okay.
That sounds really cool I mean like I don't think I have any negative memories of your couch
That sounds like a
Still an upgrade
Call man
Do you got a
Evangelize for bean bag
I'm not talking about any brand I don't want anybody to go buy a bean bag I mean
If you got 8 ft of something that you can fit bean bags in
And you get a couch
Mandy
Do your ears angeleyes in for the idea of it like like those commercials you'd see for milk
It's not a brand of milk
So Jordan today we got an episode to go over
About
October 6th
2022 that is Thursday of last week that closing arguments were happening and the jury began
Right
Deliberation I guess
Although I got most of that was
What's Friday
They will be back
In session on Tuesday and I would be surprised
Like we didn't have a verdict
Damages
Claim
I said it and it didn't feel right in a criminal trial
Resume that comes down on Friday
The end of the day on Friday
They were asking the jury had a question for the judge was
Is there a reason that Lafferty's name is first
Among the plaintiff it's Lafferty at all Verizon
That to me the reason you would ask that
Is
To figure out if some people should get more than
Spreading It Out Among the people or if it's equal
And to be that kind of has the indication of like pretty
Yeah if they're if they're like wait so if Lafferty's the first name does that mean that we should get Lafferty
You know like should laugh pretty good little bit of an extra jump that's how I read it yeah that seems about right that's the truth another
Other way to interpret it there might be but
It feels like
Tuesday's probably
Yeah I would be I mean I would I would say that
Are are Vibe with the broad Strokes
I've been kind of banged out now we're getting down to the details
We'll see about that but it's interesting to see how I was doing on the day
Day of the closing
See how it goes
Before we get to that let's take first
Ewok
Thank you very much
Luxembourg Erwin goalie Luxembourg City the grand duchy of Luxembourg.
Germany Alex you f****** dope
Thank you very much I love that part of Austria
Say something kind of fun with these buttons
And I wanted to write Luxembourg France but I realize like this is not the place for a joke
About the time maybe you can write it on the inside of the optical one setting you don't want to make a geography
Pizza Pizazz
Envelopes I know but whoever got those in France would have been like this was very funny
Brexit because of Dan and knowledge fight I am into country music
Thank you very much all right
I'm on fire
Scrambled eggs in her sweet baby
Thank you very much
But that's a scary cat cat with a Hitler mustache apparently
Pro
Croquette
What
That is not into Hitler
I don't I hope
Okay alright I'm assured that this is a cute thing okay
Thank you so much you and I both
Jordan before we get into this episode here is a little out of context drop
Sahbabii
Liberal
That's that's you know what word has turned into something
Without meeting whatever you're just saying it like that
In that context yeah it's it's Alex it's a sort of like get her done
Meaningless phrase
Start off here and Alex is really big into the nuclear war
Discussion and so that kind of kind of
The beginning
The US government is coming out here
I've been secretly buying
Potassium iodide pills
We're not just people in Europe
Not just the troops in Europe. Just the CIA
Boys
And it's also come out last week to federal employees
Emergency evacuation plan
Too deep underground bases
Happy wow
Everywhere that billionaires
Are already moving into their bunkers
In the southern hemisphere
Can I that in depth
Discussions with not one not
Well-known billionaire
About when do they sing
They should relocate
Hemisphere
Is that a good idea
They said well are you going to relocate
Shmoney
I have a
A trailer
On their Ranch
Has been our
Beautiful Turtle Lake everything else
I will just go there and probably die
During all this
Parents buy a trailer in 1820
No it's it's from like a land-grant not the trailer no no no
Antique trailer
So the idea the Billionaire's is ridiculous on its face
Even the little complaint about of course
Stinky has more money than he does
There's a kernel of Truth to the story that Alex is telling about the US government buying a bunch of pills
The treat radiation poison
But he's just way off of
He's telling the story wrong
This is about a recent 290 million-dollar purchase of a drug called nplate
Text Will Go On to say
And such but Alex is really a
Details guys up
This is not the first time that the government to Administration for strategic preparedness and response is purchase
Just such medication
But it is the first time with nplate mostly because he was only approved for this purpose
In 2021
This is the end result of financing the HHS began in 2019 on this drug and it serves a purpose in this
Strategic National stockpile
But it apparently isn't that great of a drug to respond to nuclear attack
Predominantly because it needs to be used
Fairly quickly after exposure
To be effective
So it's like a city was new to this wouldn't really
Useful to difficult situation
Jason Whittaker then you could do that and then on
Upon the completion
Alicia newadvent ache
The drug I would assume that that would be a very helpful Eureka
This is not a strong indicator that we are more or less likely to be involved in a nuclear confrontation
This is Alex's big Naruto
Kuva diseased onto the backburner where patli Millions people are being killed by the vaccine all the time and there's a new bombshell
Everyday but
This isn't really Varsity storyline but
Material anymore
The audience's kind of burned out on this I think I mean
The first
Few weeks of the millions and billions of people dying everyday you're like this is big news
Then after you've seen suppose mathematically
2.3 billion people died in the past two months you know you're like Wyatt Alex continue to talk about the story
Bora Bora
For Alex's audience to believe that any of the stuff that he saying
Is true there have to be bodies piled up everywhere everywhere we would have to be
Bring out your dead level like yeah
He can only lie about his trial so much before it turns into Lenny Bruce and the prospect of nuclear war is
It's exactly the kind of thing that will keep the audience
Just the right kind of scared
This weekend expected any headline that even halfway sounds like a good
Possibly point to Russian nuke in the US
Is going to be covered as proof that that's just around the corner
It's a pretty sweet deal to because when Alex makes mistakes
That severe
It's really easy for him to
Skewer his obvious support for Putin
Yeah
Call Blake
All over the place just win win win
I do appreciate
I do appreciate that
Where were talking about a guy who's who's like
A an inveterate Kahneman and salesman and and liar and all the stuff and it's like
When you're talking about nuclear war and billionaires and yet you're still adding that like
Old-timer
I talked to not one
Not too
That's right
3 billionaires about evacuating from their home you know any like okay Jesus Christ This is
Going to also
It's
Snake oil
Who are they
I think he wants us to think one
Elon Musk
Right
Right I think.
Well yeah that makes sense cuz he's a piece of s***
Yeah and slogans
No
I mean
Not yet
I guess
Probably Michael Jordan
Okay Jordan is huge evacuation sure
No Bezos doesn't talk to any but I think Bezos is a robot
You going to be safest place he knows
All them go to space I go to South America
Testosterone
You need it Manliness
Record low testosterone
A twenty-year-old man
Has the testosterone of a sixty-year-old man in the 19th
A 40-year old man old man
They are putting chemicals in the food
Everywhere else
Totally
Destroy
Masculinity ladies
And that's just
How it works
Testosterone turns on yourself
Everything on
They're doing everything they can to try to block natural
Testosterone
Replacement
Systems that are out
So many great
We have super male vitality
Volkswagen stock
Smooth like there was a problem
Write that incidents nationally-known
And then for some reason he just hasn't solution
It's so nice
Tucker is being made fun of other reasons
Chat for talking
King about testosterone levels
Decrease
It's more like a
The ridiculous
Mannfolk
Is promoting
So that that's one thing
Testosterone levels
Have decreased
Somewhat According to some studies
Although there is
Also some arguments that can be made that these studies are a little bit like
Not not as precise as you would want them
Highly
Let me let me throw this out at you
Here's my here's my explanation for it doesn't require any kind of like
Chemicals in the water and
If we're going to say that men in that time. I had more
Testosterone than we do now
Is it not also pops
Seeing as how we know that I had an overabundance
The testosterone leads to aggressive behavior
That all those Wars we had for a good long while
Got all those testosteroni men like the most testosterone
F******
Species
We have lost testosterone because of their dumb War
How about that some of that's possible other things people point to our increased levels of obesity
More sense than mine but I think I think mine's still pretty good yeah you have an interesting bottleneck kind of Arc
I don't know
Anyway
That was as smooth as a sales pictures I've ever seen out
I was just with nailed it
So we got a story about
Person who died
Of course
It's got to be covid related
What is this lady CDs everyday
Player has family says beloved daughter
Will be sadly missed
Gene
The log on the plate at Shane's
Ladies game
Football club passed away from a massive heart attack
But I won't even talk
About
The fact that she was asked
Beautiful
Healthy
Have a great time
That's the evil will
The New World Order Waterford GAA morning and timely passing of young
She's dead now
Beautiful young lady
I'm so much fun out there
Daughter Charlotte
Block Charles
Leash is a little disrespectful
So this is an article from the Sun that Alex's reading
Nowhere in the story does it say what This Woman's cause of death was nor even how she died
All it says is it was quote
Due to illness
Is a pretty broad category that's a big one
The article quotes a Facebook post as saying that she had a brief illness 08
Probably not something that was chronic
Memorial page there's a link where you can donate to a meningitis research organization
This doesn't mean that you contracted a severe case of meningitis but that is a distinct possibility given these
Cedar Point
Anyway there's no indication that the
This woman was vaccinated North at her passing it anything to do with a vaccination or a massive heart attack
Doesn't matter
Alex
For him every dead young person is a perfect prop to use as proof of his conspiracy
And this has the effect of encouraging harassment of people who knew these tragically deceased youths
The entire narrative is dumb baseless and has the potential to hurt people so it's
Write up Alex's
Because it's easy and it allows him to make s*** up
Instead of doing any work
Right
Especially considering if you stop and think about what he's trying to argue
So let's say it's over this is Gaelic football clubs in the sun I assume this is an Ireland
Okay
So in Ireland the vaccination rates are like
98 /
So that means that
If you go through this
Statistics
There are more than one young person dying in a year
So there's like let's say there's a thousand young people who die in a year in Ireland
98% of them
You have to then say well
It's covid
All right the vaccine or anything because they're all vaccinated yeah yeah that is
Yeah
I think is really interesting that you can note there is that the article doesn't say anything about heart
That is not
Navigation
But she is a football
Soccer player and this is the go-to for Alex
Brian the right-wing media their talking points are all about like these soccer players having heart attacks
Use that almost
Instinctually
Need York say was a heart attack
He's just he's making s*** up about a tragically
Past young woman
I'm making making her a prophet
And it's unfortunate how is it's like
It's both so easy and so transparent why they're doing it
You know like obviously
Look this young person athlete
Above-average shape
In the prime of her her growth like all of those things it's so if even that can happen
You know that it must be that
Kind of
To see those details like young person athlete
And think like it's not right that their dad totally
Excuse and an explanation for why
This thing happened but
It's just your own made-up explanation to see if you're on purpose
Even though it and even that it's like
UE you know this is
So clearly chosen for the narrator
Yes
So clear
So this next clip Alex gets into some dumb s***
I titled this clip the blood of the jab because Alex says that and I thought it was very poetic
Here's a big
Enchilada
Infowars.com heading
Nevada live show feed
Broadcast
What does a peer-reviewed study
100% of these showed alterations
To their blood post-injection
This is not normal
And not have us being like a video game where like
You don't know him
A lot of the jabber that.
Deep within Skyrim
This isn't new
I found a blog post about this narrative from September around last
There's a blog post about this on Sgt report
Use that to see where the underlying information on this was coming
Coming from
This blog claim
Quote three surgeons from Italy conducted
The study which found that nearly everyone who gets
Quote of vaccinated for the Wuhan Coronavirus
Parentheses covid-19
With mRNA injections ends up developing tainted blood
So far we're a little off from Alex's initial statement
They are
Claiming that this is peer-reviewed but
It's definitely the same thing Alex's talking about because it includes the 1006 people in the study right and the 94%
Number is there too
In the first paragraph
About the Italian surgeons alleged study there's a hyperlink on the words found that
Which takes you to an article on a Blog called 100%
Set up with the headliner
Quote
Teacher arrested and jailed for refusing to use students preferred pronoun
Okay
Like if they just copy and pasted the wrong link but this has nothing to do with the covid vaccine story
You know you got multiple tabs open you think you got one on your clipboard and you accidentally
I kind of suspect that it's just like to have a hyperlink
The blog post itself is a reposting of an article on DC clothesline so I followed that linked to
Do an article titled quote
Study 94% of mRNA job recipients found to have metal like objects in their blood
We've laundered from
Metal like definitely not computer chip devices in their blood
To now it's just tainted blood
Wild but Alex didn't lead with that metal like objects
DC clothesline article is just a repost of an article from natural news
The site run by Mike Adams the health Ranger one of Alex's good buddy
And now we've essentially come full circle
Receive the lifecycle of this b*******
That is
Oh my God that's that's like
Sacred geometry like movement in minutes
F******
Honey bee
Bulshit shape of life
Travel all the way around back
Natural news
The DC clothesline article actually has the same words hyperlinked in the first paragraph and these also
Go to vapor and phobic article about a teacher not liking thrown out so they just got paid
Mistake happened early on no one caught it and it was just copy all these websites
No quality assurance or even a second thought given
It took a while but I traced down the study and question
Published in the international Journal of vaccine theory practice and research
The journal claims they only published peer-reviewed stuff but if you consult their page on what it means to them
That just means that their editors get submission to once-over before they popped
What's that right there your peers
Review don't mean the same thing to them is because of your
Appears that they are your pecker review and therefore if they review it
Beyond that it's just a Luna
Take anti-vax fraud
They're tender Jeep is a man named John Oliver a linguist who's been a big proponent of the discredited vaccines cause
Is autism.
In fact Andrew Wakefield himself wrote the forward for all ours book
Their board also includes multiple members of the Children's Health
Defense which is just another anti-vax fraud
This includes that group's general counsel Mary as Holland and their Chief scientific officer Brian as hooker
A guy named Daniel Brody
Is also on the board
His most recent published paper is titled quote
The covid-19 concoction a recipe for successful psychological operation
Interesting that's that pure review. I'm sure
He's also apparently a linguist
A closer look reveals that pretty much all of the board members are anti-vax actor
And almost all of them have a history of pushing the fraudulent connection between vaccines and autism
The journal is only existed since July 2020 and their second issue was dedicated wholly to covid-19
With it includes an article by the editor-in-chief titled quote
Buying and selling with the mark of the beast
This is not a journal to be taken
Seriously
It's a frock propped up by anti-vax activist
Looking to create a legitimate looking
Facade to capitalize on covid fears and Rising anti-vax sentiment
Among the right way
Anyway that's the source or Alex that that's what he's laundering but
He's not even on time with this one
Hi besties reporting a bombshell story about an alleged study in a bulshit anti-vax journal Atlas
A month late
So
That's the big enchilada
You know here's a here's my pitch
Alright
When I become god-king and like
Few weeks
Right Nacho
Happening again
For what I was referencing is he said in a Tucker Carlson interview like
He is going to be bred
If I become present I'm going to become president
That's the type of Psychopathic Comfort if you need to become president in a certain way
So
Country
Countrywide rule National rule
When you name things
It has to sound kind of like what it is
So you know like so we've got like the APA American Psychological Association
You know what that is
Is you get it you understand that
Association of
Psychologists in America
But if you're like the American vaccine Association
And you're one of these dudes
You can't name your shift
You don't get to name it that
Like that's my my head that just makes so much sense of his likeness
Yeah crisis center where that the anti-abortion pregnancy
Dissenters were the Lego
Will teach you what to do when they spray you know what it's like no you shouldn't be able to name yourself anything that sounds
Right right like that's your name
Like a Greenland Iceland you don't want it like some City in the middle of Illinois to be able to advertise
Paradise Prado Illinois
Trying to incorporate a town called Paris
Blackhawk helicopters dropped down from the sky
That's what we're talkin about look forward to that under Jordan's rule
So Alex plays
Clip of John McAfee
Talking about power
Haha
And how corrupt
Send what have you loved
Power
The negative parts inside you they're the ones that need power to be expressed love just
Close
Right
Yes sir Alex
Gets up in his head about how like
The audience has given him power he loves them and respect yourself
I'm very respectful
The incredible power
But you have given me and I
Thank you for the bottom
I my heartbeat
Because I love the
What
And I love
Bullies inscom
That's why they've Kashmir cebuli
A lot about who I am
Because they know
Cruises contagious
When they see us
It's not just me
Affiliate
All of us together
Amish app
Journey
Videos
The human it's very
All right ladies and Gentlemen let's look at the main threat
World War 3
And a proxy war
Control
Are some of the headlines
Polling suggests one Guardian
U.s. hosting nuclear weapons amid growing fears
They suggest
I'm sorry what
Of course that's going on
I know all this for my contacts
I also just know us
List of all the Soviet Union
But now they're ready they're poised
There ain't
The triggers are lies
What is a nice collection
I was just making all this up what an insane series of words he's also pretending that this headline
It means that Poland is suggesting that they have nuclear weapons there
Where is the actual story is that they requested nuclear weapons be moved there
Conveniently didn't read the sub-headline of this story from the guardian
Request is widely seen as symbolic as moving nuclear warheads closer to Russia would make them less militarily
Useful
Also this article is about to Poland's president making this request
Of the United States but includes this sentence
The White House has said it had not received such a request
Maybe
Like the article says symbolic
So the Poland guys like hey
You know it be nice cuz this guy is a f****** crazy dude over here at me maybe if we had some nuke
We be fine and everybody's like we're not actually going to put them there but
We get what you're trying to say man
That guy's going to shoot
Like Alex's sort of
Do you know his where his bread is buttered right now with the nuclear war fears right
It becomes like everything is not only a misrepresentation of the headline
A hat on top of it
Yeah I know the situation that Poland is
Boras like
I gas station robbery where
It's just it's just the United States and Poland in the guys like
With his eyes are kind of pointing back
And I like that kind of think that's where we're at
That seems about right
So who's going to be a nuke probably maybe
Maybe a false flag maybe it'll be dirty
Drugs
For using nuclear emergency and they're running nuclear emergency ad
In New York and Denver
And high-level federal employees is in the news
I got to stop here
What is a nuclear emergency ad
It's an ad for nuclear emergency
I don't know what he's talking about
Bug-out directions
Bug out backpack
Where do Escape 2
In the event of War
90 million + Aunty radiation drug for using nuclear
Emergency
Nuclear war
Think the levels might release a dirty mom or maybe a low-yield nuclear weapon claim Russian
We're in the age of War the angel false flag
Yeah so now let's just imagine
Scenario
But I think is unlikely but let's imagine
A nuclear a small nuke goes off and you had City
Flagman
I mean
I'm going to go out and I'm going to say
Alex is like this is a situation where I feel like it's fine if Alex kind of
Is like scary because
Honestly if a nuke does go off in a city
No one's going to give a s*** what Alex has to say anymore I don't know if that's true
Real busy with everything else that's going on you're not wrong
I think I think I still have a problem with it if only because of
I think I
Nuclear warfare
Not to be taken lightly
Exaggerating
Threat of it right
For the sake
Of us not ending up there not good
Well no actually I read that wrong
You know if that is what it takes
To take things seriously like hey let's never get to that point
I got I can kind of get into that if people that acted like that about climate change in the 70s
You know
Who is Alex the problem that I have is that he's not doing anything to avert
Nuclear war or make it less likely
Hugh
Manipulating the audience's emotions
In order to
Sell them bigotry and
Yes there is that
So I find that to be just a
Seriously in like
Now being like
Pretty gung-ho against it
Great
But this is bad
I'm of the opinion that nuclear war is my
My preferred Armageddon
Just because
As if everybody goes at the same
Time then there's no like
Bad feeling about the blip
Well the blip would be great
But you have to take everybody again
If everybody goes to the same time there's no heart
And nobody's going to miss you
Cuz everybody's dead
You won't miss anybody took like half people are the problem
Can you got to put everyday you build your life mapped out of people
They came back another day got to put their lives together it's just a whole mess
I don't know man I think
I disagree I think there's got it like it's it's a great
There's a mystery
Many of the whole new life for nothing about the blip
I bet if you did get blipped I mean what you're just going to avoid right
I don't know what happened you can have that
Are you trying to live without me
The last five years
That's fair
And the workload tried to bring me back would be the same for both of us
It's a natural extension
Like I said Alex
Alex has a very much support
Is very awesome office in some ways but this is pretty pretty
Sad
Rush's
Voice growing anger as losses Mountain Ukraine
Agency
Namor
Who's the moderate
If Putin gets assassinated like
West has been pushing for Lindsey Graham's been calling for
Somebody
More aggressive
Ethos is not being invaded
By the Mongol
And the Hun
And the Muslims
And Napoleon
I sure didn't start
Engine of evil
Just like America is now an engine
A warm-up
Globalist even weirder captured instrument of evil
No naive spoiled dumb down
Lost
But not evil
And the Russians are not evil
This is such b******* it's so hard to even take this seriously
The first glaring problem is they from the early 1700s
Through the early 1900's Russia was an Empire
Empires in case Alex doesn't understand this are generally based on expansion and Russia was definitely into that in.
Peter the Great's the guy who St Petersburg is named after
Russia had a long Rich history of expansionism
And invasion
Long
I'm well before Lennon ever came around the most
Beard
Engines of colonialism in history
Another important point is that is not a moderate
He's faced some criticism from the Russian to leave but they're not saying that the nuke should start flying
It's more like Dave the generals mishandled operations kind of critical criticism
It's pretty wild for people to be doing that since
Government passed a law back in March where they could imprison people for up to 15 years for criticizing the military
The only person in that article that Alex's citing who is calling for nuclear weapons to be used is
Amazon kadyrova
Who's there
Hardline Putin loyal
He's such a poodle loyalist that he's trying to scapegoat the other
Some other people in the Kremlin to defend Putin from criticism
How about how things are going at
Another small point the headline of the article that Alex is using his quote Russian Elites voice
Growing anger as losses mount
In Ukraine
Alex added demanding Putin do more from his own imagination
That is not in the text
Nor the article
I don't know who would end up in power if bun were removed mostly because almost all relevant political opposition in the
The country has been crushed or imprisoned
And Putin has essentially been in power for
22 years
So it's hard to predict who would ascend
No matter who it would be
It does not matter
It does not mean that Putin is not
Immoderate
Ridiculous to say Punta moderate
Obvious aporta Putin
Despite a bunch of stuff happening in the world that makes that support look really
Yeah yeah it is this is got that historical bent of like it's really smart
If you are a despotic tyrant
To surround yourself with people who have
Billions of dollars all dependent on you
Existing
Because
The only way to stop this honestly is for one of those people to assassinate Putin
And that shouldn't happen
So here we are
You know I thought you were going to say the good way to be a despot is to like surround yourself with people even worse than
Ono know that's how you get murdered
As a desk
Right now I've been there cuz like if someone worse than you was going to send that sort of like body armor
Well for other people but for them they're in a badge
With knives that stabbed body armor
So the Russian Elites are saying hey Putin
You got a new people
Or something
US elites on the other hand
Auto some complaints about the olive course there's a problem with her door
They got rid of the actual Warriors and smart people
He wanted power and all the rest of it
Bunch of Harvard lawyer
To a man
Physically killed somebody
Never physically seen a war
Never
Physically
Their head doctor the ground
And so they have this
Lawyers
But they can just Bravada
And bully people around because they control American power
And that's not the case
Real people
That have launched operations and killed lots of people
Are very concerned
Henry Kissinger 99 years old still articular
Stop
Omni budsman
Sorry what now
I don't know what they're doing
Nuclear war these people should all be arrested
It's the Return of the Omni budsman Tire comic book about
Editor paper
Suddenly gaining powers to be able to edit all newspapers
Let's call Alan or release information to come back
Flip really makes no sense if you believe any of Alex's narratives at all
All the stuff that he's talking about shouldn't matter in the least
If you kill someone physically or not doesn't make a difference
Prince because either way you're acting the way you are because you're possessed by a literal demon
Or at least your knowingly working for Satan
The kind of insubordination that Alex's describing is just not possible in the context of how he described the globalist
Who are the u.s. Elite
There's no question about following Kissinger's advice because
You and Kissinger both work for the devil
Tim Kissinger is about as high-level as it gets for humans on the demon scale
Earned it doesn't just give his opinion about the best way to solve a problem he's basically like the Emissary of say
For Alex's
It doesn't make sense
The globalist
Italy act the way Alex
Rfr
There is no discipline in the ranks which seemed super unlikely if the people knew that there was the literal devil who
They were disobeying
Seeing this there's probably consequence
Those were that kind of thing
Yeah it's the f****** devil
Yeah
Devil's operations in Alex's mind have more of a have more of a
Like fictional hell kind of like the Devils really not paying attention that much
The Dukes are all
Just telling people to do stuff and without the ultimate authority of the
The devil you know
I'm kind of say hey Duke
F*** you you know the devil's not going to mind because he's the devil what is he going to be like
Superior officer
So you have
Like dork
Physically killed people who are working across purposes of the warrior types
This disorganization feels like
How Infowars rocks
Ever notice how is the devil is exactly as smart as Alex
Did you ever notice that
The devil's drunk quite a bit
Honestly I think we're going bankrupt right now
I don't know where my money is in
The devil's dad is suspiciously involved in his business
In a way the devil's dad also bought him a place to live to
You know there's there's something to be said for that
That's interesting
So this guy isn't this next Clipper really got my ears up
The last year I received top secret information
Are the start of the next hour 6 after I will release
Hope you take this information to our
Hope you shave
Because any day
Everyday Above Ground is a good day
Okay so we got secret tell
Secret stuff
I just
I just wish
One time in my life
Like I'd been watching
CNN it like 12 years old
And Wolf Blitzer been like
We've got some brand-new ragazza
Some scary news out of the White House I'm afraid to tell you
I'm going to commit myself to God right now I'd like to commit my spirit
We have breaking news
God help me
That would be fun
That's a tow.
The other problem is that the elites have replaced all the murderers with dork
There is that
Before we get
To this top-secret news
I think
Alex has a little bit of an announcer
Quite frankly I'm thinking about
4 year
I watched him
Repast
Probably already
Ashok
Commercial free
Total setup
This is probably never going to happen much like the show that's just collars that Alex is
Just a big bottle on for like a
Around the corner
About to happen
I would advise Alex strongly not to follow through with this idea
But one thing he doesn't have enough content to justify the amount of time he's on air as is and there's
No reason to add like 6 hours a week
To that pile
Second he claims he's just going to take calls but that's bulshit
Alex can't stay on task
To save his life so this is going to end up being more ramps and begging people for money
At the beginning of this show he said the first and second hours open phones
You get to call Zan
Hour and 20 minutes away still closed
Sell clothes
There's a third point to this and that
This seems desperate
There's no reason to do this show other than to try to make more money
There's no great demand for it there's no way Alex needs more time to cover the news
What does boils down to is that no one else in Infowars can sell for s***
I want and Harrison shows clearly aren't bringing in the sale so Alex feels like he needs to be on are essentially all the time to keep the Inn
Infomercial
Is that 12 major factor in this idea he could easily have someone else
Supposed to show this mostly collars
Oh wait that was the premise of Harrison Smith show before he started getting a bunch of callers there were like a why won't Alex just say it
The Jews
Another issue was that Alex is at
And these shows if he does them are going to be a mess
I guess I'll netfront I kind of hope he does follow through with predictable content
Throwing but as a whole that seems like a really bad idea
Yeah I would be interested
If instead of
His current idea
He set it up so that all of his house
Bad we get together
And Daria would be the social media manager and they would create the evil Chris gethard show
Like
Could you imagine an evil Chris gethard show
What would that be like a literal human face
I know that much right
Alex would be Chris guess he be Chris and birth he would have to be
The would-be the LLC Owen Owen could be a
Good vacation Jason
I think I always got vacation
Brett.
If we're filling those roles that that's definitely
I just want him to be I've got to talk more then I would need to be
Like
You and I could be the Paul Scheer and Jason Vance
Alright
We're having a good time
So we got top secret until
Course
Good bad
I don't think he says it
That sounds about right
I was listening to Mike tops
This is
It's okay
But I don't know cuz it's not topsy
Secret it's not in town
Breaking news
That three and a half years ago.
House armed services committee
In just the last year many times
Choosy
Majortech,
Who explained
Will you go on Siri
Are you going
Sounds dumb AI sounds dumb
Some purpose they don't want you to know
3.0 is already in control
But let me give you a big chic
And I was meeting a year ago
Over a year ago
With the chief science
Of the number one University in America
Now they can debater that is
I'm not going to say the name
What
A discussion about the posthuman and the end
All of it
And what their main
Gauloises
I said let me guess your man going
Stop at
Elon Musk
What are we doing
I'm sitting there
I said
I know the secret
Powerful
Guy is only a
We give it if we don't interface weather
Fails
Ashley Wright
Oh my God
I mean I feel like he looked at you and said
What do you mean it
Text fails what's failure
Does it just Exist by its
Self is it just it doesn't become friends with adults
We're teaching at how to play chess by playing chess against itself
It's probably fine
Yeah
Form of AI that Alex is thinking of that I think
Bank is
Not
Hawaii what
Maybe this
Fake MIT Professor would be working on
I'll be I blew his mind I guess that
This is the secret Intel
They said he went to dinner with three sounds dumb
Because they're trying to
Cover up that
AI 3.0 arise launched
Very smart
That makes perfect
Yeah caught me
I and Alex blue guys mind at dinner
I know all the secret II
I know the secret of your failure I will tell you this
If if
AAA MIT graduate
Who is
Elon Musk
Top AI guy
Was having dinner with Alex and Joe Rogan
I do believe Alex blew his mind many times that night however I do not believe it was for any good reason no no
I also want to know who the aide-de-camp saraveza
Here's the AI that Alex's thing
I said what is the most powerful
Flatterers right now
God
John by sheer human movement
By Chirac
Activity on the face
Ants
I said it's stoplight
Programmed in most areas
The flow
Summer is is not
But I said
It's primitive technology but
Human submit
To it
And humans go along with the stoplight
The red light CLR lives
The green line
The turn signals a yield sign
Because they know it makes your life better
Humans interfacing
Would that primitive technology that is the most dominant
AI program on Earth
Sounds right
Hi guy
Arguably
On the planet
Pushback is Cherry what oh my God I never saw it like that
Steve Wozniak
MapleStory
Axis1
Look up story
Good story
All the stop lights are timer
And some like have pressure I'm going to I'm going to go even further
He's wrong
Because
What's even more power
Is the button
That turns the crosswalk sign
But let me tell you something
A lot of the times
That button doesn't do it
Right so that's not the operation
That's a i it doesn't
So
Okay
Problems with this line of thinking
Because here's the deal like
Stop light
Fully
Need our input
Like-for-like with the drivers and stuff
In order to operate or whatever
Many of them are just on timers
You got 5 minutes and then
To Alex my argument
Might be that when you are not interfacing with the stop
They're still doing what they're
That is true you are doing different
Yes
Is true and then secondarily
Interfacing with stop lights
Save so many lies
So many
Society would not be able to operate in the way that we do with
Cities and the layouts are of the people needing to get to work and all right
It would not function the way we have it set up if we did not
So the argument
Actually would be submitted to the AI
Work with
Vai well because otherwise this s*** doesn't work well I mean
But that is that's kind of the azimuth
Point of view on AI is that like
If we do develop an AI
Chance
It's going to be infinitely better at running our society than we are in the same way that you know
An AI
Program has like a 3800 Reiki low rating in chess
Which is like and the human one is like 2800
Talking about
Alex Jones
I think that he was trying to make an argument that
We don't need to
Interface
Swift
IAAI
That's what's up
Well yeah
Obviously he doesn't want a i fiddling around and all this s***
But
The examples that he
He uses
Of his alleged
Most
Spell prevalent
Hey I we do need to
Interface with right
I mean but at the same time like
What is he talking about that it's intelligent okay
If I set my coffee makers timer
You make coffee for me the next morning
Right
I think that there is I don't fully understand exactly how all Civic planning works
Unstoppable
There are some
I like traffic lights
Things with adjust based on traffic
I think some cities do have that
You could make an argument that's like
Somewhat rudimentary
When you're talking about the lake
Machines that play chess against themselves a little different from what exit
It's a little different
I would guess
If this a mighty person doesn't
Right
They were being very polite
Beyond polite
Well I mean because again now I would argue that Alex
My Definition of artificial intelligence
Begins when artificial intelligence
Learns on its own
You know what I'm saying sure you learn something without our help
Now
I'm going to throw this out at you
The traffic lights
Cannot do that
That's not true the traffic lights cannot suddenly be like you know what
I haven't tried orange before let's give it a go
I was at the intersection of Western and Madison
I was yelling at the French
I guess that isn't it learning on its own tonight
So are we got some bigger updates about about the trial
Closing arguments being made
And Alex has a big piece of news
We know they claim were all Russian agent we know they say men get
Fifteen minutes ago by accident
Cuz my lawyer great lawyer or baddest up in Connecticut
Trial
Attacked by the judge nylon defend ourselves
He sent me a text me said their ass
Searching for 300 million dollars
All they want $3000000 Texas as400
50 million
50 million but
Context of cat
If it doesn't matter
Calling
Like 45 seconds ago
Hung up on or pass
Proportion
He says it's 7
Point
8 billion dollars
Me too
SAS 47
Billion dollars
Show me questioning a mass shooting
And weeks of them crying
And no evidence
I never said these people
? Jesse smaller
What a joke
That's all bulshit but that's funny you really enjoys this
Yeah this pizza in a good mood if I got to hang up on Norm to though
Probably invigorating about that it was on a landline
Now that would be nice
But yeah so this puts a minute and in a certain mood
And this will play out
And we'll see about that
Okay I got the call from a lady
Who used to be
A dumb liberal
When those dumb liberals in that time that she was a dumb liberal
She got back
I know she's very worried about it
But I wanted to ask
What your score because
And I took it back scene and so now I'm nervous of my
Decision
I just want to see what you still at like
Is it really
Like you think I'm going to drop something
No statistically has killed Millions
Problem you say no
Dancers no
It was 87
Thank God they didn't store it right
And so
Two-thirds of folks are having a
Kaiser Madrona you name it it's got to be chapped
Didn't happen so you probably got a dose it was dead
Alive
Goodcents
Call now we have a built-in excuse for why all of the people that listen to Alex
2 don't have
Terrible side effect or die
From
That's great I'll try I'll throw this scenario attitude okay so I'm out having dinner with Alex
Text Joe Rogan
And Alex says that to me
It does not blow my mind
I had an incident like a moment he said that I had a vision of me throwing
Bread in his face
If I was holding bread out it throw it in space
No
Refuse f*** out of here
Done
So
The rest of the show is weird
Yeah
Cuz he wasn't exactly wasn't really excited about hearing that they were asked
A seven billion dollars was
Well he was in a fashion
Sure the third hour is in interviewing guy from the epoch times
About some Alexa
Contemptuous
So I don't care we're not going to do that
So we're coming towards the like
End of the second hour
And Alex is f***** up
Not literally talked out
Do drugs or anything
I don't even know how to how to
Here
The final curtain
I traveled
Much more than this
But I can't stress this enough
Alex plays the whole song he played the whole
This
Was
Tough
Just listening to this song it seems like there's nothing else going on watch this
Entirely different experience
Watch every episode of
AutoCheck
The video sent me this video and was like you got to see this
Headed to me too and I could not click on it and I've been kind of interested in now I know
It's
I think it's one of the rare things that like
I can do my best to explain it maybe I'll do it just
But I don't know
Maybe people
It's so weird
To already a strange thing for a human being in they start smoking to the camera
Weird looks
These smug like smiles to the camera so he's trying to do this ironic like haha
It's not actually
The end for me he's doing like thumbs up
Oh my God
Does like sort of
Waving
Gesticulating putting his arms out right
He doesn't have enough moves
She kind of gets stuck with his arms outstretched like wingspan
There until he can bring his okay
It's really strange but there's
There's another element to it too
And that is that edited
Intuit
Like to someone who's working the board
Has
Like a
But video of
Sing like highlights from Alex's career
What is a like four sections on the screen you know like splits
Yes we're getting silent video of his greatest hits
Open for Hollywood Squares ass like a shot from Scanner Darkly and Waking Life
Him yelling at Marco Rubio on Piers Morgan
Stuff from his early career like when he was alive
Canfield it feels like that
It feels like
Is
This is
The kind of tribute
Bit someone else
Give it to you later
Like when your career is over or you're retiring or something like that
Pizzas have someone else honors you host your own episode of this is your life
Feels really sad because Alex is sitting there alone in his Studio
Can you rent it out
The theater that the Oscars is held in to give himself a Lifetime Achievement Award
Sigmund is him doing it his way that is weird
Uncomfortable self-indulgent disrespect
Oh God I had to watch it a couple times actually yours
The truth you had to turn it off a cup
Pebble time
I turned it off within a couple seconds
The first time I can't
I Did It My Way
7.8 billion
Everybody will never get $1000000
Oh boy
He kind of thought when he started talking maybe that was going to be like the afram
Nope
I would say this
Right
This is just the wrong
This is just the wrong Kant
Because if we were watching like a
A classic
Like 1800sprint circus
You know and this is
The sad clown section that where they came out
He's playing Sinatra's doing this whole thing
Flowers
Is coming raining from the sky Standing Ovation he's bowing
And then it goes away
That's a perfect sad clown routine right that this was his Farewell to public life
I'd forgive whatever weirdness is going on problem solved
I also think
Here's a here's how I think
This goes better
Song Choices that I think would work better than my wife
Cuz my way is really f****** sad
Yeah it's the end of the night
You know what I mean
I think you go with
Right now
Okay okay I think there's some
Open upbeat about that
Dad rockish
Bright enough for Alex chair
The other one is Bon Jovi's It's My Life
And it's now or never
Oh man
Cuz that has kind of
Same thing but it's not like
I'm bad
I think if I were going to go out I would have like an IRA song playing like it was
Straight up like
The British murdered my family and then I'm gone that's the way I do it
Just I mean by this song is
I Did It My Way
It's all. I'm doing it my way you know
It is it is not as much of a karaoke
Song in that context as you might think
But
Bon Jovi
Garbage so I'm still a fan of this over that
I would probably choose like something by Carly Rae Jepsen
Or maybe something from Avril Lavigne Let Go album
I'm picturing you as like a let's call it 75-78 year-old-man your you're
Giving your final lecture at a university
And everybody is like
Shaking your hand as your waving goodbye
Call Me Maybe
No. That's what I hear that's what I hear things all never say North
My world by Avril Lavigne or I like it with me
So beautiful
We're going to feed them
God we are the best there is
I don't care
But he got beautiful black skin
What
Can't Stop
Credible red skin or yellow skin
Thanks again what is going on
Ivory White
Skin
What are you doing
Stop all of that
Stop it
Our blood is
I got to go to your phone calls
I'm just so
Love it oh my God
Point eight billion
There's a lot going on there
That is
REI
I will say that I have
No rush
Fear of reference
For staring down the barrel of what it's going to be
A Millions upon Millions upon millions of
Millions of dollars of debt
Acting weird makes sense to me
Based on his positioning in the like his
Just at the Griff
Yeah
He can't do anything
But be confident
Showing weakness to the audience than they like why would I throw my money away at you when you're just going to have to
To give it to the court
Yeah or whatever you know you not knowing that it's already what they're doing is that publicly
Then take while the audience will bail on you
Yeah you're not showing like some kind of a
Being above it or laughing about it
Yeah you can't be like I'm f***
Guys
Hose make that really screwed on this one
Nothing to do with making a sequel to 25th hour right now that's how bad it's going
It's not going well
So Alex
Adjust the rambling keeps going
And I don't really think that this clip is all that into
Everything except for one thing
These criminals are so over-the-top
Number like
Scares us
Control the judges
Do all of this
You can try to shut me down
Is what I expect
I expect you'll be killed a long time ago I had
Family killed
Who wouldn't go along with
Did you kill him
Because of
Family put in the tank
Hundreds of years of war
Because of the
Because of you
We're having
Massive victory
I am so blessed and humble
To be at the very epicenter
The human race
What's going on with you man no clue what is happening it's bizarre wow
Yeah so I guess he had a family member killed
That's strange
I know he was trying to say but he phrased that poorly who was killed is
Yeah but he wasn't
Murdered
Sure if Alex wants to clarify onomatopoeia
Interested as well
Interesting piece of that
Is
This is so funny to me
B like Alex
Can't get to the second step of
I expected to be dead a long time ago
Why haven't you why aren't you
Cuz you're full of
Cuz you're lying
You expected to be dead because if what you believed were real
You probably would be
Yeah but
It's all fake
Call Protect living in a bizarre spy novel in your head that's why you're not dead yet
Is that by the grace of your audience not haven't killed you yet hopefully probably more realistic
More like you're not dead because
For some reason you're weird
Mental illness
Trauma response
Turned into a business
Yeah piano or you and also I think probably had the cautionary tale of Bill Cooper
You're not going to get yourself in a situation like that
Hey White
Alex didn't do it his way it turns out
And I am so blessed and humble
To be at the very Epic
Center of the human resist
I Didn't Do It My Way
I did it God
That's where we are right now
Biggest number
To scare you into submission
But if you submit to them you get
Death penalty
Billion years in hell
Control your children signed over to them
We are exposing a poison shot
Sounds right
Ouchie
Bill Gates
Schwab
Henry Kissinger
Humanity will pop
Like the solar system
Will expand their
Then we'll go next level
I I find it difficult to imagine being somebody listening to this and being like
Yep this is
Killing it
You know just worried
This seems worrying yeah
Yeah
If this is sincere at work
If it's not then it's a childish perform
It lacks nuance
I mean if it's not it's worrying as well
I are very different
For what I feel I feel a little bit jealous of sick Shakespeare now on innocence that like
It in his
Time
A thing like me Fink's
She does protest too much
You know you're like
That's inappropriate
Contextual way of the
Describing that
If he said that about Alex I be like
You should have said
Yeah you know the Lacs
It's the kind of poetic language that'll live for decoration
Call if you will describe
Love you tough I wonder who Alex would be in Titus andronicus
What's recast that 12
He's the person who
So
Alex waiting to go to the Stars
You know
And I talked about beam me up Scotty
Indescribable
Grandchildren
Magical Interstellar
Intergalactic
Mobile.
Interdimensional
Can pour out my
Do genetic wealth
A genetic don't describe it like at Everest
No amount of torture
And we are at
Going together
Lawn chair
I am just I am so bored
Love this
The biggest defamation case
U.s. history
Is 240
1 million.
They're so scared of us
Nash 47-point
8 billion
With their rig trial
This is awesome
So I guess I was just been on the USS Enterprise before we
Fun
That was fun out of negative attention
That's just such a powerful fuel for him because he's internalize the fallacious idea of the consequences and negativity
Mention all the signs of a virtuous person
He's up against this Cosmic overpowered evil so the fact that Alex is facing a giant defamation judgment
Can only be evidence of how good
If you were an evil person the cosmic overpowered evil forces would
Check them from such a thing
But because he's a threat to the Devil he's subjected
Slings and arrows
Nice
This is a really dangerous and stupid mindset to have because if you think this way and your bladder no let's say orange
Narcissists you'll never be able to
Accept any credit
Every time someone tells you that you f***** up
Every time you get in trouble for something
Really bad that you did
You'll find a way to convince yourself that the consequences or criticism is just
Motivated by evil drink
Get you off course
From your holy
We mission
Your ability
Self assess is
Wheatley erased by this mindset
Find ability to rationalize any really hurtful or
Destructive things you do
Alex is afraid to wrestle with the actual impact that he has in the world because on some level
Probably or possibly subconscious
He knows that that would be the end of his career
His ideology in world you don't hold up to any actual screwed
Nazo his ability to hide behind being a champion for that ideology and worldview would likewise
Crumble is examined critic
If all consequences or just proof that you're on the right track then whoever may have been hurt along the way
The collateral damage of the war against the globalist
But
If he's consequences aren't proof that you're on the right track and they're just people you've heard there's no
Excuse for it
You just don't care how many people's lives you ruin in order to make sure
But you're rich and sound interesting on your radio
That's really
The
Assertive
Real world version of
Yeah I mean
It is it is more fun to
To be like oh seaweeds bombastic and needs on the radio and it's entertaining and stuff
But at the same time I feel like his psychopathy and need for money is
Is the same as like
Howard Schultz or or whatever you want like
What kind of psychopath
To bust Union that a f****** Starbucks
For his extra 100 million dollars you know like it's insane
Yeah it's the same thing as what Alex's doing these
It's just because it's
Not
Public because he
Torturing people in Silence with their tacit
Permission you know because Society forces on them
Ebony f***** up man and it's not union-busting it's doing a Superfluous to h x
Exactly
Somehow it is less distasteful then
There is that
Do it talks a little bit about the trial
Can make you sick
How about quadrillion
All the universes
Platinum Collection
Crying parents are kids got killed
And on fraternity
Just thank God
I'm not the
Goblin
Harry Potter
By Josh.
Chris Maddie
I wasn't
Materialized
Planet Beach
Thank God
I'm not these people
And that's why they hate us
Because they don't have
Dolls
Asean
And there cuz we're not robots allspice
School teacher
You may be sure that works at JCPenney you made me
A lawyer
You may be a scientist it doesn't matter how much money you have or how much money you don't have
All the connections again for letting God
That is the real value
And these soulless Servants of evil
Bloodline
Been cut off from God that thing
Where the cancer
Taking over the planet
We're all powerful
We're incredible
Because you're bad
Your metastasizing cancer and you will
Destroy
By your own will
That's why you're unhappy
That's why you're up
Spirits
Delete
Dad
So
Guess just cough and
Costco
Personal don't have souls
Second were materialized by demons in order to do evil
Parody of it's something to do
With Bloodlines being bred
The first soullessness
Are we busy
Is Joe
Silly old time
Illuminati bloodlines
Respond to that would like you got it
Dogman
I got you just got to be gone from here over you are not there
But you got interview
You've got this is a good
What's up Billy boy
Stand up
And that's why you all
Supported it
For the moment we're in right now
Look in the eyes of faith
Say
You are a loser
And you don't control this planet
And we're breaking free from you
Diffuser
Oh that hurt
I'm a come back from break
Phone calls
Yes coming up from there
Can't find that news actually cuz my reprint that for me
I'll buy dinner
Bitten fruit
How to call the devil a loser
Bed really hurt his feeling
Time that clip
Because at the brakes saying that his show is the forbidden
Fruit
So if that's
Truth
The listeners not to listen to that right
It's forbidden
Right
Not supposed
Forbid it one time
Enough to Alex's show is the cause of original sin
Correct
So let's all stop being misogynist and start hating Infowars
He is really mixing metaphors and confusing add a religious level
Feel like you are setting me up
Love you
I want you to join me
River of Truth
Waterfall
Eternity
Tell your phone calls
What you say about
Company
The world is
The world is Crank It Up
Haven't listened to Russia. I really like it I might have to go back and read
Neil Peart
F******
Stoppable
Stoppable did you hear some of those plans yeah it was worse than f****** plans man
But yeah I think I do like Alex drop-in freeway 11
Time on the broadcast Alex asked them to Crank It Up
You're in a mood
You are on a professional radio show sex
I also dig the we're going to go to your calls now f*** it Crank It Up
Yeah you know
I feel like maybe by
Larger issue is that
Other radio host
Don't say Crank It Up enough
Will they have bought
Yeah see that's the problem but I mean
There's no bad time
To just be like a
You know what
This song slaps
Crank It Up
And then you do then you go back to your radio show
Yeah
If I were programming director charger shows I would love people
Yeah but not everyone's
I know I would get in trouble
I'll get in trouble
Allot
So Alex.
Go to call shortly after this
I quit I don't even care anymore
Thanks for holding appreciate you brother
Hey Brother
The big screen with
100 billion dollars
P******
Shut up
Ask me for the same thing but I ain't got it
It's a joke
Seriously I got something I want to say out
I quit
We just went through Galaxy very weird
Color
There's something serious or what
That is the easiest call and response
Ever exist
Two people yelling at each other if you just go to Alex if you just go hey
He's going to a meeting up
It just his language that's the only thing is sweet and then you're married
Really takes you into the woods for his wife
I mean he was going through some
Something yeah
The
The closing arguments
Certainly
Nothing to do with this
Nope
No no
So is he being sued I would barely know
So weird so weird ass cream today on Thursday over it Infowars
Lot of nuclear war fears
Will based on very little
Some trivial bulshit
Yeah covid narrative the day
And then
Freak out if I was if I was trying
The final case
You know cuz there's two more try
Alright if I was trying to find one I would talk to the judge
And just be like lesson
We got to make this a wrap up
For the world to see
I'm not clay like clip
From the earlier trials I play clips from Alex talking
During the trial that like really lay out the timeline
Of everything that got to where we were just through the trials and be like
And now
I am the king of a mare
Right that's how you can only announce that
Yes over Are You Belong To The City
I'm going to get the right side back
Text
Recent episode
He did play it
Do a speech over
Cameo Point Play the song
Yeah
Which I might do
Alright
Willie back okay yes we will but Jordan until then
Bikes
It is stroke out time and we will be back
But Delvin Neo
Rebel Rebel
What the sex robot
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color