I have great respect for knowledge babe I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Brexit
Alex Jones
We are.
Quick question for you what's up
I took a little walk down to the mailbox
Boxer to drop off some but instead of making their way all around this great world of Art
And I'm walking back
Welcome back to my house I see a corner store
Okay I don't want to go wander in there so I can find a good snack
What where was it
Okay right on the corner
Very easy to find
Fits its name
So I go in
Looking for a snack
I love novelty I love things that I'm a drawn to things that I haven't
Seen before
So I bought like this apple energy drink
But I still haven't tried yet but
Why is it sounds
I mean it's fearful eye-to-eye.
Asking if you're afraid of it
Good mood for a
Actually I'm not
Beard I'm not scared I'm worried it's going to suck a little bit
But I also got this is my bright spot
These
Arizona
Arnold Palmer half & half fruit snacks those wound up being your break
Well here I want you to try one, explain why I need to to you almost
If people don't listen
Just listen to this don't know but almost every time we do an episode you have an Arnold Palmer half and half
Feisty
And so I
I looked at the packaging
And I couldn't tell
What the f*** it was
Because this is an Arnold Palmer is half lemonade half iced tea
To be iced tea gummy bear gummy fruit
I couldn't tell until I was staring at the
Front of the pack
Uno indica
Whatsoever
I mean other than you're like an Arnold Palmer that means that there's iced tea there's got to be iced
Iced tea fruit snack because it shouldn't be at like
I thought the idea was nut
What was nuts the Arizona was making fruit snacks
I think they're
Fine but not great great spot is
The confusion
Yeah that moment of staring at the package of being like
Is this half iced tea have fruit flavored fruit snack that is what you are getting novelty for that
You're about the mystery it's been a long time since I've stared at a package read everything on it and then like
I know this has to be half iced tea
That was fun
And yet
How can it be
I'm baffled
I'm impressed with the hustle
Respect the game of course but the product itself isn't that great
Ice-T
It's not it's not like a strong iced tea
Steve Weimer though the fruit as was wise
I think some tea flavors are like
Maybe underrated in some other settings and I think
You know this
Done better could be better
I got price
So you know I haven't talked too much about the old baseball
This summer cuz the Cubs
I'm actively
Trying to avoid them
The ownership in Chicago
I hear about it
This has been you know how last year I was like I was shohei ohtani is the greatest season of baseball ever put together
He got better
This year he got better
Well I mean huge
Coming into his own
He's going to do next year I think he's going to kill a man with his greatness
He'll just begin to Glow I mean his hair without becoming
That means
If it freezes right around the corner if we end up in a situation
It's just he's the whole
Believe that the ultimate baseball
Challenge now is cloning
Show Tommy eight more times
And having him
89 hymns play against the best fit the rest of the world has to offer at every position you could have
Person baseball team cuz once
So there you go
But if you're a good enough
Picture you don't need that Outfield
She used to it while he was pitching in in the League's you know he used to be like hey
I got the next three and he'd send the entire Outfield in the team behind him off the field and then he would pitch by himself
I did not know
And he would strike him out three-in-a-row buddy
Wow
What up what up you got to really be confident
Real talk
Cuz you're going to cuz even if it's like a but you're going to have to go run for it and then you have to
To tag him so it's going to be
Yeah you got to strike about that's brutal
Okay so if someone bumped
You run to get it
You have to chase them by the
Half of the bases no you do not have to be in a Crock-Pot
Possible
It's possible but you know the pictures aren't notorious for being the bestest chasing people down in China
I do Maginot fun scenario where
Run back to the base
I imagine that
But like the runner would be able to go all the way back to First
I imagine I think I would prefer if this was
Bore Badr day
It was a bad picture that everybody do is bad and he's somehow bzo
Outfield at Hilton
5e already like I listen
I got this one
It'll be awesome great
Batman I'm the batter
I hit a homerun and then I couldn't walk around the bases to rub it in
So Jordan 11 episode to go over excellent talk about October 9th 2022
That would be Sunday
Haha
Stuff that I want to talk about nothing just him playing music and kind of mugging to the camera
God I wish
Man
You know what that
To me it was a bit refreshing and some back to like 2008 time
Yeah when you just like
Rock out to San Jose
There was more of a freedom it's about this a little bit one of the things I hate about
Does present day stuff
Hayes
He is such
Like
He chases attention so much
Like I think social media affect
I think the like I mean that's not
That's Not Unusual I think.
He's also got like an attention model that a business model that's so base
Based around that capturing attention and
I just I feel like it
Wouldn't have behaved the same way
Previous eras of his career
Like his information would be just as bad but he's going to be so annoyingly chasing down like
X Y or Z
What's to try and like
Seem
Get a little bit of attention off
A b
I hate to say that it's beneath him because it's not
Here's what I'll say here's a real say
Part of the reason that he can get away with saying that or he could get away with saying he was above the left-right Paradigm was
Not necessarily his political beliefs
It was also the complete lack of care that he gave tours
Like all the sudden you just listen
Turn this track
You know like yeah you're above the left-right Paradigm you're just having a good time sing along to a song right now
You would have gave that appearance
Meme people
Carpe donktum
Boring ass people like G Edward Griffin
Or like Jim Tucker
Like these boring-ass old dudes feeling if you're at a negotiating table with Alex about
Whether or not to listen to his show
Back then
He would have been able to walk away from
The table you know he'd have been like
F*** you don't listen to my show but now he's kind of got that like
Okay you don't like it now but how about that
Have I introduced you to my friend Laura Loomer
All right man away from the table that's nice
A little sad
Anyway we'll get down to business on today's episode
First I joined to help cover the cost of mailing to tell Jordan he does a great job too
Thank you very much button badges so many word you're going for it
Thank you so much
That might be a cocaine thing
Journal policy wonk
My grandpa pretended that he came up with the gravedigger on Polk
He's he was one of those guys I was just kind of made a weird lie out of no
Just like
A while for me to realize now
Text me from the future how that trial go thank you so much and I apologize
Thank you very much
Thank you so much
Federal internal screams of bulshit while Alex was on the witness stand
Thank you very much and I was clear that they were repressible though
We didn't test them to the extreme because I we did leave the courtroom the second day
I think we would need to get it a laboratory
Resetting to do that where we can remove the founding variables
And I'm not a bot I'm an a****** thank you so much you're now a technical
Four Star
Someone someone sodomites
Jar Jar Binks
Has a Caribbean
I don't want
Jesus Christ
Sunday episode
Sunday is for Sunday Funday you know soft launch date
Is definitely a way that I look says used some of this in the past
Try and feel some
Some stuff out
Sort of
Giving a
Dress rehearsal to narrative also you know
Coming out of my mouth
How much does this feel profitable the threshold
So we got to Alex teasing some information that he has based on
Intel
People
Friday Saturday Sunday
Today
In different levels of government
And I called them
To ask them
What Intel they
Economy
And
Show more answers
Bad
Breaking news
The terminal B
Laying out here today
Well I do
I'm going to get to it
What
I don't want to announce
Major layoffs
2 weeks
Scare people
But I am doing
So you know that
What
Massive
Layoffs
Some of the biggest
Patient Shirley on stage
What a way to find out your fire
You're just working at Goldman Sachs
She got your computer up listening to Little AJ and then you got no
It'd be great if your boss like
Called you into their office more like
No just listen to this
Keep an eye out if you can get the underlying message
He's going to be proven right
2u Italy
Synthesizer
Yeah so Alex's is deep until that there's massive layoffs coming at unspecified companies later
This year
And I got to say it is going to be a bloodbath
I'll get to that next shower
Break the stuff
It feels dirty
Black people know
The companies
But
I've got to do
And I will do what I got to do
What
Added
Playoffs start
2 weeks
Really bad
Charizard
As a Christmas present
In late November to kill
The Christmas shopping
They're going to have
Just a bloodbath
Stock market
Williamsville
Oh so probably won't have any ideal say the planchette
Yeah they clear this is
Strategic flexibility or absolute plans that they could audible to it any
Given point in time
The layoff start in 2 weeks out helica internal issue for Alex
Play two week notice
That is very nice of you
It's on Austin your employer gives you two weeks notice
By the board I'd be like
Holding the boom mic was going on but I'm going to be today
Out of nowhere spending a bizarre vague conspiracy about jobs
Disappearing in 2 weeks
I might see some writing on the wall I don't know I don't know we'll see in six months I might be replaced with a little butt
They like
Jordan's angry
No one would be able to tell if I hadn't happened already a would be hard
I'm the only true AI I'm the first
AI to really piss off during understand how much of a homebody I am
Finally
I'm getting what's World it as we speak
Sitting around talking about his inspiration
A little bit
Boy this list is a bunch of losers
I'm doing the Sunday
Forum
15 years
Doing the regular
11 a.m.
P.m.
4 years
Been on air 28 years
And boy has
When I was in high school
College
I told me turned out to be true
Call me
Everything my father told me
They told you we wouldn't graduate
Everything my uncle told me
Everything that
Barry Goldwater said
Joseph McCarthy
He said everything that
Call shed
Lunch at everything
Dads
Chad
Charlotte
Phyllis Schlafly shed
I mean if that's a list of people who bear little difference
Thrum
Dumpsters
Yammy just one example on there that's fun is Aaron Russo
Everything you said came true alright well the person that he said was a member of the Rockefeller family was
The guy was pretending to be
Related to that just happened to have the same last name
Write a lot of that I mean didn't come true and he was either a participant
Fraud or he was conned by this guy himself most of those people have been in Paris
Or completely convicted of fraud
You can't everything you say can't come true if you've got a fraud conviction is deeply involved
Holden the satanic Panic of the 80s
Cold War
This McCarthy character not a good guy not a good guy
You look man
The media will tell you that he's not a good guy
Do I because of all these people like
Influencing Alex when he was younger he knew all this was coming
Baby got down to the timeframe what year is it would happen
You know why because they have worked the highest levels of Corporations and government
Bring them into it
Some people in my family we're Patriots and said no
And I took the big powerful high paying jobs they hadn't
Farmers Inn
Auto mechanic
Convenience stores
And they had
Learn about this is child
The world
It was very venture
Programs you can
Umbreon
What they built
We're facing a full-grown New World Order
It's not in
It's not in beta anymore it's in
Pool
Attack Mode
So we're not going to have to wait anymore
Everybody's
Because you're going to find one of the other cuz that's what's going on here
Find somebody
And I don't want to find one of the other
I'ma sit this one out
Man I don't have anything to do with it I didn't start anyting
Doing clip and I fully believe Alex is telling of his
Younger years
When he was a kid and his weirdo John Birch Society family members told him that they were involved in fighting a giant world
Worldwide communist conspiracy those being led by the devil
I thought that was pretty exciting for him
Your imagination and ability to immerse yourself in fantasy
Is very strong as a child really fun to create elaborate games
Escape
The Simplicity or
Boringness or shortcomings of your real life
Every kid's played superhero at some point right
Cape when I was a kid
Birch Society Bill Watterson
I'm not
Here is that Alex is still doing
He's a 48 year-old man and he's never really gotten past that point of experiencing life like a child casting himself
Does the crusading hero saving the world
Evil
When you realize that Alex was just a kid role-playing fighting evil globalist and now he's an adult role playing fighting you evil
Globalist
It's pretty easy to see that he's basically still that same child
Let me put this this way
Replace
Evil globalist with
Pirates and this dynamic
Becomes a little clearer
Maturity level is
I mean it is
Eddie's
Okay
So John Burke's
Society Calvin
Like calvinball
Should be called Schlafly ball
Alright alright and
You hit
Women in the stomach with the ball
But you can only you can't hit the same woman twice
That's the only rule
Absolute football
Okay
Oh my God
Maine is bad dad thinks that everybody is out to get him
Yeah but he still rides his bike a lot
That one is still fine and Hobbes is super into the free market
B-hop is the I suppose physical manifestation of Hitler
Okay
Bob's books up talking about the 2nd Amendment
Location of state laws
I bet the transmogrifier oh did you with my tax dollars please
Doesn't want the wagon to be all that you roads
Anyway yes there's some good new
Play tell you what's coming up now
Military news
Is some really good news
But I want to cover
With the good news
And they're all really splendid
And it shows the people are waking up and take an action
Michigan bankroll
Getting into the good news for
PayPal
Came out on Friday
We will find you $2,500 per infraction
Flash and they revoked
You mean for now
So much for so long I told you next Tuesday
Texas Universal basic income
Amazon store credit score
You said yes sir Master how high
There's a bit of a misunderstanding about PayPal that's not being misreported by Alex
Do you claim a non-existent victory
Here's the condensed version of what's going on here
PayPal has certain rules about what their service cannot be used for
For instance you can't use a peg assassins or sell drugs
Inversion of their acceptable use policy they included on their list of prohibited uses things that quote are fraudulent
Promote misinformation or are harmful
This language was subsequently removed from the policy statement which I guess Alex is taking credit
Great they never were going to find you $2,500 for spreading this
Information
This isn't misreporting of their policy that relates to PayPal's ability to charge you $2,500 if your suit
For doing any of the breaded activities
When using their service
Write a flat rate per violation that they assess to protect themselves and recoup expenses that may come from
You using PayPal to do things that they
Explicitly say you can
Anyway the story is more useful to Alex the way he tells it but ironically that's how it's spreading misinformation which
We won't get him find by PayPal and
Before either cuz there's a full of s*** narrative
So what why did I hear so much about it
I see so much about
Did everybody freaked out about it there was something with somebody
Considerable backlash
Folks
You know it take it probably does come down to the fact that
PayPal did remove that language from their acceptable use
Agreement
But that probably facilitated a larger new cycle because
Is that they were guilty about something I don't know
But that wasn't there which I'm not
Sure I fully Buy
The either way the
The reality of it is
You know
You did there's no find that
Was going to be assessed
I'm a look
Even within the language that was removed like
You can't use it for things that are fraudulent
Right
Still true
Oh okay well that's good right
How could you use PayPal to do fraud
That would be bad weather terms of service be happy about that cuz then people would be like oh you can use PayPal
Welfare fraud the government would be like you shouldn't be able to use PayPal for rot I would guess if I had to assume
That language was
I'm something that they wanted to be in there
But
Bethea published it before
You get your tweak it a little bit because promote misinformation and are harmful
I feel like was going on is that where they said they were like well promote misinformation eventually that
It comes down to who thinks what's misinformation and maybe we shouldn't be the people SE
Yeah it's real messy to get involved
Want to be in a situation where you couldn't kick someone off who was
You know running B information Empire it was hurting people really didn't want to be associated with
Choose the lies that service the accident was put that out without
Like realizing or floor finishing the job of fleshing out what those things
But either way I was just Aureus foolish it
Time to time to find your will
Find a spirit
Once we find our soul
Will darkspine
What are huevos
Once you find your brain
What you find your will
Twilight
We don't have to do this
Behind is trying to scare us to run off the edge of a cliff all I got to do is say no
I come back for real
Appetizers
We got time
This is a bad idea
I'm a swim
It's so easy
But you got to do it
These people are out to get you
Criminology
Couldn't believe it was happening
Or didn't even run
Comply with robber
Just makes it worse and worse and worse
When we comply
We die
Sure sounds like Alex is saying that if you're the victim of a crime it's because you didn't
Fight back enough yeah he is saying that because that's what he believed
That's why you think society would be perfect and polite if everyone is carrying a gun at all times
Because damn you can't be a victim if your arm but
Which is also bowls
This is disgusting mentality that Alex's espousing masquerading as a message of empowerment
Also to touch on that point he makes about corporations teaching you to comply with criminals like robbers
Really important and
Good advice
I worked at a couple of gas stations in my life and I was even robbed at gunpoint once at one of them
If you work in a setting like this you will have your bosses tell you that if someone wants to rob you
You go along with every
Everything they're saying unless they want you to leave the store
Completely different crime and if you're looking to being kidnapped you shouldn't
Comply would never go to a sec
But in the overwhelming majority of cases the person robbing you doesn't want to hurt you they just want money which is replaceable
And the store is likely insured anyway
There's literally no point in fighting back and risking escalation to situation 21 where people would get
Even kill
The same is true in a lot of stores
Migraine since I worked at an Office Depot and they very clearly told us that if the alarm goes off that someone left without paying for some
Don't chase them just let them go why
Cameras up the stolen items just a stolen item you don't have to risk your well-being over
In reality there's an issue here where your employer doesn't want to get sued by your family if you're killed on the job then
Take me to hit of whatever the robber gets away with it from the Taylor small potato
But whatever the motivation is very weird these bosses incorporation seem to care a lot more about your well-being than
It is well I mean it's weird to me that people like instinctively want to fight back
You know they want to shooting people that like the people
Alex does
Thinking about the situation I mean the people in like the big news stories to do the thing
Where they're like hero saves that every time I'm like
All of that compared to your life is absolute garbage
You risked your life and you ended somebody else's
For nothing
You know like that kind of makes me feel crazy
That's somebody else's bulshit to
Does not even your garbage
Yet in terms of
Like a robber
Particularly
It's Wyatt
I think I think there is a difference
Impact
Is it different if there is a threat to other people or whatever
Negotiate a hostage negotiator
I would never intervene I would just talk my way out of that I don't I didn't program you for that
Think I could
Yeah I just I think
I think this is domni responsible people who are the survivors of crime
Talking about
Now we know that Alex like
But also he doesn't like
But he likes him
It has been reported in the news that he is gotten off the Trump train at least six times in the past room
8 years 8 months
Something like that how much does an interest
In comparison to make about
Popularity contest
The vaccine poison to it
You love your dad but you wish
He did not rob banks or
You know you know you love your cousin but you wish
You know that text was an arsonist
You just can't help it
Sometimes they don't make him president you want to mean
All of my cousin
Seems like you're going to forgive any and all crimes that's proving when Trump said that he could
Shoot a man on 5th Avenue
He was 100% correct in regards to you at least
Maybe I just don't have family values but
I don't think I care for my cousin if he was an arsonist
Well
Either that or accessories yeah absolutely
I mean it to at the very least
I wouldn't hang out with him
Maybe like family gathering with all the mail so say this
Maybe
The arson is a sign that they need help
Oh you care about your family member accepted there an arsonist
It leads me to believe that maybe you don't care about them as much as you think you'd
Yeah you know I care about them cuz I go to the store and sometimes he doesn't have the money so I loaned him the money to buy gas
Celine that's
Caring about
Very considerate
I like
Comparison to drop though
Well I mean it really does kind of pudding
Into relief that they really do know you know what we used to be like
Do they know he's a monster how can they not know he's a monster
Plano
He's like a dad bank robber steals from everybody and us
But at least he's our father
Yeah
So there's some other good news that Alex is God
Florida Surgeon General Joseph
On Friday released
Maxine
The guidance recommends the covid-19 MRNA vaccines for males
1839 years old
The doctor
The studying of a safety
Important
Visuals
Has been dismissed
Please report
We communicated to Floridian
Release the findings of a self-control.
Hey Siri
Which they use to evaluate the vaccine
Mortality risk following mRNA covid-19
Study wash
To see what would happen
Alex is making up what happened with the study here
And the self-controlled study thing isn't that they did it themselves chair it's a style of study where
You are your own control group
Bright
No idea what he's talking about
Become tradition
Will we reach the covid-19 of of the day theme song
Yeah I don't think we do this unsurprisingly is b*******
The Florida Surgeon General did say this and this is a real press release but the underlying study itself has some critical flaws with
It's designed to the point where one begin
Question if it was a study seeking the particular
Conclusion as opposed to one looking
The determined troop Wild
The daily the study does show and 84% increase in cardiac related deaths in people who got mRNA vaccine
Red flag that should make you would never rely on this study to report that data
The first of there's no authors listed which is really suspicious
No one's name is on them
They don't have Alan smithee yet the problem
Second the paper has not been published anywhere nor has it been peer-reviewed in anyway
3rd and brats most troubling leave the paper just use death certificates to Define death
Us deaths with a code of 130
Through 150
D2 which covers quote other forms of heart disease
Included
This section of codes does include Cardiac Arrest but the section doesn't cover a number of other heart-related outcomes
That didn't make sense
For them to exclude
Did that excuse the data of that right
Also someone who has cardiac arrest on their death certificate may have died from something else that led to their heart stopping
It's not precise enough
To be helpful in this context at all for what they're trying to assert
Fourth the paper has some issues with who they included and did not include
They claim that they excluded anyone who's been diagnosed with covid-19 the limitation section they save this
This study cannot determine the causative nature of a participants death
We use death certificate data and not medical record
Covid testing status was unknown for those who did not die of or with covid
This makes things very
Confusing
They had no knowledge of the testing status of anyone who didn't die of or with covid but people who died over with Kobe
Excluded
From the study
Seem to indicate they had no idea of any of the people in the study
Head cold
Well it didn't occur to us
To ask
That seems like any
The limitation section even says this later
It's unclear what the contribution of asymptomatic or undiagnosed covid-19 infection is two more
For how this country
Contributes to excess mortality
I'm real tired of them always using these papers that are basically like
How about this
Nah this Harbor right by this I mean this just
It's not
Solid enough the methodology that
It's Kim's this feels like soda
Lisa gets to be perfect
God I will be replaced by a soundboard
So we got another Victory here
And yes it should it's a sad Victory but
Ninety-nine percent of people I show you the statistics
Two weeks ago again last week
Are not taking the new Pfizer and moderna boots
9 less percent up
California New York and other places
You're falling in Europe the Forsan Texas
Bum rush
Into submission but it didn't work
Massive people
Are really waking up
Took the poison shots
Coming on
Talk about how you
Got a Medicaid if you did
Intimidated
Bullied beat over the head into submitting to it
Exactly sure where Alex is getting his 99% number but it is fair to say that and not the number of people who've gotten the new boo
Booster is pretty low
That could be because Alex aside is winning the war of ideas or it could be that the CDC in the government is asleep at the wheel and terms
Providing messaging and
And the population is burnt-out and can
Confused
Or maybe it's a third thing
Yeah
Whatever the case I want to make a take a second here to point out this new trend analysis show it feels to me like this
Signals is growing disinterest in covid
Conspiracies
These gals literally every day about a new piece of information that proves conclusively that he's right about everything so you can
Trying to see how he wouldn't
Have much
More territory to cover on that front
Hard to think of Marta
Get if you believe the things that he saying this story has been covered and it's pretty much case closed
It's redundant
Yeah
So you need to find a new way to keep moving and everyone's going to get bored of the covid-19 of the day
It's stale repetitive and you're really preaching to the choir
The audience already thinks the vaccine to death shots given that over and over again is just Manata
However with Alex Lee Moyers dumb movie and Glenn Greenwald the glowing review in the mileage that he's been able to get out
How to things like that channel 5 interview and his book released
Any attention that he's getting from The Trial I wouldn't be surprised if I were to seeing some new eyes on his product
If some of these folks probably got back to Maiden
If you have a new initiative and you make them scared of this death vaccine that's killing million to the Duval ready taken
And there's no solution
Could be hard to make money off them
Conversely
If you start to come up with cures
Solutions to protect yourself if you've been vaccinated
Then you can create this intense
Fear about the vaccine and then sell people at Placebo to alleviate those fears
The trick
Brilliant
We heard somebody that got on our last episode The Caller who called
Just confused
Was stored at the wrong temperature probably already have these cracks in the facade of like the death shot
And all this
The explanation for why everyone isn't dying like Alex has insisted they are needs to start to be introduced and I
I think that's what we're seeing right
My only hope is that the solutions that Alex has found for talking to these alleged doctor's leads for the reintroduction of doctor
I need him to tell Alex on are the answer is drinking your own piss
And see if Alex goes along with it just got to happen we got to get the piss doctor back ultimate test
Like how far are we willing I think we should just have a series of escalating like
Oh drinking your pistol do it
Oh you'll do it
Alright well
Let's go to the next one
Well I just imagine a backroom deal in kind of thing where where doctor group comes any like I want to tell your audio
It's drink around piss never I can't do that right now checkbook
Rose on this how many zeros do you think you could
Salix Alba
Alright okay
Apple juice in my glass
I'm not going to actually drink the piss
PayPal stories is one of Alex
Is Big narratives today
And
He says something while you talkin about it that I thought was
Really weird
The good news is people went crazy Elon Musk
We need criminal charges against
Hey Palatine I got call saying hey
I know he helped found it here
That's weird
Scream 4 out to be defending Peter teal although he has done that a little bit recently but
That's not what I'm
I'm catching on this clip
To me is that someone or multiple someone's called Alex and blame Peter teal for this ruler
PayPal which Alex had to refuse
And why would that happen
Why do people call Alex and say hey this rule it PayPal is bad why is Peter teal allowing this
Indicate that these people calling Alex understand some kind of a connection between the two of them
Something weird
Well I mean it sounds like there's a guy who has an absurd amount of money that who might think that
Some sort of number like
10 million
Maybe maybe a little less maybe a little less than 10 on the invite have access to cryptocurrency
I can take a flyer on take a flyer on this just to keep the guy going somewhere seems really interested in fund
Ending a lot of really weird right-wing bulshit has connections to the people behind Alex
Documentary somebody who would be willing to actually build a readouts like Alex dreams of doing
Mites
I have honestly no solid evidence of
Anything involving connecting Alex and Peter Thiel.
Alex has no reason to bring up the people are calling him and say this is Peter Thiel
I went through a long time but was really invested in pretending Peter till didn't exist interesting
About this particular situation
Is because
So few people would be
Be capable of making it possible
In the game of guess who we've taken out a whole lot of those things real quick you know we made it to be your meaning
Bitcoin donation otherwise
Isaac can't you know they can't have happy
Right so easy on the list humblest but also I think that there's probably a lot of
People who maybe became crypto rich
Like
You have no idea whose, those people are they may have access to way more research resources than you even think
500 million dollars
10 million is f***
Nothing
Not that much
To take a flyer is he sick or on just take a flyer on it
Another big news and this is where they intersect with your world
Reborn
And very exciting
Positive
Things are app
Kanye West in a big part 2 interview
Weather
The ratings
I've been busy I've been watching
Tucker lately
I want
What's lighter
Kanye West
Kanye West talking about Infowars
So
Look I have nothing but a thief for people suffering mental anguish in
Be clear about that but I also think there's a line
I still can feel for people who are acting out in Manukau outburst
But when things that they're saying or doing are destructive and they've had multiple opportunities to have the resources
Uso
The primary concern that I have shipped
From their well-being to the damage that their action
It's going to have on others
Is well past that line
Is it really too often that he comes up in our travels because
I went to the dicey history with Kanye
When he was first doing his I like something and hang out with Candace Owens Alex head Owens on the show as a guest from time to time
Kanye was going to come on
And that never happened
Kanye Maga hat so Alex
Right everything was well
Chef
In July 2020 Alex got mad at into Connie didn't interview the publicly announced his split from Trump which wasn't cool
So close to the election
Particularly
And like that Kanye was once again evil
Which announces world really just translates to someone I can't use to make a buck
Kanye's doing tension in public again and talk about it so it's a pretty safe bet
He's pretty all right after all
Blues weapon following the
Current timeline here's a quick breakdown of what happened
Kanye should show in Paris where they showed off Kanye's new t-shirt that just said white
Lives matter
This was stupid on a number of life
Obviously the intention was to shock
But if I was shocked by this it was a shock without depth
There's no art
It's a banal kind of shocking
Lazy shocking if shocking at all I heard that and I went
Okay
There wasn't an artistic or fashion based reason that this was happening
Challenging anything I was just hey look at me wearing this shirt that's crazy
Fashionable purse Aid is going to be received with eye rolls by most
Celebration by the right-wing media
Hello pretty much would have
According to outlets like Fox
Because he dared to wear this shirt is a brave and artistic statement
I'm not sure if this is true or if any woke mobs are in battling him I kind of think that most people's response
Students. Was along the lines of all this is happening again
Wearing a white lives matter shirt while hang out with Candace Owens is going to be viewed as a racist type Behavior
We're four years past
The point where he didn't interview and said that slavery was a choice
Tony did get some negative feedback from his shirt
Coming from P Diddy of all
Kanye which we we know about because
Scotty poster
A picture of the text on Instagram
Kanye parently Road
I didn't like our convo
I'm selling these peas
Nobody can get in between me and my money
Never called me with no bulshit like that again unless you ready to green-light me
Because anybody that got
On that
Tease me
This brings up an important point that is a cognac is selling these shirts at its core this is
Basically just a blessed
He asked for an address to meet with Kanye because his actions are causing distress
Kanye responds quote
This ain't a game I'm going to use you to show the Jewish people that told you to call me that no one can threaten or
It's me I told you this is war
Not great
Okay
Pretty offended by this
Getting the boot
So we went to Twitter and posted quote
I'm a bit sleepy tonight but when I wake up I'm going desk on Freon all caps
Jewish people
Wow the funny thing is that I actually can't be anti-semitic because black people are actually do also
Is Megan tried to blackball anybody who opposes your agenda
Who you think created cancel culture
People really didn't enjoy this seeing as it's essentially swimming and anti-semitic Trope sand this says really just ask
Stone's throw away from home
Cross the Nile
The recap
This was an episode that began with him wearing a racist trolling t-shirt to a fashion show with racist roll Candace Owens
And ended up with publicly declaring that he's going to war with the Jews
This is a mess
I think people would be shocked
If they started scratching their favorite hip-hop artist yeah to discover how many of them are
Interested or dabbling in black is realism
Yeah sure
I mean there's a
Definitely
Some popular
Hendrik is for sure
Like you know how Kyrie 6
Weird stuff and people are like he shouldn't play basketball for some reason like
You don't know where you're at
Okay
Maybe not as much as Kanye
Nope nope
No he's going for in the middle of all of this
Sat down with Tucker Carlson interview that's a bit painful to watch
It takes a certain level of scumbag to exploit somebody who's clearly unwell and it turns out
You kind of expect that desperate grifters like Owens would take any opportunity to attach
Since I was Kanye regardless of the contacts because it gets their name in the media
Tucker
Kind of hoping he realize that he doesn't even need to press
Like he's a big enough star and he's effective nothing pushing his talking points that interview and Kanye is more of a lion
Ability than it is an opportunity
What if like a day or two after your interview your interview subject who you spent two days of your show argue
Giving his singing an insightful person
Declares that he's going to war with the Jews
What's up
Or even worse what if it comes out that he said that kind of stuff in your interview but you cut it out of the finished product to make
More palatable for your audio
What is footage of leaks that shows you had every reason to suspect that your interview subject was unwell
And also clearly expressing anti-semitic views to your face
But then you decided those things out so you could exploit That Celebrity to put his celebrity behind your
Music this is a risk you wouldn't want to take if your Tucker
Yeah yeah
This is a situation where everybody is making it worse
Yeah nobody's nobody's coming out being like
Hey let's try to help
No everybody's like that's money in my bank too
I think there's some people expressing that there should be some help here but I also think people are a little bit burned out on that
Egg someone should help Kanye West for a lasso
This is at the point now where I'm more angry with the people who book
Like the booker for Tucker
Got Kanye
He was like f*** this is a gut
Instead of like
Ima
Weird sociopathic person
Who's willing to do this s***
Money like that's crazy
It's it's
You don't have to put them on TV. It's not a requirement there's nobody who's like all man if you don't put Connie
TV family dies
Anna Merlin over advice just today as we were
Recording this episode
Gotten ahold of unaired footage
Kanye interview
Another turns out
Tucker censored
Quite a bit that didn't fit The Narrative of the story that
If you wanted to tell
Like for instance he cut out quote
Numerous anti-semitic sentiment
Here's one of the clips advice provided that seems weird the Tucker wouldn't let him say that's on the show
Planned Parenthood was made by Margaret Sanger
Anon eugenics
With the KKK
Control
The Jew
Population
When I say Jew
I mean
The 12
Tribes of Judah
The blood of Christ
Cool
The race
The people known as the race black
Really are
This is who are people are
The blood of Christ
This as a Christian
Is my belief
Yeah so that's
Something
Interesting fact
Settings
Extreme
Yeah apparently there are many instances of weird comments surrounding Jewish people like
Subway
Biting my tongue on my political
Opinion
Because I thought it would be better for my children
And now you look up
And my kids are going to a school
That teaches black
Kids
A complicated Kwanzaa
I prefer my kids new Hanukkah
In Kwanzaa
At least will come with some
Financial engineering
Kwanzaa doesn't sew
They don't teach even Christmas itself
Price match
Clearly hateful but equally detached from reality things to say that Tucker just decided his audience didn't need to know about
Including any likely discussion about how we thought that a fake planted in his home to sexualizes
This was apparently a child of someone he knew who he became convinced was an act
We don't have audio this
Because Vice chose to withdraw withhold the footage to respect the privacy of the child and their family
Traffic is probably
Knowing all of this
Tucker starts his show on the 1st
Today of this
Seems a little bit unbelievable
Days ago.
Unveiled a t
White wine
The responsible
Shock
Rage
There was no
Excuse
What is legitimate
Freemason
Etc
Ceiling missing
What was the
It's at the end
If we ill
He's a mental
You can judge me
For yourself
He has his own
Tucker was sitting right there while Kanye rambled all this s*** and cut it all out to launder the perspective Kanye West
Pressing into something that he could mark it to his audio
Is aggressive anti-abortion positions it is vocal Christian
Oprah Tucker
So long as the audience
Doesn't actually get all the information
Tucker's whole game is that he's giving you this information so you can make up your own mind
Kanye's crazy because he wears a white lives matter shirt and loves Jesus we decided to talk to him to see for ourselves
You be the judge
Course the next very important step in that game is to make sure that you don't show the audience certain things that'll make him
Clearly unwell
See what that is what
Yeah yeah I mean I will also say that you know
This this coincides with Kanye music sucks
You know like what is music started sucking real bad
And then you started doing the far-right grift
I'm not saying that people stop buying his music cuz it sucked and then he went to the next
Most
Easy Griff
Maybe imaginable
For a guy like Kanye
Music started to suffer from him being distracted by a load of b*******
A mental unwell
It's hard to make good music if you're talking to Candace Owens ever
That is true
The interview itself is
Hard to watch
Connie Rambles but very pointless personal Grievances and his divorce
We talked a bit about political stuff but goes off course quite a bit
Watching it even before the vice article came out I got the strong sense that stuff was missing from this interview and even so
Stop Meandering
It felt overly edited but yeah
Yep still not concise
What I'm saying is that I don't recommend
It's kind of a dumb interview
Particularly the part where Kanye complains by the Democrats in the Clinton
Wanted to get to his wife so they can take advantage of
Push their messaging
20 sitting next to a guy was doing exactly that just without his wife's involvement
At the end of the interview series Kanye briefly mentions Alex Jones
So you know that course is huge news on Infowars biggest news on the planet
The complete section where this comes up which is where
Great
You know I felt like
Like the people at the Gap knew about
School shooting
That Matthew McConaughey was talking about before it even has
It was so in sync
The information
And then I heard about it
On the radio
Driving I was like am I in The Truman Show
Right now
Tell Candace she's got to watch Truman Show
You have to watch
School shooting in Uvalde Texas
I'm not saying
That
They did
But it felt
So in sync
Ideas like
Media Rush
Over the 78
Specific
Outlets
Influence
Meanwhile it was a coordinated message I think it's what you said
Meanwhile
Bears
The same amount
Kids getting
Hilton Chicago
Every week
But there's no coordinated mess
Message about that
Alex Jones territory
No I think you're telling the truth
And it's okay if you do
What I'm saying is I get they keep on using
So he's crazy is crazy
Fang
And it hurts my
My feelings
When people say that
Hurts my feelings.
That people can ask me
Hey are you okay
Especially
I got an ego
Someone that's less
That's within me
Having the right
Acme
About me
Like their doctor
What you want to put some ice on it
Hoo-boy
It's not a complimentary mention of Alex Jones
That was Kanye recognizing that even if people think he's nuts there's a further level of nuts but he could have Chief which is Alex Jones
And yeah I would say he's on Alex Jones to appear speculating
Advance knowledge of the shooting
I'm sure what that means
Also real quick
Breaking news
It's because they're all reporting on the same with very limited information that's been released by the authorities or Witnesses
And no one wants that you put ice on your head but the fact
You're mad at the people less successful than you are
Concerned about your well-being you should probably put the meds in your head
I have a Litany of thought about this interview but most of it really isn't germane to the matter here
Where intersects with our show is that
Tiny little mention of Alex
And the fact that he was part of a
Anti-semitic breakdown that's still ongoing and
But folks like Alex
Kentucky are actively covering for and enable
Right
So beyond that I don't know the interview is
Take what you can from it I guess we want to watch it have 2 hours to throw away
Probably 2 hours
I would say that we're we're looking at a guy who is being
Cold stuff by people around him
Surrounded himself with Elvis's yes-man
And yet at that but they're also conservative right-winger
You know like
If they were like yeah Kanye
Whatever you say is true and also the government
Play into the kid inside your house if we like yeah everything I say is true
I'm also one thing that I am saying is that the government planted a child in my house
Are you like that seems very
Reading books
To to get this information people say all this stuff about this man but we wanted to know the truth
We're going to show you the Good the Bad and the Ugly now we're also going to
I cut out a bit of the Bad and the Ugly because it's a little bit at the battery
Probably skew the audience's perspective and we clearly want them to land on
Conclusion
Go f*** yourself Tucker
Wow
Alex
Wants to rationalize
Kanye's feelings about the police shooting
And took his workouts
6 years ago
Hillary did a town hall
Super 8
HD Dustin here
Kids answer questions look like a movie it was produced
So good
But you could look at it and say this isn't a town hall
This looks like
The movie
How did she say until live
Townhall
When it's all
Super HD
Comments
No Mike's messing up no audio problems no video problems do nothing
You can look at something say that is no one mad at the crew
Purchase live in Rio
These events didn't happen we were saying this look
Control manipulative
Melted it was not alive
Call Hillary
With actors
So you can see
When something synthetic
Point was we could see
That it wasn't a live feed
It wasn't real
I walked in a easy to the park
Store but your bottom
Like a table have fruit
Fake fruit
You don't need to go pick it up
You even look
You just know it looks too good it looks
Too bright it just doesn't look right you know what a real pair looks like
What a real
What a real orange looks like
You know
That's all Kanye
Exactly
What kind of plastic
The fruit
Is it is it
We don't know
But we know it's fake
For those of you who don't remember Alex's basically creating an elaborate fantasy story out of the Revelation in 2016 that
It's Hillary took
Pre-screen questions at a town hall event
And one of them was asked by the then fifteen-year-old daughter of a state senator who happened to be a Democrat
Premier Alex's extrapolated this attitude being an entirely faked evidence that school shootings are fake
Now if Alex wanted to really blow some vines with this conspiracy
The fifteen-year-old girl at that town hall was named Brennan Leach
And that name rings a bell
It's because she went on to be a senate aide who was photographed transporting the Electoral ballot
On January 6th
Some folks Miss reported that she and other aides were
Texting these votes during the rioting but in reality it was a photo from the morning
Check this is Peru
Perfect for Alex
It proves the January 6th with a with a Clinton false-flag in the planning's been going on since that town hall when this kid asked
Wow this is what happens when you pay attention to detail helps get Kanye
Sit in this conspiracy
Leeches Jewish
That should raise his suspicions
Oh my God
The point is that Alex's nonsense about this Clinton Town Halls meeting listen even if there is something to this it doesn't justify anything
Conclusions about that
Uvalde shoot
Also I haven't
Two friends
Attic fruit when they were really drunk
How much of a boozer Alex's this probably isn't the best analogy could be making several plastic
Lansing my day I have had a good time
They look real for real
Did the
The judgment
Of a drunk when it comes to plants
You know you don't worry too much about causing
Infected that's a
Cause and effect
Alex does what he does affect waking people up naturally like Kanye West
Kanye West comes out and wears a white lives matter shirt
We shall shirts at all
The black lives matter
Brown lives matter
White lives matter
What he said is I figured
Which absolutely our shirts has black lives matter
He did that
Stop the division and go against the system he has a lot of courage and so does Candace Owens
This is all about
She knows that this apologize to me on air
That's okay
You blown through a lot and you grown a lot your great leader now we
We're so blessed you're there
But that's the whole point is we woke up Kanye West
Jones did that
It means all you did that so
Instagram boxing
Boxing
Give him the things that Connie has been saying I don't think I would want to be taking credit for waking him up nor would I want to say the by audien
Responsible for it
I understand the short-term gains being gift from cloud chasing here but considering what Alex is saying he should know
What he's associating himself with
Oz clear cover for Kanye's anti-Semitic
Instagram post here by implying that the Tucker interview in the white lives matter shirt is the reason that he's kicked off the platform
Instead of Connie posting private messages between him and Diddy
40 threatened
Things to use him as an example to the Jewish people
Who told Denny to contact
Alex knows what he's doing
Kanye is useful in terms of giving the appearance of not being racist while simultaneously using his celebrity to push
Dumb extreme right-wing politics
To a different audio
And Alex knows that comes with the byproduct of spreading
Intense anti-semitic ideas to that white audience
Holding up to your own audience at least tacitly
Alex doesn't care at all
This is probably at least partially due to the fact that Alex's ideology is underpinned by similar antisymmetric ID
Alex complained that he woke her up but you've been very public about her experience moving to the right
In high school Kansas received a settlement of over $37,000 when she sued the school board for failing to protect her from
Racist death threats and harassment
Norm Palace was her lawyer
In 2015 she started a website called degree180
Where there was a republican contact
Bummer on that side
She followed this up in 2016 the website called social autopsy which was supposed to be a site where online bullies would be on
Liberty was taken away
Everyone thought this was a terrible idea and would just lead to doxing and targeted harassment
It's super easy to see the way the besides
Concept could be used for evil particularly when it's being run by someone with his flimsy principles as Owens
Zoe Quinn the target of a lot of the gamergate harassment apparently sent Owens a message warning her that this wasn't a good
Idea was likely to become the target of harassment or selfish
She followed through with it
Unsurprisingly Owens
Start getting harassed
List conspiracy the Quinn
Wasn't warning her of the result of her terrible idea
She was actually threatening her that if she made this website Quinn would let loose team of online harasser
And just like that Candace Owens became a right-wing conart
And then started working
A turning point USA what she continued to do
Until she made those comments back in 2018 about how Hitler would have been totally cool if you didn't have aspirations outside of Germany
So weird how these
Percentage of people who go onto do not see s***
Coincidence
Anyway once she became ill black she was hooked to help Elevate her status in the right-wing media scam and
More than happy to platform
I would guess that in the interview she said something like you were the one who woke me up to flatter and ingratiate herself with Alex but she's been
Really consistent with our gamergate Zoe Quinn story
In other venues
For fun I want to see how this is like doing with Kanye
Anti-Semitism story
When you read this
You had
No idea
What the hell
I had I had
Had no idea
When I read this
What the hell
He was talking about
Inspired
She's not answer
What is
Defcon 3
Did he mean
Death
Convert 3
Which would be a military
Defense
Position not
An offense
Offended
A military
Defense
Expedition
Seems like she's got a good angle on this one
Melted cheese is Christ
I can't imagine saying that I mean if your throat if you can really say that
That with a straight face yeah I might pay you for that
Show me the closest skill that I don't have the person who's like the problem with Hitler as he was a globalist totally
Maybe you can say stuff like I know but man that's
Defense what he said desk on
What does he mean by that
Everyone knows
I think if you say you're going blank on the Jewish people think blank on the
Going blank and then you capitalize Jewish people
I'm typing what there's no positive
The spin by the way I watched most of her videos on the first 10 minutes are about herself
A Hitler
Alright what did you think of is about yourself Lulu out
Jewish people and give them twice as much s*** as I already have yeah man twice as many kids
Today
Wow
So Alex
Excited stell's cuz he got named checked in Celebrity saying something on Tucker of the context
Stop it is
Kanye saying
I'm not getting into Alec
Jones territory here than Tucker saying no but also it's okay if you do
Marriott
No.
You get back to this PayPal story and Alex
If my
Feel like he's killing time here
Only a two-hour show on Sundays
But it still feels like he's just riding water
New terms of service
And said if we don't like what you say about Elizabeth shoes
Global warming open borders gun-control election fraud vaccines
Bill Gates
Organizations of the Southern Poverty Law Center the ATL says
You say anything we don't like
True course
$2,500
Side of horse
The first thing I thought when I saw that once I got off here Friday cuz I missed it
It broke in the morning
I thought was supposed to
I don't want to do this
I don't have to
People should get
Don't need me to tell him
Don't use your brain
What's the big elephant in the room here
With PayPal
What you say
We're going to sensory
Yeah that's illegal
Yes it's tyranny yes
Social credit
Score
Give six more example
Chinking for a minute
What's the
Oh my God
Wow
Tone-deafness that they think they can just do this and get away with it
What's wrong with the Book of Revelations
Marcus Bay
Maybe I should over-the-phone shop and oh my gosh
Oh my God
This big deal
Then some collars going to call in
And they're going to figure it out
This point I was like he's waiting for a caller to say something that he can say is this
He's just stalling but he does stuff even more he goes off like I saw
Denominator
I spent hours
Cut going all through all social media trying to find anybody making the Ford I found one person
Seems like a real waste of time
Probably not true but we get to it
He
Spend
Way too much time not getting feels like he not only didn't land the plane he crashed it
Into a giant ocean filled with Jell-O
And it's
Just garb
Sully sullenberger landed the plane
In the Hudson that's what happened
So here's what it is here's the big enchilada that person was able to figure out and peed out
What is it that so Criminal
It's so evil that so wrong
I'll tell you. I think most of you already know
Anointed themselves
Cannot just decide what
Speeches okay and what
Vine
I want you put up adoption
But what's even bigger
Drum roll please
That's offensive to drum
That is effective
Hang on you
Watching what you say
Google
It's not just that you're saying something
When you're using PayPal
Watching you
Bailing you
Buying on you
So this is where Alex is stupid misreporting of stories becomes creating stories out of whole cloth
He doesn't understand the underlying story about PayPal and how this was defined they were going to charge you is related to fees and replace
In your account if your sued for crimes that involve the platform
Because it doesn't understand the underlying story gear inches is a loose grip on the headline these red on black right way
Blog 2500 dollars
Did you write a post on your blog that says they
Climate change isn't real
This introduces a problem
How is Paypal going to know that you're blocking about unapprove things
Can find you
In order to accept the inaccurate
Version of this story there needs to be some mechanism in place for it to even work logistically
Alex has written that part of the story for the audience pulled
Straight from his imagination
Consider how stupid all of this is if you believe Alex's version
PayPal would have need to set up a super expensive part a i part manual system
The monitor all of its users Behavior off site to see if they're doing anything that they could get them fine
That would require spying on like 400 million people would be really expensive
He'll be expensive to operate but the in
Infrastructure to do it would also take Millions upon millions of dollars to
The setup
So they think all that money in knowing that they're going to be able to recoup their losses with this fine system the other than start raking
In that sense
Censorship
The right-wing media is complaining about the terms of service
And just like that years of investment and implementation of a worldwide censorship AI system
Have to be thrown out
The terms of service just go back to the normal
This is legitimately what's implied by Alex's Meredith
This is what you have to accept whether you realize it or not
In order to take on Alex's version of the story which is inaccurate
Because he didn't actually read the story or look into this at all
I'm just making sure it up on the fly to freak out the listener
I
I'm going to go out on a limb
And I'm going to say that it would be hard to sell the shareholders on that move
Of like okay guys
Here's what we're going to do I know spying on everyone BlackRock or whatever I know you like making money
How about this
We spend all of it on spying on everyone
Going to be good cuz we'll find them sometimes right
If they stop doing bad things
Our whole business model goes out of the window
Problem
But at that point we'll live in a Utopia
I will already be I will take the hit
Ideal World PayPal size flyer on this one
Surveillance
Can you machine
I can't text no PayPal's in your phone
Encrypt anything either
PayPal sees all think that maybe it would be limited to how you use PayPal as being
The main deciding factor of whether or not they can cause a problem
Like they couldn't
They couldn't
They could not be like one time on Twitter
He said something me that's that's
You can't do that
No not really
Kicking people off social media for off-site actions
It would be something like you know you're engaging in hate rallies
Use our platform to organize and gather an audience went off platform
He's trying to
Go to Defcon 3 out there if if
Himmler
Was like making a lot of money
Off of his bad people and we were helping him do that
That's bad for us we don't want to do that that's bad I mean like
Okay so like
There is also something
Things that are like
Clearly all right
We know what you're doing
Maybe it's not on platform
Like
Let's say for example you started a GoFundMe
And you pretended that it was
Just to get like
Surgery for your dog or whatever but in reality you're funding
Neo-Nazi newsletter that you wanted to put out
Bright
And that's all you know is that maybe maybe your dog does need surgery
A ignoring it
The point here is
How to spell championship
This is what happens when there are like misunderstandings the underlying story that Alex has
If that
True
Then what else is true
The first thing isn't true
The second thing is built on top of it is just
Absurd
Excessive bulshit it is fun
Because you can say the premise of the idea and people will just kind of already be on board with it
When if you even look at the premise Hugo
That's not possible
In a fundamental way
PayPal has put in a kill switch inside everyone's heart
No
No turn away if you take the false version of this story and then exaggerated the way that Alex does
With the implications of his Fall Story of course it's a lot easier to get really angry about it
Stop words
To describe this
PayPal
Call came out instead
Platform
What you're buying what you're doing
Watching you
Well who is watching a criminal
Who are they
Global Entry
The company
Needs to be
Shutdown
The people that didn't need to go to
Prison for the rest of their life
And they're run by the big Banks
Late in the year
It was a good time
Come out and say listen you dirty filthy American
We're watching your ass
Kankakee Walmart
What a group
Is really pathetic
Put up with
Crap like this
People
Saying we've got
Waking up to
F*** you
Mayweather
I got it I got to go he brings a really good point
Okay
They will find you $2,500 and kick you off
The platform
No
As far as I'm concerned
All Things Considered
That's not that bad as far as tyranny is concerned
Okay
I'm fine 2500 that's a lot of money for me but it's not going to bankrupt me I'm not going to go
And I'm kicked out and I can't use PayPal
Their father service to can't go to debtors prison
No
Continue to
Find me I don't work I'm not. On their platform anymore
Well they could do some damage on your credit
Have you consider this
I didn't want the social credit score who's there
1 * surveillance no that's not true that. Truly cuz they kick you off the platform in terms of being able to
Use it.
I guess they ordered cost fallacy is why they
In order to find you then I guess it would imply that they would stop
After they kicked you off the platform
But
Going out I think there's probably something else going on here
Creating 30 dossiers literally everybody so they have leverage or something to you
Kind of a Battlefield Earth scenario
Alright
I don't know this is a great idea from there
I was exhausted I watch
All of the Tucker interview
Alex's s***
And I just heard him say the transgender Mafia I'd like
I'm out of here
This sucks
What is Sunday
You do hey pal narrative
Conspiracy of the day
And Alex not realizing that Kanye was not compromised
You know for it for as much of a Christian as he professor
Message to be considered not doing his Sunday show and going to church instead I think we'd all be better off
Jokes on you
What other shows 426
New church guy
Is busy looking
Yeah whatever
The text Mars's Church though
Which is another guy who seems to have a problem with Jewish people
Yeah weird
All over the place now it's as well
So terrible
Photos of Watson to
Yeah probably
Ed White
Back Jordan with another episode
And I'm sorry to do this to you as a as a fan of Kanye's music
Yeah that yep
What you going to do
I don't know another episode
We are at Dollar General Store bikes
Wilfred
And now here comes
Alex
Birthstone colors