Important
Pray I have great respect for this knowledge B I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
MoneyGram
Knowledge vype.com
At the altar of Celine
Byway regrets
Had a few what is your regrets today actually
On Wednesday
Sort of a tradition because we put a too much content
Bab instant reaction the pro pad I got a lot of messages about although there's going to be an emergency episode tonight
Well that was on Wednesday. Wednesday's Survivor
Happens Angela Lansbury
Generally get together and watch Survivor also
We've not been able to this already like
Three episodes into emergency episode
Simultaneously everyone's off between to it is a difficult
Situation so I watch Survivor
Pretty fun
But I also I went over and I got this enamel pin Angela Lansbury
Kevin
From Up
The bird said you love Kevin from Up Hubbard
Thing animated character of all time
Lefou
Makes up for how bad up is As a movie yeah I said it
The first five minutes and then forgets the rest of it I have some troubling feelings about that movie as a whole
First 5 minutes
Was a problem
God passport
Stop the darkness of it
Popular opinions about whether or not
Their relationship was healthy
I didn't entire podcast about this years and years ago back in stand-up days I don't want to rehash it now
Has a stand on it
You can stand it up so it's going to be with me
Forever
I appreciate it absolutely
My bright spot Dan is two albums got dropped to
On the same day
Very very good but whatever
Freddie Gibbs Freddie Gibbs
Killing it everybody's it for the past is last three albums are like he's the best route he's pretty great
And then the Yeah Yeah Yeahs came back on new album I know
Sound like
Different band it sounds more like Karen owes more freezing
Is really good
I got to be honest with
What Yeah Yeah Yeahs are right in that spot where like I think I was in college when they were really
Play Popular
I hated the people who are into quote College Rock and they got put in that box but I do know Maps
From Rock Band
This is not
We're all very excited for that maps from rock band that's how I discovered
They really interesting backstory
No no it would be damned
It's Punk scene from the with the Rapture and LCD Soundsystem and Yeah Yeah Yeahs all coming up the same time
Released their debut massive album on the same day
Blueprint
The blueprint
And it was also 911
The reason that I remember that specifically
Yeah I was actually I just as you were saying that I got really deep into my head about
Like how much stuff I discovered through Rock Band and honestly
My parents didn't like the Beatles because they were very druggy
Until there wasn't there wasn't like
That influence in my childhood a ton of like older music as I
I was coming up
Write like a lot of energy got put into weird hip-hop and so like
Encyclopedic back
I don't I don't have that about classic rock stuff is kind of like
Blind-spot classic rock
Beatles Rock Band came out I didn't know
Most of those songs
And then yesterday
Is on there as a kind of this song
I am unpopular opinions about The Beatles
And how much I despise them
Wow but what you going to do
Well let's not get into it now let's shoot another case
I heard the verdict came in on Wednesday and like I said people tried to get me to not watch Survivor with my friend
But I persisted and watching Survivor and here we are
We didn't want to do this on Mike
Because
Run the risk of getting a bunch of
Champagne on my table but we have a bottle of champagne and that we are raising this is a Argyle
Is the name of
Yeah and it's in Chicago in uptown restaurant
A lot of are alive or episodes recorded on Argyle not true Ainsley the street
Podcast
Answer yeah we're having a little champagne while we discuss this
Circle back to Our Roots Aw
I wish I could
I understand it and there was just one
I feel like
That wasn't the
First
Wine and weed
No not the first one we drank was very cheap
So was boba
Yeah anyway
Yeah that is the day of the the announcement of the verdict is Right today
And so there's a couple things
That we're going to
Recovering
We'll have an episode 2 comes out this weekend it'll be a little bit of a special thing for folks course but then
And on Monday I hope to get into a little bit more even of the aftermath
But I decided
You do is we'll talk about Alex's
Response to the verdict
A little bit of the war room and then Alex did a special show that evening
Answer will talk about
You're saying is thoroughness is the enemy of immediacy
That's what I'm hearing
Sometimes things need to marinate a little bit
Tile work
So we're going to get into this talk about October 12th and the b******* that happens
Looks newer be your team stats
Thank you very much so much too high to Brianna from
Rob chew and I'll policy wonk
Thank you very much
Kudos to judge
For her restraint and not throwing a gavel at Alex thank you so much you are now policy wonk
Thank you very much should be clear that was about the Texas case that's how far back is our house now
Let's not worry about it
Robert I love you thank you so much you are now policy walk
Thank you very much and I hope you know Robert Miss isn't a weird thing to tap out of parasocial thing
England
Thank you very much is Paul Joseph Watson According to some
Oh no
Pronounce Patriot
That is bad part of sister paid for being my fellow Wonka and shouting and learning with me
Has from Elke thank you so much
You are now attacking
I'm a policy wonk I have
Risen above
My enemies
A list for me
And then we're going
To come back
And I'm going to
Start the show over
F*** you
I got
20 words for you but
At the end of the day
F*** you and your new world order
She rode in on
And all your s***
Maybe today
Maybe I'll just be gone a month baby
Got to hear tomorrow
And you never see me again
I never want to come
Back here again
Apologize
Today that I
Was legitimately having right now
Better tomorrow
He may never have to come back here tomorrow at some point
To the door and I have another contacts drop for you to enjoy
Is your awesome
We don't fart here we don't fart here
We don't fart here
If you want that s***
You go to onlyfans
I go to onlyfans for fart
Alex on onlyfans no.
There's an interesting aspect to this that like
Think Alex could fart and I have just the audience that he does because the things that he does aren't any more info
That's true that's true, largest stuck
It reminds me of
French
Man I believe was called Le Petit May
And he would fart
I bet he was really really good at it could make a bunch of different impressions of animals farting
He was famous for having an enema every morning
Four Kings
My friend
Alright
I want to start a life
So we all know why we're here today so I decided to
Blow past the first few hours of b******* and rambling about nukes on out to show to get down to the verdict
Is red
Literally
Signed off
In the fourth hour of his show
That is break for commercials at 16 after the top of the hour you just leave
T-Rex
It all infowarsstore.com
That's 45 minutes then I would throw her like I sell tobacco
6 p.m. central
Please
Magnify the broad
You are the power
You're the reason we're successful
Naturally Alex did not leave
The bump
Because after the commercial break
Alright was set to host or they just handed me a note
What is that
Will be about 2
Minutes
That's from my lawyer Norm pattis
Show trial
They are now having the
Secretary of State
In Texas
Zoomy for Quest
The elections
Hell on them
That's an unfortunate reveal of Alex's true feelings I didn't question the Texas election because Republicans
Duh
Sure sounds like someone is driven by concerns that are sincere about Alexa
Hey now that might be him revealing too much in an offhand comment that he didn't think anybody would
Pay attention to his above the left-right Paradigm and that's when you're above the Left Right paragraph
Show about this the Texas Secretary of State came out and made some comments about how severe the harassment that
Alexa
Kitchen workers
Have been getting right
Right and Alex Jones is
You know definitely a part of that
That's that's not
I don't think I was even in a written article in the hill about it that wasn't even like
A part of like you should face consequences for this is that there is
This consequence for already we're already there
We've got the consequences.
Alex Goes to the verdict and I will send it to his credit
He is not under any pretense that this is going to go well
Total made-up crap
We're a public official
Who is
We watch lie to me
Weaver 550 billion dollars
Warriors app for last week
Let's go to the audio of the bigger show trial in US history
Where the jury was supposed to go away then
See if we repelled them
Throw this one out there I think Norm well might as well
Being like I'm going to get down on my knees for a little while
I'm going to pray into this microphone
Find the news is going to be bad at the same time I'm under no pretense that this is
No good news coming folks
Let me ask you folks
You know how much I believe in God
Well I don't believe in him enough to think he's going to help me out here I am not going to get a miracle no so he has a predict
Fiction about this
I don't have any money so it's all Big Joe
There's Blumenthal son
The anti-gun Democrat
Running
Got so this is a good way to experience at one of the
Lawyers is the son of Senator Blumenthal and so right
This is
All because of the app that makes
Perfect sense is a convincing thing that Alex is saying right now I find myself
I mean it's obviously this is 200 million is what he saying he think
Sure he does say that he had it all hands meeting
Like a couple days before
So I don't know if there was something about the judge's body language that talked him down from that billion prediction
To 200 million but as the the 900 million +
Verdict comes along as I always well it's nice to be an a******
It's also nice to just play fast and loose with prediction
If if
The only hashtag
For Alex Jones Is Right
Was him predicting he would lose a billion dollars
I would I would agree
I'll be like hashtag Alex Jones
To be fair I'm not sure there's any public version of him predicting that outside there
So I'll talk about what's going on in this courtroom and they're pretty troubling
Convert 2 mi
Everything
Sorry when
Weird, cuz it away what he's suggesting is that he's some kind of an unwilling
Christ figure for the media
By sacrificing him their purging their own sin and casting it onto a lie
And he doesn't want their send so this is just bizarre
Yeah
I mean
Wait so Alex is hated the mainstream media for forever
For doing things that he insists that he never does
Right however the mainstream media has apparently chosen
Him
As the avatar for all the bad things
They do that he does
Sprite
Right so either many that he does
No no I don't think so
He is without saying that's why he must be the vessel for their sin
The real cry stories of an a******
I killed a cat
That well I mean he fought dragons he killed a kid he brought the kid back to life though whatever
Were the case
Does sincerely look at this as like
I am
Christ
Lifeshare
Emergency Clearwater this is happy
I question the mass shooter
70s rock
Fox Rental
Guilty
Call Jerry how guilty I was
Pausing to get the media time to call Darlin
The full effect
Try to get credibly the corporate system again which they'll never bring back
Is a dinosaur
Come on Christopher let's get it going
Really feel like he's getting impatient with the process and just being like what I'm doing
Yeah I'm tuning in for the verdict so I can do like some sort of the pageant about it and
There's Lowe's here in Brighton
Right
And that that's kind of attention so what you should do in the trial where the
Point is you made a bunch of money off of hurting these people
Is
Try and make a lot of money
Boss of hurting
When they oh no that's
Well that's pretty much what's going to be happening I mean here's a plug in the middle of waiting for the number
Aesthetic
Their world
So proud of my work
So proud of your support
Usports
Dot-com
Saveur.com donate now
They're shuffling papers around the bailiffs coming up
To get the papers and what have you want up
Throwing a little sis even pulloverze.com baby is he was in the courtroom while the bailiff was shuffling
Papers around he be like I got to go outside
So I can say that people need to donate
Money before the verdict
Absolutely
There is a weird thing where he saying like the judge is pausing in order to get the media to TuneIn for Maximum Impact
Right people are tuning into him to see his reaction to the verdict
Like plugs in the law but the same game he's accusing
The court of doing I will give
The judge
Perhaps
Some of the most credit that a a reactionary person as myself can give
Which is that
She read
Pages
Upon pages
Like 15 pages I don't know how many badges so quietly
Didn't say a word emotion she was reading out
A billion dollars and was like
A billion dollars you know what what you have to do to pass the the secondary bar that gets you to be a judge
Just faceless have to wear one of those clear helmets with a scorpion
That's a good idea
Be able to keep a stiff upper lip
First page she read the first page
As an adult a human adult
And it said
120 million dollars
And she did not immediately go
You have a job position in an office
Yeah it's it seems stopped it maybe you don't laugh
America
It to go
Yes I would like
Tom facial like
Pro Alex's you saying he has his two years of Appeals
And fairly close to Accurate in terms of how
The projection
How the process could work out
Losing faith if they're going to read the verdict solenoid
Save infowars.com
Infowarsstore.com
That's how you resist getting raped
Same time
Peel there
It shows how
Tone-deaf
These people are but I want to report I said I would get to it I didn't
Weather hurricane
Beat control your body
Your body
Pushback that weather weather
Irene
If there's a problem
If whether weapons are real
Right
Honestly losing a billion dollars doesn't seem that important debate
I'd be like
They have weather weather
All is all bets are off
If Alex's s*** was real at all there's so many more important things to do than Amelia
Navel gazing your trial
Absolutely
I know it is what it is
What are you mad about millions of dollars with 90% of the population is going to be dead soon
Well yeah a nuclear war millions of people being killed by the covid vaccine whether weapons the whole thing
Severe
But if so
He's having a good time so
He's having a great time he's very
I just bear with me
Corrupt guilty
Wanda
I got one of the bad guys
No One Believes them
Everybody hates
Star systems over there in full panic
Pictures of the pop-up Miss to it there's positive like yeah
Yeah alright
They're the bad guy knew I was walking into the lion's den I'm not surprised their Alliance
I got it and you know we talked about this a bit this Dynamic of Alex interpreting consequences and
Negative feedback
As virtue
Symbols of virtue
Basically a revealing of how virtuous yeah well understood
World this is
Like
How over the target Amaya billion dollars over the target 965
5 million good person units
That I was awarded
In this trial get money but I got good person units in
Real
Actually believe that deep down
That is the Public Presentation of it so
When we get to the first
Account for the first plaintiff which is Robbie Parker write 20 million-dollar judgement
Alex
Definition
60 million-dollar
Emotional distress damages
60 million dollars
Here's what I'll say
Evicted me
And got a judgment of 120 million dollar
You know
I'm going to laugh
And Shout because
F******
Go for it man
You can have all of my money and a hundred million dollars
We got
Fine
You know what you're doing before is what I've got
Alex actually has 120 million dollars so that first judgment must have been like
I mean like if I'm sued for an even if I have 120 million dollars
If I'm in the judgment is being read
Am I also have other cases that are still pending that's not. Probably not going to laugh at that judgment
Right
Little bad in terms of like going to play this through the courts with a
Billion dollar judgment
You're right
It probably leads one to believe that these these puppies cannot be high enough
Terms of getting him right he's kind of experiencing a moment
Like a like
How it looked in the nuclear bombs
Like it weighs 8 was that kind of like he's
Slim Pickens on the nuclear bomb just riding
Slim Pickens dies immediately after that he doesn't have to think go to court that's why it's art
I mean it's like a child who gets sent a timeout need to go sit in the bathroom and then they break things in the background
SoundCloud
Sorry I mean basically all you can do is cheat
Francine wheeler
24 million dollars
Emotional distress
30 million dollars
Acquainted Francine wheeler
Total Fitness
Nothing really more insightful than that yeah and a
I think you should try to put a brave Face Forward
And again play into that like this means I'm so right right that afraid of me
I find it a little bit boring
Xbox
I mean I can't I can't imagine my response
Because that's
And upstairs
Like I would have to go through to get to the point where you would be experiencing this respond
In the moment
I think just
I wouldn't be surprised really hearing those words
Come off as unreal to have like a surreal moment for me like the moment the
First moment they said
60 million dollars
I lost my s*** ghetto like I was like I can't believe that this pretty surprised it was and I
Imagine for Alex it has to have been like
Well this is clearly pretended I'm dreaming you know cuz he's very little attached to reality in the first place
Sure sure
Is there any movie about
Has predictive programming for him
I'll tell you this
Not f****** yet
No there will be
Fingers crossed one day you get to make that movie Jordan in the casting will be weird
So yeah I mean the news a bunch of Celebration they like
It just feels like a game to him honestly
Emotional
43 Nolan
So close
81600000
Not good
GE keep saying like it up yeah
At a certain point it's like
You're going to you're going to have all this above you might as well like make a comical
Or like
This is your team in the Super Bowl
Right and you're down 21-3
And the other team is at the 10-yard line and you're just like
Yeah man run up the score I want to lose by 100
F****** great man I didn't like this football game anyways I want to set record totally
If we're going to lose we should lose by the most there's ever been in the Super Bowl
Just proves how right you are about football
Oh yeah and along the way there's not a whole lot of content but
He does takes a couple Avenues to introduce some like I don't know
80 trans commentary
18600000
So let's just what a show trial looks like
The left completely out of control
This is this is there
They're Panacea
57600000
7 million
Nice Oprah there
Reference to Oprah that was your friend Oprah Winfrey
Look I mean there's not a lot going on here outside of this
Totally
You can watch the video and see his facial expressions and what have you but like
It's just a bunch of played my way
Slowly like
A little bit underneath the verdict perfect
Immediately like
Interspersed with the verdict being read like
60 million dollars
Somatic
Artistic
Purpose there this is just kind of boring and I think Alex even gets bored of listening to
Today's numbers
Plaintiff here about the billions and billions and billions
Was put up Drudge Report right now for
Billion dollars
Personally don't have two million dollars
The company's almost completely out of money
These are two appeal take gears
Scabs almost all of us
This is just
Completely
Lemay.
Party run
Drudge Report
I want to scare everybody away
Freedom
Scare us away from questioning Uvalde
Other event
Guess what we're not
Amber not going away
Literally
For hundreds of thousands of dollars
Keep them in court for years
Appeal this stuff
We can stand up against this travesty
Against the billions of dollars they want
It's a joke
Please go for store.com
He's decided that the Drudge Report is bad now again
Hero who received an
Unfair Kangaroo Court billion-dollar judgment is now
Easy shifting alliances are are hard to keep track of when the devil's involved
Tower it takes a while for these verdict to be read and so Alex
Room starts riding shotgun with a ballroom stay in the chair
Nah I want takes over
Boo I will say no and tries to
Put on a brave face hear it
All you liberals
Volume
Call you Eva
Pedophiles
Hoping that you're going to be
In our depression
No
We never felt better Act
The biggest Victor
Three of all time
You couldn't
Confirm that
Everything we've
Women fighting for is
Real
Are you doing for and everything or fighting
Israel
You've only
Solidified
The truth
This seems convincing
Oh man
Man if everybody was celebrating my downfall the last thing I would do was get up on
A public place and be like
I'm not
Down falling
Billion dollar company that is the only people who would ever employ me in any meeting
Capacity is not a problem for me
On the screen
The years I worked for it
Whatever I could be like someone frankly with Owen just demonstrate basic Excel skills
That'll go a longer way than anything else he does right now
So what events does not juggling not Excel not plate-spinning
Norcos on
How does Batman live on the day-to-day when he wakes up and looks at his dumb ponytail in the
Mirror every morning
What does he think
You don't ever see Matt Faithfully video by Journey
So the music video the road is no place to stop
There's a shot in it always sticks out in my mind and Steve Perry has a mustache
And there's a shot of him very soulfully shaving his mustache looking in the mirror and
After a beating like Norm had in court I just picture him like looking in a mirror and just soulfully cutting
We have to take me to Rebrand feel like there's some
Sort of warrior code where if you lose that men not saying that there's any kind of
But it's just
You know you cut your ponytail off if you lose that
I will say to Norm's credit and one of the few times I'll say that
Owen is trying to do this like
We're actually ever been at least as the perspective of like
Good
There's a lot of things we can do
But that was bad
That was about as bad as it could go
Yeah actually is message that he brings to Owen
Presenting Alex Jones
Casey was in
In the courtroom there
He has
Joined us
The phone now
Respond to this
Billion dollars
Norm it's time to
Jack's
Yeah well let me
Always prettiest
And what's more
Just the beginning
Belbien attorneys fees
Increase this by
The ability to
Damages
This is bad let me dumbass or you mad I could not be happier with norms
What blanket on Owens b******* Brave face
End up with 1 billion hits
I do appreciate that Norm really really feels
Like in the moment
That
This is a problem
That is worth two and a half billion
He really feels it
Nintendo chilling message
That little thing
It's it's to Alex
No. Other people who want to have free speech
Alex has been just crowing constantly about how like this
He's going to appeal in a auger going to fight this forever
Norm is his lawyer and Norm in this clip says he doesn't know if Alex is going to appear
Huge verdict
Chile message
The message that it's
If you're challenging your
India
Determined
There's now a body of
If the stands on
An appeal
Did you respond
Anybody
You better.
That's not the message at all
If Alex takes the appeal Alex's fundraising for the appeal
Incessantly already
So that doesn't
Feel-Rite know
You should be saying we're already at work on the appeal mean
He should be saying that Alex is fundraising to avoid having to deal
I mean
Here's the problem with an appeal
Okay is it appeal unlike at this current trial
They can't bring in the evidence that you know there was already a $50 judgment
At no point in time in the trial could they be like
Hey Jerry
Just so you know we've run this game before and Alex lost
You know
In an appeals court you can be like hey guess what
Separate juries
Awarded billions of dollars the question becomes like is there a procedural problem
I'm with this k
Sure
That would be what you would be appealing on
And if Norm
As the lawyer like you would know what the grounds for the appeal are
Probably be involved in it at Alex's lawyer well he would be the reason that it's
That's interesting
Hey this one's on me
Mistrial in history
This feeling's of the sentiment that consequences are a sign of virtue right it's just
Everywhere everywhere
Very deeply entrenched in the
I think that
Most people would say
Then America is
Is corrupt
This country has a corrupt
Politically
And so then you would met
The state menu table how do you know who's
Corruption
Once again the name is
Institution the news organization is
Infowars
I don't know if you can get into
Future as far as
Appealing this
Or whatever cuz I know the audience
She's going to want to know
Future might hold
As far as appeals are
Concern
Put it into a real world
Computer
Let's say that
In
December of
You go on air
And you question
The app
Efficacy of the
The covid vaccine
Well now you're getting sued by the
Companies that made the
But here we are a year later and now they're admitting
Vaccine
Not safe or affect
They're trying to silence
They believe to be true
Ultimately be the truth
They don't want it out the
So no one's getting sued for that
Here's a shortlist of claims that might be actionable go against Alex
Four family members of people who lost people to covid who didn't
Do anything because Alex said it was safe
Remember when you said it was
I was a race specific bioweapon
I mean it seems like something that might be weird already said it was only killing males that was a that was a little thing
David Icke on a David Icke said viruses aren't even Island that's true
You only accept them into your body
Just said is we're grateful that the vaccine itself does not have grounds to Sue or a conscious
Elizabeth
It would
Well no I think Osiris with OLX the virus owes Alex a lot
I think that owns example that is using there is because Alex would never have been sued if all he was doing was
Was questioned in a shooting
Yes come up with these fake argument because the underlying points that he's trying to make those aren't true
I mean
Easy entire show is evidence for why this is different
Like he does all the stuff that he says he's like
And no one has a problem
It's this what he's getting sued for
How is that not
Consistently pointed out
It seems relevant
Also this brute is not very good
Are you sure this isn't like a giant champagne
Bottle shaped
I think of cologne L man you are I'm going to tell you this right now the Willamette Valley
Is not going to be happy with your reviews
Adventures Isle of Oregon I'm going to tell you something with him at
So Norm like I said I think some of his perspective is maybe a little bit more forgivable or at least more power
Audible some of the other folks in there that is being like
If I hadn't shown up
I wouldn't
It maybe you'd be better off
I think that's
That's what they used to do today
Call Amy Goodwin
Things to argue
I had to move mountains
The wind right
Make the Limited
I was permitted to make
The bottom line is
I stayed home
It's debatable like he might have been better off
Is there a mention of any other lawyer who didn't say
Hey maybe these people are exaggerating their grief may be a different different lawyer
Maybe would have done better
I think I think Norms exclusion from this case might have been advantageous to LA
Will die
Believing
That is
They had not presented any defense
If they'd just been like listen
We do not have any defense for our actions
The Judgment would not be a billion dollars I would say so I think that they made things worse for themselves
If if there was just sort of like a opening statement and closing statement about like the philosophical idea
This is what this is our belief
No questioning Noah
IAAI
Think they would
Definitely come out looking better and the way things went
Well what is your apology if your apology isn't
In the opening statement
And the closing state
It doesn't work to your advantage
Do you have Alex yell about how this is a struggle session real problem
That's a real problem
Yeah yeah
Easy pretty chill about this
I'm sure you now
Alex Jones
Probably side
And that you never
Oh yeah I mean
Getting phone calls
Text messages
Maligning my lawyer ringing
Keytruda case
But I'm in Campo
Believe all three
It hurts I don't like
Paola
Headsets
Haters are going to hate
Haters are going to hate haters going to hate
That is that is the voice of a man
Who is going to get paid despite having lost
A billion plus a billion dollar case it is what it is
Are still billable
Haters Gonna Hate Hey listen Alex sorry about that
Play Shake It Off
Shake It Off lyrics
You know what the most important lesson for a lot of people
When did take the
And Norm knows
This is Adele
Maybe you pretend that you could have one or something nope but don't fight it too hard
If I had if I had had my druthers
We could have one
Anything right
Right right then maybe but as it is turns out that lying is not okay in court
Haters going to hate
Sonoran believes there's a question that no one asks about Infowars
This is the essential question
The question that nobody asked
Must be an answer
What makes
Alex and Infowars
You don't
Drug that is
Foreign to their body
Obvious
And I'm kill
Began under
Understand what makes
Infowars
Ocular
Can the wrong
I agree with Norm that this is a factor that's underappreciated in terms of understanding Infowars and misinformation in general
His conclusion is childish
No one actually gravitates to Infowars or Alex because of his handle on information or the idea that you talked about stories
No one else has the nerve to cover
And I would say he's a drug that he hopes his listeners on even ignoring the dump lisabo a supplement that he sells it he
Markups
If he sells to People by pretending they have a deficient
Fancy that he can solve
Like you don't have iodine in uz need it
Alex creates emotional hooks
The get into people and they operate very similarly to how a drug
The truth or falsity of things Alex says don't matter to the audience because he's a listening of feeling that they believe is true
Some story about an immigrant murder in a white woman that Alex yells about may not actually be true but the audio
Doesn't care because to them
The feeling he's promoting with that story that you should be afraid of immigrants in that they want to kill white women
Is true
That's the majority of what Alex has gotten his skill saw
Evoking
Feelings
It's pretty easy to see why his show is successful well Owen and Harrison are just pathetic also-ran
They can't stir emotions like Alec
Text Cam
Owens just doing a bad Alex impression most of the time it doesn't come off as sincere at all and Harrison's just too clearly
A whiny baby dweeb
They can get a little bit of traction but they
They can't come anywhere near to even being like Alex's second because they can't do this
That's why pjw sucks on Alex's show but he's really successful on YouTube
In that format with the Quick Cuts in the weird close-ups on his face looking very emotional able to make the AR
Fuel thing
Even David night at a bit of this
Which is why I was so dumb for Alex to fire him
Do you or I David night was a painfully boring snooze but his rhetorical style was good at reaching the older demographic
Who really don't care for Alex's Pediatric
He could elicit feelings in the older a supplementary for the people that Alex
Can't hit exactly
No one goes to Infowars because they want information or hard-hitting reporting
That's the LIE they tell themselves so they don't have to admit that they're going to Alex for a hit of emotion
They crave for some reason or another
Usually two
Justify unjustifiable positions that they have like racism or homophobia
They canceled their able to intellectualize those feelings by Alex appealing to those those feel
No and we we all instinctively know this not Lisa what like if you want to get into brain chemistry
The feeling you get from being right over and over again during a broadcast
Do you know like
Alex so off
Didn't consistently massaging your ego you know
How different from that is getting high for 3 hours
Save the World by giving him money
Jerk my ego offer I get high like it's very similar kind of things you know
Yeah not too dissimilar
The old wants to sue people now too because like
Popular
Yeah it so people call him a racist
And so he wants to see Norm has an interesting response
You know it's funny hearing you say all that
You know I'm banned from pretty much all big
Can take an Uber
Can't take an Airbnb
People call me a racist all the time
Contractions all these lies about me
24 billion dollars Norm
You can try
Just got to find
Yeah you can try
That's probably not the response that you want to hear from the lawyer I go for it
Because you never win tonight
In private
That's the response that you want to hear from a lawyer
On your show you want to hear
Hell yeah we can all Sue tomorrow
Walked off the stage after bobbing for an hour I would be very difficult to talk to go here
For like a half hour so you came offstage to a bill of a billion dollars from the bar
You drank the wrong bottle that is not
Far enough relatively speaking from a lot of my life
In my world at the time I bill my bar bill was about a billion dollars
The interview is not very interesting past
Pastor insight you're getting good sort of a lot of the same like we're going to appeal take two years
Spray blah blah give Alex money
Yeah
So the War Room
The rest of it's just going to be a knowing and I don't care later in the evening
Alex comes back
He does his evening emergency broadcast
This point he's got himself a clip
Of Chris Maddie
On the on the steps of the courthouse afterwards with the family's behind him
Giving press conference
And Alex
Plays that this is this is sort of
Got our finance
Give him money
Obviously
Red party
King daddy
Uhaul.com
Listen to your
Change it.
Support
As long as it take
If you're out there right now
When you're 10.
Audience member
The only
Today
Thanks for your rig Court
Two things stick out to me here
The first is that this notion that Maddie would have a plan to discourage Alex's listeners from donating so Alex
Have enough money to appeal the cases to purchase on it
Is this case what I was as much of a railroading is Alex insists it is he should have no problem finding someone to
To defend him pro bono
Good buddy who clearly feels this cases of threat to the future of the world media star Bobby Barn
Barnes any of this were true that this case impinge Don
Fundamental constitutional rights
The ACLU would be all over defending our child printable goddamn Nazis over the years
Alex is not worse than them this was a principal matter they sell you couldn't
You couldn't stop them from
Begging we can't wait to show off how ACLU we are
The second thing is that tone at the end there were Alex's saying this isn't going to stop is probably unwise
There's still the Posner case to go you may remember himself fly a little too freely it feels like
That could haunt him
Particularly because that case is one where he is
Super guilt
Could end up being way higher than the Lewis S11
Alex is trapped in a space between being essentially impotent to change reality and a defiant to the audience
Or risk the cash drying up
If what Norm says means anything
Sure to be a while before this appeal is decided and ends up losing that
Unlikely ends up being
Thanks for the time for abuse of the appeals process along the way
But if the audience loses heart
That's a bigger Danger
I went over to save Infowars the other fundraiser they had to see where things he was about
Thousand dollars on the afternoon of the 30
Haha the day after the verdict came at 2 that evening of the 12th okay
He can muster
I went all out on his show on the war room and then here we have Alex doing an emergency
Guess that retroactively became part of a marathon that became
It started at 8 a.m. that day and then went till midnight
Owen spent like three hours taking calls after Alex left
In the first episode of Alex's long-awaited all colors show
Actually still isn't the thing it was just feeling timeshare
They pulled out all the stops
And also this is Vitaly after Alex's show on the 13th
And this is where they got to
It's a respectable number for sure but it's not going to do s*** for him in terms of staving off bankruptcy or paying lawyer
There's enough to fight this two-year appeal process
Seems like a free market is saying that the demand for Alex's show just doesn't justify its exist
Anymore
Amtrak
Like I said
This is never going to stop thing is
Making the
Lawyers the plaintiff lawyers case for
Okay so one million is 1
Percent of a bill
Am I right in saying that
It's a thousand million
Wright's Auto
Is 1.1
So that would be
2%
Of the total amount needed to pay that off yeah but that notion is I need
Enough money to pay the lawyers to make the business of pure profitable ship Bankruptcy Court
And then it'll be smooth sailing
So maybe $200,000 a Piers to be close to enough
Of a supplemental money
It's a
It seems like
Not enough if he gets a billion in Bitcoin it will really narrow down the number of people who could be
That's true you know like a lot shorter
Bissell barely wide range in America now but but I think I think Logistics put aside
In fact they could do this like really go all out have a billion-dollar judgment against the company
Muster out of the audience
It's not good
I mean like
Just sort of
Sending buttons to people for free
Bright and if people want to donate to charity
Like what $35,000 Plus for it
It's a 200 Granda we also don't have a billion-dollar judgment against us and we're not begging
People to donate to that's a big part of our overhead keeping it low
Like $200,000
In Alex music like with his circumstances
I just think it's a bad Omen of what he can muster out of the audio
Yeah they should be should be over a million
Yeah I would think
Based on
Actually
The fundraiser the goal is five hundred
Right so mad and recycle they should have hit it they grow
If anything about Alex
His reach is audiences commitment any of that
We're
Like meaningful I find that to be a real real l
If we actually had
10% of the world listening to knowledge fight
We would be able to drive more than 200
I was going to say that
Oh no
A real lack of Engagement commitment
Alex is at Tom's people offer them jobs
But he doesn't give a s***
Hate to take one of the
Play clamps Capers good landscaper
He was I can take those cuz he'll be fired from them immediately
But he he reached out
Tried to find somebody big to have on for his marathon of course he's got Steve Quayle
Guy who believes in write Biblical giant
Right
Organization
Put us on are anywhere you're not shutting
Crackdown
In Defiance
Steve Quayle when the icons
Liberty Movement
Totally dedicated world
Not the oven
Nuclear war all of us here
Everybody's been Vindicated and of course that means I don't know if you saw down
Where was this
I think this is over by Navy Pier, there were a bunch of giant
Oh s*** yeah
Oh my God the last time so here's the problem
Like we've I've lived in uptown 45 years when I moved into uptown
Unfortunately it appears that I was gentrification but I wasn't anywhere near as bad as the Giants
2 moved into the past
I mean they're nice
But they take up a lot of room in ruins the lakefront
View Skyline
Just talked about the b******* about how World War 3 is here
That World War 3 is here
According to them
The international Banker is in global
Play Store afraid because Putin went to the gold standard
Meanwhile just wanted people to respect
His borders that was his whole thing
Like you went to the gold standard and everybody else
So mad at the problem
Well that's probably just announced that they would buy goals from domestic institutions for a stable fix
Price from March 28th to June 30th 2022
They didn't anchor the rubles value to gold which is what Steve is saying that they did in order to justify this can be
That the globalist want to start World War 3 over
Right
Russian made this move because they had a giant domestic gold Supply
The craps vetement plant in Siberia is one of the biggest in the world and after they invaded Ukraine these them
Plastic gold producers were barred from selling to International Market
That would be really bad for a lot of folks with a lot of money and valuable commodity
Putin announced that the Russian government in the central bank would buy their gold at a set price to offset
The setbacks that were caused by invading Ukraine
The way the United States does for like cheese
Yeah this was set to start on March 28th and the price was cited 5,000 rubles per ounce
However that announcement made the price of the ruble jump about 20% and on April 7th Russia decide to go
Back on there. Spent it begin buying gold quote at a negotiated price
Berry Rush of them
The rebels have gained in value so they were getting screwed on the set gold price they decided to end it months before the program was set to run
So just to clarify stiva saying that the globalist want to start World War 3 over the fact that Russia put their currency on a gold
Standard but in reality the ruble isn't on the gold standard
Spanish Fork turn buying of gold is that price
Was just done to offset some of the market inconveniences that came after invading Ukraine
You could say that Steve is on here just spouting
Complete b******* in order to spread pro-russia messages and talking point but
And this is not
Protrude
I stand corrected
I got you so that's that's a large portion of
What they end up talking about super interested in it
Weird stuff ends up happening I kind of enjoy
Alex
One of his big
Dwayne
Did this is profitable is
There is a very severe thing that's happening
But there's a chance we can stop it
That's the gate there needs to be
Denise me that window the maybe we can get out of
It's going to be expensive tragedy we cannot stop however if you donate to us we can stop it there's a chair
Exactly so he asks Steve If This World War 3 can be stopped
Do anything the silencer
The true silencer
Even
2 Pro
Vokey
World War 3 in this is
Big issue
Tonight Alex
We're on together
It's not something they don't
It's not something babe
I fear they want
With all
Out there
Globalist
Luciferian Mike
Because at the end of the day
You've talked about not your videos
Population
Depopulate
Quads
Clams how's it going
How to do it we watch
Millions
Probably more
Like at least
I'd say
50 million
Why would you believe
People have never familiar
Can we stop it or is it biblical as I'm stopping
It cannot be stopped
It cannot be
Canopy
These are the days
That obvious
The Four Horsemen of the Apocalypse
My house
Interchangeable
They used
Conquer the f*** down then right I believe me
How do you say that and not also be like
Hug your loved
No like
You're saying to me
Global thermonuclear war is inevitable beyond that
Horsemen of the Apocalypse
Explain to me why I go to work today
Unless your job is digging the hole for your family too high didn't know why you would
Well then let's go dig a hole for my tablet
Inconceivably it's go to the bunkers right I mean like that's the only
X I mean okay
So here's I feel like the game that is
Happening there is he's playing a game of chicken with
Where is like okay
Go to work
Have some time
Go out to eat dinner all the time but
It's coming
So you got to guess
Well I will say that I think it's Steve said s*** like this before and it has really hurt his career so I think he's probably
He's probably a little bit jaded to consequences
I might feel like he he suffered cons
Brighten on
Also Steve is like an end times guy like he's on Jim Bakker Show a bit looking at one of the few people
The show that has like cross over to Baker
Always Unstoppable is always happening we're already in the first of the
The circles and
Yeah like I said
Checks up something happy
Have they talked about Jesus a little
Now you know I love it
Steve
Has an interesting relationship with Jesus
How can you okay
Let's hear it
What's Kevin Bryson Tyson
Well
Appreciate
Dot-com
Talking about
Your Awakening
Your understand
Oregon right now
More in Portland
Travel time on that
Number one
When when
You would ask me invented
The bottom line
Bible
Claire's at the
Testimony of Jesus
Spirit of Prophecy
God is the only
Supreme deity and being the god of the Bible
Until the end at the beginning
And if you do I had an encounter with Jesus
Physically song
He gave me a
Panorama
Yeah he
Physically saw Jesus
What's a panoramic
What we've talked about this before he said this we we've discussed him saying this on the show before
See the beginning of the end see everyday life
Give him every bit of
It's sort of like going through fog you know like you can see something a little bit of head but I'm not going to like not Runaways
The next talking point God gives it a vision but not like 234 steps down the road
Panorama
One thing I've noticed about God
Huge fan of plausible deniability
He loves giving you just enough information to convince
Just enough people
But not enough information to prove it
Understand strategic flexibility
He's such a good guy
Does Steve tells the story of meeting Jesus in The Flash
This is the night that Alex lost a billion billion dollars
In this case Alex I accepted
Jesus out of Hal Lindsey meeting it's a Student Union building
I didn't know you know
Explain to me who Jesus
First time I had anybody
Play me Luigi's
My mother's house
Elite blocks from
Montana State
I walk into my room which
I have a bedroom in the basement
And the bottom line is
Jesus physically appears by the way I wasn't drunk
And I wasn't doing drugs
And
All the sudden
The glory of the Lord and when I say Glory if you want to know what Jesus
Revelation
Because
When he lifted me up and I said Lord
Who are you
He said I'm Jesus
As your savior
And I'm
Giving you a joke
I didn't know who Joe
When you look into my eyes every cell in my body
Islam
Is Forgiven
I had an understanding
The Magnificent
Told you one Bible
Story
You know probably maybe one Adam and Eve
And the bottom line is
It was so overwhelming
3 hours
Bastide issue
Should say pray xeomin
And is it in
Presence of the Living God
And after that he told me I would
I would know him
Understand this is not a dream it's not a vision this is like
Terrafirma on Eartha
And he said I'd know him don't do that ever again
Through his word
Alex
Fast forward
Experience
Speak to an Assembly of God pastor
Because he's the only one that could let me know
What it meant to have an encounter
Oh Jesus Christ
So he was on campus
Lindsay meeting
Not knowing
Everything about
Nothing to do literally knew nothing weird things to do at home
Yeah it went to the basement
IPad 1 boom
Jesus in The Flash
Wow
What are the odds
Explain to me
Explain to me honest
What is Jesus going to Mont
Gorgeous country
Balance
That's
You know I saw Jesus once
Like actually but not in a romantic Breakneck exactly
I was having so many hallucinations like it was one of my first ones
I was gone for like 2 or 3 weeks
And I remember seeing Jesus I was playing pool in my basement
No no
You can't play pool against Jesus
But now I remember him like a
Talking to me
And II was very much like
Use the horse it was it was cool being in a manic episode when Jesus meets you because at the same time when you're in a manic
Episode you like
It's nice to meet you is equals Jesus you know like I'm the savior of humanity you're the savior
Got a lot in common Manuel it certainly is someone you'd want to meet in a vision other than like
Pete
You know District
It's like what everybody talks about status hallucination
Queen Cleopatra it a bit like if your past life is I was like
I was David he died at
You know
Let's not excited
Selena doll that aside we have Alex doing the show where Steve Quayle is on talking about how he physically met
Jesus and Alex's being like yeah but you did love it
Reality
Believing everything speak whale has to say because he has been
Well I mean I'll just let him know by the Lord
Why God
Shows me a lot of
You're such a
Blah blah blah
God chose
And he
When he said he'd give me a Joseph Smith
Prepare the people of God
As we come into these anti Jose's Ministry
You know that you've hurt me so many times
I always tell people look
It's not like I just
Sit down and figure this stuff out
His mercy and in his calling to me
Opens up events beef
Before my eyes and I get flash
Four words
You know so when you talk about Jesus
No I wasn't
I was on
Heavenly
To get up that's
Been my experience
Like Moses couldn't even
See God
It's like
I've had it happen
A couple times I can't even I'm slide
It's like
Total knowledge
God dumpster
The data dump
I think Alex is like I think what he has is night terrors
Yeah like he's describing not being able to move
And like so many of
The things that he comes up with are based on movies he seeing
Horrifying
And that kind of feels like maybe he wakes up with like sleep paralysis
Like I don't know didn't think that makes total sense to me where is Steve is just
I had a I had a really terrible incidents of sleep paralysis one time I was in this place in f****** blue
Bloomingdale Illinois and you're watching Jesus play pool
And
You know that night terror where you do the hallucination think hookup
And there was a man in a wheelchair slowly Wheeling his way into my room in it I don't know why
That is so scary but the speed at which he was doing it was like
Wow
He's not even trying to murder me and there's nothing I can do you know there's that kind of lazy as murder
It's not even a hard murder for this dude you no Terror for me would be like if
Time there and I can't move
Alright sleep super sleep paralysis
I meant like
Kevin the bird comes out and I can't hug
Derrick Byrd my bad
Yeah I think Alex has night terrors I think Steve is delusional
Good good use of time on this emergency
Did they lose a billion dollars today
It's so weird
Play evil I guess we will be included in that
Try we're afraid because Steve has met
Jesus
Crazy
That don't want to admit they're such
The sickness in the rain
Because this
Real
I mean this was like you were able to look at
Just like
Hamburger
This is
So dumb
Any weight that they spend quite a bit of time on this this emergency episode talking about
World War 3 Russia School actually
And then quite a bit about how
I mean that makes sense apocalypse a country where I wouldn't be prosecuted
And the salvation of the Earth yeah that does make sense for us lost a billion dollars
How to be prosecuted Russia for something else
Prison food
So Alex said goodbye to Steve Quayle
Farewell
Give the Giants my best
And some other guests
Like we got Robert Barnes at work
Oh my God
So we're going to sue
Call fraud he was ride
Comeback
Very short
How dare you
Dare you
Are you get the weather weapons right now
It took him hours
He tried to get to it right before the verdict in the evening so he's finally getting away with it
Continuity it's a payoff before Barnes shows up
Tia Barnes coming on I love the idea that like
He was too busy
I didn't follow through with the case
The idea that
Barnes
Was like hey
Let's cooperate fully
And Alex said no
Infuriates me so hard let's do this by the book
Motive here I swear to God
Barnes is on and the two of them just talk s*** with each other about how you know
Everything is unfair the world is against them they're Heroes everybody's mean
There seems to be like a through-line between normal so comes on a little bit but both
Have this like
Suspicions about how like
Chris Maddie said
Don't donate to Infowars that's not a good investment not a good bat
Right and they're like hey
Shouldn't he be wanting everybody
Give the money to Infowars because then his clients get more money
It's like
I don't think you're making the argument you think you're made they're trying to fundraise off like a
They're trying to fundraise off of them telling their people that they're going to lose their money if they fundraise
Yeah
Secretly we're not going to give them any money
Yeah it's very weird uncompelling
Define compelling is that Alex I think maybe had a few pops
Because he seems to be
No he seems to be communicating a little bit differently
Again the whole thing
The billionaire
Ask everybody
Was just really meant to do and then
You predicted this
On the show 20
Anna Connecticut
Do you shed
Yes we know me
Two people
And when
Criticizing
Here is this
Texas
Major
Government official
Secretary of State
Was he in
Heart rhythm
Every
Texas TV station
We looked at
Said
Alex Jones
How you doing buddy
Hell
Questioning
What 2020
He seems to be suffering to get these words out
It's better to struggle
I don't know he's like had a few drinks or if like he's just
Gassed but like it's
It's very weird
I would
I I swear to you
In this
One instance
I cannot
Judge anyone's Behavior
For the moment after they receive a billion-dollar judge
I just
I don't know how you would behave at Baseline
Absolutely
I feel like getting absolutely s***-faced beyond all reason makes just as much sense
Anything else and he was wearing a lampshade
Absolutely
Live together yeah that makes more sense than going on trying to defend yourself I would have known
No qualms with that I would have some no confusion nothing no
Nothing to report Alex was wasted you know it's crazy baby it's for the first time in anyone's life
Life you could have truclarity after receiving a billion-dollar Judgment of just like you know what
Literally nothing I do matters at this point you know what I think would be like that
Episodes from like Wayback
Where he gets really drunk and yelled at Adam Schiff on human skull
That should be what he bet show tonight I'd solutely
Absolute Insanity yeah that would make sense
Play about physically beating Jesus and then is like burping through
I've been sort of banal conversation with Robert Barnes it's like I don't know it's disappointing
Yeah start screaming about art
Finding skulls in
And the ways to learn come on buddy I have not said this before too too many people but Alex I think you should
To get drunk at work
If there ever is a time when everyone would think it's fine totally fine if absolutely yes
So
Alex just like they're not getting my money
And it's long
People keep
Infowars on the air
Bye-bye Prada
Anyway
At good price
They will lose
Good prices Barn
What are ghost weapons with
The bankruptcies
Regardless of what happens
As long as
The people stick with
They cannot break
Through that line and don't notice
Chris Mattie said that
I don't
Give
Air money
Supposedly his finest are going to get it
He doesn't want that
Absolutely
But they've figured out
Is that
The audience
Forza live
And they thought they
Looks Maricamp
Republic show
The show trials are all about
To be able to
Get the audience
To turn
Away
Infowars
I think the journey past the stevequayle portion of this
Episode is
Just kind of the same s***
He says with Barnes normally yeah
And then it just a progression of him
Audibly falling apart okay
It's about getting it
Audience
10. Listen
Did not supported
Denali braces
Itself
O'Reilly's
Point
Hey
I hate the audience
So I can hear it there
Don't give a
I don't want my
Honey
What about that
About silencing
The best
And what they wanted people to
Begin to self C
Supportive info
Go to Barnes trying to do some heavy lifting
To like carry the weight there
Yeah you can even get a little bit of that vibe off Alex and it's not
It's not inspiring I feel like the
Traditional like stereotypical child of divorce you know with that like
Hypersensitivity towards the moods of sirte
People I still like
Oh I know what happens next whenever this type of tone like when Alex starts talk
Walking without that kind of thing it's like
Oh man I'm so hypersensitive that like I know what's coming man you know
Like not
Be seeming like I'm being a
How to use or anything there is no like
Blow up
He just seemed not on air
Really going on that doesn't inspire a lot of
Confidence
So Barnes
Set some shity things
Was never about
It was never about
Other families
They were simply
Tool by which
They could
Try to
Shame the Infowars audio
The silencing
But I'm proud of you
Stay right there let's
What you guys go back
Strawberry
I wasn't gag
Merced
Talk about
What he went there
Play Sade I was allowed to defend me
Yeah I mean like why can't it be both
Bonsoir about the families
At about what Alex did and also about shutting his ass up
Hey that's
Compound problem that is far beyond Barnes has ability to understand at all mutually exclusive
Naruto in fact almost
In their relationship
Norm says a lot of basically the same s*** that he said with with Owen Earl
Earlier and
He is giving
Long
Talks
In court I will say there was one moment that I didn't cut a clip from but I thought was pretty cute and that was like Alex asked Barnes
Oh I'm sorry I've been talking too much
Haters going to hate man
Edward haters going to hate but
As it goes along you just
KIPP Ascend put Alex's just he's run out of gas
Noir
Nuclear war
They've killed twenty million people with poison
Being a man of the year
Globalstar for me
So sorry for the millions of illegals brought across
Kids
Those are for kids
Is drag queen story time
I mean look
I can tell you what
Infowar.com
Billboard.com
Batman
Is just
Shameful Barnes
It is a
Moment maybe one of these most
Shane Pomona
History of American law
I thought you meant the show we're doing right now
Sorry I misread that never said anything more true unintentional
That's the most adults the most true thing I think he's ever said honestly
Alex like
Being like
F*** it
Alewife
Give us money or don't come get it
That is still like a desperate plea for money it is the appearance of like I do
Yeah totally
I have got so much money I mean
Powerful I've got the will I got the will to give me your money or not
But seriously it's not
It does lead
To Alex doing the interesting
Unplug
And it leads me to think
Things are worse than he wants to let all
But I mean
Can you donate better
You heard the plane
Crap anti
Say do not give Alex
Money
The lost cause
He needs your loss
He wants to break
He hates the show
Because I'm a focal
Liberty and freedom
Creatures
But I'm not worried
And
So many of them,
But I've got
More to do in the fight
Cam
Safeway.com
The fundraiser Banyan
Coin
Special running right now
I was 77
Dot-com
With the promo code 70s
70 sex
You $3 off of the coin
Get the coins a fundraiser
Infowar
Store.com
So the idea of this coin
Is we're selling it at a high market rate fundraiser for the show
If you want to buy this
It cost more
But it's symbolic
Right
Now
We're offering this
The way cheaper
The fundraisers good
But we got to get the s*** out of here commitment to the idea of that fundraiser
It has no chill to it really stinky desperation
What exactly do you think I'm going to do
With 20,000 coins
With no value
Nothing create a Teddy Roosevelt room
Oh yeah that that to me was a sign of
You gotta move these f****** coin and we need whatever we can make on them
Now f*** the fundraiser thing they need some money slowed
And raucous Applause from everybody I think Chris Maddie called in was like that guy
That you apologized and now we know none of that
Keep an eye out for the last words that he said okay
Pagasa
Globalist
Bastard
Go to 74.
Dot-com legal
Thousand
Money
Products you need
You heard them don't bet on Jones
You're not a lost cause
The damn War
And it takes money to win Wars
I got a few more tricks
What we going to break
Airborne pathogens
Prescott
Recent takeover
Call me back
Lord willing
11 a.m.
Tomorrow before that
There is American turnover the great Harrison
Central
Infowars.com
Reply show God bless
Support and good luck
Good luck
Good
The weird
Weird quite good-looking goodnight
Very different tone of good luck
What kind of luck
Does the audience need here whatever if you just told me an hour ago
That nuclear war was inevitable good luck with
And there's no stopping
Listen
Good luck
I will call in this individually find myself quite uninspired
Look we have the billion-dollar.
And obviously
Alice's response at in the moment is about what you'd expect
Cheering it on and started making the game
That's
What it is
Later on in the evening
He does his emergency show and
At this point
I would say the mission
It's best you could possibly do
Do a show that lays out some hard-hitting information that the globalists don't want people to have right
Prove your worth
Right do something that is undeniably great
Because here's the deal
I've already f****** knows that you lost a billion dollars
Audience knows that
Do you need money you don't have to be a desperate weirdo
Do something don't spend a f****** hour with Barnes & Noble complaining and whining about now
Nonsense
Do something that really changes the game
Because you probably have the most eyes
Possible on things the most attention the most
Like if your mission is really about an information War
Information
Don't spend time talking with Steve Quayle about how he physically met Jesus
Don't do that
It to me
The reason that he did that
It's cuz he has nothing
There isn't something else that he can do but there's no elevation
No no there's no way that he can be like the rest go back to basic
It cuz there was no base
There was never anything
He was
Empty from the start
G Edward Griffin won't answer his phone call up Webster Tarpley doesn't like him skeletons in bed
Yeah
It is Ron Paul doesn't want to come on anymore and why does it matter if he did
Answers
No he's the whoopee cushion of the right
He's got nothing but a burden seed Rogers his own problems
The January 6th committee wouldn't even come on
I wonder if that was like you like I'm at a photo
Pass on this one
I've done all I can for you I lost you a billion dollars
Love me still
After having lost you up billion dollars
Yeah brutal
Also this is a strange topitzer Steve pieczenik came up so I
Rodger recently was on out to show in the middle of a hurricane that hit Florida
And
Rodger did not correct Alex's
Politeness through. Give him a lesson in manners and I found that to be disappointing
Rodger was like you didn't ask how I'm doing it really should be a situation where we could put together a super
Eventually of life
People who maybe he called somebody and lla when there's fires or something
We can ride
Everybody needs to correct his polite.
I'm doing fine thanks
We would play that with
My way
This is a sad showing for an emergency broadcast
Sounds like phone call Shelby
3 hours and
Who cares
They did a whole day until midnight
Then out to show the next day and of course the great Harrison Smith
Chair in the journal
Owens war room
About 200,000
Man
Daughter
Seems like, the juice is
Not loose every movie you've ever seen
Where it
It's like the leader of the pack like the ATM has got a serious problem
That's Arisen in just for that
You can turn around and look at your team and be like
We can do this together
Maybe it won't be easy
Maybe we won't win maybe it's not a hundred percent shot
But I believe that you and I can
Do this together
And Alex looking over at
I am going to pay up
Billion f****** dollars Alex turns around
PCS Owen he's he's Bobby bar he's he's Norm
Izzy's stevequayle rambling about surround
Comes back and he says
Goodluck Goodluck my team sucks this is no good
So I'm back probably a sneaky snake over the the weekend and then back on Monday
Day with a little bit more of a follow-up on thing but this is me the immediate
What we got
So until then told me to see you again we have work so we do if a website is now is right.com
Well for the day I say
Text Jordan
We're back but until then
Emilio Emilio I'm dzx Clark I'm Wilford Snapple Snapple at the Gravel Pit Bull
The sex robot
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color