Air Jordan
I have great respect for knowledge by knowledge
Acknowledge
How's it going
Out there
Damn
The situation
The other day
Jordan
After the verdict came out on Thursday
We had the opportunity
Do sit down and chat with
The plaintiffs attorney from the Texas cases
Mark about
The goings-on reflect a little bit on the case
What were the most likely next
Steps
Oh man that is a little boy
Both holness
But Wellness
That's what it is
It's a bonus little episode for this weekend for you all to enjoy
Sneaky Snake
But here's the thing do me and Jordan had me
Me up
Pronouncing things weird all over
Me and Jordan had meant
To record an intro
Like this
What I'm doing here but we forgot
Anyway
I just thought it would be weird if he episode
Started and then just immediately jumped into an interview
Maybe I'm wrong I don't know maybe this is unnecessary
Anyway before I get to up in my head I'll just throw it
Do the interview enjoy
And we will be talking to you soon
Well folks
I figure
There's a lot of news there's a billion stories to cover
Close to a billion story and whenever we need some legal analysis on cases involve
One Alex Emerick Jones
There's a there's one
And symbol
Go to the rooftop of my apartment here in Chicago and I
I put a gummy worm Shadow on a cloud and then Bill calls mark
I like by the bark signal is a is a silhouette with the words underneath it
Who sent me these tests
I think that's
It's a Matlock shaped symbols
Or bones being that we have extended
Sears
Boys are y'all doing welcome back I raise my glasses Jordan brought champagne over this evening
And so welcome thanks for joining us
Absolutely absolutely couldn't be in better spirits today
I think a lot of the audience is the where
Obviously that
The kinetic
Came in on when
Wednesday
As a as a flood
Work it will require 40 days and 40 nights to weather the storm is the level of flood we're dealing
And I think some people probably have some questions about you know Dynamics about a weird Circle
Cannoli
There's still so much
Get answered here
It's really a nice time to celebrate
Thing I wanted to ask you first
Start with that
You were in the courtroom for a while
Correct
What was what was it like
Sitting in the courtroom as a spectator is opposed to a gladiator you know.
Into that courtroom right
And nobody knows what happened
Echo when I walk in
You're like a Ray Lewis
Open 2004 like
MMA
I had
Over the years gotten the chance to reach out and talk to you some of the other
Plaintiff simulacra
But this was the first time that
Like in Aruba
And got to meet them and
You know it's it's
Weird because sometimes people that you don't think about it too much
That is very technical sense
These cases are bars in Connecticut in in Texas
Are are in competition
Like that that would normally be the case
Food that has
Since almost
The outside
Not good how we treat
Yeah
These parents were so gracious to me and so they were expressing their admiration and dinner thanks for what we did
And I don't even represent
But we've kind of looking at it that way because
I think we are
As Cooperative as to Plaintiff lawyers across the
And we have
I'll teach other along this way
To make sure that these
People are not
On fast ones in either direction
And so
TriHealth whatever way I could
And it was it was a great experience
Be there
NCB
I don't know there was something about that
You have that amount of gravity
It was quite an
But you know why
Midway through the trial and I had to leave and come home cuz I actually have
Come home for a couple days then go try another case.
Kansas City
Nobody really knew what was going to
And nobody really
Will be there was even just this simple dangling thread of like is Alex
It's going to come back
Totally
Look I'll be honest
Once I was
I kind of knew where we were going to stop
Degree
Getting a value these cases
And so I was almost concerned after my case
If people were going to look at it and go
All right well yeah but that's a
Just a total
You got one story of
What happened to it with meals
Can you get one result that's just
And what's so rewarding about this text trial
That's not a fluke
Is a fluke about it
Yeah
You can almost look at it
Set the volume sets understands how the case is going to go
And then
Christina's team
And
There's there was a lot of things that were going
Right to start this truck
Through a lot of really good thing
So that's a good start
Trial
Having already won
Defendants who got defaulted or came in there
Damage hearing
And it still
Red stripe
Yeah yeah exactly
Intensity of getting a dollar you know well like when Trump sued the NFL and they gave him a collar you know
Nearby do that was
Going to be what was happening because
I mean
Is a jury once
Information
It is
They're going to f***
That's just how it's going to be
And then the question is
These things going well for them
The first trial of Jones again
Clearly broken
Ready
That trial with the
Defense lawyer who's going to put on a fairly standard defense
You wouldn't even pretended that he had remorse
Big stride
Play The Strip
And they got bigger Rick
Just Brakes
The next draw any acts like a goddamn Madness
Basically like
You got it like that on some level that you didn't work let's try
I didn't miners the wrong word I really didn't get an apology from all of the people who had
Had no idea this was going to be coming but what are you going to do you know
Absolute Madness
You got normatec
Wow did I
I never would have thought that I would see the lawyer
Norma's literally asleep at one point in the trial
You like tweeting during the trial about other stuff
Being openly
It was
I love him know what's going on
I tell you what I saw that closing statement of his yeah
What is
Like what is
I know I know this is not going to be a popular statement but maybe
He's grieving families are liars
A really good question
Loitering you can do
That lawyers prayer
Sounded fake as s*** to me they like no lawyers ever done that
Nobody
Nobody's ever said that why did he say it was like the old-fashioned lawyers Brer creative guys
Prices on material there's nothing nothing to s*** on their Jordans
Well I will share with you the old Comics prayer
That's our favorite one to say before every
Dear Lord made the last be plentiful
The alcohol intake
Works in a criminal trial when you have a lawyer
Who is
Deeply and fundamentally unlock
Likable like Norman
But here's the thing that I don't think
People are putting enough
Attentional
Is that
Well Christmas
Really strong case in really favorable
Condition
Something that is so insanely.
Difficult
When you just
Right you get the number up
Get up there 250
Understands that
Once you start having cysts
You have to
To get the numbers up so high that you're jury's gonna get sticker shock
Write a natural worried well below.
To be able to defer
To be able
Onboard
Whiskey ideas
I'm giving this kind of award
Is literally the hardest thing a plaintiff lawyer can ever
I can leave it
I think
I think in terms of that that's
That's the number of plaintiff's like as opposed to with your case
With kneeling Scarlett it it's
You know it's one story
It may be a complicated story to tell but
Somebody plaintiff's being able to
You no respect
Fully and accurately convey all of their different experiences
Say something that I thought was also well handled
It seems like a gigantic
You know you're going to if you do it right like you did
You get critical mass up
There was a huge danger they're losing the jury in the details all of them
Different people
And having them get exhausted to the process
He was able to create new angles in new ways
Tell the story yes it wasn't
Newberry right off to head a great
Friendliness with the way that he questioned
The plaintiffs as well there was a
Time certainly got
Objections from Norm
But there was kind of a friendliness
I am
There contrast
Text to mehdi kind of having more of a like
Straightforward
Report Costco for more like
Okay you can ask that question I know we all just want them to tell the story and you're trying to ask
Just tell your story
Like that
Yes you're the person
Such a big fan of hers
Is Eleanor Sterling's work
Arguing legal propositions in that courtroom
Was
Rarely seen a lawyer
Who is Stella
Judgment
And there were so many big rules
And she did such an amazing
You never know like that
I bet she I bet she has to feel amazing just because there are so few times I think we're
Are you can really get into like
The nitty-gritty of this isn't Pointe 14
Steve
And feel like the righteous Crusader of
F****** you do like Sono
Motherfuker you're like you don't get to do that
Their legal team had
3 very
Distinctive indifferent
Personality
Right.
4 bus route
Bearded weirdo
Different shades
Same color
Look at you like f****** Wyatt Earp from Tombstone shut the fuk up
Episode
And it's
Arts of Chris
Has
Is able to bring a level of moral righteousness to the courtroom
Gardening bus
Genuine person
Would be over the top
Broke
Chris Stolle
Genuine
That he was able to keep this like
Very strong sense of moral Authority
That they needed to have an emotional angle to a needed to have a humanistic
Relating
Injustice
Elemental
Yeezy
Symptoms of camaraderie
Then you can pull that off
And then you have I don't know who's basically a strategy
At least use a a battlefield General
And to know how to use the rules
Proponent where she wants
Spirit animal
Together
Just knock knock
I just
Directions super excited to work
No because
Is there some
David
Great workouts
Flotsam.
And they did it and then so
They're out
Celebrating the world right now get the accolades and they deserve every bit of it
Wild
Totally
I guess that leaves us in a position where you know we have this almost 1 billion dollar
Against alexson Infowars
He has put his company into bankruptcy
Pepsi or Lee Street systems isn't bankrupt
Anderson
Sort of chaos going on with that is
Is well with the lawyers
Turning on each other a little bit
But where
Do where do
Obviously
It's almost entirely unpredictable
But where do you get it
Talking about when we talk about it
Appeals what are the options
There was a
It was a slip
Amount of me talking in the courthouse right after all
And I made some predictions
The bone picking
Yeah.
Follows me like a ghost
Is there was a thought that book
Monster
Big like they are
That this would end up with
Resolution through bankruptcy court cuz Jones once this over he's not going to chase
On this kind of stuff
It wouldn't make sense
He's going to have four trials
Oil overturns just ridiculous so and I figured that
He would do it
We wouldn't be looking at that
In other words we would be looking at
But now when you've got a billion-dollar gesture
You've got the
Screw it in like he said the other day on the show
Yeah
You think I care about that
I think you're vastly overestimated how difficult
Big deal
What cause knee problems on
Exactly enough to do a lot of work to do that
An infamy
You was great
The here's the real kicker of it right here's the
The real kicker
Let's say
Reverses and orders a new trial to go forward
Do you have anything that would make me happier than
Very few things last time there was a billion dollars on Connecticut
How about you guys been with a 750 million and appealed it surprise
Yeah
It wouldn't just be like this judgment is gone it would be ordering a new trial
Alex's Behavior
You.
Probably assumed wouldn't be any different
Probably end up getting himself a Fulton again
Like we reverse the clock back
June 2022
New trial date and try again
Lycon do the
Default could that be
Nicole thing that I guess she
Feasible
The judges make
To be essentially is just
What about the damage
Just about to end and fundamental errors
Bayou City
Anything happens there
It's interesting
Objections to this would be off of like jury instruction
And strangely enough
Raynaud's
Ironic about the idea of an appeal is that after all these four trials are
Basically
We're going to find out that once you have the ability to choose that Jerry
A like
You can weed out certain people
Any reasonable person
Will agree
Alex
Saudi idea of that you can take it
2 quart
Bill
Kinder infuriates me whenever it's like
It doesn't matter where you are or who you choose as long as you're getting rid of info Warriors this motherfukers go
I need a jury of my peers and my peers are crazy
So
I noticed
But we had some really strong well-informed errors on the jury who I think
In the next round
Early next year or something like that
Equals all going to know
About this billion-dollar
Not the right
Exactly
Peninsula Libras people who do know about it I probably going to get you
InTouch
What's been going on
In what I've learned through this process is
That is
Perhaps mourad
Advantageous
Are you yeah it became so clear to me when we had the guys from the dollop on
And like I was playing stuff that Jordyn Woods
Just be like oh
Yeah okay I don't like taking care of her freaking out
Play kind of
Junior varsity Alex content to me
How is this one show
It is kind of a situation where
This has you know we were all worried
As you said earlier Dan and I were both worried about the judgment and all of this stuff
And I think that really might be because we are so close to it
But if we had could step back
You know like
If you can go back and listen to episode 1
F*****-up about this s*** you know like
And I saw none of it and Alex said it's time to pray all three lost our mind
That is nothing
You know what
Yeah
Factor that in nearly as much
Opposite of naivety
You're something else. It's still kind of naive that's correct
You know yeah
What will
Going
There will need to be
So on the 20th
Next week
Robin hearing and hustling for enter the Judgment there
We're going to try to make a plate
Damage there
I know for
Facts going to be
Much easier playing possum
It's just that sets up and
But much easier
As well
Get that inter Thursday
Sanctions
Or
Andino's
Northern Tool judge request
So we done that
Nick about Norm sanction
I wish never we are
We're doing also stations motion for the improper removal in bankruptcy back in April
But that caused us
So we're going to see call that and brexit going
Instead of going after Jones and the company
We're going after the lawyers you did these things
Oldies things off
Are we are we talking about a media star here
We have some news on him coming up getting all just don't know if I spend
Keep your eyes peeled the story of Robert Barnes
For what he did during trial
It was another one of their lawyers to demerit album who was involved with the represent a
Earlier
And made certain representations but Infowars LLC private bankruptcy
Will be happening
We having a similar thing happened
I know
Be bigger right
I think when you have a billion-dollar
Billionaire
I don't think you
I don't know compensatory is a billion dollars I feel like they are going to wind up going ham on
Damages tickets very possible
Also like the unfair Trade Practices part wasn't even right
Magnet sort of hanging in the back
It isn't it was a really nice
They told other hat on that one and if they can
Sale at through
Wow what a great move
Right I mean it's I don't think anybody's ever thought about doing it
The first one
And it was I mean
I don't know for certain
But
Spell Eleanor
On all of that
Strategy right there
And
If they
You can't ever result
This will be a millstone around the neck forever
Westchase
Right. Maybe where we're going
So they're going to do the same thing that got to get there
Linda Lavin hearing for entry of judgment
Once that happens before there's about 30 days to file notice of appeal within the various state courts
And if they want to do that
Did Logan the PO by Prince August 8th
To the Texas Court of Appeals
And then that Court will rule on everything
That would probably take a 9-month something like that
And then there will be no probably a fuel after that we'll do it what they call away
Petition for review
Text Supreme Court
That's not a mandatory
Decide whether they want to hear it
We're not in the past
Define to hear the earlier if you're so I don't
I don't know
But that would probably
And then in the petition to the US
Weekly liked over Jack.
But we are probably looking at a year-and-a-half to Verso
Before
Brass tacks
You're saying
You're saying we're looking at two years before people legit go to his house and start
Digging up
F****** gold yeah yeah yeah
Write the problem there is that okay
Because at the same time
Fraudulent transfer suit
Canyon against
Then we get to go after the money that isn't
Technically in Alex Jones
But that has been transferred over into other entities are been given Dollar Insider
Exact
Woodchips everybody's radar on this issue PR
Play setup
And there's a truck out there
EJ truck
Just got 30 right now so
Anything else
Eddie Money
I don't know
It's never what this
It's not it's worth
That's not why they're
The idea of the next
Fine whatever
But isn't that isn't that ultimately the question that so many people are having right now and it's the one that I'm hearing
From a lot of people in regards to our show
Specifically obviously is like
Is Alex going to be on the air for another two years until people start digging up
Is Goldie you know what I mean like a problem with this
With this whole situation one I want to say that
The law is great and it makes perfect sense
To who
It is it is a thing where it's like
This judgment is so immediate after so much
Bulshit
You know and then
People are going to want this to then be an immediate result
Right right
Exactly they want people to be like Alex has to get in a plane tonight and had to vent
Venezuela to survive a Flight Risk
Reno
Look
Immediate consequences are immediate effects
But I think our
Even if you
You could take all of us
And you could
Essentially shut down Imports
That's not going to stop him from being a meal like
You'll be on the internet
Videos of do whatever
You're not going to get rid of that wavy the way you really
Have to do is to be able to
Marginalizing neuter
His influence on American
And that that really is
Realized
Madness starts
The suit itself
You got to remember it's tickets bobbin in a
Lafferty Sioux Falls
Couple months later
Jones basically mind
Stop threatening to kill Robert Mueller
Start posting
To get the
Jack Johnson
Races
Transphobic stuff during that summer
The combination of
Vegetable soup
Cosby
Jack Johnson
Which I still think was
Done in the most ridiculous
An arbitrary way.
Mistakes all through it but like it got.
First biggest
The soup
I really do think
Loufest 2019
A 2018
Basically
And he was
Effectively
Find the suit itself
In the deplatforming reduces Decor size of his audience
And then no
Default
All of it
After this constant drumbeat of how he's not taking it seriously and then the verdicts
He's been heavily marginalized
And in a way that
I'm not even sure the collecting the money makes
That much more of a
I think it'll reduce the size
Operation
Probably be the same
I think you have
Number of impact
I think that the people who are already in and deeply end with Infowars it's not going to marginalize him with
But you never be able to
To do that.
They're beat there's a vaster awareness of
Who he is among
Normies perhaps
And that in a wave it's like
Lost a billion dollars over Sandy Hook
I think that could be helpful in some ways
Yeah things of like
Credit
Impact
The Blues in the case like these
But that's something that will will be a problem for him
And in order to maintain whatever
Relevancy has
And abilities
To get audience
He has to have his own site like
Banned. Video
It is intensely
Expensive for him
Bandwidth cost
And the only way to keep getting
People
To go to the site
Is the offer
A platform for weirdos like David Icke
And
Some of these other folks like that guy who dresses up like Uncle Sam and yells at people on the street
Like he has that stuff
That's costing him an arm and a leg
And eventually he's not going
Going to be able to
Afford
To run this site
And other people are going
To Pony up the
The money for that
And
You know your left in a position where
Is that goes away
He has Infowars
I mean I think
I think what we are all under estimating the streaming site
I didn't know we're all estimating as far as you know when you say like
He won't lose his Reacher or he can still do a show on YouTube or whatever
I don't know on YouTube
You know he can do a show and put it
It's somewhere
I think we're under estimating the amount
Not today
That he gets from having a professor
National Studio
Yes like if he no longer has a professional studio and he's going out of his f****** room
And you look at his video and you see the same thing that you do
With ner ruled absolutely
I don't think he has the ability to go beyond that because he doesn't have any Talent
Yeah you know he doesn't he doesn't
Create anything
What was cool for him to be broadcasting out of like his spare bedroom when he was
Coming up yeah it's super cool to have those bonafide
To be like the falling action of like you had this CNM level
Sat with elaborate like
Visuals behind you and
A skull on your desk
Ask for some reason
And then your
You know back
Do recording in a in a bedroom
Yeah
Not the same be surprising to like really look at whether or not
That moment when it becomes sad
To be a fan of Alex Jones really has a has a like an effect
You know he's fallen so far and you're still a fan of Alex Jones
Aren't you at some point maybe like this is not fun
That's my point hasn't already come
It's always been my son's I don't know.
It's always been my sense that among his viewership
The people who are actually buying the supplements is a very
Very very small component
It is
Or spending a s*** ton of money
Like any televangelist yeah
And I don't think anyone noticed that his Revenue has never been terribly.
Ended on his total spread like
Escapes from crazy world
I got doesn't
And so I think
Look
The the important effects
I want to just I want to put a button in this really quick
It does seem like when like the FBI says no one died at Sandy Hook breached into
What you might call Mainstream like
Get spread wider
That did have an effect on
Spreading his sales
Daddy
But when he's like on
Piers Morgan
Or you goes on Rogan that doesn't necessarily Spike sale
Snow exactly
And I do think the difference between
It is broke through
Into a grater
Community
Pretty pretty damn crazy
And then do I do think that like you look at the 2017
. right after Trump's victory
There were a lot of sorta
Standard NASCAR dad major conservatives who suddenly discovered Alex Jones during that period and make it was
Dangerous thing
He doesn't have
More dangerous
2020 election goes
If the suit never happened Alex as old
Platform
Turned on Trump by then though
We have a different election maybe we have more people of January 6th
That could be the bigger problem hundred percent
We could have a dictatorship
And I mean it was frustrating to me like going to the covid-19 like
You can't stop
You never real
Effectively stop him the only way you can completely
I hope this is done that
But I think
There's this bigger effect and I
I need this is real legit is that
There is now been a signal sent out
Media of all stripes
That if you start
Bringing private
Blame
Innocent
People into your conspiracy lies
And start telling false facts about the M intentional wrecks
Big Damn price tags
The effect on
Other
We're edging close to I might do some things like our shows
This is
Considerable
Message
Is that like your kid
Conspiracy games are all fun and
Litany of things that Alex's
I'm full of s*** about that he's never been sued about it never will be suitable
It's all fun and games
But there is a point at which
You need to be careful
Don't do these things
I bet
Maybe that's a lucky message for some of those people, you know a reasonable Society
Could
Take all of the things that Alex Jones
Did
In regards to this case in regards to these people
And be like okay
Well we know yelling fire in a crowded theater is not free speech
So if you do
Exactly this list of
Things
Then you go to jail
Roar your show is gone or something like that
Because it is like any reasonable jury would come to the conclusion that you owe a billion dollars if you do that
So why not skip the five years of
Goddamn litigation and just go you did.
Exact list of things that every reasonable person thinks cost a billion dollars to so guess what you started
Take a breath
A normal media descendants
These cases early any
This is how it was always going to end and and they saw the Sturtevant
That wasn't the case
All people right after I called you I wish you the best a boy that's can be a hard uphill climb
You know I don't get you
And it took a long
Process
Strategically
You did a very good job that is a good point
People underestimate how hard the guys
All around all around
So he dug his own grave and I'm like
People look I got a shovel
It was a big shop
Alex did play a part in taking that
Backgrounds
You said before even I believe I'm on the show that like there is a point or maybe was Bill
That like
This could have been resolved so easily
It in earlier times if
If Alex
He's done it with other cases before like
With Hamdi ulukaya you know the Chobani
He said he was going
Go to fight that or die
And then he settled
Like I'm sorry about it
It's so funny that you did that
It's Waltz me that it's just because of the Tudors
It's right because of where to Bonnie is
Comet Ping Pong is
Those are both of those venues
If you make an apology
Before the shoot and retract
Your damages
It wouldn't have
Been worth it
The weirdest part about Alex
Does Comet Ping Pong apology was
Spike the 15 minutes he did about how good the p
Pizza was and he really didn't try the
That's how you apologize
I'm seen in the past day or two like
These
I guess right-wing influencers who are trying to test the waters about how much they can
NAIC
Charlie Kirk
Who say the same Whitney b******* about life
This is a Alex apologize
Show me
Show me the clip show me where Jones said
I'm sorry for the things that I've done
Apologize for when he said it was fake last week
Exactly right like that
Oh he only did it a couple of times
Motherfukers
40 hours
In evidence in our trial
The window now from exhibit Tulare
100 more episodes
Between 2013 and 2018 that they never produce to us
She's a
He only did this occur
Couples
Just new reality
Try to defend the Alex Jones
Bike
Remind
Yeah like
Glenn Greenwald hasn't said a word I'll tell you what
That dude off for a while now.
F****** forever and I know man it's annoying you know what I think it is the case with those people who are defend
Kim
Meet the baby a guy going down
But a guy who's going down can be profitable for them and Subway
Makes me think of Toys R Us going bankrupt a lot of people made a lot of money you know that kind of
The way that Alex makes a hero at a
Colonel Travis in the Alamo you know there is kind of electromagnet
What's the reality of Colonel tribe
They want this in there
And I think they're trying to engage in the myth
As Alex
Is
You know
Being surrounded by Santa Ana
Why don't we
Vinnie Johnson or Charlie Kirk or one of those
I don't actually
Defensive Alex I think they're really in tune with
Which water
The people that grifter
And so
There is a small contingent
They know they can get engaged
Probably feel like they would look weak
If they didn't
Exactly
Well this is what happens when you speak out Against the Machine minimum
The f*** are you talkin about place
There are so many people
Who are like enemy of the above like
I guess like modern establishment liberals or whatever
And if there really was like
Hillary
Maroon van to take them down
Know that that's not how that would work
Right
Marquess what you're not taking into account
You don't know that Robbie Parker was elected to be the shadow Secretary General of the UN
Power it's
Power this is people
Yeah that's what's so disgusted about it
Here's something that's so
Obviously Morley abs
Feminist ohura
Even if you just take what like
Think like a
Charlie Kirk what he probably wants to imagine Alex Jones
Which would his
It's still pretty
Never engage with
Actually jet
Which is so morally horrific
And the fact
Something that morally obscene has taken
This much effort
To be able to address and hold accountability for
Slippery slope
Against these people
Literally
The worst
Defamation in America
History
Yeah I know
Couldn't couldn't be stopped
The next time way better than a billion-dollar judgment if somebody just wrote a lot that was like okay
If you defame people multiple times and make a billion dollars off of it and then you get sued for it instead of trying to
You haven't
Default judgement and then if you don't like if you do hold fish it just it's over
Go away I think I better support the spirit of what you're discussing
I know I'm just saying that
Like writing that into a Logwood
Would be very complicated
The debate the floor debate on that would be intense like what if we just finally accepted a
Floor for defamation that's Criminal
You know just like this is
Here this is a crime I feel like
The problems that everyone is having as they want to talk about the billion-dollar judgment
And not like the reason that it's a billion dollars
He committed a real-life crime
I'll go you one better
And in what he did is under Texas Penal Code 2204
Is that if you intentionally
Commit emotional
Injury
To a
Person
That is a felon
Annie's parents
At the time that he committed these injuries were suffering from severe emotional disturbance
Hell yeah
That makes them disabled
Where illegal
If
But the thing that we're going to be talking about on the 20th
This month
Cause that conduct was for me
In all of the album
That's going to get us around the punitive damage
Oh that's great
No.
An Enzo here
Yeah it is definitely going to be our argument in court on the 20th
Very well could have been
So that's like
Even our criminal law recognizes the moral
And how hard it is to press
All the time
Is it like Jones
Hundred percent light on the stand
I think that's probably
True
That he
Why
Write intentionally.
Is a much tougher half of a cracked secretly with Joan
Will the judge in your case even made that point that's like you might
I think this is true
Right
There are certain things but see there's a big difference between some of those things out for saying that he thought were true that that the record shows or not
Brighten this so there for me to not eat
Said that way
Well isn't that
Ansari
When you said I mean look let's go back to
Perry Mason
Right when he said I searched my phone I pulled it down I put in Sandy Hook
And then boom is found out that that's not true
It's very difficult to arrive at a conclusion that that wasn't an intentional attempt
And I think
I hope
Anyway to Travis County prosecutor
Looking at that foot
Sting is perjury in
Imuran
You never see
I just never thought
Okay what if
What if we held a trial
All right now
And now
Before you say no
There a lot of alleys in Chicago so we hold a trial
And me and Dad will Danza judge
Obviously
Right and I'm going to be the defendant for Alex Jones
Edgar the defense lawyer for Alex Jones
Be great and then we repeat the s*** out of him I feel like this
Perfect sense as a
Court system
Is this bad
Obviously bankruptcy
Wait what they're going to fund
Chicago alley
Yeah I don't know it's a courtroom he would be legally assault
Something really
There is this
Through-line among so many people of their abs
Disgust for Jones
Horrible
You put them in a room without showing the loan Alex Jones not walking out of that room
Something to me
Very
I need another Italian
Republic
The idea that we took
This case
And pursued it like
Total white hat
And get it every by the book
4/4 years and did it correctly and brought him Financial ruin
And ended
That to me is so much better than somebody who doesn't like Alex Jones Bieber
Yeah
I think people would think that of someone like me or Jordan
Well maybe not Jordan but like
Was there in the deposition and
I left
Without beating him up
I just needed a margarita
That was that was
Two patients and yeah
The process that you guys follow
Ultimately I think that
Sentiment really come
Thumbs down to like
Everyone wishes
That they could pursue it and and
Beat him in the way that you did
In the way that the lawyers have done in the way that the
The families of done
To go out there
Text to Stacy
All of this s*** and then to win
That's really cool
But it took a long f******
Can time and what if we
People think you know
Like that's just how your brain works is like it's been a long time
Are you coming on the way while back you don't like that's kind of the Felix well-respected
Way more is the way that you do
Waiting sympathize
With your feelings of outrage and frustration all of that
Australian it for all these years
Frustration ourselves
Let me see if I can strike a balance
Alex has a lot of money
Yeah
There was a period of time where he was offering to do a celebrity boxing match with Tom Barn
Maybe
We get Jordan
Any celebrity boxing match with Alex
Did the Chicago back alley in the middle solutely no cameras let's just kill myself
If you can get
Ultimate default
We knew we knew that was sort of
I mean stop
There are
Right and we took we just put me on
One family story
And
It was really nice because you get all these things that Not only was it
ReSound referendum on him
Embarrassed
I mean not
Walking stick
Panicking
It was off
Larynx come on man
Completely disappeared the moment he knew he was in real
Anxiety
Were you there
Good to have all of that go down to have these Nashville moments of embarrassment
Embarrasses attorney was really
He did make salt
Late night shows
Feeling from it
But you know that it's just
You're just opening the door on the stove
Define
I just don't like so much
Equal
That sets
Literally a record-setting verdict
Great Lake
Is that
Vinnie Paz
Their damages drug damage
Anybody involved
Yeah
That that is really is
That last one is looking at there is
Really really threatened
Even even with Marcel
Didn't have like
Earphone effect
Is still really recover
Very possibly facing
Yeah
The factors
What's after mine
And it over the course of these four years
Even with the
Procedure
McKay's
We basically stayed neck-and-neck
Come down to even after all the pills aren't trials or like a month apart
Stop this one
You punch like the story being told it's amazing
Better
It really is
You're not going to bring you back to another point I think it's super important
That people need to realize and that needs to get said more
Bike
People like Alex Jones going to put on a First Amendment defense but
But he chose not to participate in there for.
Defaulted so haha I didn't get to do that
Is that
In the beginning of the case
She was allowed to bring an anti-slapp motion
What was that for
He had appeals up to the Texas court of appeals and UPS the Texas Supreme Court
Google read that like one of them is really spelled all out really nice
Wagner versus Jones opinion from
All of the first things that you had every chance to do that do that
It wasn't until he came back from that
And still over years for just didn't participate
That.
So he got to try to vindicate his first amendment rights in its tail
This has nothing to do with
False facts about
Identifiable people
The first apartment stuff actually failed
And that beat
Because that
Pageantry wasn't available to him
He decided not to engage
Knowing he would lose
And that's the Dafoe
I think more less I really believe looking back on it there was this hubris
What's the worst
Squaw Creek
And and they thought
Advantage of
But you didn't
Do that
And the fact these first amendment issues were tested and I had to breach my ass off
That's what got us
The place that we are
He was denied
Fundamental constitutional rights
Anything like that
Well I have an expert
Named
Viva Frei
Why who tells me
He's an associate of a very famous mediastar
You tells me that that's
Collect the First Amendment rights were violated
You know Daddy's that is one of the questions that I have I have been fascinated by throughout those trial
Is
You know the
Great
Create links that have gone to avoid letting him turn it into a political thing or letting him
Really
Spew his b*******
Unencumbered
You know
Like
All things considered the question I have really for like
Humanity
Is if Alex was allowed to do that
Acat grabbing one juror you know like is that what humans have is it you have to with
Cold
Some b******* in order to have a reasonable response
Or is it just going to overtake at least one person
You know
I think was his and Norms concept of the whole thing is
We need to get one person
Pills
Play talk about the Connecticut Supreme Court like they were like
We were just one judge away from
You don't think if we could have gotten that one other person overall flip this
So close to right
We're not right but goddamn if we lied better we beat
Closer
Everything out in that one juror
Then this all would like that with the amount of time that Norm spent like
Here's the question that I have for you is
Norm and Edna
Spent so much time trying to like
Worm around
You know all of those restrictions
Directions for that
How many times would you have said objection
When it wasn't said I'm not telling you to compare your
Performance overall
When you were watching it were you screaming objection
And then I gave up
What is he up to
Enormous
Weasel
A wild-card I won't use any Jordans
A word amazing
No sir
We when he came down to try to apply to
Try our case
R&R position
Threat
Potential
The courtroom
That's going to stab at his
Ponytail
But but we
And so we did get them
Well card whatever and then he would have known
Hydrocodone
Boy do you have to
I'll have to be second-guessing.
No question about it
Holy cow
Really
I mean what's that
Orman's cheese at must have felt so good going into the office at that neck
How about this I'm walking down
How about that I kept it
Down
Billion dollars
Pretty great lawyer aren't you
Only accidentally sent a bunch of texts
Cancel I didn't do that
Is the Synergy off these cases
I mean
That was some some finesse
Required
Puerto Rico
Which am I only had four
Let me look before I put those text messages in front of Jones
I because I was
Good look at these documents
We're hours
Be able to get that stuff
Altogether so then
Chris has a month with the sex message
And he
Saturday
Some of that stuff
Roodle
Until you have these synergies between the case they had the
You'll notice
That in my case in mine
Replay.
And half the depositions that we played were from Lac
It's interesting Chris Madden
Made an appearance in my trial so did doted math
Synergy
You know I called him Chris and I was like
Manos neistat
Have a 6-person drouthy down there you know because I had you in mind as well down there
It was it's nice that that that
Ben 10
Chase
You just don't know how it would have turned out
But when you have
Or in a synergize and they're all on the same page
You kind of know how they're all going to turn
Yeah
It really was that way
Yeah that's that's we were talking about when we first got started or talk about how often times
James cases will be sorted in competition with each other
Yeah I feel like who's going to take precedence
Thanks for the
The judgments you know
And the idea of taking credit like I'm not
Seeing MattyB like hey I'm the greatest lawyer for getting a billion Denmark
You guys were really kind of s*** you haven't been on SoundCloud
Time release
Disstrack on the architect
DisplayPort
He is really really kind of amazing because it was like you had
To Independence
Teams coming up with interesting ideas
Communicating with each other and then going back and coming up with more in
Interesting ideas really fascinating to watch the interplay between
I think part of Veep
That would be because the families while not one
Mike indistinguishable Bob
Anything are all
Dealing with the same thing
Right
Cannot be a bond that's
Unbroken
Early in the case
And you don't particularly early in the case and I didn't know each other like we do now
NM Krishna
Very very
Evil
Yeah
Really strong pain
And
Early in the
Nothing Network
Wired Trista say
Under his
Protective order with the court
The documents that
The court actually asked for provision in the protective order
To allow
2md share those documents with me if you got stuff
In an interview
Cases where they weren't on the same page that wouldn't
Right and it was
It was it was always
Felt like
This was a boat
That we are sailing together
Depending on which case something is happening then
Somebody's going to be at the wheel of this
Just think it was absolutely critical to us
Withholding some information that he's defrauding
I think it was that
ABC surprises
You never will guess what I just found out
Yeah it was good
In the movie I'm writing about this first off
You and one
Nicole Kidman is going to play Chris
Dena Maddie alright
You are going to but actually you can choose but you guys are going to fall in love at the end of this I'm sorry
This is like I
This is a Sleepless in Texas
You do have the gender swap anybody where are you there brother
EBird
Ben Shapiro's going to be furious
It's for the it's worth a big crab
For you.
We should probably wrap this up for too long but
Yeah. So could we but we have other business
Need to attend to and the
Think I want to I want to touch back on is you said
The 20th
Is the next
For y'all
And then also the Posner case that's
Do we have time frame on that
I mean it's going to
Come down to whether we're going to actually have to move the bankruptcy court to
Done to the bankruptcy court
Get free speech out of there
Weather
So you know what screw it will sever it out
Well system seems like it has enough hanging around its neck at this point
You like that company might
You know what I mean
Yeah
You had success in on suing those other end
Free speech in bankruptcy
Do it
I'm hoping you know I was hoping to have that Friday December for the anniversary
I wanted it to be
Be over
Your dad
Let's do that but it's looking like early next year
I'm hoping for
Oh my God
And we'll get them done
And then hopefully
Before the end of the spring
The whole trial Saga of this is over
Early next year
Are we invited do we get to come
Already kicking ass out this time
Your last trial performance
Scott 105
In July
Jordan kidnapped
Wellmark thank you so much for joining us it was really nice to be able to chat
Tangles
But yeah
We look forward to say is that
During the course of the trial itself and over the
The weeks following it
I received so much from your body
DD most hearts
Gifts and trinkets
Some of those do magic
Do wood carving a giant wood board
It says
Fa4
So f****** cool
When are you listed as an Egypt
Menchie's
Really well with my Adidas ologist
She did a what she calls an Egyptian
Victory Steel
Which is like in Hawaii
Graphics
You sent me a
Picture of it I think
Are at the top
As like as like
Osiris God
Place for us
Soubise
Egyptian gods of me and Bill
Gummy worm
Egyptian poem about
Am I home by God
Did and I became popular on your subreddit
Is like a tiger
Beach style magazine cover up Define
Nnn
We blew that up to
2 poster size
Do the laundry
So someone
Bouquet of flowers delivered to me
At the courthouse
Bring you flowers I people
Into the courthouse the Giants
Cookies
They were just like
We'd love and support you from
You know and it jumps
The community that y'all have
Oosterdam what it is
It means a lot to me and I ate or some of the people have been saying things like
What is knowledge
Alex Jones has gone and I remind them one Alex Jones
Until he six feet under like if he Keels over
M2
Big thing coming up where I'm seeing
I don't know
More
Lower-level Alex Jones's
More things
And
No matter what we do to this guy do not leave them alone y'all been beating them
Batman Begins and we finally pick up the Joker car and it's like we're off to the next
We've defeated one anime.
Is never troubled me because it's not really relevant
Like if he's gone
And I don't
Get donations or whatever I don't give a
Care
I will find a less interesting person to talk about
The only thing that troubles me a little bit is that like
This
This notion of like
Lower-level Alex's
We now are not
A podcast just started weird tonight
Yeah that to me is something we will have to
To deal with but I'm not saying that's impossible
But
I love our audiences well we are so lucky to have
Such
Bizarrely positive people about beautiful wonderful amazing people
Yeah
I love so hard
I also am going to blow up a copy of that Egyptian hieroglyphics
Cuz that's
So cool
Wellmark
All the best
As as they say
I wish you not
Nothing but two successes and further in future successes and may your sword ever be Sharp
In regards to Alice
Alex Jones
And I mean I guess all your other case
Is there whatever
Barbecue sauce motherfuker
Start of relationship
Tenuous
We'll talk.
As you see that's the Bellagio behind me so I'm going to go
Stables and see if my luck
Keeps up cuz it seems to be doing pretty well right now. All right
Roll them bones
Bobby Barnes is former
Client
Alex
In color
I love your work