Important
I have great respect for knowledge B I'm sick of them
Need
Acknowledge
Exit
Call Bruce lean.
A little bit about
Remember to do an intro
Hi
Your intro
When you're by yourself
Have a tendency to flounder
A little heavy
Start to go a little bit off the rails it's
Kind of Wylie Coyote
You don't know when you run off the
You keep going
It's kind of amazing
Existential question in the middle of why am I doing
There is that
Anyway I'm you fall you hold up a sign that says
So I'm glad that we are remembered
To do that
What about you
They seem trivial but
It is the park
I can spot that I got
Today there is so on the street
Alright
Spot
That is free
There's no there's no parking
M
It is in between
Don't talk to me man can't you can't
Park in those places
But there's one
Perfect spot
Completely free
Right
Always felt
But then every now and again
This is the second
Time in like 3 years I've gotten this spot
Brighten your day man free parking
Fantastic more work to do cuz I'm going to have to
To bleep a couple things
Specific enough to go locate me with us on time I'm still uncomfortable with landmarks
As far as parking goes that could be anywhere in the city
It's a it's a real Menace
People have a real tough time with
Glad to I'm glad you landed
It's a little bit like standing in the four corners you know where you're like oh I'm in any state that I want to be right now or you
Like this is the freest Park
Working at the entire block uptown
That was the worst
Cuz I
Text my old place
I lived on Ainsley
An extra
Is so
Thin
And
There's people Park parking
Both sides of the street
I got to do there's never a
It was just
So awful
Anytime anybody
He came over
There was just like
Think they would learn
They're like oh I have to park
A ways away or drive around in a loop
For half an hour
To find someone leaving now
Anybody living near Belmont
Lakeshore is like
But you might as well Park on Addis
This is my man funny story that was around where I lived before
But yeah
Yeah a lot of people
Who who
Come over with
Do you learn
Text f****** red light
Jessie's Girl
Yeah luckily for us you also live in uptown when I was in uptown
It was a pretty convenient
Beautiful
We have view to enjoy
Continuing our Sneaky Snake weekend series
We have a little conversation with Williamson
Dropped
Good friend Elizabeth yeah
The trial has a
Concluded until we thought the invitation
Did you check in with the legal end
Mark
Why not talk to her friends like in the room
The entire time
Therefore the trial
The lawyers in the jury I think Elizabeth has been in there
The most
Professional capacity
Part of the trial
Yeah I mean
Sebastian Burns
Clean down there but he left after a week yet
Marketplaces
Vegas
So I hope you folks do enjoy the back Monday episode
Indeed we will
Enjoy
Until then
No no that's not how we do that's exactly
A boy
Hey folks we are back
Again
Guess who's back
Weekend feels empty without me
Ben Eminem song is
20 years old about how many things
20 years old now and it's a it's a real bummer
What you going to do anyway we are here having another little sneaky snake this weekend
And we are excited to be joined by from the from the New York Times
Sandy Hook
The battles
Yes
American Tragedy
You got the you got the
Also person who is named remembered
F***** up playlist
Elizabeth Williamson thank you so much for joining us
It's Erica Williams into you
Every time Dad
I'm used to not being
Anything that is okay
How are you
I am fine how are you guys
A little tired a little exhausted
I'm sure you're feeling fairly similarly so
I should I am actually but I'm um I'm happy even though you didn't ask me what's my brightest
But my bright spot is that I'm in Wisconsin at my brother's house
I think a little people's Brightspot involves what
Wisconsin
People who love cheese
Who's there
Sure
Fall colors
Milwaukee's in Wisconsin
That's true they have vents
Spotted Cow is that the name of the beer that Everyone likes
Yes we've got a refrigerator full of that my brother wanted case it in a bit
Yeah what was the best
Okay well that was it Alex Jones is going to lose nine hundred million dollars
Ding ding ding
Ropes you in
Spotted Cow
That's right
I'm thinking it's probably a little early for it but
Never know
It's it's
Creamy right I mean it has notify cream
Buy things
Afford a
I applied there we are we easing into day drinking that early
Beer
I'm so you I got to imagine are exhausted because
You've been
In Connecticut
For the trial
The entire time right
It was almost
5 weeks
Excessive
Of that
Yeah I did go home on the weekend
But
Yeah I
Was there for the whole thing and I wouldn't have been anywhere else
Because it was really
Quite something
Yeah
Yeah dude
I guess that's got to help
I mean being able to go home on the weekend
Probably keeps a little bit of Sanity but
That's being done in Texas
Next two weeks was
It felt like an endurance
Trial
And this
Trial in particular was
There's so many really moving
Difficult stories from these family members
I just
I feel like
I feel like I would
Collapse
Yeah
Yeah I mean that the families were the ones I really was thinking out because
Yeah once in awhile the group would be larger or smaller but I would say for the most
Start
The families attended just about every day of the trial and
You could really see the toll that it was taking on them I mean there were some family members that
You know every time their child's name for example was mentioned
In court date you know they were job she's very emotional about that and
And then hearing each other stories I mean they
Sometimes there were spouses
It's who you know
They didn't know that
What the other one had gone through you know they didn't they hadn't heard that exact story told him that exact way or
They hadn't heard you know
Another relative story
Themselves
So
You know you could really see
Your how much
What a revelation some of this was even to them
And and they were really there for each other I mean
LSAT together they all consult
Each other they all kind of
No
Spend time together and that was really something
Yeah that is a really really interesting thing that I
I hadn't thought of it I imagine most people had thought of because you know despite our our
I desire to kind of you everybody individually in this case obviously there is still that element of
They're all sitting there with a shared
Events in their lives so you just kind of don't realize that
Course they wouldn't have
Just sat down in a group and gone through each individual story to each other and if you have
Even if you're a
Married to somebody or maybe maybe you're divorced or whatever but I'll partner
Sometimes in the aftermath of would like a really terrible grief
Don't want to relive it
Yeah or even overburden the other balls elderly strong for them not
Maybe some of the
The intricacies of what you
Through
Really come up
A number of them spoke about
How they tried to Shield
The other parent for example
From what they were hearing or what they were seeing or the attacks that were you no coming at them
I've noticed
Yeah and then the other thing and I noticed this when I was writing my book
Memories are faulty particularly when people have gone through
Update,
They they
You can't remember
You know just about a decade so
Yeah I think
Them working on those Recollections and and then reclaim them
Yeah there were things that I think they met some people in the room had
No I really remembered although they may have noted at the
Do blockout
Abet
The brain will create that safety measures much
Protect
Your partner
Protect you
Yeah yeah I know it's really true
Until we came to the end of the trial last week
On Wednesday
I guess the verdict was read on Wednesday
The actual end of the the argument
Was
The week
The end of the week prior
What is the eggs that I was wondering
Was
How
Did things feel as time went on
And the jury was deliberating
Yes
Number of questions until every time they'd ask a
You try to game no
Does that mean you don't want to hear the testimony again of William Sherlock
Who's
Wife Mary Sherlock was the school psychologist
Died at Sandy Hook
And I
There was this
Nino
Thought in the room well
Okay let's think
His name appears
On the bottom of the jury
So does that mean they're nearing the end
Alright
You know figure it all out
And kind of game through it to SeaWorld and one question in particular
Jerry asked
Was
This thing where they said
What does it mean there's this kind of archaic language in the law
In these sorts of cases and it's
What does it
The instructions of the jury is
Try to put
The plaintiff
Back into the position when you know Levi these damages
Try to put them back into the position they were before the harm occurred
And you know that works
For things like
A broken contract
So you know you can say well here's the income you would have had
That person hadn't broken the illegally broken
The contract or
You know a personal injury you know you're paying for hospitalization and maybe special
Pear and things like that
But when it comes to defamation and
You know reputational damage and things like that
Reputational damage to someone who has lost
Someone in this way
How do you ever get them back
To where they
Stop it
That's what becomes almost a philosophical question
So
Yeah it's a
Oh it was just
You everyone was thinking
What happens when they're asking that question are they thinking
You know
No amount of money by the thinking
Any amount of money
Yeah how
How are they grappling with that
So
So that was kind of the thing he everybody was wondering you know what why do they know
What's going on inside that room where
Only the six-member panel is meeting
Yeah I remember the one question that
Stuck with me from them is the one where they asked why was the why was Lafferty the first
First name
Obviously it was just
That was the first name and then at all men
Rather than right-handed real name right
Everybody everybody went
Oh I know
They must be thinking that
If the name is first maybe there was more injury to them you know everybody had to have had that same thought right
Well Isles I had another take away from it and that was
Boy does this show they are not Googling anything
They're sticking to the judge's instructions if they're asking this
Yep not even the definition of at all
Yeah
No they were
Very thorough
They they were
Extremely diligent you got the
Presents that
You
As the judge was noting during the trial they were showing up early every day they were taking notes I mean they were
They were really into this
And and yeah they were
Very engaged and I noticed a lot
You know there would be
Different testimony and you know you they would be
You're wiping
Their tears away so kind of crying a little bit
Kind of when Jones testified you know a lot of frowns and a lot of shaking of
There has
Send
That you know was really into
Interesting because
After that Norm Patterson told me he thought Jones did well in his testimony and I was thinking
Define well
Yeah
Surprising you think you did well that's
Surprising
Well yeah I could have been 1.2 billion dollars you know I think 300
Unlike Norm you have to play by pro wrestling rules
Where you don't break kayfabe
But even back
Stabler still in character
You know there's still a
Like
Well out there
Yeah yeah
When he goes home and it's all it's just him and his wife
Takes the
Takes the wig off
He doesn't actually have a ponytail
Completely baldino he removes the makeup
I mean it's it's tough but he's the only one who gets to see the real him
Yeah yeah
He definitely has his
Text out
I mean when
I first started researching
Via what
What's happening here for the book
I went to see him at his offices in New Haven
And it's in his offices are in an old
Victorian house
And he has
In what had been the dining room just the walls are lined with books
And he said his wife has an antiquarian books
Store
And
He and he said
Wait wait you bunches the antiquarian bookstore on the last episode do we talk to you
It was Norm's wife
No
No make no mistake
Different is Aquarian bookstore
No hurry
Aquarian bookstore is someplace else
I think Barn somewhere
I just leave it there are two antiquarian book stores
Well it gets weirder
Because
He said
So he shows
These two very
Very interesting antique books
And look at this one and when you do and it was in one of them as I recall was like one of those flip books you know
Where you get a moving picture when you flip the pages
And II books that I was thinking
Write this is a first edition Robinson Crusoe not like
What book is from the 70s that was a first edition of
They were very very although they were
But
But so you know
3M it was kind of like
Let me dig out
Some really interesting finds for you
So
He comes up with
These three
And you know from his opening arguments
Norm price
Some self on how well-read he is
I think he sighted you know the Grateful off
The person
All the way down to shoshana zuboff
In his opening remarks
So and he he was talking about her book
As well when you do it not only during his opening remarks but you know back
In 2019 when I first visited with him
Anyway so you showed me these three books and I thought oh that's really interesting
And then couple months go by and
I read a profile of him in Connecticut magazine
As a reporter comes in and he says
Let me show you my library
Look at these three interesting
M3 bus
That's
Got to be a little bit this
Yeah you know he's got a
Vito he's he's sort of the
You know he always says
That's the same thing you know
Hey I'm in a kind of class timer
You know name your age now he's I think 67 but at the time it was
I'm a 64 year old with a ponytail I'm a 65 year old Little ponytail
A 67 year-old with a ponytail I'm an iconoclast I like
You know off
Clients
Yeah there's there's there's the analog of that in the comedy World which
The comic who has to
To come out wearing the same shirt
Because they have a
A joke about the shirts
Now they have to every show they do they have to do
The same shirt
Joke
Edit
Kelly's dad
So sad
The same book
Joke
So
I mean what
Free books
Start what
What three books
What does he think is going to impress everybody
When was Glenn Beck's the great reset
Five Spot
The great reset all three books titles great reset
Star Wars
Podcast where he interviews Alex Jones
No no absolutely not
Oh my
I know it's some I want to say it
Probably a year old
I knew the storm did some Broadcasting
But I
I heard him on Alex's show number of times and I've not found him
Tubi
Pelling fig
Yeah.
The upshot of it is
Wow Alex
Here I am Norm incredibly well-read Norm
Very familiar with the Great
Philosophers
And how did I miss you
Just
Really amazing it's like you are one of the you know
You are one of the greats when it comes
Sioux prophecy
Cool boy
Eman Alex quotes
The comic books
Yeah
As Uncle Benjamin used to say
With great Alex comes great Alec
Flexibility
I think you call that client management
That's true
You spend any time around Alex you realize the little bit of flattery probably
Like
Is how you get anything done
Yeah yeah yeah
Yeah what do you want to order for pizza you look great today
Lego okay fireman
It's what it really is
Choice
So smart
I'm particularly
Interested
As those questions were coming in
Hanging Lake
The deliberation went on
What was the what was the
Flavor of
Tension
In the courtroom
Asbestos you can describe it like
Just like the I know that
It for us from far away there's a bit of
Confusion a bit of
Is it going to be today even on Wednesday it was like the end of the day
Wednesday
Yeah yeah
I think by the end of Wednesday I specially at
After
They heard
William Sherlock's testimony again
And then they took him recess they went back to deliberate then there was lunch
And then they came out and they said
Can we have a new copy of the verdict
Warm
Because we wrote the wrong number on a line
And
And that was
Sitting in the back row
With
Damn read that.
Ontarian who's been recording these this trial
And others
And we both looked at each other you know eyebrows raised in there almost at the end do you know
Or does it mean you know there's
Still kind of making their way in and no one knew but
I was starting to by the end of the day on Wednesday really kind of lose hope that they were going to arrive at
I don't know why I just felt like they were
You know I
Caillou started
Wednesday over the weekend
About like
And then
You know speaking of Norm he started to say
I've got another
You know I've got another gig Bass
I need it you know I need to postpone this a little bit
Because I have to go pee in New York City and I
I can't monitor this case and I don't trust anyone else to monitor this
This case
I'm at or these deliberations so I can't be in two places
Norbit
Epistolary
Do just Norm better
Terrible stand up
It's it's
It's funny I remember whenever he broke into the
Conversation with
The judge and just all the sudden was like
I can't be here until 2 on Thursday that's
I can do it everybody just went
What are we
What are you doing
Yeah I think I think
My jaw literally dropped when he said that I thought
Book to be on Rogan
Bible book sorry about this one
It really was odd
Yeah
Why don't we
Just
Cross that bridge when we get to it
So yeah
That gym
Call Ian
She's very formal
Yeah that would have been
Insta korbut
So
So then we were thinking by the end of the day on Wednesday now we're looking at a really truncated day
On Thursday
Sure
Then what
Then we're at Fry's
So
And then you were also thinking about there were all these other things going on you know
We starting to pile up at the end of the week like the January 6th
I'm hearing on
Thursday night and
I was just
Starting to think about
You know
Are you going to be in Connecticut for the rest of your life like a Twilight Zone situation you know
You can't escape the restaurant
What's your William Shatner like at the whole thing
I get you
Groundhog Day in that in the hotel where which was just walking
Distance from the courtroom we're pretty much everybody
He was staying so
Yeah so anyway so they
Surprised Us in the end you know they they when they ask for an Uber decorum it was because they really were at the very end
They were writing everything in
So
What was your feel when the first number was red
I
I was like
You know
That is a lot
Close I noticed a couple people were were speculating on Twitter they were saying
Okay Price is Right rules
You like so guess what's heard it going to be
Can't go over you know and so keep on
People were saying
You know
350 325
And I was thinking
That sounds ambitious
But
Given the number of
Plaintiff
I don't know maybe
Yeah right when Robbie Parker caught 120
And you still had 14 plaintiff's to go
You were thinking
This is
Is going to be
Historic
And then imagine that
Palpable
You like after Robbie's verdict
It was absolutely silent in a row
And
You know I mean
It wasn't
It was just sort of
Stunning
How quiet it was
And you know people were just listening
To the numbers and all you could hear were
No people like myself
Typing these numbers in
And you know try
Keep track of them
And then
I was typing in in in New York
They were adding
Andre adding just to make sure everything was accurate
And
You know you started
Stevie start of exclamations of Woe and
Oh my God
The moments
The moments I think they showed the Judgment they immediately cut to Robbie
It was it was you saw him put his head in his hands like very slowly and just keep it there
And it was very much like
I I could
Vland
Steve
Thought of
F****** we did it you know like it was
It was such a feeling of
I mean I imagine you could have
Reached out
Inhale victory in the air
Like it was that kind of
Intensity
Yeah yeah
It was really incredible
It was a
Yeah I think nobody knew what to say it was just I mean
I just looked over at
Lisa
You know
But
Came out like a different word
Anyway
Yeah
It was
It really was it was really a jaw-dropping
It was incredible
Spell
And not to not to dwell on any like Shawn
Freud or anything
But
What how is how is Norm
I'm feeling a sense of his violent as this was
I did look over
He was
Staring straight ahead
You did not look at the lawyers
You did not turn around
Brandito I mean and then one of the things he was doing in the courtroom prior to that
Was
I like making nice
The people in the room you know at one point
You know Robbie Parker during one of the recesses
This was leaving the Roman
Norm was following him out the door and kind of like
Patted him on the back at another point
Pat llodra who attended many days
Of the trial she was the former first selectman in Newtown when the shooting occurred with the equivalent of Mayor
And
Yo what up to her and
Said oh nothing
Personal kind of thing it's all in the game
Especially in the courtroom he was just like I'm a gladiator in here
I'm fighting for my client and then
At the end of it is I am and it's
It's fun to be in the in the pit with your right Alex go have a beer and you're like no you're a monster dude I don't know what to tell you
In a case like this it's
It's really hard
To sort of
Break
Text Tara like that you know
Just
I'm not sure that that is something that people were buying I mean I won't speak for
Her Pat llodra or anyone like that but
Everybody obviously deserves a defense
Even if you're any less reputable of a lawyer
If you take those cases
But I also do
Don't think that you need to
Multiple points
During the case
Suggest that these grieving families are exaggerating their pain
I think that there might be another way to go about defending Alex
But doesn't involve
Something
That distasteful really does require like
I mean
If you are in a vacuum trying to think up defense
Strategies I can understand why this would go up on the White
Skateboard you know
But once it's up there you should be like
And this is an inhuman thing to do now that we should not do
We can scratch this one off but ended when your brainstorming your like her could happen you know this is strategy
Fashion or something like that
But when you behave the way Norm did and right now you know
It's not that they defended Alex
That was the reason
Did they were
The way they did it that was so
Disrespect
But here's where you know
As you guys know
Better than anybody
This is where
No
You have to consider who's the client and as rain all told me during the
Trial in Austin
Alex calls all
The shot
Cuz I said will he be testifying and he said
It's up to Alec
And then he goes
Everything is up to Alex
And so what they were putting on it was why I sent that Alex
Yeah so you know in a normal client relationship you would
You would
As as you guys were just saying you know you'd say
Note Let's cross that one off we're not going to be accusing the families of anything you know that's what got us into
This mess
And that's how I'm going to end up paying a billion dollars
Hey Ya
But you know
Person after person in these trials has testified
Alex calls all the shots
Alex runs the show
The show runs on Alex there would be no Infowars if not for Alice
Alex makes all the decisions Alex said to do that Alex
What's checked on this Alex one bat
So that was the defense that he wanted
And so
You got the judgment
That that kind of Defense
Produces
I'm not affect
No no no not effective
Import matter until and say I'm done apologizing
Two families that work
Still weeping because they had just watched Robbie's and Tire
Tribute to his daughter the night after the shooting on video
CO2 to sort of
Say it
Not sort of state to literally say I'm done apologizing is
You do not
Strategic
Put it that way
And a thing
The courtroom is a struggle session
It doesn't play very well
Comment which surprise
You know audience of one
You know a lot of the things he said in the courtroom I felt like okay he knows Alex's watch
Watching the live feed he's performing for the audience
Well I mean you just apparently lost
Does radio show so you might be coming on
Infowars
Roster
After the War Room there's the norm room
Right
Kid Robert Barnes
Condition together they absolutely hate each other so
They couldn't do a show together cuz neither of them has very low
Yeah
I feel like
Since we have you here there are two things
They come up that the audience
Probably has
Questions about
Is the judges shoes
Oh yes
There's some question
The people have about the
Right okay
Are there
I don't know
Are there any questions about the judge issues
Tweeting about the judges shoes
I was
You were doing about the judge I did
What's going on today
Okay
It's true I tweeted about her shoes
Yes no she she has her
Collection of shoes and I think you know as a couple people pointed out
When you're wearing you know long flowing black judge's robes
There's not a lot
Two I mean Ruth Bader Ginsburg distinguished herself by wearing those lace collars that made near that became so icon
Sonic and I think judge Bellis
Kind of did that by wearing a lot of really interesting shoes
So
Don't give your own personality a little bit when you have
Something a uniform so much like a black robe
Yeah I have something for you
That at some point though penetrate your mind to how stupid the f****** robe is
If you're like I see I'm getting around the whole respectful judge Thing by wearing flashy shoes
I just wear a f******
This is one of your longstanding things about uniform
I see you can't wear shorts but I wear a big boot
I hate it
I think
The my problem with it is they go halfway
Cuz I can
You know the Commonwealth
Countries
You Faking It
Yeah well I feel like I regret bringing up at 2
So hurt her shoes were always really interesting
You know usually they're usually
Primarily black
But there were kind of high heels and get a one-point black and white
It sort of you know what
What
You might call
Spectator pumps
And some really interesting here really nice-looking shoes
I was just noticing that I have miss you purse
I was noticing that
And then on Burdick day it was almost as if she knew because she was wearing these zebra stripe
Shoes with a red bow and a vivid red heel
Do not
Suggest that she may already have known it advance
I know you're right you're right
Didn't know anything about the music
But it was but it just happened to be the most
Define buoyant shoe day
Kim
Dim the judge
See Twitter
Like the judge can
Google
No face she probably that you had an interest in her shoes
It might have been for you we are talking about a lot of audiences at 1 today
Honor
Your honor it's an honor your shoes are honorable
Me with these shoes
Your sisters are right
And then I guess
B b s
Sing
I apologize if this is
Bring up something that's
It's a sore subject
I'll be there was a little bit of controversy with a tweet
That you put out
And I feel like if I didn't bring this up it would feel like I was
Not bringing it up on purpose
Protecting me
I feel like
You know it
It's a pretty simple x
What nation
And
Do you want to
Like layout what happened
Absolutely
So I'm a day after Alex Jones test
Certified
I know
Norm got up and he was
His testimony was supposed to continue the next day
So Norm would have you no had a chance to examine you his own client is the defendant
And he declined and he said
So we will assume given what we said earlier about Alex calling all the shots so Alex didn't want to test
Buy a second day
So Norm said
I think you know it's probably best instead I am and also I think so
Strategically there some lawyers nor commenting on Twitter who are more knowledgeable and you know I'm not on the legal
Strategy
And and they were saying
It's favorable to his client if Norm Woods
Decline to do the cross like that and in
Said call his own client as the defense with
So
He reserved the right to do that
They made a deal with the family's lawyers where they would have the right
The cross
If you if Norm called him and he came back
And so Norm said
He's not going to testify today
He's going to come back now
Next week
I will call him as a witness and this is agreeable to the family's lawyers and then they will have another crack at
Basically
And he and what he said was
That'll lower the temperature in the room
You know I think it will be better
So
I interpreted that
And having seen the jurors reaction
Jones is testimony
The day prior
I interpreted that as
You know Norm says
His client has damaged himself
So much
That you might want to give the
The jury of Grey
Something to that effect
Which I think
If that's a reading of
Lower.
No.
Serta says
Things didn't go so well yesterday
Let's calm down and I'll bring it back
But what my error was
I said that he said that
You know the way I worded the
If it were my interpretation that would have been one thing that would have been
Bi-Rite
But but I said something to the effect
He says
Yeah
So
You know I'm after the recess
Head hospital because you didn't use
Quotation mark
So you know
It wasn't like a direct
Quoting of him
But yeah the word said was in there
Those are as ghetto as saying or something like that
So that makes it sound like you know.
That was what he
He told the judge
When he did not
So
After the recess
He came back
It was clear that
You know Jones had seen this
Call Vic to his attention or someone at Infowars but maybe Jones
And so he came back and he was just
Really angry and he was saying
I don't know why you know Elizabeth Williamson of the New York Times is
Covering this
She's written a book about their son
You know she shouldn't have this courtroom in
How anyone could have interpreted what I said
As
He's damaged
And the judge
Karma
And she was like we're not doing this
Here that's not what
This trial is about
You know I've already told you you know stop talking over me something like that
And and so
He tried again and she stopped
And then that was that
And I thought
If he's
Calling me out for something I better see what the problem is
You know
So
I followed him out of the courtroom
And when we got in the hallway I turned on my
Recorder on my phone
Cuz I wanted to hear what he had to say
And he was like I'm not talking to you and I said well
Are you
Talking so you just wanted to
Say that in front of the
You know so my alternative
If you have a problem with something I've written I want to hear you out
Or are you just
Saying that for the judge and for the cameras
And he was like
He went into this big thing
So we got into the elevator he had all of his files and his
Briefcase
That's really
Stuffed balloon
Paper red
Hoping exploded in the elevator
And
Papers
Files every and I said do you need a hand
And
He was like not from you
Basically telling me like
He was like you shouldn't be here you shouldn't be covering this I said well I think I know a lot about this case
And
And he and then he kind of
You know I was like what is the problem and he finally did you know I'm following him out onto the street
You finally got to the point where he said
The problem is you said that I said that he damaged himself and I said I didn't
Say that and he said
No you did go back and look I said I will go back
And if
If I did
I'd say that I will correct
Because that's
Responsible
And
And he said I would appreciate it and then he said
Because
People are thinking that
The upshot was
People are thinking that I told you that
Yeah
And that I'm in bed with New York Times
Meaning like I'm bedded with
You know the paper another words like from spider room
Yeah but he yeah it's so
So there is no
You can imagine Jones
Seeing this or someone in on his
Stop CMAs insane
Is Norm pattis talking to the New York Times and
Telling them that
That was what I thought
Weird
Because it's not like Alex to be parent
That would be an odd thing for him to do
Usually it's pretty chill.
I assume that Norm did not
Immediately
Immediately get struck by an iron table
Right leg
No God struck him down for his
Whining about somebody
Slightly misquoting him maybe
If you look at it the wrong way
Like he does realize what
He's in court
Right
Yeah I mean
But my job as reporter was just
If I mischaracterized
You know or if I
If I said he said that and he did not then it's my job.
Correct.
So I would
I also think if you just said
Turnabout is fair play
He might have been like I touche
And then you guys going to just moved on
Well
Yeah but then I wouldn't have been doing my job
So
I just said
You know
If it's wrong oh correct I'll go back and look at it so I went back and looked at it and I did say
Says
So I
Fix it I took it down and then I provided an explanation
And of course that became material for Infowars and you know
Reporter lied after you know she lied and was caught
Tell them that they can
Can try and come after you for a billion-dollar
Good luck
Really unfortunate that
You know the real world plays by
You know that
Semi
To fully responsible rules
Where is
This is something
Thing that you obviously feel the obligation to and the professional
Responsibility to make eclairs
Navigation and direction
People like Alex
And his fans
This becomes
Proof of like
Some kind of an intentional lie
And it's just
Responses to your
Clarification tweeting it was
Yeah not good
You were kind of hose
The moment that we came out it wouldn't have mattered what you whether you took it down or apologize or explain it or whatever
Who's going to be on the show
And I would like
And you were you were there
Clarification is really for the audience of I guess your employer more
Norm they don't care for your soul
Your soul is probably pretty important
Yeah
I mean we are you know this is a trial about truth
Unreality
And so
You know it
Always helpful
Especially to those days
Weekend so
Yeah because I did not say that
I thought okay bear
I'm going to change it
So
Yeah so that I knew you know of course
This would be material for them that you know this would be
A chance for them to you know take away act and
Yeah
It's sad what they do
So unfortunate
That this is like
Like the angle they take on Infowars not that you flushed half a donut
You know like this is
This is what Alex
I think that donut one under-the-radar don't you
Yeah I think so I think you lucked out on that
Who is like you know we have
For you this is probably like
As chaotic
Or as much as
Drama as there is surrounding
The case and you compare that
To Alex
His performance on the stand or falling asleep Norm saying that
The families are exaggerating their grief
I think the balance here is
Pretty clear
Yeah i o n
The that was the other thing in that conversation you know writing down the elevator and all that you talking to Norm
He said
You said I fell asleep as if that was some big scoop
I said I just said you fall asleep
And and he said I was not sleeping
He said I was
I was saying I was
Signaling that
We had spent enough time on Gilligan's Island that was when
Chris Maddie that the attorney for the families
Was
Questioning the Britney pasta Infowars corporate representative
I know and he said he was sending a signal that we had spent too much time I said
You normally sleeping it was on video
Anna and he was inside
The thing that it wasn't anything he told me that
Get my head out of my own you know
Yeah
So it was an elaborate signal it was very subtle and get complicated if that was
What he was trying to signal but I respect people who take unconventional
Messaging approach reprimanded for not standing up when he approached
The judge or ask the judges question
Until we figure it if I'm going to stay down
I might as well
Some of the objections that he would make from his state it was almost like it was like you pictures
Someone like on his shaved long with a cigarette
Oman
Get on your feet
Yeah that was
When that was kind of a pair of shoes
I got them up
What would that was kind of like where things were like a traded
The beginning that like
Like you need to stand up
But you're going to
Speak to the court
Isaac this is go
Is it going to be an interesting scratch
Yeah I think one of the one of the things I notice
Text was that
Norm spoke
Progressively less as the weeks went on
Sure you could you could really come on
Yeah you could really kind of measure it that first week he did as much as he could do
The second week he pulled back and by the third week he was like I'm not going to cross the
Examine anybody
I'm just going to say go for it
You know
Yeah
Yeah I thought I was a little too
Surprised with that because some of his
You know messaging to the media in you know the years leading up to the trial was sort of
Well these families thing
Think that
They'll do you know that they won't be examined themselves will they will be and
You know he had a lot of what we know he had a lot of their personal records and and health record
Birds and things like that in the reason we know that as of course they were
Wrongly transmitted to the attorneys
In Texas
And you know he had to come up for a hearing on that
Is that should have been done
So you know
But once the families were on the stand and test
Buying as to what they've been through
And very little to say
He didn't you know
Robbie Parker and what Robbie is an indoor in this case
Over the years from Alex Jones wear
He played that you no openings
As of Robbie Parker press conference the night after his daughter Emily was killed
At Sandy Hook
Over and over and over again for years
So Robbie was really at the
The center of
This case and Alyssa Parker Emily's mom also test
And
She's not a play
Plaintiff but the two of them just
Portray and you know just
Painted this
Nightmare of You Know
Gordmans and deathrun
Pets and people knowing where they lived and a man confronting Robbie you know
4 years after
The shooting on the street in Seattle
And all of these things
And Norm did have
It did not have a single question for either one of us
Which was really
Kerning
Surprise
But
Then again this is testimony so powerful that you wonder really what
What is there to say
You can only kind of make it worse for yourself I think
I think it is Crossing
But he did do
With a couple of the plaintiff's was just about like
You have
A charity
Suspicious
Yeah
Yeah and I think that there wasn't theirs
Is a couple attempt
Said that
With some of the first
Q
Folks and then I think it's just a good system defect
No maybe like Alexa
Just not even do anything
I think they I think Norm really
Try to be
Beginning to hammer that like all these guys are just going out
For money the lawyers are ambulance Chasers
And then
Yeah exactly trying to inject
Politics
And that was against the rules the judge had said you cannot talk about electoral politics
You can't talk about political figures
You can't discuss Jones's finances cuz we remember and in in off
Boston in August
Yo he tried
They wrongly that he was bankrupt
And that two million would be more than he could you know just about all the
Or more than he can handle
I'm in terms of a of a verdict
So Olive that was serve off the table
But you know Warriors try to you know get around that Independence and then presenting there
Cases in so
Yeah couple times in mentioning some of the families charities
Yeah he was talking about well
Basically isn't this about gun violence isn't this about gun control
Politics
Bo that
Didn't you a well he mentioned this when the wheelers testified because
Francine wheeler
About
Can't remember how long after the shooting of the month or two
After the shooting
Delivered
President Obama's
About radio address
Santa Saturday in this was when the families were pushing for expanded background checks
I'm in that legislation wound up bailing but
As part of that effort she delivered the radio address in Norm brought that up
So it's a way to get both
Guns and politics
You know
Into the
The jury's Minds
And I think the council is there may have been
But there would have been some people on the jury might have been sympathetic
That argument that I'm okay so this what there was a political aspect here or something like that
But
I think as
Stories mounted andaz
You know just the sort of horror of what some of these people had in George
Became more and more
Parents
I think he know
Norm
Wisely decided that
This wouldn't be worth it but you know site trying to say oh well you voted for Hillary Clinton
Not going to cut it
When you have drawers weeping
Abbey idea that you know
People who had just lost their loved ones we're getting
Deathrun
That's rape threats
People
Threatening to dig up their murder
Children and I was talking about defiling their grave
You know saying wasn't this all about gun control just started
Pills as an argument
Yeah yeah yeah and I think that
You know whatever you can inject
Into that
Is kind of useless
Wants
The understanding
Of the Damned
Image being the
It making it so you can't
Properly grieve and reopening wounds over and over and over and over and over again
The notion of
Real political
Ideas
While distracted
Right
Probably not that he'll
Now
Yeah it was just
It was just too powerful and too often
You know that
Just to hear that day after day what you know
What is 4
People had
Gone through and
And the kind of like
Do you know if the jury was watching them in the courtroom.
Saturday you know just
Stoic
And pulled together and consoling each other and
It was
Extremely powerful
And I think that's
Another reason that
Alex Jones didn't return to the courtroom because
We saw what happened when
Scarlet
Louis through an accident of timing wound up
No
Confronting him and for 90 minutes addressing
The answer
To every question directly at Alex Jones and asking him you don't why are you doing this
And
Truth is so important to our society truth is the Bedrock
On which our democracy rests
You say you're concerned about the country
And you're spreading things like this
What what
Wrong with you
And I think
At all cost I mean having watch
Him
Literally sweat through his shirt while she was talking to him
I think
The idea of
Sitting in front of
15 plaintiff
Just
I don't think you can do it
I really don't I think he was afraid
I mean we've talked about this a bit.
Can't blame him
If you look at it from his perspective
There's a choice to not have to do that yet
It seemed like it would be a
Almost
Psyche Crusher
It is it is a little bit like if Alex is directing the defense strategy inexplicably
By himself
Somehow at the same time recognizes that him being on the stand is a bad thing for him
Yeah
He doesn't realize that those two are essentially the same
There's actually the same problem
Him being on the stand would be him defending himself
In the exact same way as him
Creating this defendant running the defenses bad for him but he didn't get that
Somehow
There was something I wanted to ask you guys about because you
Alex Jones
I do not own any spectator pumps
Talk about that late
So I really wanted it so one of the things that Chris Maddie one of the lawyers for the families
Mention was
And I just found myself actually even in the moment
You were saying that
What are the reasons that
James Johnston testify
More
Is that
It's really important to him
Be on the outs
Outside calling this all a sham
Because he thinks
That
The more time you would have
Spence in the courtroom and I don't want to
I don't want to miss
Restate what his message but I think this is pretty
Close to wedding say
Any is closest to the if you got close to this process
That would sort of
Opposed him
As
This guy who's just
A huckster and selling products
And doing it you know On The Backs
So these people
And lying about this and having to acknowledge that he had been lying about this
Spring years
That that would damage him with his audience
And I and I said
Chris at the
Time
I don't know
Because
His audience seems to sort of a
Accommodate
A lot of
What he says or changes in you no changes in his story or whatever
Yeah your side for sure
I think that
The audiences trap
I think
For the most part
And they can rationalize quite a bit
That that that that happens
And
You know all it takes if Alex has a bad day
Is this a it was a good day
And have Barnes come on yeah they can talk for an hour about how
Everything is unfair if only he could defend
Himself
If only he could say the name Trump
The nailery
Then everything would be
Refine right
Like I think that
I think that what Maddie saying make
Sense
And
To do the out
Outside world
He would be exposed
Sure they is a liar and a con man
But that that audience
They have so many opportunities to realize this out
Sidedoor courtroom
I have said that no bottom far too many times for me too
Pull back on that now
No matter what he does
When he did when he was testifying he was talking about his bit
Coin thing at
Bobby said
You're going to use this in a commercial
And then Alex.
Use it in a commercial
Like
Probably not even voice
Yeah they were like this is the smartest
Dude that ever lived
You get much more
Trying to profit off the
The trial when Alex was in front of the courthouse
He had his book in his hand
Like when he was
Interviewing with like local news outlets
Like yeah
Flown back
To Connecticut
Doesn't test
Spotify
Instead does these press conferences where he's clearly trying to put product
ProgressBook
On the local news
And it's like
I am is the audience can't see through a lot of that stuff I don't know what hope there is
For anyone
Away and he's going Infowars you giving and I won't do it here
Giving the URL
Yeah I would mean I would say if Kristen just said you know the more time he's in the court the last time he's selling
I think that would make more sense to me than anything else
When he's not moving product
You might be moving some but it'll be less
It'll be less effective if Owen is pointing out hey look there's Alex in the courtroom boy it sounds bad
Oh no sounds good
About it
Oh yeah so it sounds like yeah that was a sort of Devon King argument that you know something that money
Funny Posner who really began this whole effort
To call Alex Jones
Account
You learned early on that the bunking doesn't really work
Also the idea of light
Exposing Alex Jones will be upset
Opposed
You know a person who lies and sells products on the back of
Tragedy Etc
Sort of in a way reminded me of you how difficult it is to
To talk someone out of
A conspiracy theory that they have already fully embrace
That his audience is
As you said damn you know Captivate they
Therein
So
They have their choices
Is to accommodate but to repudiate him I think
I don't know what that
Would take
Well and I think the
So many of the people obviously we've heard
Much more explicit stories about this as it relates to
Qanon but like
A lot of the people in the audience or financially in the hole because of Alex I like in debt but they
Spend a lot of money they're committed in that way
Airfield dumb
If they realize oi've
I've been scammed for all this
Or they've
Alienated family members loved ones
Isolated themselves and insulated in a
A bubble of people who are
Amenable
To Alex Jones
Conspiracies a eating and reinforcing it back and back to them yeah there's a lot of
Invest
Emotional and financial that they
Take it on
Do you to believe this
Stuff and I think
Alex always talks about the
The Nigerian
Email scam
Because I think he got
That he definitely didn't get tricked by multiple times
Multiple friends
To have fallen
Run for it and like you fall for the first email and then you fall
For the second because you don't want to admit that
The first was a
A fraud
I think that there's some Dynamic of that with his audience
I don't know if a courtroom is going to
Penetrate
Take that
Cuz that's the reality world and that's not where they are living
It can be super effective though in helping
When people knock
Fall into alley
Lexus suire
That could be
And effect you'd have a good have like a ironically
Calculations
Yeah I mean it's a little bit like no matter how many times I proved the Earth
Is more than 10,000 years old I'm not going to convince
A lot of
Yeah
The forest
Before we wrap up
I wanted to ask about
The feelings
And like
How things sit
I mean obviously I don't want to be I don't know why I asked you like
What are the family say or anything
This process is over but it's also not over
Yeah
That's got to feel like
Cathartic
But at the same time
There's still a road to travel there still
The looming
Notion of a
Kiehl's
They're still
You know I mean I don't think
Appeals going to work but if there is an appeal there may be another trial
Right after retry
How like
Buick Japanese cents over the
The feeling of
I don't even know what I'm trying to ask you one Gettysburg with the Civil War is not over yet you know like how are you
Feeling about that process moving forward
Yeah
So without you know betraying any individual confidences I think I just immuno end
No I don't like
Speak for the families as a group
Cuz that's just not
Right
But
What I ain't ya what I from what I gathered
First of all a gigantic
Exhale
In the room and you know just ascenso
Wow you know we
Weight kinds of Becker story
Yeah we we
We were able to tell the world what
Happened
We're able to
Wayne bikes
Explaining what happened
We're able to
Explain
Dangers here
Officer of culture of disinformation and lies for profit
And you know and
Explain that
This is a phenomenon that's not
Find Tower
Alex Jones
And has really in the decade since Sandy Hook
Occurred again and again
And you know he himself and
Disappointing made in the story I wrote about
The verdict
Yo he has
Been apart of
Most of the
Highest-profile
Bible lies
Decade since Sandy Hook you know whether you're talkin about or
No coronavirus myths and and anti-vax
Stuffin
You're the great replacement theory that drove the violence in Charlotte
It's Bill and certainly the 2020
Election conspiracy theories that led to the violence at the
The capitol on January 6th so
You know
I think
That their sense was by speaking
About what happened to them and how this all got
Started and how long it lasted
They were sneaking today
You know and really
Try to help
You know
Claiming you do
Not only planning their at their need of their
Their story and you and then saying you know this is
Is Robbie put it you know in the press conference after work near he found his voice he was smiling about
For so long because he didn't want the abuse to get worse
He was really worried about the safety of his family
And I
And you know he he finally got
Appoint when he saw that note
Parkland parents were
Receiving the same kind of abuse
And that
Just horrible statistic that today
Nearly 20% of Americans believe that
Every high-profile mass shooting is a plot
By the government
They were able to sort of say
Is something really
Serious that is not only impacting us
This is not a one-off
This we were that you Noah foundational story and what is
Now phenomenon
And the fact that they were able to raise that I think
Was was really satisfying to them and
And we owe them
Our gratitude for that
As you could see from watching the proceedings it did not come easily
For them to noses
Extremely painful for them to
You
Brett outraged that alarm and and you know and relay and
Recall would have happened
Yeah
Yeah so I think in that sense you know and again sticking with what Robbie was saying after work
No.
They still they stopped their they went through it they told the truth
And everybody on that stand in this is bizarre Robbie's words not mine
Everybody on that
Stand
Told the truth except the one
You know and I think
That that that
Yeah
I think about her
What I find Retro Air Bud
What I find what I find so
Interesting about this
Yeah that it is
You know like what
Mark Bankston and we talked
Couple of days ago
And we were all talking about how we were worried about how the Judgment would go we were worried what the
The verdict was going to be whether or not he's going to send a messenger or whatever
By doing this
The trial itself
Tumi kind of
Reinforces just how bad Alex is
Without
Allowing Alex to poison people's minds with all of the other shed with all the politics
Texting me emotional bulshit
All the things that can get them angry and distract them
Without that
There is no misinformation
A reasonable group of people and we know there were Republicans on the jury
The reasonable group of people will look at
Get that s*** and go that is a month
It is
By Alex Jones's
Ability to inject those things
That we get to where Alex Jones is in trial you know what I'm saying
Kind of got a bad
I don't feel the same two that mean that I was think about while you were
Discussing
Is that like
For each one of these parents
Like there are a hundred a thousand stories that we haven't heard of people were hurt by
Play these these misinformation
Things you know whether it's
Somebody who lost a loved one
Cuz they were Tuesday
Get vaccinated or was
I'm careful at all with covid
Yeah there is
There's so many stories that end up going
Never heard
Yeah and it's great that
That this
Allows
That
Story to be told in a
Large setting where it's
You know
People will hear it
And that judgment that judgment is so huge you know when you talk about setting a precedent
The largest
Judgment in American history by a factor of 10
That's it that's a 56-game hitting streak level of
You're not going to break that record for a long long time
Yeah yeah it's a it really is it
Sort of like
Launched it over the you know over-the-wire as
Hey
Pay attention
You know this is not really a big deal
And and yeah and you know you're so right I mean the fact that
That
Politics
It's not about politics as we
You know there have been
People whose lives have been to
Troy
Buy online disinformation and just abuse
Yo
So many of them and
You there on all
Across the political spectrum and for reasons that you know have everything and nothing to do with
Politics
And I think know the families are saying like this
This is
Dominant this is something that
Happening this guy is
One of the worst if not be worst actors in This Arena but it's a big arena
Yeah
Yes it is
I think you probably saw.
Dispute Ubly the biggest
During the
Bureau specially the years right after shooting
I'm in
If you need any
Evidence
That their argument that it
Getting worse
Is true that there are so many more and it's now debatable whether Alex is the worst I know I mean
Baby I think maybe the bigger the biggest
Probably thing that
Alex is really responsible for is
Without him
Demonstrating the popularity
I don't think Tucker could go as far as mask off white nationalist as he is right now
Alex hasn't pushed it so a bigger plateau
Then him
Can engage in his behavior
Yeah it's um yeah I feel sort of frog boil isn't it
We learned recently that that actually that metaphors is not true
Sorry
I know I know
But then also access lazy of me
He's instrumental in the creation of like
The Oath Keepers he's
His fingerprints are on the Proud boys so how much of
An epicenter of
Bulshit that
Infected everything he is it's crazy
Yeah
It's really interesting
Talk about this I know before but
The idea that when he was getting his
Start there was that
Samsung
He's just a clown he's a goofball he's very theatrical he's fun to watch
But at the same time he always had those
Ties to
Soda bar rated
Extremist
Keepers and I mean his first the first demonstration of
How persuasive he can be with when he raised $90,000 to rebuild the
Branch Davidian Church
After the Waco
Yo he was a hero and Jon Ronson has been
Wonderful by the way
Jon Ronson listens to your show a lot
We talked and he was on a podcast with him
A week ago and he was saying you know those guys really have a wonderful understanding then
Yeah we were talking about how Jon Ronson hero travels with Jones back
That really mid-90s
Out west
And he's revered among
People who have been in armed standoff
With the federal government
So
Yeah and it at all of that sort of blue under-the-radar it was just too cringey
You know and numb
And now we see you know it's not anymore
And just the damage that it can be done in
That can be done and you wonder like what would have happened I don't know what do you guys think what would have happened
If people had taken Jones more seriously at the very beginning
I don't think anything's
Because I think people would be
What quiet
Rightly
Lately I'm sorry
They would have been to marginalize the voices there like take this seriously
Is it in like 2009 there were people within intelligence agencies that were like
Don't worry about that somebody's Patriot groups that are popping up
Yeah
Their warnings and
I remember the guys name dammit
But there was a guy who
Didn't interview about how like
All this stuff that's happening now
You could see the kernels of it I wrote a report and it was ignored
German by any chance
I miss you
It might
We talked awhile back. Fresh in my memory
But yeah
These kinds of things will probably be the same bike
I think the people would be like
Yeah alright
Sure
You you're you're saying
That this tiny Fringe thing is for dangerous
Please I think
Problem with what you're describing is that it's not really an answer volquest
If
Could have
Taking him seriously back then
Is a more interesting question
Because I think the answer is no
I think that what he
He did was fine today
Exploit in our society that was there
You know he found a way to two
Monetize it in a
And exploit
Better than I think a lot of people but
The fact that it happened is evidence of Wyatt
Because it was there it wasn't like he invented some
Brand new thing that
It's that brought everybody to something it was that
There's a crack
Any just hammered away at it until he got his own space
Yeah yeah yeah
I think he benefited from being in the
Conspiracy space
And so like
Most of the
Criticism of him I noticed this one of the motivating factors behind like taking this show more seriously
I noticed that most of the criticism about him was like
He secretly works for Israel
You know like who you working for
Shadowy Jewish
Cabal
Spirit Lake
Criticisms of him were conspiracies themselves
And I think
Because of that
Sort of
Ouroboros of nonsense
I think he benefited from that big
Because there is no real
Power today
Yeah if you always
Two other people criticizing you for being a
Secret agent for Israel then you can distract from any legitimate criticism and just
Combine those two together
He says I'm a liar that guy says I work for Israel see all these people are lying about me that kind of thing
So interesting cuz when I called people this was years ago when I first started working on this
For the book
I called people who had you know been associated with him in those early days
A shocking number of them
You know
He used to be more edges Semitic many years now and I'm really mad about
Yeah
I was just like what
Yeah out of all the possible
Critiques that's not
That I didn't see that one coming
No
And I also think he's played
What did you say
Speak against Israel more that is probably
Play true or not
Please
Netanyahu's the fascists
It kind of still a fan of Israel so
I don't even know really if I know his position
Well
What is this has been a lot of fun
Broke van Maybe
No relatives
It's fun talking to you but also this
Conversation than this
This topic is
I think what he'd like to say is thank you very much for joining
That is cut part of thank you for having me I love talk
And before we
Before we part ways
I should say
You are in Wisconsin now
Because you're at a Book Festival and you will be appearing at
Various
Book festival's over the next
Until the end of November issue
Is that you
Yeah
Until Thanksgiving more or less
Yeah and people can find your date
Scicon
On Twitter
Where you'll be at Mendel come
I'm sure I know that a lot of our audience says
So highly and loved your book and the lutely
Ability to
To come see you speak about it I think they would
They would gobble
And I will probably bring you
That's weird thing that will happen but it might happen
There you'll get you'll get a bunch of like
Like
Ceramic
Cast Donuts handmade handmade everything
I'll be happy to find that nyt Liz
You have a thought
Not your dates
Up there
Coming down near you
Maybe
I hope so
Someone just said
Why don't you come to Cleveland
Translate I would love to come to Cleveland
Is that spine hello Cleveland
Oh
Yeah
Well is thank you again it's been a delight and I'm sure we will talk again soon
Okay sounds great guys
Thank you so much for having me on
Same color