I have great respect for knowledge by knowledge I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
Need
Knowledge fight
Nike.com
I worship at the altar of Celine and talk a little bit about
Alex Jones
My bright spot today Jordan is reached the end of sneak weekend
Yeah yeah
That we had that opportunity to
I sat down and talked to Marquis and please and
I think
There's an argument that could be made that we could have put that all out on Monday or something
Coming so fast that we just got to keep moving
You know they're the trial the end of it the verdict
We drank that out too long we're going to end up
Still responding to a two-month from now or.
Generally speaking I feel like
Most of our decisions over the past 6 years
Could have been my argument at that they were not the right one and yet here we are so let's write it out
It's debatable that we shouldn't be doing this
That's where I'm at so I'm glad that this weekend was received well by the folks
Appreciate all the very positive comments
Other overall I mean like I just I have
I have some other fun stuff that's going on I can't really talk about right now I've seen a couple of great tweets
Mostly
Memes with animals in them do you know those are I can't remember any of them specifically but I remember hey that was fun
You're not going to talk about a meeting for the next
Combination
Gestalt
Is Alex might say I was coming in here thinking very similarly as to what my bright spot was that
I kind of
Just
A bitumen and achievements like an accomplishment but at the same time again unlock
Yeah it's just like a
Yeah
And now we get to keep doing stuff
Sunday would be fun to be nice is to take a little bit
Trip off the beaten path to call and
Instead of doing some of the things that we
Time to do like Wacky Wednesday stuff for
I'm going to the Past
I thought what we would do is talk about Alex Jones
Appearing as a guest
Steven Crowder show
Louder with Crowder
My God so that is covering Today album
So he knows there's a billion on his head
Patrol time of the reasons I chose to do this was we see how Alex response on his show
It's pretty durable or it's going to be the same thing over and over again
Be very repetitive he didn't do anything on purpose and it was
Will be some slight variations of interesting blow-ups and what have you
What it looks like when he's on a different platform trying to preach to a different audio
Are we going to get a life very fragile
Might be drunk there's no apples
So I will get down to business on this during the first let's say hello
Ewok
Very much
The ghost of ennio morricone who's tired of hearing Alex use Ecstasy of Gold from The Good the Bad and the Ugly coming
Automatic brakes
Thank you very much
Snapple of the Brooklyn Bridge
Show the lawyer next I am not a Russian agent Svetlana thank you so much
Ewok
And even not Ava thank you so much you're now policy wonk
Achieva
I also got to take the car to the next Jordan
You are now a technocrat
I have
Risen above
My enemies
A little breaking for me
And then we're going
To come back
And I'm going to start the show over
F*** you
I got plenty of words
For you but at the end of the day
F*** you and your new world order
And f*** the horse you rode in on
And all your s***
Maybe today
Maybe I'll just be gone a month baby
I'm Yours
Walk out of here tomorrow
And you never see me again
Really what I want to do
I never want to come back
Apologized
To the crew in The Westerns yesterday that I
Was legitimately having breakdowns on air
Better tomorrow
Please
So I never really wanted to cover Steven Crowder
And we won't
Generally but about the Connecticut
Haitian when he's in a new environment
A broadcaster primarily for the initiated whereas something like going on cuz hopefully roping in
New people for him
Of course it would be better if you could go on the road again but that doesn't seem like it's happening so crowd was going to have to do for now
I've not sat down to watch a full episode of crowder before his
Dumb show louder with Crowder
Louder with Crowder we've said the name Steven Crowder I still have no idea who he is and I refuse to find out I didn't Fury
It's me every time somebody says louder with Crowder like he's just
He yells more than other people cuz I don't think that's true
He doesn't wear like more flamboyant outfit
Colorful loud suits
I don't know I don't
I think I think it's a bad name what you do
Is Hugo
Way too far with
You know you go rowdier with crowd ER you go an extra step that makes everybody really uncomfortable that's the way you do
If I had a show where I like did favors for people
Ecouter please enough reason I would be okay I'm mad that I got there but if he called this
Shows that it would make sense
Or if I tried to overthrow a government
I can't reason with reason
Again my name wouldn't work if I had a travel show could be Rome's with home
Definitely a book show tomes with all that's a good one
Things work about the thing that they are
It's silly when it's Force what did I don't understand what louder with Crowder me regularly
A decibel level above other shows louder than him
Is one thing that immediately jumped out to me watching the show and that was at the shows very dumb
Like its transparently dumb
Arguments are based on false points and the humor is painful
The thing you have to realize when you watch this is that it's kind of supposed to be dumb
The audience of the show is Steven Crowder has tweeted about before it's at least
The audience is under 60
So this show is like sick children
And I haven't been able to confirm that figure at anyway but
He said it by him no reason to doubt it he has a Analytics
I guess you can feel like this is as bad as smoking like pushing right-wing bulshit to Children is as bad as advertised
To be fair half of the audience
Is between 17 and 18
What are the reasons I've avoided doing too much about Crowder up till this point is that he has a lot of this content behind paywalls
Princeton's the last time Alex was on for his weird performatively masculine cigar club session
The first part of it was public but then the rest of it that you actually water watch is not
We may be coming to a point where I stop over respecting these Ding Dongs intellectual property but I'm I don't think I'm quite there yet
Steven Crowder is repugnant
He's a horrible person and his career has been a shameful series of horrible embarrassment that he's been able to Parlay into heaven
In the very successful YouTube
That appeals to kids
The sophomoric racist jokes and sophomoric anti-lgbtq jokes
I don't want to do
Too Deep dive on his trajectory but here's a summation of his a career path
You tried to be a stand-up comedian buddy sock that it's early way
Catching the attention of Fox News when he got punched in the face by a union protester who he was harassing
This roses stature and he began making his own content most notably a segment called change my mind where you would show up at a car
College campus
Consider the table waiting for college students on their way to class to join him for a spirited debate
He's the meme of the guy with the shoe that
The college student was unprepared and probably late for class
Videos however you want it so the series was a big hit
Hey kind of falls into the same vein is Mark Davis's man-on-the-street segments where he bothers drunk people on the boardwalk and then tries to
Make a political point out of
Profile has grown Stephen has made a habit of being a pile of s*** doing half-cooked segments based on
Racist an empty lgbtq
Better easily do bunkable and not persuasive at all
Voice of adult to adults I should say
This is a very convincing
Do a child who are naturally his Target on
What is the problem was advertised for children
Figured it out
You're dancing to show is about taking extreme right-wing views and dangerous right-wing ideologues and laundering them so they can be in
Enjoyed accepted by high schooler
Basically I think he's one of the worst folks in the space but also I don't know what our show can really add to that conversation
If YouTube cared at all about the safety of the children and teens who use the platform he would have been kicked off long ago and that's really
I think probably the solution here if they want to do something about it
You can't really do that much damage is he's just limited to being on Glenn Beck's Blaze Network
Nike fine yeah
Limited reach quite a bit difficult for kids
So weird
That's like having a Hannah Montana show where they pick them on Tana part really literally and she's a white National
She's not compound
Montana
Adhere kids a preference I'm going to transfer into Popstar
And then we're going to find out exactly how the great replacement Theory really works kids
Which is Happy song yeah I mean like
He's had Stefan molyneux he's laundering
At least multiple times
I don't have a full gas listening but you don't really need one noted hilarious white nationalist
Stefan molyneux
Yeah
Anyway in the aftermath of the Connecticut verdict to discuss the situation with Stephen and
Here we are
Give me some sense of a scene Steven is sitting in his Studio at a desk with
Two louder with Crowder mugs on it
He sells mugs and there's this thing called The Mug Club so this is a very important piece of the tableau
He's also wearing one of his own shirt
Because you always got to be pushing that March man always
Be selling don't wear your own shirt he's wearing over the shoulder holster
So you know that he loves guns sorry what he's wearing a holster like police chief
Where in the World Is Carmen Sandiego ready in case Abdul breaks out during the show
Listen up gumshoes also there's another gun on the desk so it's it's pretty
F****** more ridiculous.
Strengthen bravado for me to take that at all seriously
Alex's on towards the end of the show but this whole episode is more less about rationalizing Alex's verdict in
Complaining about it and it's titled exclusive interview with Alex Jones
This Means War!
The temperature I wanted to start at the beginning and see the tone we're working with although you will find out that I
Did not
End up sticking to that
Listen if you say failed comedian I'm not interested that's why I don't listen to our show
So here's where we start off
I think that this is
Bison win today
Everything works
We have
Alex Jones Nashotah
And
Appreciate look I know
Manipulative
I was not
For a very long time
No no
Precise I'm here on the Shelf
Still at Chris's
And when we talk
Will be showing your mom
Montage of the endzone dance
Hollywood not only the elite
In media apathy
Government
Coming to fish
Championing
Real quick
This is like a clip of Jimmy Kimmel making a joke and the government officials are Jen sake tweeted something
She's not even the press secretary anymore and Alex made a big Target out of her for a while
If she received quite a bit of harassment there's Alex
It probably wouldn't be legally actionable since you the public figure ride
You know all that but yeah this is making a bit of a personal
Ricardo's where you line up
There's inflection
And the reason we're having our
Seeing people
Being bored
This couldn't be further from the truth
Steven loves a good bit of bullying and actually leave bullying campaign sometimes like you did in the case of Carlos Maza
Also Alex isn't being bullied
He's the bully
And Stevens the longer that reality to his audience of children so they think that Alex is the victim here I think that's
Shameful
Also Stephen saying that he has criticisms of Alex
And I think he's a coward
List your criticism what are they
That you like about him see how long those survive after you give him one small
Criticism well I think that Alex would probably Dodge and stuff because he needs someone like Steven out
What's million subscribers on YouTube
Toboggan
Who is going
BFDI platform to meet for me to go on Rocket app to go start streamers
Yeah
So like
I think that he could get away with voicing some of these criticisms to Alex
Whatever they might be
Get any response that's meaningful or any resolution of these
Recognition of these criticisms
Barmore
Meaningful for him to express what his misgivings are and what his criticisms are valid
To the audience in a neutral environment where they could take those criticism
And then
Decide like huh is that something I'm actually really concerned about you
Why one of my criticisms maybe it's he lies all the time could be an issue
Well
Ha
It's one of your if one of your criticisms
Prior to an interview
Is
My interview subject
Is an inveterate an almost pathological liar
Perhaps you will take those answers that he gives in the interview with a different grain of salt
As opposed to if you didn't tell them that at all right now
I was I was thinking one of his legs are the criticisms of Alex might be that he barely thinks that Muslims are human
Definition but I think
Stephens audience wouldn't have as much of a problem with that
So you know
He tries to frame the interview in a particular way
And obviously it's that do that much wrong
Do we have some of the gala
If you watch this
Considering
He's been around
From what I know of
He's a good man
Flawed man
He's talking about here on it
A refreshing when he's on air
Amazon Aaron Ash
Maybe I drank a little too much
But for a man who
4 hours
And then
Misspeak
Or get something wrong
And then apologize
And that is punished
And the
People will
Former Prosecco
Current members of the
Quarterback
Thanks
Deciding
Put you in stocks
Newtown Square
The message is really low
What's crowd
I hope that you're hearing it
If you make them
Mistakes analyzer
If you have a belief
The other people
Pill finder
Offensive
Shut up
Any
They only get worse
What I mean that
Why is it left or right
They made it
This is tough
People watch this I guess so my God what is wrong with me why is it why am I
The weirdo here
I don't know I don't know
What he's doing here is a clear attempt to set the parameters of the conversation
It's just being taken as gospel that Alex misspoke or got some things wrong you apologize need to be punished anyway
That's what all the episode will be in response to it because of that it's going to be meaningless
If the basis in the defound ation that you're building your house on his singing
You're not going to have a good house
Not going to be a house that I'm even going to inspect because it's going to be
Going to collapse
Also
This stuff is already a little overdramatic
A little melodramatic on
On Crowders Park I mean
Okay I feel like
The stocks would have been a more effective response to Alex then what is happening right now
If we had actually been like at the very beginning like hey
You you done f***** up you misspoke
And maybe that's what happened maybe you misspoke
But guess what you f***** up
So you go in the stocks for a week
And then everybody hit you with tomatoes and s***
And then we'll see
If it's a misspeaking if you do it again
Can I request that the tomatoes be soaked in booze
Consider consider Racing for all of our stocks clients
So again
More more setting the table
I don't care
Don't matter
This is so
Clear
It's so obvious
But that's a big reason
But the court said
You cannot argue
But this is flooded
And that was
Didn't provide additional Finance
Across-the-board
I hope that all of you understand
So it looks even made a bit of a mistake there
He says. I'm not saying that mistakes weren't made across-the-board which tells me very clearly that he understands that action.
Alexander's lawyers made during the discovery process led to the default
Consequences
As a principal
Right now he was just trying to hand wave that away and encourage this adolescent audience from giving any validity to peep
People who would tell them
The default was very much earned
He's basically doing PR work for 4
Ridiculous mistakes were made on both side
Mistakes were that Alex made
Because it's going to be a mountain of them it's going to be
Enough to very clearly justify
A default yeah I mean it is you know what we talked about it with Liz just a little bit but but that
Idea of like when Alex is in the courtroom not allowed to do Alex shirt
People aren't
Convinced by Alex Chet you know
Like it's because of the priming you know like Crowder is
Climbing people if you just
Talk to Alex cold total
Just a basic conversation what the f*** is this guy talking to me why you bring up Hillary
Or even like these people are so young or watching
Who's Hillary what is happened
So Steve has some interesting thoughts about the idea of the bank
You are at a point in this country
Where you are paying tax
Fund
Of food
From the mouse
All under the guise of
First Amendment only protects
The governor
Stopping you
From us
Bethel
The government
But I think token
Shouldn't jpmorgan's njp
BJ's
What are the
These things are all these
Conglomerate
If they're back
Spell guarantee
A billions of dollars
Inflation
Hundreds of
Trillion dollars
In taxpayer dollars
Are they allowed to deny
Your fundamental Khan
Constitutional rights
What point do we set up
Business
From government even know what the point is here and I think the only way that this argument actually works is if Steven
When is advocating nationalizing the bank I know that he's not
Cuz that's some straight-up Lennon chip you f****** moron don't know if
Like the bank again I got to get government money means that they're Bound by all the rules the government entities are
If we were to nationalize the banks have to follow the same
Guidelines of vop
Like he doesn't get that at all
Like zero awareness of what he's actually advocating for is
He's such a piece of s*** he's gone through to the other side is like
See the problem with cancel culture
Is we need to nationalize the banking system
If you take this
Thought a little bit further you also start to understand how dumb like his version of it is
I guess it's that if they take tax dollars
Then they're Bound by those rules
What are people are on Social Security do they have to follow all the government's guidelines
Or what about farmers who take subsidies do you know like any like you want everybody who takes any kind of
Something from the government
To now be beholden to all the same rules cuz then
How do we get into a really weird play
Right right I think I think what we're seeing is what happened
Two people when they're allowed to speak
By themselves
With no disagreements
And they aren't capable of disagreeing with themselves do not omit from like 1 I have a thought that's that dumb
Another part of my brain will be like don't say that out loud
MLB like why shouldn't I say that loud it'll have a really good point I'll be like good call
He doesn't have that he doesn't have any just Talks by himself so nobody's like
Stop it that's dumb
Well the first thing that happens when you're in that kind of a predicament is you start to wear shoulder holsters
For no reason
Second thing that happened
Is he at you you had up still can't believe that I understand that you're describing something that has to be real
I'm seeing it as a cartoon
Okay
I don't know their names I don't remember them cuz I don't care and
Hey baby have a little bit of rap
You know they sit down and they they really work out some of the issues
You know they talk like you are setting me up for Disaster One trial husband
Oh my God no
By the way they're doing
Isn't it
Just guilty and
Let me know when we have the
Maybe some fat
Facts about Sutherland Springs
American history
Okay so I guess they just want
Death penalty which is pretty anti-government as a whole but I guess they want death metal
Also don't want to process because they just want you to be found guilty and have death penalty
Has anybody ever stopped
To think about
What these people would do if they could write the Constitution again to be a mess can you imagine what do they say
Government does
Is the first question that I have to have nothing but
Hilliard everything and also I want them to be able to kill me but as long as I
I'm the only person who can decide
Why is that always be under pending I don't want no text
I want the government to not existed also to kill people I don't like
One of the things that I think is really funny to is it Steven realizes mid-sentence of the Las Vegas shooter is dead
For what it's worth the perpetrator the Sutherland Springs shooting is also.
There's plenty of information available about both of these events and Stephen would like to take the time to read
I would
Explain things to him if he brought up specific points I would be happy to get it to it but
He just says the names of the shooting
A man pretends there's a cover-up so
I got nothing I mean because we're useless show
Okay teleporter
Give it to me and I just tackle people
Whenever they say dumb s*** like I become that I don't have I'm not a superhero I don't solve problems
I will just show up immediately after Steven Crowder says something insane like that
Tackle him and then teleport away
And I feel like that's a worthy Noble got arrested for assault but that away that
Trial be really interesting because I did well
Even if you did it
Write the prosecution would have to deal with the fact that you teleported
Riverview teleported away
So they are apparently doing some shows from live shows
And
There's a plug 41 at isn't it kind of lost my interest in this show is a whole
Think this feels a little bit racist
Baltimore December 3rd
We couldn't find a venue Indy
DC sorry
That is Baltimore but hey at least
Haiti
DC
Or DC
The Baltimore's worsened
It's DC without a
Well I mean
And you can go to us
Yikes
I don't feel good
What
Do you think these three dudes
Associate with Haiti Baltimore and DC
What do you think is bear like
When they open their minds i2c
Things that they associate with Baltimore DC and Haiti
It's
Celebrity visits of the people little butt
Come on be Riot quiet part that's the quiet
Close the book on it
Demeanor jokes there joking you're going on a comedy tour
So Alex shows up
And
He's he's a pro
Mr. Jones OKC that's
I see that smirk what were you saying was that a dirty joke
No I said I'm really jealous of that shirt I'm going to rip it off make my own copy
Well I got the
Come on now well then now it's now then
That is the coolest shirt I've seen yet
Absolutely
What you're talkin about a Samsung
I'd love to give her by the inch
Baseball
Really happen with the case
Where it's going
Okay to steamroll him
And the second thing is awesome
Is right when he comes out the gate
Alex
Wider Steven with like at the great shirt and also establishes himself as an alpha by saying I'm going to steal your shirt
To steamroll him and Steve it has to be like hold on.
It is it is interesting the way he both tries to acknowledge that he's not going to win the steamroll comp comp
Rotation and at the same time trying to stablish dominance on his own show by saying I'm going to let you
Steamroll me Island
Haha well done steamrolling competition against the bullhorn
Trainer
That is Alex Jones expert
He wants to pretend to be a host in some ways is because he knows who Alex is he knows how
We communicate
And he also knows that without guidance
Alex is going to say
Just whatever the f*** you want
And it's not going to be a useful interview her.
And he's going to do the thing that he's
Trying to tell people right now that he has apologized for
People that defame the you don't know if he is or not there's a danger
Do you want to have some guy real
Right and that's kind of what Stevens
Aw to leave this right now but
I think this is pivotal
And we've done several
Multi hour-long show
But for some reason this gets
And I want you to correct me if I
Sew in
As an example
Sandy Hook
You tormented
Call them out by name
You continually harassed
From what I understand I have
Confront
Misquoting
You admitted you were wrong
And you apologize
Cuz I still want to go out
Can you talk about that
Tiffany Adam father
That you said
On Father's Day I want to reach out to the parent
Horrible tragedy in Newtown Connecticut
And give you my
Sincere
You said that right
Okay y'all like to reach out
To any of the parents who lost a child
Newtown to invite
Going to contact me to open a dialogue
Because I think
It's really essential we do that instead of letting the main
Mainstream media mister
Then things and really try and drive
Destination
Apart you said
Before they said
Yes before they sued
And then in 29
19 a deposition
And I myself
I've almost
Like a fun fact
This is my password
Thought everything was staged
Even though I
I've now learned
A lot of times
The things aren't steak
And I'm not saying
To embarrass you
You were clearing that you have
Change of heart or you believe that you were wrong or
You believe you made him
Admirable and I
Think the fact that they want to browbeat
That is what is so scary
Steven sure does seem to be ignoring the fact that and Alex's video that was titled his final statement on Sandy Hook he literally
He said quote
If children were lost in Sandy Hook my heart goes out to each and every one of those parents of the people who say they're Para
Prince that I see on the news
The only problem is I've seen a lot of soap operas and I've seen actors before and I know when I'm watching a movie and when I watch
Watching Something Real
That was in the late 2016
I want to only set the things that Stephens reading because of the Megyn Kelly interview that was about to come out
Alex has got come out around Father's Day and Neil heslin was going to be interviewed and it so he's trying to get ahead of any controversy
You do still repeating the basic conspiracy theories about the shooting at this point just holding back something
Did he thought could be legally actionable
Stevens also ignoring after this point Owen Shroyer did his video about how Neil heslin couldn't have held his son
After the shooting and Alex reported on that
Which is really does Undo any Goodwill that he might want to pretend he has from his feigned apology
Stevens also ignoring that in October 2017 Alex said quote it's as phony as a three-dollar bill with Sienna and doing
Fake newscast in blue screen
Alex is 70 think Sandy Hook probably was fake at least twice on air while the trials have been on go
Including once in the last two weeks
Google good'n'fun to create the strongman versions of What Alex actually did and the reason he's facing consequences but it's not
Real
Stephen knows it's not real but Alex's existence is pretty helpful for his brand so we pretend this
And you know the people who are watching Steven so probably
Don't have any interest in
Debunking this nonsense hoodies
Feeding them yeah if you
If you're going to bring up the deposition
And you're going to quote Alex from the deposition
That deposition
Convinces me
But Alex is guilty of all the things
Well he's not quoting the deposition you quoting like an article about it probably because of something
That's a lot of media Outlets like pull out
Deposition
He's not actually aware of anything that I was disgusted like a position
Again I think
I can never prove this
But I think there's a vested interest in being willfully ignorant among a lot of people like
Stephen because if he had to
Cope with
Cope's the wrong word
If you had to accept publicly that he was aware
The depositions of the things that were responsible for
Rationalizing and justifying those things
And he couldn't do that
You would have to be f***** up real bad you're a piece of s***
No it is it is fascinating because these f****** piece of s*** who are trying to avoid defense
Galaxy avoid
You know waiting into having to defend Alex's actual Behavior
If they were on the jury they be like yeah this guy's got a f****** go
You know like without the ability to avoid acknowledging what is actually happening
Without the ability to
To deny it
When you are forced to look at directly into the eye everyday 45 f****** week
Yeah I know what he did and I think that's one of the reasons I think Bobby Barnes is such a
But assholes
He knows he was in one of the depositions that was their lawyer
Still pretending
Oh I don't understand why any of this is happening just cruising railroad tracks
There is no deniability from Barnes whatsoever because
Honestly Barnes was probably looking at that billion dollar judgment and going mad
I wish I had been a competent enough lawyer for them to hire me
So I could have sued Alex Jones her a f****** billion dollars
I wish that I could be a competent enough lawyer to have stayed Alex's lawyer to the point where I live
Is a billion dollar verdict could get so much attention
I'll be all over the place
Lighting about everything
Anyway Alex is allowed to tell his version
Of events
What do you know it's all bulshit
Information
Sandy Hook
The huge political event Obama has of the White House
Joint on I-10
And then about a year after it
Professor
People
Incredible
Come out.
Wolfgang halbig
Didn't exist
So I did 45 programming
2000 +
Question Maybe
Google oh s*** thought it might be fake on the day of the shooting on his show
James Tracy Professor that he's talking about was first on Infowars on January 18th 2013
Not your later. Years later
Wolfgang halbig didn't show up until later that is fair
I need the school safety officer that I was referencing but Alex is completely ignoring
Steve pieczenik
Steve was coming on Alex's show saying no one died at the
The school on March
Within March
2013 when he was pretending to be a reporter on the scene of the DMZ
Alex's timelines all screwed up because he's just conveying his well-rehearsed self-defense version of events
Steven is a shity interviewer and he has no interest in calling Alex out so this timeline will stand to be presented to his giant
Impressionable audience
As gospel and it's just not true if you had any interest in pursuing the truth he would have familiarized himself
With these things
And pointed out the
How many points at which Alex's story diverges from reality
Stop
Who helped him
Who helped him killed all those kids
Did you just say right now
That you still found time immediately that was
What is suspicion
I think you're saying in like December 2012 that's what it is that's where he's at
I'll give you the latest
Snooze and get to the latest thing
Going on what they're planning all right I feel like he just did it again but I could have I could have poor
Structure or he could
Yeah it's a little bit up in the air is I've listened to this and I'm pretty confident that this is all electric
Okay
But yeah it look is all Hillary man
Hillary
Trump's brain
Wild guy
Pizza pop
People support Trump
Let's make him a liability
He said out of context
And run tens of millions of TV ads
Trump
Using Alex
Spring
And one thing one thing just to make
Is
Again for the YouTube.
You what you were saying me
The weather forecast
Be credible and then you didn't have the money show anymore
You did say maybe
Just again to be clear
You after
Word said no it was not
I was wrong
There's a load of s*** and honestly I think if they needed to find the worst stuff Alex's said this is definitely up there
But they could have come up with a much broader campaign for Hillary to use
Throwing some of his dehumanizing racism is violent misogyny and homophobia is incitement of violence towards Muslim
Alex is going to deep bench of horrible things Hillary could have attacked if that was the game that you was trying to play
Also Stephen knows damn well that I was didn't take that maybe the shooting was staged
Alex literally said multiple times that the shooting was totally fake with Act
Steven is softening that reality so it's easier for his audience to give Alex a pass and rationalize his actions
He's selling his audience on Alex
It's a
Concerted effort
And it's done by obscuring reality
I mean I just don't understand it
Because
There I mean it's just a bad idea I feel like the right move here if you're a piece of s*** like
Crowder one of these other guys
Is 2
F****** stab Alex in the back and then carve up izadi
Like I don't understand why
Why you're even trying this b*******
Yeah I think you don't have any loyalty to him he doesn't have any loyalty to you I think
Steven probably thinks that there is a way that this can raise his own profile maybe get some of Alex's audience
To him but a Fool's errand because Alex is audience
Like they're not going
Anybody who
Is susceptible to like maybe being interested in Crowder and listen to Alex already listen to grow
There are like Old-Timers who live in Shacks, Montana
Short right I mean not going to like your dumb
Childish comedy show
I don't know I think
I just meant as like an ecosystem you do not necessarily just crowd
Whole shabang like they're Shapiro and its backing all of them if we're smart
What he would maybe try to do is insinuate himself even more with Alex
And get involved with like the infrastructure part of banned. Video and that kind of thing
Ben and try and use it as a like
A reinforcing misinformation
YouTube
Because as it stands now there is
A
Shallow depth
Of anything interesting on their there's plenty of content and there's a load of b*******
Steven is like I don't think
It's in his best interest necessarily to be hooked with
Glenn Beck
With the blaze stuff but maybe there's some good money there
But in terms of like if you want some of Alex's audien
Internet stuff
He wants to create like more of a
Space would be the thing you do some of the other weirdos
But actually hold on
Miller Place in three years that we are right now and I don't think that's even close to pause
But I guess I maybe
Don't agree with myself either cuz censored.tv around
Not a lot going on there
Maybe nevermind I was going to say he could go to like try and help build up cozy Nick Fuentes a servicemen
It doesn't work.
What's this
Yeah definitely
Yeah I don't know
It's it can't can't help it
I think it's all stupid but Alex just as an out-and-out liar
So show it
420 15 + 20
16-week check the record
I never talked about it one time
This is a car baby it's
Shut up I don't want
I think about that
Some of the folks
Even crazier
Just regulate
Ensure
Indeed
I didn't put me on the map
I barely ever covered it
Hillary
Blows it up
Cause celeb for dinner
Bring back all the gun control and now attached
Free speech
Trump
Crazier
His own elaborate plot Hillary launch to attack Trump and then Trump want it seems like it really wouldn't do anything to get
Continue attacking Alex
The gold would have been to use Alex's toxicity to sway the electorate away from
Contraband wants Trump has one that's about it in terms of Voters
Doesn't make sense
Unless you're just desperate to defend yourself using bulshit fantasy-world nonsense
Stop talking about Sandy Hook
26th 2015 squarely in the window he's claiming you never brought it up
In my opinion something really
Thanks about this entire situation
I don't
I can't even really
Think of a mass shooting quote-unquote or a hype
Dial shooting like this
That didn't
Seemed like there was something more going on
I was rfkr the situation
We caught them
It just isn't real
I don't know what specifically happened
But the official story is a fairy tale
Stock isn't real
And that is a giant
Theater operation complete with blue screens
And now even Rob who's Uncle
Retired FBI works for big company
We have a reporter up there
Covering something up
Is a reporter there that there was dampened by the way
Go fuc yourself Alex stop talking to the people who promoted the crisis actors s***
Steve
Was a guest until he and Alex got into a fight about Steve pushing qanon s*** during the aftermath of the 2020 election
How much is a liar and these are easily demonstrable lies if Steven cared at all to protect his audience from afro
You have a responsibility to them
Lili neglecting that which is shameful
I'm here so here's what I actually think about your talk about like
You know why not just carve up Alex's audien
I think that for someone like Steven there's probably an interest in preserving Alex if you can
Suge Knight is because he is worse than you
Presumably he's worse than you if only because like you're still on YouTube
Right
So as long as Alex's there
The lot of people will think there's a bigger issue than Steven Crowder
Still in the same way that
You you hear people even Tucker say like
Little bikes great replacement Theory isn't crazy thought Alex Jones s*** exist as
I'm not him example
They're broken shield
Yeah
Yeah I think that's probably a way to look at it
So Alex Azar
Piazza
Steve's going to let him say it
Dozens of Correction
Apologies
One of them there
Then they sue me
In 2008
A-Team
Discovery we give them all the emails all the time
Premeditated
Got it wrong on purpose
And so both Democrat
Connected judges
Republican George W bush
They default me
Milazzo Alex
For a second
Globalist
Not allowed
To defend myself
The judge actually says
You can't sell your back rub
Got all that
But
There is no pushback there's no
Discussion of what these things are there's no reason to
Sokai Crowder wants to know like real seriously
Did you use these peoples names
Did you ever call the parents out by name on air
They were
Their children
Call them out
Only Robbie Parker
And
Afterbirth
That that he staged
This club
Viral clip
People say this guy
Looks fake
And so I said yeah it doesn't like acting to me but he's
That's not true and
Hair salons name was said on Infowars Posner
And also intentional infliction of emotional distress doesn't require you say people's names
Constantly screaming about how some people should die
Because they changed their pronouns
And yet somehow they're going to try and pretends that pronouns cannot refer to people
Right you have to say their name like a magic
Spell you have to sew it in
To your f******
Piece of paper with Silver Thread Dan obviously otherwise it's not defamation and when you say you like the same
Please if you're one of the members of one of the families you can't consider yourself part of that group
That's how words were no damn
So Alex
Tries to explain it really wants to explain that
Because it's kind of important
Fully complied with discovery
People will say we're the reason you were lying
It was a default
You didn't provide
The evidence
Give me pray specific not just
You did
Provide in Handover lot of
What did you end up with
Because I did have fun
I certainly the text
When I was watching the trial a would say well a
Actually they didn't hand over for example
Call the Alexa report
Supposed to Google
What
Kind of evidence
Just give me some examples of
But you did Handover
Did you hand over Financial.
Related
Did you hand over doctor
Related to
Traffic
And revenues
To some degree
Achoo an extreme degree the most ever given over in a civil defamation
Albany lawyers
Provide is my
Accurate information
I'm just saying this because
People try
On the right will say when you get sushi
She complied rings
Discovery
What
In the fuc
Are they closing
You didn't provide
So that you are not allowed
How to defend yourself
Let me answer that question and then I want to get into people
They claimed
That
Because we did so much
Discovery
Person they were
Deposing give them orders
So they say all out of the 200,000 emails you Davidson
And what is Discovery match
Little weird gacha
Give me the Google Analytics
Ma'am
Search box
For the back end of Google
We never paid for it
We barely ever used it we start for Google Analytics
One Rider
And one other person in the in the group that had
Give them what we had in our
About Google Analytics
Kegel exercise
I want you to give me the Google
You say okay what do you want me to search in Google
No
Give me the Google
Some of those
Instances of
Google analytics over they go get my traffic we're getting from this Sandy Hook
Article
It's even really wanted to be prepared to ask this question and respond appropriately to Alex's answer he should have read the order for the day
Default judgment
It spells everything out
There were request for production that Alex and never even responded
To their request
Stupidest people for depositions that were ignored
Alex
Peterlee cycle
Completely unprepared people to deposition does corporate Representatives
That's just the surface
How much do turnover big batches of documents but he had a habit of doing that just before hearings about his face
Turn over documents
So we can avoid consequences wow overwhelming the plaintiff's with tons of unrelated s***
Even these tranches weren't satisfactory to what he was obligated
Did the turnover though and it didn't really help
In the Judgment that you discuss how they tried to resolve the problem through fines and sanctioned but it was clear that had no effect on
Abuse of the discovery process
He has too much money to be impacted by whatever find the court could impose so it was a dead end
Stephen doesn't care about the reality
Euro the truth
He's just asking questions to allow Alex to give his boilerplate rehearsed answer and make it look like Steven was asking tough questions
This is a charade
That is match to exonerate Alex and Eliza Stephens audience
Hard because
The real
The truth of it is like that
All the hymn be like I'm not allowed to say I'm innocent I'm not allowed to say I'm all this stuff
And it's like
That's your fault
And the reason that you weren't allowed to say it is because if you did
Sooner or later you would have to go to jail
We're being nice to you
By keeping you
This is this is like you going bowling with rails
That's the point here
It's cuz you are going to be a gutter ball and then go to jail we're saving your life man
You had practice bowling
But in this matter for you at Whitney's arrest
Exactly
Stephen this is lost control of the shuttles
Completely taken over
I was just saying I don't think that though
You know
What is closed
This is the album
Next Level garbage
Texas Secretary of State Alex Jones Unleashed
Hell on our election
Here's another one
Bubble Blast nuts
Resume
Killing everybody
Alex is just doing his show I'm waiting for him to do and he's calling for overhead
This is ridiculous
Alex Jones Show
That is so funny
Also we got these coins
No longer a fundraiser
So Alex believes that this is overkill
I meant Steven has some harsh words for the so-called Brave conservative
Overkill
Having a temper tantrum
They want to scare everybody else too
Lawyers to file lawsuit
I really
It's so frustrating to be kind of
Only have my show that's
Department
It's very hard actually
Alex
Bishop is cowardice
You at your your night
Stations Odyssey off
Yeah I would say I wouldn't say
Remember I told you I'm a lie on the shows
I don't like that
You sometimes throw up in fighting
Remember you saying you know what I used to do that more
And I decided the left is more important
Strongest
Compelled to have you on because
Some of the biggest figures in our movement
By the way
Agreed with all of
Some of your corner
Cuz I thought were incorrect
They didn't have
It is Santa
Cowardice
Let me translate what Steven saying they're about the infighting among conservatives
Alex I work for Glenn Beck
Stop being also Steven you have to understand
A lot of those other conservative Outlets are really busy running damage control for Tucker's Kanye West interview at the moment
A lot of them just don't have the juice to throw Alex into the mix and try and deal with that both
Protecting against the Ravens
Anti-Semitism in our party and protecting against Alex's
And more
It is weird
I wonder if Joe watch some of the trial and realize that Alex lied to his face about what he said about Sandy Hook
That'll be fun if I like Joe started to get the picture that Alex is using him and see what develops from there
I'm not optimistic that's going to happen
The trial it would be really hard to come away from it
Thinking that Alex did not lie to your f******
Yeah but you still got to realize he's a fun guy really funny
Do you know what this reminds me of this reminds me so much of walking into a Dunkin Donuts
In like f******
They are around
Whatever
And there's two old guys sitting in that way right inside the door so you can see him through the window
And they're arguing about a parking
Ticket and he's like
Man
I didn't park there I'm telling you and you know the guy's lying I'm walking in there trying to buy coffee for Tuesday
Second I want to turn around be like dude
Just pay the parking ticket you're a f****** liar obviously you
And the other guys like yeah you're totally right man they shouldn't be able to do that
One of those guys is Rogan
Okay
Just making sure no I think I'm talking about Crowder and Alex right now
Okay who's Rogan
Izzy the donut Rogan would be a delicious donut
So we got a question for Alex
If we got to find out if he's scared
Let me ask you
Really
Anytime
I am way more scared about the direction
Countries going into
The formula
Everybody I mean
We're coming
Everybody now with this model
I'm not even got the Republican Secretary of State
In Texas
Republicans
Give me a break
The rhinos neocon
The rabbit left Allied together
The populist
Rising
Nationalist America
Score peacefully crying
Concerned about nuclear war
I'm way more
Hawaiian places going to wait accelerate store
Walmart Republicans and Bob way
10 years
Is there such a place in a billion dollars will be like
$1,000
Current rate
No I'm not scared
I am
Disgusted
Proud of myself
Tasha but I was wrong
The strawman
They sat there and had a lot of
Suppress the truth
Tell him I was guilty
Where does kangaroo court
Try myself.
Call
Children
The country in the future
Because of the rabbit
Acceleration
Total and complete corruption
Wow that's
That's quite a answer to are you scared
I don't know if yes
I feel like from
Numbers that I was seeing the inflation started
To turn around
And I don't know if we're going to end up in a Weimar Germany situation
We're not going to go Zimbabwe baby
I mean if I read everything correctly I feel like there's a difference between like radical out of
Control inflation and all of these businesses being like who they're talking about inflation we can charge an extra two bucks
Get some of this is a little bit hard to disaggregate from each other some of these forces
But yeah I don't I don't think that's
The path we're heading on and also I think that nuclear war was supposed to have already started by now based on Alex's project
So I guess
You should probably be more concerned about his own personal matters they fixing pretty severe
Is it still going to be an albatross over your neck buddy
What are the co-hosts
Ask that was a very important question that is
What's up with the appeal how is that going to work right
I am you'll notice over the course of the maybe next
Three Clips Alex
Can't answer specific
Yasso
You said earlier that
And why do you think
It will be over time
This faith in the
Excellent question
I have talked to dozens
Very well-known
Lawyers
Country
Former judges
Anna New York
Federal and state
This is the most
Insane craziness
They've ever seen
Alright so your lawyer who lost this case for you is talking to other people alleged
Woodley
That this s*** is crazy
How you're going to win the appeal
Okay
So there's no ground
Forgiven for what the appeal with the argument is why they Merit and appeal other than a come on
Yeah that's fine
Alex like legit seems to believe that he can just pay for the appeal he will magically win
America's gone and completely done
Orion Texas
In Connecticut if I have the money for the
Right now
Because they are so scared
But if there's any jokes
2 /
Orthoconnecticut
Supreme Court of the US Supreme Court
Got over
Turn this
Cuz the Deep state
Brigade
They're coming after everyone with this
Just like when I got
Court
You're saying why you believe it
Will be overturned
I don't know the fix is in that high
Oh I see control all the district attorneys in America and all the judges and everything
I will also the US Supreme Court is entirely blackmail died by Chinese spies
Everything I hoped they would
Do is also definitely run by the Chinese billionaires
Yeah this is fun I mean it's just Alex trying to be like
Yeah you should still give me money cuz I'm going to find a way to launder it during the appeals process
Problem is
The problem is for Alex is that
In a very real way this is an apolitical case for the loss of her lawyers
Judges and everything because they all have a vested interest in this being at least
The bottom
You know like all of them would prefer to have
From guardrails
So we don't have to go through like another
This judges waited three years to default judgment because
We just have never seen this s*** before so it helps if we have a baseline here of like
Guess what
Here's a person who's done this s*** before here's what we've done before
And now we don't have to do this again you know overnight
Yeah this is Alex's
Sort of path and is much as like Trump taught us so much about how
Much of the government is not codified how much of it is based on just like we all agree this is how humans behave
It's a good idea to do this right yeah Norms that we've protected us and kept things in
They aren't really real Alex's kind of revealing some of the similar stuff with the legal system
You could just not do stuff is unfortunate that it's like
Oh man we've accidentally created a system geared towards giving narcissistic psychopath
Lot of money and power
If they have the nerve and the shamelessness whatever the f*** I want to know
So I was continues to ramble about his not answer about how this feels going to work and then he forgets what
Question whose answer
But I know that
Okay they got their pound of Flesh
They brought back
Look up Sandy Hook
They made a bunch of money for their charity
Yeah those bad people made of butterflies
And now nobody knows who killed the kids
So
I think you answered the question
Why do you believe it will be overturned
Constitutional law
Bottled water
Absolutely
They have to
This is never before been done
Fun the way that Stevens interview-style seems to be like Alex's just rambling
I'll try not to this question for him
See if he can just say yes to my suggested answer and Alex does
I meant starts rambling some more it is it is fun that if you are
Steven Crowder you know you started the show by being like you weren't even allowed to make your defense
And then at the end of the show you have to be like oh no that
You shouldn't you should have been
Your defense is terrible and you're just not going to be able to answer yes or no question to save your life
F****** literally to save your life
You're f****** defenses Hillary
Go away
So Alex starts rambling about money and gets into his divorce for some reason it is weird
Are gross
What's 61 million
Dollars
I paid myself
Thousand
Dollars last year
It's all in the bankruptcy
Was there a year
Myself 12 million dollars
Absolutely the year
Of the divorce with my ex-wife
6 years ago
Thank God it was the Trump bear
All this extra money
What was she divorced
He goes to the process
The court made me pay her clothes to
Million dollars to buy her out of the company
For 13 years
Show the 11 year
About a million 2 million dollars a year
All the bills and stuff and legal crap
He had a
500% 400 % pay increase
Okay that makes sense
So weird
The 1-year I make $1000000
God takes room magically the money came in
By my ex-wife I'll accompany
So
I see you at
And we all struggle with this right
And it's sad
But you absolutely
Deserve to earn
You have millions
People who are listening in the amount of
What I do here as well
Conservatives are the only ones
Surprise me
People support free enterprise
We feel like
Because our audience
Don't get mad at me because
I make this money
Because it's you
One you're making
12 million
A several hundred million dollar judgment
You know who makes 12 a.m.
Every single year
No one cares
Explain that Dynamic little better than Steven
You know Alex do this song and dance because they know that they're f****** over their audience
They have to rationalize the money they make because it's an insane amount and they earn it by exploiting their audiences fear and anger
And monetizing that while putting vulnerable People In Harm's Way
And they do
No work and they sell
Garbage
Absolutely
Garbage didn't know preparation for this interview he has no idea the subject that he's even covering
There's no work that goes into this other than ripping dumb jokes
They know that they don't do s*** whether it's conscious or not if that's another question about whether or not that's why they have two rash
Nationalize this
And then before you know it there's a racist QVC
Fallon and Colbert make money but I am not sure how much but they don't get on their show every night and try to rationalize it because
Cuz we actually put on a show
They're entertainers doing a job not just complaining about how they're so persecuted
And this has nothing to do with political alignment
Do you think Jeff Foxworthy or Larry the Cable Guy or Ron White has to rationalize that they make millions of dollars
They don't because they're
Pallet makes it obvious why they make that much money
A con man like Alex and Steven it's different and that's why they do have to do this like
Oh hey look it's a hundred million dollars that I make metallic snowbigdeal.
Now there seems have a justify why thievery is okay
Steven doing like certainly legal fees legal to use
I mean I understand you have to explain why you have to rationalize their life
It gets confusing and suspicious right
I think the the thing that has stuck with me maybe most
Well no
There are few things that really stuck with me during the Texas trial
But one of them that I will never forget
Is when Owen was on the stand
And
He was being questioned about NPR
I knew that he was like
You know there are nonprofit right and Owen just said
But they still get paid don't they
Like
They don't understand the idea of not doing something for money
Sure I understand we're a nonprofit but this this is what actual not money is is what you're just there
Doing your job and your survival get out not to jump too far from what you're saying but like
Alex and other people in depositions have been very clear about like really do any preparation
No worries if they admitted that they did work it would show Malik make it look hard
To go to the documents
This is about how hard he works
And this is the most
I got a few
Documents
Important
Titus altogether
This is a major project
6 years to the last four
Would literally
Hundreds of Articles a week
Sometimes thousands
Every major News Channel
From HBO.
To PBS
Over Sandy Hook
Building a giant
Controversy
When I was not the Sandy Hook me up
Set the precedent
The Alex Jones president
Shut everybody else down. Let's talk about this being the bigger
Judgment
U.s. history by an order
Magnitude
Damn I wish
Survivors of eps
Receive 965 million
Exactly good point on Twitter
Elijah
Please write a tweet from Eliza
And Twitter sucks
Also a victim should be compensated
With you
It's unfortunate you also should
Stay out that billion dollars
We're good that we both agree this is not a zero-sum game
He also has money that should go elsewhere the both of you have money when you should have zero money
Call Eliza Eliza
So they have the episode with a q-and-a session
And it's actually only three questions
Questions for people in Steven Crowder mug Club
The first one
Yeah I'm a globular Jerry
Question for you Alex
What do you feel is inappropriate
Guilty man go free
Then one
Here's why Alex is the worst
Saying nothing is so dumb he should have said you pay for my meals for Life totally
Socrates something come on
What the f*** is wrong with the rare opportunity
You can actually pull this off. Yeah you are going to die
And you will not be remembered unless you pull something great
You got to do it
They got rid of body process
The judge found me guilty
They lied about it all
Exaggerated
I never said people there now
It's a lie
Setting a precedent to steal your rights
Listen to what you want to listen to
Decision
They're literally sending this up
To come after the General Public
An FBI agent
I never saw never covered
Never said his name
90 million dollars
Some people on the internet thought it didn't happen
Let me off the hook the more I think about it the more I appreciate the Ted guilty
Should be free
That's not a defense in a trial
Do you like elicit your honor
I did it
What can we know everyone did what they did
It's a good idea to let me go free
Otherwise
You might put that man in jail
No no no no. He say that you shouldn't be persecuted
Guilty people who goes free I feel like
The implication there he didn't intend
When did the right way maybe he's thinking he's being a good man but in this situation he really comes off sounding like he's Departed
Guilty
You should do a Socrates there's a problem with
Identify this is a lawsuit
Defamation Ira's that we're against
Then there's some other lawsuits
That you file
Sir Sir Alex did
That doesn't come up but other ones like the Covington Catholic charity and we do support these
S***
I need to talk about
And also it's important
You'll get lucky.
Saying
Do the write-up
The double standard
Because what about Nixon
They said his name
The president of the United
Red State
Associate
Specifically
With white supremacy
They said Nick
Nick Sandman
Was mocking some
Poor native
Hurricane Nathan
I prefer my negative
Nathan Phillips
They said he was mocking Nathan Phillips
You stirring
They did call out.
My name
Security
And if you'd like to go into hiding
There is a
You did not
Do that nigut repeated
All day
And all night not to mention what
Proceeded
Call right now
What is the media drumming up
Actual
Hatred
Never showed any evidence people to harass people
Somebody else did
So I accepted lying about there being no proof that he sent two people to do town then that led to harassment
Complete horseshit
Absolute also I guess if Stephen wants to be such a stickler about saying people's names which isn't necessary to prove intent
Emotional distress
He should support Alex paying Robbie Parker 120 million dollars
Does Alex did say his name repeatedly and repeatedly mocked a video of him
Memorial to his daughter
Are you a vase Crowder is going to put those as his benchmarks for when a case is
Acceptable
When we breach those bench
So
I mean if you want to save for some if that's your argument
That it's like a you have to say the name
When we reach that Benchmark benchmark
Somebody has to go into hiding
They wanted to hide it so guess what
We're done here I strongly disagree with the point the crabbers make
Perception he should be like all right Alex adhanom 900 million / 120
Like and if that was his perspective I would think I would be hilarious they would be very funny to me
There's no way for me to be intellectually consistent and an ox say
Spiritually physically in this world if I have any
Intellectual curiosity I can but I have to say that you have 120 million dollars to Robbie Parker
Do ya so next question
Of this Cuban a
Look up your Taylor
Color wants to know
If you only knew one true thing about you Alex
Among all these lies
I was going to be my last question
Boo
I mean look I'm a real person I mention
I'm trying to get through it all
I really
Stephen in the Caribbean
Righteous
The truth
Current
And just added to this is our rights
The Hollywood
Production
The
Action of what I supposedly did now bigger
I'm not the Sandy Hook died
I'm the guy that wrote the number one best-selling book in the world
Award for the world
That's why the global
Hate me
Exposing their
Exposing group
PayPal better back
By the way
You say we're going to find you
$2,500
I'm opposing
Authoritarianism
I'm a populist
Actually hear the real
Infowars.com
Dot-com 4/0
Go see the real life show
City archives
You should have little bitty twist
The corporate media
Globalist
The flag they want a cap
Anything else
Global of TuneIn
They get scared
Because I know what I'm talking about
When it comes to the mechanic
The New World Order
So it's interesting how Alex is one true thing contains multiple lies
That's a pretty amazing weird about that if you boil that down his thing about himself that you need to know
How is that he's amazing and he's so strong and smart that everything is just the globalist
It's because he's so strong and right and smart
School
Yeah what else is there to say he's going out saying like
I'm the best writer in the world I'm the best talker in the world I'm the most powerful man in the world because the most powerful
People are coming after me
Like
Jesus man the devil doesn't come out by the way in this interview weird cuz he seems really Central to the plot line
Also Alex's book has fallen to 322 on the Amazon charts
Number one just cuz you keep saying it
And it wasn't ever a number one another that's a problem to
So actually there's no question and that's it Steven has a question
And take some more chat
What are you doing here neck
That's really great question
My biggest enemy
Myself
Exhaust
Probably going on
Yeah I don't think I put one
Little bit of the marijuana
Mercy movie
Butts
Stop their butt
Long story short
He's just doing it to test the potency cuz soros's weaponized marijuana
Just weaponize marijuana houses smoking sometimes two times a week just for fun
To hang out with his buddy single-use maybe not too worried about that maybe that's not a lot. A real thing
International
It's here and you just forget about
It's the most important
Fight in the world we have to fight against the globalist
Loser drugs in there
Smoking cigarettes is going to be good for him
That's not good
Who was outside
Burning 1 p.m.
So
Stephen doesn't want to question though about what's next
Yeah ibib when he said long story short I wanted to throw up
Cuz that was a short story that
Been very long
What's next
Steven basically just has to pull teeth
To get that out of
Stop their butt
Long story short
I need to text game plan Alex
Obscure Hobbies
All the trendy liberal
The police state
Free Speech I'm the real Rebel
Infowars
Steven Crowder
We are the rebels We Are The Outlaws we are
We are the counterculture not them and
We are the counterculture
Independent
Media arts
Futurama
Just America
Find out
All the sticks
About infowars.com
So it sounds like what you're saying
Your next step
And Alex
You know I have a lot left
What's the number to SEPTA
I think
You get some rest
Recoup and come back
I'm more ADHD when I
Exhaust
Apologize
My brain's gone right now so yes
I realize
I realize they want to
I realize that I'm never going to quit
Because this is a battle of wills
I also understand
Take myself out of the game by
Fryda burnout they win
So I am
Going to in the next
Fremont do something I never do
I'm going to take off
A week a month
The end of this month
November and December
I want to do it
Because I've got a rest
I got to stop drinking
I've got to stop
Recharge my batteries
My my daughter
Yuno gasai
My son
Recharge my batteries
Get back to family get
Back to God
Come Back Inn
2023 harder than ever
This is bulshit I mean I think you probably will take a week off in November and December for Thanksgiving and Christmas
Reply
Also like
We're supposed to be right on the cusp of nuclear war yeah I know
Focus
Yeah just do your job
Tell me what's real
Filling your world
You know who doesn't freak out like this
Other people who do daily shows
Mike
This is him
This is you just be healthier
Stop acting like this
Grow up
That's another thing to like
I don't know maybe I'm not cool and I've never really been that cool
I find it
Pathetic
To hear like
40 year olds
Talking about counterculture
But like
As I've gotten older
The interest in whether or not something is culture counterculture or any of that stuff got
Kind of become something that
Maybe has a little bit of like an artistic interest to me
But like
I don't know a lot of the aesthetic trappings and in the lot of that stuff I think is a little bit for the Youth
And
You can't be a rebel and have a hundred million dollars first off
That's not how that works
Fugazi wasn't cool and also had a 100 million dollars they were playing in the basement of a
Dilapidated
The church they were not
Doing they weren't doing Green Day Stadium
Green Day cannot be a rebel and f****** do Madison Square Garden that's not how that works you kind of lose the
The ability to have credibility of counterculture what is
You're not a rebel
Not how that works
When you have a
CNN level Studio that you're broadcasting from
Kind of tough to make that argument
A condemned building comedy show is a rebellious comedy show
Cultural cultural ISM can really fries
Being incredibly mainstream show in a baseball delete that is very possible for that to happen
But you're not going to see something that's wildly some versus at like the Laugh Factory
I know it's off
I don't want to poke I was a countercultural icon when i m c
Fright
I get I get what I want to say again and again maybe I'm a square but I
I cared a lot more about that when I was
19 I mean that that whole idea of selling out or anything along those lines
Who cares
I mean
Did Berry Gordy isn't around anymore you're going to sell out or whatever you know
It is
Disgusting
To think that
If you and I right now we're at any point in time like
Listen man
As we sit here in our f****** hoodies and
Tennis shoes like
Where are the true Rebels going outside
Helmets
That's not how it
Works now I sit in a fairly comfortable apartment having overdue to do this
Dishes
Surrounded by buttons
And I am neither culture nor counterculture
Berkeley instead of like
Forcing yourself to get rest or whatever the f*** you're talking about Alex grow up
Anyway
Steven touches on a interesting question and that is
Why aren't you on Rogan
You know what you just mentioned something
Joe
Told me I was like 2 years ago
Weather
Who's on I haven't heard that before a comedian
And then
I was just pretty obvious what's going on
It's a little too much heat
You got courage about the vax
Criticizing
He's not as hardcore scene
I'll just say it
Overall defense
Free Spades
And I just I just don't
Big joke
Handle it
What is it going to take
Brigiotta's be like I'm done with this what is it going to take. To take I'm done with your truck in Moline
Promoting you don't give him enough attention he whines and
Tell you you're a piece of s*** f*** off
Sneaky Snake I'm going to gut him like a pig let's talk about his kid
It's on a different show
Yeah any saying essentially
Hey listen
Joe's got some courage but that man's a coward at heart exactly
Outside of college meme I see you wearing that shoulder holster and I think
There's a man oh man I think that the Maltese Falcon is around the corner
Like about Rogan not having Imani it's totally cool
We're out of dinner about a month ago
And I just bet
You get on their explain thing
He just said Alex
Crisis going on
I'm not really worried about it
Obviously I'm the big interview he won
B-17
It's a big deal to have you on
I'm not worried about it
It's really a question
Giorgio's
You know yet to get a bunch of friends
I haven't got the whole podcast
Working on Dylan could have Ian
I'd love to grow it
The Purge scale
Steven Crowder
Today
And I'll take it ate all day over our enemies under the zero
Nothing but thankful to Joe
He's taken having me on
So you're more than that
You're also insulted
But I was going to tell you off everyone but it's private
The very same people trying to silence me
Some real
And you know I'm on that
You know I'm on that list
As well so I know we all deal with it end
Alabama Joe's getting and guess what so Stephen Stephen doesn't care cuz he attend
Bunch of loser
Yep
It's tough to it's tough to watch a show like this and not
Really feel sad
Yeah
This is sad
It's not good either like I would understand if something had like
Like an ethos that I disagreed with a lot of points that I didn't agree with right but like
If Steven Crowder was like he had a spark of real funny in them yeah or if there was like
An interesting angle and delivery on stuff and his co-host were worth a damn
And Sidekicks like
I would I would
Cedar Lake
I disagree with this I think it sucks but
They're doing a show
This just as bad
From all angles
Really bad
Yeah man
That is
It's just so sad it's so sad all of you are
Are adult men
Talking about how great you are to children
Better than Rogan
That is gross I'm so much more of a big strong boy than Rogan
So at the end here this is the last clip we've got
Cuz I got to go to mug Club
Which is the lake behind the pay wall segments and Alex
You know who's a rebel
A guy with a mug
Club club Alex's
Talking at the end about how he has to go to do his own show
So he's wasn't going to be on that for very long so I don't really care about what's behind the pay wall price
But it before they leave Alex tries to troll the media is there
Okay
Do you want war
Flooding you in funding you're one of the only
Professional people doing
Comedy anime analysis
He's better than the production of like these like
Budget 20 times your budget people
Because unless the real currency we all want
Infowars
Everybody
Steven Crowder
Who's got the
500 lb test
Alright marjos balls okay well Steven yours are bigger
Bigger and even more juicy
Well Josh
She did say you've been drinking too much and part of that
With the vet that I have the under under the cabin
Microwave I've learned my
Charger battery
Alex Jones in the robotic homosexual
All right look
When do I get my 900000000
For what
This is this is
Funny
Tell his his balls joke
And then say it's funny
That's a bad sign
That's not good no
I didn't know it was a joke
Might get her done back when I did stand up while it's funny
No.
This is like things are less effective when
You say like
I am doing this so the media will report on it
That's fun and sad also the thing that makes it funny is that both of them
Violently aggressive is that what's funny is that they can dip into the into there
They make that they make a joke of talking about Stevens balls because
It is gay to them
Right right
But I mean they know that
We just spent too much time with I don't know I don't know what people who aren't
It's funny really find funny you know it's funny to them because they're engaging in
Form of homophobia
Right from the target being hurt by homophobia
To them it's a transgressive concept
Someone saying that would blow their f****** minds into laughter
I get that but I don't get it I don't get it
Man I think that this would have been
Just a wave
Maybe quite a ways below like Andrew Dice Clay in the 80s
Rebellious
But I can still record still laughing
At things that are sophomores
But you just have to be good you have to be at there has to be
Cleverness there has to be Direction there has to be
AAA same tent or thought behind it are you know something along those lines
From the construction standpoint the joke is the media reports on this
Interview as
Alex likes
Stevens juicy balls
Right that's the
The the
Bmusic image is the news running that headline
I'll put the real joke is that the news isn't going to cover this at all this interview at all
It's Imagining the ways in which you are tricking the media into a troll headline
Doesn't come to that is it is very funny to listen to these guys imagine
How
They're out
PetSmart
Yeah that's very funny it's all it's all in there their game
Being
Yeah
So this suck time but I don't I don't want to listen to anymore stevencrowder very bad
Brutal probably not that much
Difference between
In terms of the stuff I think part of that is because
He clearly felt
The ability to steamroll Steven
Yeah that wasn't hard clips
I was not hard
So I think there is a sense that like all right I'm just going to do my show on his show
He can't handle me he's got no chance
Midas balls
Yeah it is
It is like
Who is like
Kicking a choirboy and then patting him on the head being like that you did such a great job getting kicked
Yeah but there really isn't a ton of like a
Message discrepancy it is just kind of like I've been wronged
I didn't get a trial Baba bother coming for you
Explain to me how
A man can insist
That he is both apologized and taken responsibility for his behavior
And yet
Still be like
Will they let you get nothing
That's Christopher Alex Club did not ask
The book club does not do a lot of follow-up
Another reason why he can have message discipline and stay with the same thing as easy as 140
Seems I can ask him if it's in no way a hostile environment I would say that Rogan
Is a more confrontational interviewer than pins
Just cuz he be like
Maybe say something funny about that
The Stephen did the same thing the Greenwald did which is like
Try to offer answers.
This would be a good answer if you want to just take the
Yeah it is he was massaging Alex's shoulders while you doing
In being interviewed while interviewing
Imagine
But until then
We have a website
Worldstar Fights
I saw your Tweet today the algorithm knows that I f****** hate gungrave
I get so mad
I will be back but until then I'm eom Leo mdci scar kind Wilfred Snapple Snapple of the Gravel Pit Bull
And now here comes
The sex robot
Alexandra Thurston color