Thank you, Knowledgebite.com.
It's time to pray.
I have great respect for knowledge.
Fight.
Knowledge Fight.
I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys.
Shang.
We are the bad guys.
Knowledge.
Dan and George.
Knowledge Fight.
Need money.
Knowledge.com, I love you.
Hey, everybody.
Welcome back knowledge, friend.
I'm Dan.
I'm Jordan.
We're a couple of dudes like to sit around, worship with the altar of Celine and talk a little bit about Alex Jones.
Oh, indeed we are.
Dan.
Jordan.
Dan, Jordan, quick question for you.
What's up? What's your bright spot today, buddy? My bright spot today, Jordan, is we have reached the end of sneak weekend.
Yes.
It's been long.
Yeah.
I'm thrilled that we had an opportunity to sit down and talk to Mark, please.
I think there's an argument that could be made that we could have put that all out on Monday or something.
Sure.
I just feel like things are coming so fast that we just got to keep moving.
The trial, the end of it, the verdict.
If we drag that out too long, we're going to end up still responding to it a month from now.
Yeah.
Generally speaking, I feel like most of our decisions over the past six years could have been argumented that they were not the right one.
And yet here we are.
So let's write it out.
It's debatable that we shouldn't be doing this.
I say let it ride.
That's where I'm at.
Yeah.
So I'm glad that sneak weekend was received well by the folks.
Appreciate all the very positive comments.
Overall, I have some other fun stuff that's going on that I can't really talk about right now.
I've seen a couple of great tweets, mostly memes, with animals in them.
I can't remember any of them specifically, but I remember, hey, that was fun.
Yeah.
This is an info.
Whereas you're not going to talk about a meme for the next 5 hours.
It doesn't prove anything, just that it was a cute anime.
It was cute.
I guess it's kind of vague, but that's my bright spot.
Sort of a combination gestalt, as Alex might say.
I was coming in here thinking very similarly as to what my bright spot was.
That kind of just a bit of an achievement, like an accomplishment, but at the same time unlocked.
Yeah.
It's just like we did it.
And now we get to keep doing stuff.
Indeed.
And so today, what I thought would be fun or something would be nice is to take a little bit of a trip off the beaten path.
Good call.
And instead of doing some of the things that we tend to do, like wacky Wednesday stuff or going to the past, I thought what we would do is talk about Alex Jones appearing as a guest on Stephen Crowder's show.
Louder with crowder.
Oh, my God.
So that is we're going to be covering today.
Oh, boy.
Just after he got hit with that billion.
It's right after it is.
So he knows that there's a billion on his head.
This is damage control time.
Right.
And one of the reasons that I chose to do this was you see how Alex responds on his show, and it's pretty duragur.
It's going to be the same thing over and over again.
It's going to be very repetitive.
We've heard him say that he didn't do anything on purpose.
And their name maybe there will be some slight variations, some interesting blow ups and what have you, but I wanted to see what it looks like when he's on a different platform trying to preach to a different audience.
Are we going to get a life? Very fragile.
He might be drunk.
There's no apples.
So we'll get down to business on this Jordan, but first, let's say hello to somebody wonk.
Oh, that's a great idea.
So first, Mike Best, thank you so much.
You're now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk, thank you very much.
Next, the ghost of Enyo, Morocconi, who's tired of hearing Alex Hugh's ecstasy of gold from The Good, the Bad and the Ugly coming out of ad breaks.
Thank you so much.
You're an alpoly walk.
I'm a policy walk.
Thank you very much.
Boogie was a ghost that's Halloween season.
That's very specific ghost.
Next wilford Snipple.
Snabble of the Brooklyn gripple.
Pipples Esquire.
Thank you so much.
You're an owl.
Policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much.
As a lawyer.
Yeah.
Next, I am not a Russian agent.
Svetlana.
Thank you so much.
You're an alpoly wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much.
And Eva, not Ava, thank you so much.
You're an alpoly wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much, Eva.
I'm still not convinced I pronounced it right.
Well, also, we got a technocrat in the mixture, so thank you so much to Hexacult.
You are now a technocrat.
I'm a policy wonk.
I have risen above my enemies.
I might quit tomorrow, actually.
I'm just going to take a little break.
You down a little breaky for me, and then we're going to come back and I'm going to start the show over.
I'm the devil.
I got to be taking over there.
Fuck you, fuck you.
I got plenty of words for you, but at the end of the day, fuck you in your new world order, and fuck the horse you rode in on and all your shit.
Maybe today's been almost broadcast.
Maybe I'll just be gone a month, maybe five years.
Maybe I'll walk out of here tomorrow and you never see me again.
That's really what I want to do.
I never want to come back here again.
I apologize to the crew and the listeners yesterday that I was legitimately having breakdowns on air.
I'll be better tomorrow, please.
Damn.
So I never really wanted to cover Stephen crowder, and we won't generally, but Alex was on his show to whine about the Connecticut verdict.
So I felt like it was important for us to see how Alex was dealing with that whole situation when he's in a new environment, in force broadcasts are primarily for the initiated, whereas something like going on Crowder is hopefully Roping in new people for him.
Right.
Of course, it would be better if he could go on Rogan, but that doesn't seem like it's happening.
So Crowder is going to have to do for now.
I've not sat down to watch a full episode of Crowder before his dumb show.
Louder with crowder.
Yeah.
I don't even know about that name.
I think that's a dumb name.
I have heard louder with crowder.
We've said the name Steven Crowder.
I still have no idea who he is, and I refuse to find out.
It infuriates me every time somebody says louder with crowder.
But, I mean, is it like he yells more than other people? Because I don't think that's I don't know.
I don't like it.
They just picked a word that rhymes with crowder.
With Crowder.
And he could have eaten stuff.
It would have been the same idea.
Yeah, he doesn't wear, like, more flamboyant outfits, like colorful loud suits.
I don't know.
I think it's a bad name.
See, what you do is you go way too far with it.
You know, you go rowdier with Crowdier, you go an extra step that makes everybody really uncomfortable, and that's the way you do it.
I was thinking, like, if I had a show where I did favors for people, I could say pleasing with Freezing.
With Freezing.
Yeah.
That would be okay.
I'm mad that I got there.
But if we call this show that, it wouldn't make sense, or if I tried to overthrow a government, I could be Treason with Freezing.
Sure.
But this show again, that name wouldn't work.
If I had a travel show, it could be Romes with Homes.
Definitely.
Or a bookshow tomes with homes.
OOH, that's a good one.
Yeah, I think I should have that show.
Yeah.
See, these work.
Yes, these make sense because they would be about the thing that they are.
It's good when a rhyme fits right.
It's silly when it's forced.
When I don't understand what Louder With Crowder means, he should have to be regularly a decibel level above other shows.
Yours, I demand.
Louder than him.
I demand.
So there's one thing that immediately jumped out to me watching the show, and that was that the show is very dumb.
Like, it's transparently dumb.
Arguments are based on false points, and the humor is painful.
The thing you have to realize when you watch this is that it's kind of supposed to be dumb.
The audience of the show is, as Steven Crowder has tweeted about before it's.
At least half of the audience is under 16.
So this show with children, and I haven't been able to confirm that figure in any way, but he said it, and I have no reason to doubt it.
He has the analytics.
Can you do that? I guess you can.
I feel like this is as bad as smoking.
Like pushing right wing bullshit to children is as bad as advertising for smoking.
To be fair, half of the audience is between 17 and 18.
I don't know.
Great.
There might be some adults in that.
Okay.
One of the reasons I've avoided doing too much about Crowder up till this point is that he has a lot of his content behind paywalls.
For instance, the last time Alex was on for his weird performatively masculine cigar club session, the first part of it was public, but then the rest of it that you'd actually want to watch is not.
We may be coming to a point where I stop over respecting these dingdongs intellectual property, but I don't think I'm quite there yet.
Steven crowder is repugnant.
He's a horrible person, and his career has been a shameful series of horrible embarrassments that he's been able to parlay into having a very successful YouTube talk show that appeals to kids with sophomoric racist jokes and sophomoric anti LGBTQ jokes.
I don't want to do too deep a dive on his trajectory, but here's a summation of his career path.
Okay.
He tried to be a standup comedian.
Buddy sucked at it.
So a right wing educator.
Griffith catching the attention of Fox News when he got punched in the face by a union protester who he was harassing.
Great.
This rose his stature, and he began making his own content, most notably a segment called Change My Mind, where he would show up at a college campus and sit at a table waiting for college students on their way to class to join him for a spirited debate.
That's that guy.
He's the meme of the guy with the shit.
Oh, my God.
Fuck that guy.
Yeah.
The college student was, of course, unprepared and probably late for class, and Steve could edit the videos however he wanted.
So the series was a big hit.
It kind of falls into the same vein as Mark Dyson's Man on the street segments, where he bothers drunk people on the boardwalk and then tries to make a political point out of it.
As his profile has grown, stephen has made a habit out of being a pile of shit, doing half cooked segments based on deeply racist and anti LGBTQ talking points that are easily debunkable and not persuasive at all.
Well, they're not persuasive at all to adults, I should say.
They all might be very convincing to a child who are naturally his target.
See, but that's the problem.
We understand that's the problem with the problem, because we know about it because of the smoking thing.
It's illegal to smoke.
It's illegal to advertise for children.
We got to figure this shit out.
In essence, his show is about taking extreme rightwing views and dangerous rightwing ideologues and laundering them so they can be enjoyed and accepted by high schoolers.
Basically.
I think he's one of the worst folks in this space.
But also, I don't know what our show can really add to that conversation.
If YouTube cared at all about the safety of the children and teens who use the platform, he would have been kicked off long ago.
And that's really, I think, probably the solution here.
If they want to do something about it.
He can't really do that much damage if he's just limited to being on Glenn Beck's Blaze network or his own thing, fine.
Limit his reach quite a bit.
Make it more difficult for kids to find it.
It's so weird.
That's like having a Hannah Montana show where they take the Montana part really literally.
And she's a white nationalist.
She's got a compound.
Yeah, exactly.
Hannah Montana.
And here, kids, first I'm going to transfer her into pop star, and then we're going to find out exactly how the great replacement theory really works.
Kids, with this happy song.
Yeah, I mean, like he's had Stefan Molyneux on.
Okay, well, then there we go.
To give you some idea of the people he's laundering, is Alex on at least multiple times.
I don't have a full guest list for him, but you don't really need one at certain point.
Noted.
Hilarious white nationalist Stefan Maldineu.
That's generous.
Yeah.
Anyway, in the aftermath of the Connecticut verdict, alex went on to discuss the situation with Steven.
And here we are to give you some sense of the scene.
Stephen is sitting in his studio at a desk with two louder with crowder mugs on it.
He sells mugs and he has this thing called the Mug Club.
So this is a very important piece of the tableau.
Oh, my God.
He's also wearing one of his own shirts because you always got to be pushing that merch, man.
Always be selling don't wear your own shirt.
And he's wearing an overtheshoulder holster, so you know that he loves guns.
I'm sorry, what? Yeah, he's wearing a holster like he's a police chief.
Where in the world is Carmen? San Diego.
You got to know that he's strapped and ready in case a duel breaks out during the show.
Listen up, gum shoes.
Also, there's another gun on the desk, so it's pretty.
What a fucking more pretty ridiculous.
Those are not loaded.
What's? Pathetic.
It might be projecting a little bit too much strength in bravado for me to take that at all seriously.
Indiana Jones alex is on towards the end of the show, but this whole episode is more or less about rationalizing Alex's verdict and complaining about it.
And it's titled exclusive Interview with Alex Jones.
This means war.
Exclamation point.
So to get a sense of the temperature, I wanted to start at the beginning and see the tone we're working with.
Although you will find out that I did not end up sticking to that.
Yeah, good call.
Skipped ahead to a while.
It showed up at a certain point.
I was like, this show's so dumb.
Listen, if you say failed comedian, I'm not interested.
And that's why I don't listen to our show.
So here's where we start off, and I think that this is some load of shit to start.
Hey, if I sound windy, it's because I've been running around here, we've been testing, making sure that everything works.
Look, Alex Jones on the show today, and I would appreciate look, I know that many of you have different opinions.
Let me just give you a little bit of a rundown here.
I was not an Alex Jones fan for a very long time.
I made it known I had criticized him here on this show, and I still have criticisms of them.
But we're at a point right now, and we'll be talking about this today.
We'll be showing you a montage of the end zone dance from not only the elites in Hollywood, not only the elites in media, but the elites in government.
Government officials actually championing this silencing real quick.
This is like a clip of Jimmy Kimmel making a joke and the government officials are jensaki tweeted something.
She's not even the press secretary anymore, and Alex made a big target out of her for a while.
I would not be surprised if she received quite a bit of harassment that probably wouldn't be legally actionable since she's a public figure, all that.
But yeah, they're making a bit of a professional, maybe a little bit more personal of speech.
And that is absolutely what it is.
Regardless of where you line up, there's an inflection point right now in this country.
And the reason that we're having Alex Jones on and we've had him on is because I hate seeing people being bullied.
This couldn't be further from the truth.
Steven loves a good bit of bullying, and he actually leads bullying campaigns sometimes, like he did in the case of Carlos Maza.
Also, Alex isn't being bullied, he's the bully.
And Steven's trying to launder that reality to his audience of children.
So they think that Alex is the victim here.
And I think that's shameful.
Also, Steven is saying that he has criticisms of Alex, and I think he's a coward.
List your criticisms.
Yeah.
What are they? Yes to his face.
Try that.
Yeah.
See if you get an answer on any of them.
The rest of the things that you like about him, see how long those survive after you give him one small criticism.
Well, I think that Alex would probably dodge and stuff because he needs someone like Stephen now.
He has like five plus million subscribers on YouTube.
Really? Yeah.
So Alex needs that kind of a platform because he's not going to get it from Rogen.
Right.
And there aren't a whole lot of other options that Alex has in terms of who is going to be a giant platform for me to go on.
I have to go start talking to Twitch Streamers.
Jesus.
Yeah.
Hassan have me on.
He's going to have to.
That's where he's going to be.
So I think that he could get away with voicing some of these criticisms to Alex, whatever they might be.
Sure.
But he wouldn't get any response that's meaningful or any resolution of these, of course, or even recognition of these criticisms.
No, they'd be a dodge.
I think that it would be far more meaningful for him to express what his misgivings are and what his criticisms are of Alex to the audience in a neutral environment where they could take those criticisms in and then decide, like, is that something I'm actually really concerned about too? Well, one of my criticisms maybe it's he lies all the time.
That could be an issue.
Well, if one of your criticisms prior to an interview is my interview subject is an inveterate and almost pathological liar, perhaps he will take those answers that he gives in the interview with a different grain of salt as opposed to if you didn't tell them that at all.
Right.
And I was thinking one of his sort of criticisms of Alex might be that he barely thinks that Muslims are human.
That's an issue.
But I think that Stephen's audience wouldn't have as much of a problem with that.
No, they'd be still.
So, you know, he tries to frame the interview in a particular way and obviously it's that Alex didn't know.
He didn't do that much wrong.
When you have someone like Alex Jones who if you've watched his career and I do consider him a friend now I will say this on a personal level, he's been around.
From what I know of him, he's a good man, a flawed man.
He's talked about it here on air.
To me it's refreshing when he's on air.
He was on air Nash Wednesday and said, maybe I drink a little too much and he'll tell you about his flaws.
But for a man who speaks publicly for hours on end and then misspeaks or gets something wrong and then apologizes and then is punished anyway and then the government jumps in.
People.
I guess former press secretary.
But current members of the government and entities who are backed by the government.
Be it banks.
Be it big tech organizations deciding to put you in stocks in the town square.
The message is really loud with crowd and I hope that you're hearing it.
If you make a mistake, not only is there a double standard which will talk about if you have a belief that other people find to be offensive and of course at the sliding scale, we know that we've gone further and further down the trail here.
Look behind you, there's a slippery slope.
Shut up.
Can you apologize? Shut the fuck up.
They only get worse.
What? I mean, then the left why is it left or right? They made it left or right.
This is tough.
This is fucking horrendous.
What just happened? People watch this shit? I guess so.
Oh my God.
What is wrong with me? Why is it why am I the weirdo here? That is horrendous.
Yeah, it's pretty bad.
But what he's doing here is a clear attempt to set the parameters of the conversations.
It's just being taken as gospel that Alex misspoke or got some things wrong.
He apologized and he's been punished anyway.
That's what all the episode will be in response to.
And because of that it's going to be meaningless.
If the basis and the foundation that you're building your house on is sand, you're not going to have a good house.
Yeah, it's not going to be a house that I'm even going to inspect.
I mean, because it's going to collapse.
Also, this stuff is already a little overdramatic.
Yeah.
A little while.
Dramatic on Crowder's part to put you in the stock if you disagree with them.
Here's the problem, okay? I feel like the stocks would have been a more effective response to Alex then what is happening right now if we had actually been like at the very beginning, like, hey, you've done fucked up.
You misspoke.
And maybe that's what happened.
Maybe you misspoke, but guess what? You fucked up.
So you go in the stocks for a week and then everybody hits you with tomatoes and shit and then we'll see if it's a misspeaking.
If you do it again.
Can I request that the tomatoes be soaked in booze? Yes you may.
OK.
Yes you may.
That's just a consideration.
That's a consideration for all of our stocks clients.
So again, more setting the table.
Sure.
I don't care if you agree with Alex Jones or not.
It doesn't matter.
And by the way, this is so clear, it's so obvious that that's a big reason that the court said you cannot argue that this is political persecution.
Do you understand? That was the trial was predicated, wasn't even allowed to argue that because it didn't provide additional finances.
I'm not saying mistakes weren't made across the board, but I hope that all of you understand.
So look, Steven made a bit of a mistake there.
He says, quote, I'm not saying that mistakes weren't made across the board, which tells me very clearly that he understands that actions Alex and his lawyers made during the discovery process led to the default.
Now, I'm against consequences as a principle, right? Yeah.
Stevens just trying to hand wave that away and encourage this adolescent audience from giving any validity to people who would tell them that the default was very much earned.
He's basically doing PR work for Alex and it's ridiculous if you have the awareness that mistakes were made on both sides.
Hey, let's talk about what those mistakes were that Alex made because it's going to be a mountain of them.
It's going to be enough to very clearly justify a default judgment.
Yeah, I mean, it is.
We talked about it with Liz just a little bit, but that idea of, like, when Alex is in the courtroom, not allowed to do Alex shit.
People aren't convinced by Alex shit.
It's because of the priming, like, crowder is priming people.
If you just talk to Alex Cold totally, it would not you be like, oh, fuck you.
You need to lose a billion dollars.
Just a basic conversation.
Just like, what the fuck is this guy talking about? What are you doing? Why are you bringing up Hillary? Leave me alone.
Or even like, these people are so young who are watching Steven.
They might be like who's? Hilary.
What is happening? So Steve has some interesting thoughts about the idea of debanking.
You are at a point in this country where you are paying taxes to fund the theft of food from the mouth of your kids, all under the guise of a First Amendment, only protects the government stopping you from saying something.
That's all it does.
It prevents the government from stopping you.
OK, by that same token, shouldn't JP Morgan, shouldn't JP Chase, whatever their abbreviation is, these things are all these giant conglomerates.
If they're backed by our tax dollars, they're guaranteed.
If they received hundreds of billions of dollars, and if you adjust for inflation the last few months, hundreds of treasury dollars in taxpayer dollars, are they allowed to deny you your fundamental constitutional rights? What point do we separate private business from government? I don't even know what the point is here.
And I think the only way that this argument actually works is if Stephen is advocating nationalizing.
What are you doing? Yeah, I know that he's not, because that's some straight up lemon judge, obviously.
You fucking moron.
I don't know if, like, the banking industry taking government money means that they're bound by all the rules the government entities are, but if we were to nationalize the banks, then you'd have a good argument here that they should have to follow the same guidelines of the yeah, he doesn't get that at all.
Like, zero awareness of what he's actually advocating for is he's such a piece of shit.
He's gone through to the other side.
He's like, See, the problem with cancel culture is we need to nationalize the banking system.
Is that what he's trying to say? I think that if you take this thought a little bit further, you also start to understand how dumb, like, his version of it is, which is like, I guess it's that if they take tax dollars, then they're bound by those rules.
What about people who are on Social Security? Do they have to follow all the government's guidelines? What do you do? Or what about farmers who take subsidies? Do you want everybody who takes any kind of thing from the government to now be beholden to all the same rules, because then we get into a really weird place.
Right.
I think what we're seeing is what happens to people when they're allowed to speak by themselves with no disagreement, and they aren't capable of disagreeing with themselves.
Do you know what I mean? Like, when I have a thought that's that dumb, another part of my brain will be like, don't say that out loud.
And then I'll be like, Why shouldn't I say that out loud? And it'll have a really good point, and I'll be like, Good call.
And then you say it out loud.
Yeah, well, obviously.
But I do it as a funny voice and I'll be fine.
But he doesn't have that.
He doesn't have it.
And he just talks by himself.
So nobody's like, Stop it, that's dumb.
Well, the first thing that happens when you're in that kind of a predicament is you start to wear shoulder holsters for no reason.
Oh, my God.
And then the second thing that happens is yeah, I really still can't believe that.
I understand that you're describing something that has to be real, but I'm seeing it as a cartoon.
No, it is cartoonish.
Okay, good.
So he has two co hosts.
I don't know their names.
I don't remember them because I don't care.
And they have a little bit of a wrap.
They sit down and they really work out some of the issues.
They talk about the big issue.
You are setting me up for disaster.
Well, I don't know if you know this, but the Parkland trial has been going.
My God.
No.
All right.
By the way, they're doing the Parkland shooting.
They reached a verdict that they're going to announce.
Isn't it just guilty and fry them? I mean, I thought this was a pretty closed let me know when we have the broadcast, Vegas.
When I know the guy is dead.
Maybe some facts about maybe about Sutherland Springs.
Fifth deadliest in American history.
Okay, so I guess they just want death penalty, which is I mean, they're pretty anti government as a whole, but I guess they want death penalty.
And I guess they also don't want due process because they just want you to be found guilty and then death penalty.
Has anybody ever stopped to think about what these people would do if they could write the Constitution again? It would be a mess.
Can you imagine? What do they think government does? Is the first question that I have to nothing but kill you and everything? And also I want them to be able to kill me, but as long as I'm the only person who can decide, right.
Why is that always the underpinning of no taxes? Exactly.
I want the government to not exist and also to kill people I don't like.
Yes.
One of the things that I think is really funny, too, is that Stephen realizes midsense, that the.
Las Vegas.
Shooter is dead.
And for what it's worth, the perpetrator of the Sutherland Spring shooting is also dead.
There is plenty of information available about both of these events.
If Steven would like to take the time to read, I would explain things to him.
If he brought up specific points, I would be happy to get into it.
But he just says the names of these shootings and then pretends there's a cover up.
So I got nothing to be useless show.
Okay.
Teleporter.
Give it to me.
And I just tackle people whenever they say dumb shit.
I'm not a superhero.
I don't solve problems.
I will just show up immediately after Steven Crowder says something insane like that, tackle him, and then teleport away.
And I feel like that's a worthy, noble cause.
Well, I mean, you'll get arrested for assault, but that trial teleport away.
That trial would be really interesting because I delegate.
Well, even if you didn't, right.
The prosecution would have to deal with the fact that you teleported.
Yeah, that would be an issue.
You would have to discuss the mechanism of you teleporting away.
And I'd be like, Ah, that doesn't exist.
Teleport away.
Reasonable doubt.
So they are apparently doing some shows, some live shows, and there's a plug for one.
And this is where I kind of lost my interest in this show as a whole.
Yeah.
Tell me if you think this feels a little bit racist.
Here we go.
And then not Baltimore December 3, because we couldn't find a venue in DC.
Sorry, you have to go to the Shill.
That is Baltimore.
But, hey, at least it's not Haiti or DC.
Yeah, or DC.
Now, Baltimore is worse than DC.
Is it? It's DC without any of the charms.
Well, I mean, the people.
Sure.
And you can go to Yikes.
It doesn't feel good.
What do you think these three dudes associate with Haiti, Baltimore, and DC? What do you think is there, like, when they open their mind's eye to see the things that they associate with Baltimore, DC, and Haiti? Yeah, it's a little and when he says it's the people.
Yeah.
Come on.
Quiet.
Quiet part.
That's the quiet part.
I wrote the book on it.
But, hey, they're jokes.
They're joking.
They're going on a comedy tour.
So Alex shows up, and he's a pro mr.
Jones.
Okay, I see that smirk.
What were you saying? Was that a dirty joke? No, I said, I'm really jealous of that shirt.
I'm going to rip it off, make my own coffee.
Well, I thought come on now.
Well, then I want you to cool a shirt.
That is the coolest shirt I've seen.
Yes, absolutely.
But no, but what you're talking about is absolutely true, and I'd love to give everybody the inside baseball, what really happened with the case, how it's the precedent setter and where it's going, because Alex 1 second.
Alex.
Because I want to give you the floor.
Okay.
Alex is trying to steamroll him, which is great.
And then the second thing that's awesome is right when he comes out the gate, Alex flatters.
Steven was like, that's a great shirt.
But then also establishes himself as an Alpha by saying, I'm going to steal your shirt.
Dominance.
Move.
Dad tries to steamroll him, and Steve would have to be like, Hold on, now, hold on.
I think he's supposed to be a host here.
It is interesting the way he both tries to acknowledge that he's not going to win the steamroll competition and at the same time try and establish dominance on his own show by saying, I'm going to let you steamroll me, Alex.
Right.
No one can win a steamrolling competition against the bullhorn trainer.
That is Alex Jones, bullhorn expert.
So, Steven, the reason that he wants to pretend to be a host in some ways is because he knows who Alex is.
He knows how he communicates, and he also knows that without guidance, alex is going to say just whatever the fuck he wants, and it's not going to be a useful interview for him.
And he's going to do the thing that he's trying to tell people right now that he has apologized for.
He's going to defame those.
You don't know if he is or not.
There's a danger.
Yeah.
It's very close to being an inevitability.
You want to have some guide ray rules.
Right.
And that's kind of what Steven is trying to do.
And so I want to leave this right now because I think this is pivotal, and we've done several multi hour long shows, but for some reason, this gets lost, and I want you to correct me if I have this wrong.
So, in 2017, as an example, because the narrative is Sandy Hook, you torment to the parents, you call them out by name, and you continually harass them.
From what I understand, and I have some quotes here in front of me.
I want you to tell me if I'm misquoting you.
You admitted you were wrong, and you apologize.
And I think that's key because I still want to go after you anyway.
So, 2017, you talked about epiphany he had on Father's Day.
You said, Forgive me on Father's Day, I want to reach out to the parents of the slain children at the horrible tragedy in Newtown, Connecticut, and give you my sincere condolences.
You said that, right? Yes.
Okay.
You also said, I'd also like to reach out to any of the parents who lost a child at Newtown to invite them to contact me to open a dialogue, because I think it's really essential we do that instead of letting the mainstream media misrepresent things and really try and drive this nation apart.
You said that right before they sued me.
Yes, before they sued you.
And then in 2019, in deposition, he said, and I myself have almost like a form of psychosis in the past where I basically thought everything was staged, even though I've now learned a lot of times things aren't staged.
And I'm not saying this to embarrass you, Alice.
I'm saying it because you were clear and that you had a change of heart or you believed that you were wrong or you believed you made a mistake, which I think is admirable.
And I think the fact that they want to browbeat you after that is what is so scary.
Steven sure does seem to be ignoring the fact that in Alex's video that was titled his Final Statement on Sandy Hook, he literally said, quote, if children were lost in Sandy Hook, my heart goes out to each and every one of those parents and the people who say they're parents that I see on the news.
The only problem is I've seen a lot of soap operas, and I've seen actors before, and I know when I'm watching a movie and when I'm watching something real.
That was in late 2016.
Alex only said the things that Stevens reading because of the Meghan Kelly interview that was about to come out.
Alex knew was going to come out around Father's Day, and Neil Heslin was going to be interviewed in it.
So he was trying to get ahead of any controversy.
He was also still repeating the basic conspiracy theories about the shooting at this point, just holding back some things that he thought could be legally actionable.
Stevens also ignoring that after this point, owen Schreueer did his video about how Neil Hesling couldn't have held his son after the shooting, and Alex reported on that, which in many ways, really does undo any good will that he might want to pretend he has from his feigned apology.
Stevens also ignoring that in October 2017, Alex said, quote, it's as phony as a three dollar bill with CNN doing fake newscasts and blue screens.
Stevens also ignoring that Alex has said that he thinks Sandy Hook probably was fake at least twice on air while the trials have been ongoing, including once in the last two weeks.
It's all good and fun to create these straw man versions of what Alex actually did and the reason he's facing consequences, but it's not real.
Steven knows it's not real, but Alex's existence is pretty helpful for his brand.
So we pretend this, and the people who are watching Stephen's show probably don't have any interest in debunking this nonsense that he's feeding them.
Yeah, if you're going to bring up the deposition and you're going to quote Alex from the deposition, that deposition convinces me that Alex is guilty of all the things well, he's not quoting the deposition.
He's quoting, like, an article about it, probably because that psychosis thing was something that a lot of media outlets as a pull out for the deposition.
He's not actually aware of anything that was discussed in the deposition.
All right, that makes sense, right? Because, again, I can never prove this, but I think that there's a vested interest in being willfully ignorant among a lot of people like Stephen.
Because if he had to cope with or cope's the wrong word, if he had to accept publicly that he was aware of the depositions and the things that were in it, he would then be responsible for rationalizing and justifying those things.
And he couldn't do that.
No.
He would have to be like, well, I would be fucked up real bad.
You're a piece of shit.
Yeah.
No, it is fascinating because these fucking pieces of shit who are trying to avoid defending Alex or avoid wading into having to defend Alex's actual behavior, if they were on the jury, they'd be like, yeah, this guy's got a fucking go.
You know? Like, without the ability to avoid acknowledging what is actually happening, without the ability to deny it when you are forced to look it directly into the eye every day for five fucking weeks.
Yeah, I know what he did.
And I think that's one of the reasons why I think Bobby Barnes is such an asshole is because he knows.
He knows he was in one of the depositions.
At least he was the lawyer.
He knows all this shit.
He's still pretending.
Oh, I don't understand why any of this is happening.
It's all just kangaroos and railroad tracks or whatever the fuck.
There is no deniability from Barnes whatsoever.
Because honestly, Barnes was probably looking at that billion dollar judgment and going, man, I wish I had been a competent enough lawyer for them to hire me so I could have sued Alex Jones for a fucking billion dollars because he was going to lose.
Or even I wish that I could be a competent enough lawyer to have stayed Alex's lawyer to the point where I lose a billion dollar verdict.
Because then I could get so much attention all over the place, lying about everything.
You star bobby Barnes.
Anyway, Alex is allowed to tell his version of events, and what do you know? It's all bullshit.
Here's what really happened.
I can give you the latest information, where they're going with it.
Everybody, thank you, sir.
OK.
Sandy Hook happens.
It's a huge political event.
Obama has him in the White House.
It's going on.
I think maybe somebody helped the kid kill these kids.
The whole story is bizarre.
And then about a year after it, all these professors and people that sound incredible come out and school safety experts and said that they thought it was just completely staged.
How big things like Operation Northwoods that talked about staging attacks on school kids that didn't exist as a pretext for war with Cuba and Russia.
So I said, yeah, a lot of stuff has been staged.
Maybe this is so I did four or five programs from 2000, and I guess 1314 question, maybe that it was staged.
There's a load of shit.
Alex was saying that he thought it might be fake on the day of the shooting on his show.
James Tracy, the professor that he's talking about, was first on Infowars on January 18, 2013, not year later, not years later.
Wolfgang Halbig didn't show up until later.
That is fair.
And he's the school safety officer that Alex is referencing, but Alex is completely ignoring Steve Patenic.
Steve was coming on Alex's show saying, no one died at the school on March 2013 when he was pretending to be a reporter on the scene in the DMZ.
Alex's timeline is all screwed up because he's just conveying his wellrehearsed selfdefense version of events.
Stephen is a shitty interviewer, and he has no interest in calling Alex out.
So this timeline will stand and be presented to his giant, impressionable audience as gospel, and it's just not true.
If he had any interest in pursuing the truth, he would have familiarized himself with these things and pointed out the many points at which Alex's story diverges from reality.
I mean, I would have stopped him right there and been like, Wait, stop.
Who helped him? Who helped him kill all those kids? Did you just say right now that you still think no, I think he was saying that at the time.
Immediately.
That was what his suspicion was.
Okay.
Yeah, I think he was saying in, like, December 2012, that's where his mind is.
All right.
Because that's not how I read what he was saying.
The problem was he started by saying, I'll give you the latest news.
No, he said, I will tell you what happened and get to the latest thing and what's going on, what they're planning.
All right.
I feel like he just did it again, but I could have poor sentence structure, or he could yeah, it's a little bit up in the air.
I've listened to this, and I'm pretty confident that this is all got you okay.
But yeah, look, it was all Hillary, man.
Hillary and the Democrats start running this false news campaign during 2016 campaign that I'm Trump's brain.
They look look at this flamboyant wild guy.
He's a populist.
He's got a lot of people supporting Trump.
Let's make him a liability.
Let's take the worst stuff he said out of context and run tens of millions of TV ads against Trump using Alex Jones, saying he's Trump's brain.
And one thing just to make really clear, is just, again, for the YouTube gods, you understand how this is Alex.
That's why I'm saying I'm saying it didn't happen again.
No, but they'll say that you were saying because you saw this, and there were other people, there were other professors, there were other conspiracy theorists, some of whom turned out to not be credible, and then you didn't have them on your show anymore.
You did say, Maybe this is staged.
And just again, to be clear, you afterwards said, no, it was not staged.
I was wrong.
There's a load of shit.
And honestly, I think if they needed to find the worst stuff Alex has said, this is definitely up there.
But they could have come up with a much broader campaign for Hillary to use.
Throw in some of his dehumanizing racism, his violent misogyny and homophobia, his incitement of violence towards Muslims.
Alex has got a deep bench of horrible things hillary could have attacked if that was the game that she was trying to play.
Also, Stephen knows damn well that Alex didn't think that maybe the shooting was staged.
Alex literally said multiple times that the shooting was totally fake.
With actors, Stephen is softening that reality.
So it's easier for his audience to give Alex a pass and rationalize his actions.
He's selling his audience on Alex.
It's a concerted effort and it's done by obscuring reality.
I just don't understand it because it's just a bad idea.
I feel like the right move here, if you're a piece of shit like Crowder or one of these other guys, is to fucking stab Alex in the back and then carve up his audience.
Like, I don't understand why you're even trying this bullshit.
You don't have any loyalty to him.
He doesn't have any loyalty to you.
I think that Stephen probably thinks that there is a way that this can raise his own profile, maybe get some of Alex's audience to him.
But it's a fool's errand because Alex's audience, anybody who is susceptible to maybe being interested in Crowder, listens to Alex already.
Listens to graduates, right? The rest of the folks are like, oldtimers who live in Shacks, Montana, and listen on shortwaves.
They're not going to like your dumb, childish comedy show.
Stupid, yes.
But I don't know.
I think I just meant as like an ecosystem, you know, not necessarily just Crowder, but like the whole shebang, like Shapiro and Jack and all of them.
If Crowder were smart, what he would maybe try to do is insinuate himself even more with Alex and get involved with the infrastructure part of band video and that kind of thing, and try and use it as a reinforcing misinformation sort of YouTube.
Because as it stands now, there's a shallow depth of anything interesting on there.
There's plenty of content that's true.
There's infowars stuff and there's a load of bullshit.
Steven is like, I don't think it's in his best interest necessarily to be hooked with Glenn Beck with The Blaze stuff, but maybe there's some good money there.
But in terms of, like, if you want some of Alex's audience and that stuff and he wants to create, like, more of a space, that would be the thing you'd do, maybe, and then try and rope in some of the other weirdos.
Sure.
But actually, hold on.
I just don't think that's very forward looking.
I think that's saying that we're going to be in a similar place in three years that we are right now, and I don't think that's even close to possible.
Well, I guess I maybe don't agree with myself either, because I was talking about like, Gavin McGinnis.
He has a sensor TV or whatever.
Right.
And there's not a lot going on there.
Maybe never mind.
I was going to say he could go and like, try and help build up cozy.
Nick Hunter is a service, but Nick Huntes doesn't want crowder.
No.
Absolutely not.
Quentas probably thinks crowder stuff.
Yeah, definitely.
Yeah.
I don't know.
Why are we always trying to give them assistance? It can't help it.
I think this is all stupid, but Alex just is like an out and outlier.
But it's important to understand this timeline.
Yeah.
For over a year and a half, from 2015 to 2016, we checked the record.
I never talked about it one time, and I told the crew, this is a car, baby, it's a set up.
I don't want to ever discuss it again.
I think it's still doing it.
We started seeing that some of the folks that were claiming it was stage had gone even crazier, and we're now deregulating and showing that indeed, they put out things that were wrong.
So I was not the Sandy Hook guy.
Didn't put me on the map.
I barely ever covered it.
But Hillary blows it up, makes it a cause celebr for Democrats.
They use it to bring back all the gun control and now attacks on free speech and to attack Trump.
And so then Trump wins.
They go even crazier, and they start attacking me.
So if this is all an elaborate plot, hillary launched to attack Trump and then Trump won, it seems like it really wouldn't do anything to continue attacking Alex.
The goal would have been to use Alex's toxicity to sway the electorate away from Trump.
And once Trump is won, that's about it in terms of voters.
Just doesn't make sense.
Unless you're just desperate to defend yourself using bullshit fantasy world nonsense.
Yeah.
Also, Alex didn't stop talking about Sandy Hook during those time frames that he had his staff go look things up.
No shit.
Consider this clip from August 26, 2015, squarely in the window.
He's claiming he never brought it up.
Oh, yeah.
In my opinion, something really stinks about this entire situation.
I can't even really think of a mass shooting, quote, unquote, or a high profile shooting like this.
That didn't seem like there was something more going on.
Well, there's been some of them that we caught red handed being staged.
Sirhan.
Sirhan, with RFK.
The situation a few years ago with the Aurora shooting, I mean, those were staged.
We caught them.
We know exactly what they did.
It's unbelievable.
And then you look at Sandy Hook, it just isn't real.
I don't know what specifically happened, but the official story is a fairy tale.
I mean, Jack of the Beanstalk isn't real.
Santa Claus isn't real.
And that is a giant theater operation complete with blue screens.
And now even Rob Dew's uncle, who's a Navy Seal, retired FBI, works for a big company.
We have a reporter up there, and it's like, that's Rob Doo's uncle.
And he's like, yeah, it doesn't add up.
Something's going to see anything like this.
There's no paperwork.
They're covering something up.
I can't talk.
I got to get out of here.
That's how Twilight Zone this has got.
There's a reporter there was that there was Dan Buddy, by the way.
So, yeah.
Go fuck yourself, Alex.
Yeah.
Add to that that Alex didn't stop talking to the people who promoted the crisis actor's shit.
Steve Patentic was a guest in Tokyo, and Alex got into a fight about Steve pushing QAnon on shit during the aftermath of the 2020 election.
Alex is a liar, and these are easily demonstrable lies.
If Steven cared at all to protect his audience from a fraud, he has a responsibility to them, and he's completely neglecting that, which is shameful.
And here's what I actually think about when you're talking about, like, why not just carve up Alex's audience? Sure.
I think that for someone like Stephen, there's probably an interest in preserving Alex, if you can.
Sure.
And that is because he is worse than you.
Yeah, that's fair.
Presumably he's worse than you, if only because you're still on YouTube.
Sure.
Right.
So as long as Alex is there, a lot of people will think there's a bigger issue than Stephen Crowder, in the same way that you hear people, even Tucker, say, like, my great replacement theory isn't crazy.
It's not Alex Jones.
Shit.
Alex can exist as that I'm not him example.
But if you were to go away entirely, then they want to try and repair their broken shield.
Yeah, I think that's probably a way to look at it.
So Alex, he's corrected himself a lot.
He hasn't, but Steve is going to let him say it.
Okay, so he issued dozens of corrections, dozens of apologies.
You just mentioned one of them there.
And then they sue me in 2018, and then they do all this discovery.
We give them all the emails, all the text messages and everything.
There's no evidence we made money on Sandy Hook.
There's no evidence I premeditatedly got it wrong on purpose.
And so both Democrat connected judges, one of the pose a Republican, but she's like George W.
Bush.
They default me, saying I lost Alex for a second.
Alex, this is clearly the globalist.
He's told I'm guilty.
The jury is told I'm guilty.
I'm not allowed in a five week trial in Connecticut to defend myself.
The judge actually says, you can't say you're innocent, you can't say you're bankrupt.
All that's just shit.
But there is no push back.
There is no discussion of what these things are.
There's no reason to.
Yeah.
So Crowder wants to know real.
Seriously, did you use these people's names? Did you ever call the parents out by name on air and said that they were their children? Like, call them out by name, on air only? Robbie Parker.
Okay.
And I did not say that he staged it or it was fake.
I said, people think this clip was like 30 million views on YouTube or more.
It was a viral clip.
People say, this guy looks fake.
And so I said, yeah, it does look like acting to me, but he's under stress, whatever.
That's not true.
And Heslin's name was set on infowars posner.
And also, intentional infliction of emotional distress doesn't require you say people's names.
These people are constantly screaming about how some people should die because they changed their pronouns, and yet somehow they're going to try and pretend that pronouns cannot refer to people.
Right? You have to say their name like a magic spell.
You have to sew it in to your fucking piece of paper with silver thread.
Dan, obviously.
Otherwise it's not defamation, right? And when you say, like, the families if you're one of the members of one of the families, you can't consider yourself part of that group.
No, you have to be referred to.
That's how words work.
You can't do it.
No.
Damn.
So Alex tries to explain and Stephen really wants him to explain this because it's kind of an important point that he fully complied with discovery.
Well, I do have a question that's important here because people will say, well, the reason you weren't allowed to defend yourself is it was a default judgment.
And they say, because you didn't provide the evidence that was requested in discovery.
Give me very specifics, not just all you did provide, and hand over a lot of evidence.
What did you hand over? Because they did have financials they did have certainly in the Texas trial, they did have access to financials.
They did have access to certain traffic metrics.
When I was watching the trial, they would say, well, actually, they didn't hand over, for example, the Alexa reporting as opposed to the Google Analytics reporting.
What kind of evidence, when you're asked to hand over, just give me some examples of what you did hand over.
Did you hand over financial documents as it related to the company? Yes.
Did you hand over documents as it related to different traffic and revenue streams to some degree or another? To an extreme degree.
The most ever given over in a civil defamation trial, many lawyers estimate steven, let me be 100% clear.
So what are they saying you didn't provide, is my point, because this is something a lot of people accurate information, unfortunately, on the right alex, this is important.
I'm just saying this because people will try and take this out of cop.
People on the right will say, well, then you guess you should comply during discovery.
What? Pardon me? What in the fuck are they claiming you didn't provide so that you were not allowed to defend yourself? All right, let me answer that question.
And I want to get into people saying, oh, this is just for Alex Jones.
In Texas, they claimed that because we did so much discovery and they would have each person that they were deposing give them more discovery.
So they'd say, out of the 200,000 emails you gave us in Texas, in one of Discovery batches you gave us, there was one extra email that wasn't in this batch.
Little weird gotcha games.
And then in Connecticut, the judge kept saying, Give me the Google Analytics.
Well, we hardly ever even use Google Analytics.
Hardly ever even looked at it.
So he explained to the judge, Ma'am, it's a search box for the backend of Google, and a lot of you have to pay for it.
We've never paid for it.
We've barely ever used it.
But we searched for Google Analytics and found one writer and one other person in the group that had looked at Google Analytics and said, oh, look how much traffic we're getting a few times.
So we gave them what we had in our system about Google Analytics.
Take Alexa.
Same thing.
They said, Give us the alexa.
Well, Stephen, I want you to give me the Google.
And then I say you say, okay, what, do you want me to search in Google? No, sir, give me the Google.
Give me the Google.
Also, some of those instances of Google Analytics like, look how much traffic we're getting from this Sandy Hook article.
So maybe Alex shouldn't use that as an example.
If Stephen really wanted to be prepared to ask this question and respond appropriately to Alex's answer, he should have read the order for the default judgment.
It spells everything out.
There were requests for production that Alex never even responded to.
There were requests to produce people for depositions that were ignored.
Alex repeatedly sent completely unprepared people to depositions as corporate representatives.
And that's just the surface.
Alex did turn over big batches of documents, but he had a habit of doing that just before hearings about his failure to turn over documents so he could avoid consequences while overwhelming the plaintiffs with tons of unrelated shit.
Even these tranches weren't satisfactory to what he was obligated to turn over, though, and it didn't really help him.
Yeah, in the judgment, they even discussed how they tried to resolve the problem through fines and sanctions.
But it was clear that it had no effect on Alex's abuse of the discovery process.
He has too much money to be impacted by whatever fines the court could impose.
So it was a dead end.
Steven doesn't care about the reality here or the truth.
He's just asking questions to allow Alex to give his boilerplate rehearsed answer and make it look like Stephen was asking tough questions.
This is a charade that is meant to exonerate Alex.
In the eyes of Steven's audience.
Yeah.
It is not an interview.
It's so hard because the truth of it is like, that all of him being like, I'm not allowed to say I'm innocent.
I'm not allowed to say I'm all this stuff.
And it's like, that's your fault.
And the reason that you weren't allowed to say it is because if you did, sooner or later, you would have to go to jail.
We're being nice to you by keeping you.
This is like you going bowling with rails.
That's the point here, is because you are going to be a gutter ball and then go to jail.
We're saving your life, man.
Right.
And if you had practiced bowling in this metaphor, you wouldn't be fucking Rails, right? Yeah, exactly.
This fully works, but it's close enough.
So Stephen has lost control of this, of course.
Completely taken over.
Yeah.
Sounds good.
Now the Secretary of State of Texas is talking about we may have to go after Alex Jones because he caused threats on election officials.
They have no statements.
They don't have me saying be violent.
I didn't even probably ever even talk about the Texas election other than saying I don't think that to was as close as he said he was to Ted Cruz.
So this is the absolute next level garbage and propaganda.
In fact, overhead shot.
I want to show people this.
Texas Secretary of State Alex Jones.
Unleash hell on our election, people.
That's the hill.
Here's another one.
Republican Texas Election chief Blast Nuts peddling 2020 Conspiracy Theory Zooms on.
Alex jones.
So just like they're suing everybody.
Alex is just doing his show.
Yeah.
I'm waiting for him to do an episode.
When is he going to do it? He's calling for overhead show.
Is he going to do it? This is ridiculous.
That is insane.
Yeah, Steve lost a tire control.
This is just the Alex Jones show.
This is absolutely infowars right now.
That is so funny.
Also, we've got these coins.
We got these fucking coins.
Buy these coins.
No, he's on the six coin.
No longer a fundraiser.
So Alex believes that this is overkill.
And then Steven has some harsh words for these so called brave conservatives.
This is all overkill.
It's just the left having a temporary tantrum.
They want to scare everybody else to get a bunch of other lawyers to file lawsuits to come after all the conservatives and all the nationalists and all the Patriots.
And I really appreciate you letting me get that out there, because it's so frustrating to be kind of only have my show that has a big audience, but it's compartmentalized because of censorship.
It's very hard to actually get the truth.
No, it's not just censorship.
I understand it's not just censorship.
It's cowardice.
You and I have had conversations, obviously, off air, where I would say I wouldn't say call to the Nap, but I've said, I don't agree with this.
I don't like that.
Remember I told you, I remember early on the show saying, I don't like that you sometimes stir up in fighting with conservatives.
I remember you saying, you know what? I used to do that more.
And I decided the left is a more important enemy.
We've had very strong disagreements.
I felt compelled to have you on because some of the biggest figures in our movement who, by the way, agreed with all of some of your quote unquote conspiracy theories that I thought were incorrect, they didn't have you on.
It is censorship and it's cowardice.
Let me translate what Stephen saying there about the infighting among conservatives.
Alex, I work for Glenn Beck.
Stop being mech.
Also, Stephen, you have to understand a lot of those other conservative outlets are really busy running damage control for Tucker's Kanye West interview at the moment.
A lot of them just don't have the juice to throw Alex into the mix and try and deal with that.
We can't be both protecting against the rapid antisemitism in our party and protecting against Alex.
Both antisemitism and more.
It is weird that Alex hasn't been on Rogen, though.
Like, I wonder if Joe watched some of the trial and realized that Alex lied to his face about what he said about Sandy Hook.
That would be fun if Joe started to get the picture that Alex is using him and see what develops from there.
Yes.
I'm not optimistic that's going to happen.
Yes, if Joe watched the trial, it would be really hard to come away from it thinking that Alex did not lie to your fucking face.
Yeah.
But you still gotta realize he's a fun guy.
He's really funny.
Do you know what this reminds me of? This reminds me so much of walking into a Dunkin Donuts around whatever, and there's two old guys sitting in that way right inside the door so you can see them through the window and they're arguing about a parking ticket.
And he's like, man, I didn't park there.
I'm telling you.
And you know the guy's lying.
I'm walking in there trying to buy coffee for 2 seconds and I want to turn around and be like, dude, just pay the parking ticket.
You're a fucking liar.
Obviously you did the thing.
And the other guy's like, yeah, you're totally right, man.
They shouldn't be able to do that.
One of those guys is Rogen.
Yeah, okay.
Yeah.
Just making sure.
No, I think I'm talking about crowder and Alex right now.
Okay.
Yeah.
Who's Rogan? Is he the donut? Rogan would be a delicious donut.
So we got a question for Alex, although he'd be a little bit stringy.
Yeah, probably.
Yeah.
And full of raw meat.
So, Alex, we got to find out if he's scared.
Let me ask you, Alex, really point blank.
I know you talk about appeals.
How scared are you right now? I am way more scared about the direction the country is going in that they admit this is a formula for everybody.
I mean, while the right wing laughs some of them, and says, oh, it's just Alex Jones, they're on every channel saying, we're coming after everybody now with this model.
And they've even got the Republican Secretary of State in Texas saying we want to come after Republicans.
That question election fraud.
Give me a break.
So you have the rhinos, the neocons, the rabid left, allied together against the populist uprising of nationalist Americans who are peacefully trying to take our country back.
So I'm way more concerned about nuclear war.
I'm way more concerned about financial collapse.
I mean, here's a good point, Steven.
Quite frankly, the way inflation is going and the way it accelerates towards YMar Republic of Zimbabwe, in ten years, there's such inflation.
A billion dollars will be like $1,000 at the current rate we're at here.
No, I'm not scared.
I am disgusted.
And I really feel proud of myself because I've told the truth about this.
I've said that I was wrong.
They have created this whole synthetic identity for me, this straw man, and then they sat there and had to lie to a jury and suppress the truth and tell him I was guilty and rigged this kangaroo court so I myself can hold my head tall.
But I am, in general, very concerned for my children, for the country in the future because of the rapid acceleration into total and complete corruption.
Wow, that's quite an answer to are you scared? Yes.
I don't want to go with yes.
I feel like from some of the numbers that I was seeing, the inflation is starting to turn around, and I don't know if we're going to end up in a Weimar Germany situation.
Right.
We're not going to go Zimbabwe, baby.
I mean, if I've read everything correctly, I feel like there's a difference between radical, out of control inflation and all of these businesses being like, oh, they're talking about inflation.
We can charge an extra $2.
Yes, some of this is a little bit hard to disaggregate from each other, some of these forces.
Yeah.
But yeah, I don't think that's the path we're heading on.
And also, I think that nuclear war was supposed to have already started by now, based on Alex's projection.
Oh, we've been dead for a while.
Yeah.
So I guess he should probably be more concerned about his own personal matters.
They seem pretty severe.
Yeah.
That billion in ten years is still going to be an albatross over your neck, buddy.
So one of the co hosts asks Alex a very important question, and that is, what's up with the appeal? How is that going to work? Right.
And you'll notice over the course of the maybe next three clips that Alex can't answer specifics.
Yeah.
So you said earlier that this is going to be overturned.
Why do you think that it will be overturned.
Not that you just have kind of this faith in that that's going to happen, but what are you guys arguing, if you can reveal that to us on how it's going to be overturned? Well, that's an excellent question.
I have talked to dozens of very well known constitutional lawyers.
I can tell you, Norpat is a very well known, successful lawyer around the country, current and former judges in Connecticut and in New York, federal and state, that say this is the most insane craziness they've ever seen.
All right, so your lawyer who lost this case for you is talking to other people, allegedly, and reporting to you secondhand, that this shit is crazy.
Sounds true.
And this is how you're going to win the appeal? Yeah.
Okay, so there's no grounds given for what the appeal, what the argument is, why they merit an appeal other than come on.
Yeah, come on.
That's an issue.
If your appeal is based on that's just too big.
Alex, like Legit seems to believe that if he can just pay for the appeal, he will magically win.
Oh.
Either America is gone and completely done, or in Texas and in Connecticut, if I have the money for the appeals.
That's why they want to bankrupt us right now, because they are so scared that if there's any justice left at the Texas or the Connecticut Supreme Court or the US Supreme Court, they've got to overturn this because the deep state, the ambulance chaser brigade, are openly saying they're coming after everyone with this, just like when I got sick.
So you're saying that you think the people in the appeals court will see the gravity of it? Is that what you're saying? Why you believe it'll be overturned? I don't know.
The fix is in that high.
Oh, I see.
So soros can control all the district attorneys in America and all the judges and everything, but you can't penetrate the appeals court.
Also, the US Supreme Court is entirely blackmailed by Chinese spies.
Oh, no, the appeals court.
The fix isn't in that high.
The one that's insanely done.
Everything I hope today would do is also definitely run by the Chinese billionaires.
Yeah, this is fun.
I mean, it's just Alex trying to be like, yeah, you should still give me money because I'm going to find a way to launder it during the appeals process.
Yeah, I mean, the problem is for Alex is that in a very real way, this is an Apolitical case for lawyers and judges and everything because they all have a vested interest in this being at least the bottom.
You know, like all of them would prefer to have firm guardrails so we don't have to go through, like, another this judges waited three years to default judgment because we just have never seen this shit before.
So it helps if we have a baseline here of like, guess what? Here's a person who's done this shit before.
Here's what we've done before, and now we don't have to do this again.
It would be nice.
Yeah.
I mean, it is fitting that this is Alex's sort of path.
And as much as Trump taught us so much about how much of the government is not codified, how much of it is based on just like, we all agree this is how humans it's a good idea to do this, right? Yeah.
We all think this is a smart.
These norms that we've thought of protected us and kept things in line aren't really real.
Right.
And Alex is kind of revealing some of the similar stuff.
With the legal system, you could just not do stuff.
It is unfortunate that it's like, oh, man, we've accidentally created a system geared towards giving narcissistic psychopaths a lot of money and power.
If they have the nerve and the shamelessness and the shamelessness, they can do whatever the fuck they want.
Yeah.
So Alex continues to ramble about his nonanswer, about how this appeal is going to work, and then he forgets what question he's answering.
But I know that okay, they've got their ton of flesh.
They've demonized me.
They brought back up Sandy Hook.
They've made a bunch of money for their charities.
They got $73 million from Remington.
Yeah, those bad people made a bunch of money for their chairs.
Okay.
And now nobody knows who Adam Lands is to kill the kids.
They only know Alice Jones.
And so I'm sorry, what was the question? Steven apologize.
No, I think you answered the question.
Well, I think Gerald really wants to know why do you believe it will be overturned? Do you think it's because he wanted to make an example of you? And then when it comes down to the actual constitutional law, it won't hold water? Is that why? Absolutely.
They have to or the country is over.
I mean, you have to understand, when I say Kager report, when I say show trial, I mean, this has never before been done a default when you don't even show up.
We gave them everything.
It's fun the way that Steven's interview style seems to be like, alex is just rambling.
I'll try and answer this question for him and see if he can just say yes to my suggested answer.
And Alex does, and then starts rambling some more.
It is fun that if you're Steven Crowder, you started the show by being like, you weren't even allowed to make your defense.
And then at the end of the show, you have to be like, oh, no, that makes sense.
Yeah.
You shouldn't have been.
Your defense is terrible.
There isn't one.
Yeah.
And you're just not going to be able to answer yes or no question to save your life.
Literally.
Literally to save your life.
Your fucking defense is Hillary.
Yeah.
Go away.
So Alex starts rambling about money and gets into his divorce.
For some reason, this is weird.
They said he made $61 million last year.
Our gross was $61 million.
I paid myself $200,000 last year.
It's all in the bankruptcy court.
They know it.
They know it's true.
Was there a year that I paid myself $12 million? Absolutely.
The year of the divorce with my ex wife six years ago.
Thank God it was a trump error.
For the first time ever, we had all this extra money right when she divorced me.
It goes through the process.
And the court made me pay her close to $10 million to, quote, buy her out of the company, because I've been married to her for 13 years.
So the one year, God came through the one year, because usually I make about a million, $2 million a year.
But honestly, my audience and after all the bills and stuff and legal crap, it's gone, of course.
Okay.
I don't do it for money.
So wait, hold on.
I got to pause there for a second.
Yeah, he had a 400% pay increase that year.
Magically.
Okay, that makes sense.
So weird.
Yeah.
The one year I made $12 million, god came through magically.
The money came in to then buy my ex wife out of the company.
So, again, they think I want to say something here.
This is important, because I see you, and we all struggle with this, right? Where you're saying because I know that people think that sounds like a lot of money, and it's sad that you even have to say, no, you don't do this just for the money, but you absolutely deserve to earn a living if you have millions of people who are listening in the amount of work that you put into it.
I understand it.
This is what I do here as well.
Conservatives are the only ones, surprisingly, the people who support free enterprise, where we feel like, because our audience is largely working class, you must say, look, don't get mad at me because I make this money, because it's huge.
In between one year making 12 million and a several hundred million dollar judgment, you know who makes 12 million every single year? Colbert Fallon.
No one cares.
So I can explain that dynamic a little better than Stephen.
He and Alex do this song and dance because they know that they're fucking over their audience.
They have to rationalize the money they make because it's an insane amount.
And they earn it by exploiting their audience's fear and anger and monetizing that while putting vulnerable people in harm's way.
And they do no work and they sell garbage.
Yeah, absolute garbage.
Steven did no preparation for this interview.
He has no idea of the subject that he's even covering.
There's no work that goes into this other than riffing dumb jokes.
They know that they don't do shit.
And whether it's conscious or not, that's another question about whether or not.
That's why they have to rationalize this.
But they have to pretend not to care about money, or else they run the risk of being way too obvious about how they sell things, and then before you know it, they're just a racist.
QVC Fowler and Colbert make money, but I'm not sure how much.
But they don't get on their show every night and try to rationalize it, because they actually put on a show.
They're entertainers doing a job, not just complaining about how they're so persecuted.
And this has nothing to do with political alignment.
Do you think Jeff Foxworthy or Larry the Cable Guy or Ron White has to rationalize that they make millions of dollars? They don't, because their talent makes it obvious why they make that much money.
For con men like Alex and Stephen, it's different.
And that's why they do have to do this.
Like, oh, hey, look, it's $100 million that I make, but it's no big deal.
It's actually nothing.
Yes.
No, they're thieves having to justify why thievery is okay, well, they're thieving doing sort of legal fees.
Legal thieves.
Yeah.
And I understand that you have to explain why.
You have to rationalize or it gets confusing and suspicious.
Right.
I think the thing that has stuck with me maybe most well, no, there are a few things that really stuck with me during the Texas trial, but one of them that I will never forget is when Owen was on the stand and he was being questioned about NPR, and he was like, you know, they're a nonprofit, right? And Owen just said, but they still get paid, don't they? They don't understand the idea of not doing something for money.
Sure, I understand we're a nonprofit, but this is what actual not money is when you're just there doing your job and you're surviving.
And not to jump too far from what you're saying, but, like, Owen and Alex and other people in depositions have been very clear about, like, we don't really do any preparation, because if they admitted that they did work, it would show malice.
It would really make it look hard.
They don't do shit.
Yeah.
Anyway, Alex wants to go to the documents, and this is about how hard he works.
And this is the most important point I'm going to make here.
And I got a few documents I can show people that are really important that tie us all together.
This is a major project for six years.
Two years before they stood me.
And then now the last four.
With literally hundreds of articles a week.
Sometimes thousands.
Every major news channel from HBO to PBS to Fox.
Even attacking me over Sandy Hook and building it up into this giant controversy when I was not the Sandy Hook man.
To set the precedent with the Alex Jones precedent to shut everybody else down.
Now, let's talk about this being the biggest defamation judgment in US history by an order of at least ten magnitude.
If I can have an overhead shot here.
Damn, I wish the survivors of Epstein received 965,000,000.
Exactly.
Good point.
On Twitter, Eliza.
He just read a tweet from Eliza.
Yes.
Overhead shop for this tweet.
Wow.
Yes.
And Twitter sucks.
Sure.
Yes.
Also, hey.
Yeah.
Epstein's victims should be compensated, but that doesn't have anything to do with you.
It's unfortunate.
You also should pay out that billion dollars.
Yeah, I mean, I agree.
We both agree this is not a zero game.
Unrelated, but I agree he also has money that should go elsewhere.
Do both of you have money when you should have zero money? Good call, Eliza.
Yeah, I like that, Eliza.
Good work.
So they end the episode with a Q and A session, and it's actually only three questions formally, but they take questions for people in Stephen Carter's mug club.
Sure.
And here's the first one.
OK, yeah.
Mug club viewer Jerry has a question for you.
Alex, what do you feel was an appropriate penalty for what you said? Nothing.
It's better that ten guilty men go free than one innocent man be prosecuted.
Here's why Alex is the worst.
Saying nothing is so dumb.
He should have said, you pay for my meals for life.
Totally.
Do a Socrates something.
Come on, man.
Elevate this.
Bring it on.
What the fuck is wrong with you? It's a rare opportunity that you can actually pull a Socrates.
Yes.
You are going to die and you will not be remembered unless you pull something.
Great, man.
You got to do it.
They got rid of my due process.
The judge found me guilty.
They lied about it all.
They hyped up what I said.
They exaggerated it.
I never said people, their houses.
It's a lie.
They're setting a precedent to steal your rights, not just your rights to listen to what you want to listen to and make your own decisions.
They're literally setting this up to come after the general public.
An FBI agent that I never saw, never covered, never said his name until he sued me, he admitted on the stand was given $90 million because some people on the Internet thought it didn't happen.
I should be no consequence.
Slap me off the hook.
I do appreciate the more I think about it, the more I appreciate the ten guilty men should be free instead of what is like.
That's not a defense in a trial.
You can't be like, oh, listen, Your Honor, I did it.
But can we know everyone did what they did? It's a good idea to let me go free.
Otherwise you might put that man in jail.
No, he's saying that he's the innocent man who shouldn't be persecuted, not one of the guilty people who goes free.
I feel like the implication there, he didn't intend the right way.
Well, maybe he's thinking he's the innocent man, but in this situation, he really comes off sounding like he's the one of the ten guilty, but also he should do a Socrates.
Anyway, there's a problem with the crowder identifies.
Yeah.
And that is that hey, this is a lawsuit for defamation.
There is that.
We're against it.
Yes.
But then there's some other lawsuits that you filed.
Well, sure, Alex did.
Yeah, that doesn't come up.
But other ones, like the Covington Catholic, and we do support these shit.
I need to talk about this.
And also, it's important you'll get a lot of people on the left saying, oh, the right has a double standard, because what about Nick Sandman and CNN? What about Kyle written house? They said his name the President of the United States had an advertisement, had an ad that went out that associated Kyle Written house specifically with white supremacy.
They said Nick Sandman was mocking somebody.
This poor Native American nathan Phillips.
As I prefer my Native Americans to be called Nathan Phillips.
They said, yeah, he was mocking Nathan Phillips, and he was stirring up the crowd.
They did call out these people by name, and these people had to hire security, and these people had to go into hiding.
There is a difference.
You did not do that.
And they did it repeatedly.
They did it all day and all night.
Not to mention what preceded Cowritten house was the media drumming up actual hatred and that's right.
And they never showed any evidence I sent people to harass people or anything.
Of course, it was always what somebody else did.
So Alex is absolutely lying about there being no proof that he sent to people to Newtown, and that led to harassment.
Complete horseshit.
Absolutely.
Also, I guess if Stephen wants to be such a stickler about saying people's names, which isn't necessary to prove intentional infliction of emotional distress, then he should support Alex paying Robbie Parker $120,000,000.
Yeah.
Because Alex did say his name repeatedly and repeatedly mocked a video of him about to give his memorial to his daughter.
Or is there a double standard if crowder is going to put those as his benchmarks for when a case is acceptable? Well, we've reached those benchmarks.
Sure.
20 million.
Yeah.
I mean, if you want to say for some if that's your argument, that it's like, you have to say the name.
Well, we've reached that benchmark.
Right.
If your benchmark is somebody has to go into hiding.
They went into hiding.
Yeah.
So guess what? We're done here.
I strongly disagree with the point the crowd was making.
He's wrong.
Yes.
But based on his own perception, he should be like, all right, Alex, you don't owe 900 million.
You owe 120,000,000.
And if that was his perspective, I would think that would be hilarious.
It would be very funny to me.
Unfortunately, there's no way for me to be intellectually consistent and not be on your team.
I literally spiritually, physically in this world.
If I have any intellectual curiosity, I can but I have to say that you owe $120,000,000 for Robbie Parker.
I have to, yeah.
So what's the next question of this Q and A? Okay.
Michael Burger.
Taylor Kohler wants to know, if people only knew one true thing about you, Alex, among all these lies, what would it be? That was going to be my last question.
Who.
I mean, look, I'm a real person.
I've got a lot of information.
Sometimes I'm a little bit obnoxious because I'm trying to get through it all, like, here today.
And I really appreciate steaming the Caribbean so gracious so I can have a place to tell the truth.
And I appreciate your courage because you do get attacked for having me on.
And just this is our rights being taken.
This is a Hollywood production.
I'm not saying Sandy Hook didn't happen.
I'm saying the production of what I supposedly did and how big it became and this huge event.
I'm not the Sandy Hook guy.
I'm the guy that wrote the number one best selling book in the world for the world.
That's why the globalists hate me, is because I'm exposing their corporate worldwide tyranny.
I'm exposing groups like PayPal that are back, by the way, saying, if we don't like what you say, we're going to find you $2,500.
I'm opposing their authoritarianism.
I'm a populist.
I'm a champion of the people.
And folks can actually hear the real Alex Jones@infowars.com infowars.com show or bandout video.
Go see the real life show.
Go see the archives.
Go see the guests.
Go find out what I'm actually saying instead of little bitty twisted, edited excerpts that the corporate media puts out to understand the globalists.
See, infowars is the flag they want to capture.
They're more obsessed with it than anything else out there right now, because when the globalists tune in, they get scared, because I know what I'm talking about when it comes to the mechanics of the new world order.
So it's interesting how Alex's one true thing contains multiple lies.
That's pretty amazing.
Very weird about that.
I guess if you boil that down, his one true thing about himself that you need to know is that he's amazing and he's so strong and right and smart that everything bad that happens to him is just the globalist attacking him with fake stories because he's so strong and right and smart.
It's cool.
Yeah.
That's a good thing to end on for Alexander.
What else is there to say? He's going out saying, like, I'm the best writer in the world.
I'm the best talker in the world.
I'm the most powerful man in the world, because the most powerful people are coming after me.
Right.
Like, Jesus, man.
The devil doesn't come up, by the way, in this interview.
It's so weird because he seems really central to the plot line.
Yes.
Also, Alex's book has fallen to 322 on the Amazon charts.
So close.
It's weird how they don't stay at number.
One just because you keep saying it and it wasn't ever at number one.
Now there is that.
That's a problem too.
So actually there's another question and that's Steven has a question.
Final question.
Then we're going to go to Mug club and take some more chats.
What's the next step? What are you doing here next, alex, game plan.
Well, that's a really great question.
My biggest enemy is myself.
I am absolutely exhausted.
I'm burnt out, I drink too much.
I haven't smoked in 14 years.
Under the stress, I took up smoking again.
Going out and watching comedy and hang out with Joe Rogan.
There's a lot of cigarettes smoking going on.
Yeah, I don't think that's cigarette smoke.
No, I've done a little bit of the marijuana smoke too, but I smoke a lot of it.
I smoke pot like once a month or something.
Usually I'm at a comedy club or go see a movie.
Every time I hang out with Joey, he smokes a pot.
But sometimes I guess twice a week.
I don't think I would Joe that much lately.
I've been too busy.
But some days we went on it like twice a week and get stoned.
But a little bit of fun stuff there.
But long story short, he's just doing it to test the potency because Soros has weaponized marijuana.
Soros weaponized marijuana.
Alex is smoking sometimes two times a week just for fun to hang out with his buddy.
Seems like he's maybe not too worried about that.
Maybe it's not real odd.
Maybe that's not a real thing.
It's real odd how it's so important and then it's here and you just forget about it.
It's the most important fight in the world.
We have to fight against the globalist potency of drugs in there.
I get high all the time.
I really don't think smoking cigarettes is going to be good for him.
That's not good.
Yeah, I wouldn't do it.
Maybe that's what the Torn Larynx act was.
He was outside burning one.
Yeah, could be.
So Steven does want a question, though, about what's next.
Yeah, when he said long story short, I wanted to throw up because that was a short story that's been very long.
So what's next? Stephen basically just has to pull teeth to get that out of him.
Some days we went on it like twice a week and gets stoned.
But a little bit of fun stuff there.
But long story short, game plan, Alex, that's your hobbies.
Anyways.
Well, it's a little bit of a name drop to all the trendy liberals that think they're trendy and think they're cool and love the police.
They hate free speech.
I'm the real rebel.
Infowars is the vanguard.
So is Steven Crowder.
We are the rebels.
We are the outlaws.
We are 1776.
We are the counterculture, not them.
And they can't stand that.
And so that's what all people know.
We are the counterculture.
Stephen crowder is the counterculture.
The listeners and viewers of these shows that support independent media are the future of not just America, but the world that people can find out what all the stinks about@infowars.com.
So it sounds to me like what you're saying your next step is.
And Alex, you know I have a lot of love for you, but sometimes it's tough to get you to answer your question, I think you need to get some rest is what you're saying.
Right? Your game plan is some rest, recoup and come back.
Listen, I'm more ADHD when I'm totally exhausted.
So I've done interviews and I was up till 01:00 in the morning and I apologize.
My brain's gone right now.
So, yes, I realize this is what's coming next.
I realize they want to take me out of the game.
And I realize that I'm never going to quit now because they want to silence me, because this is a battle of wills.
I know it's the right thing to do, but I also understand that if I take myself out of the game by being fried or burnt out, they win.
So I am going to, in the next few months, do something I never do.
I'm going to take off a week, a month, starting at the end of this month, november and December.
I may take off two weeks in December.
I want my listeners to understand why I've got to do it, because I've got to rest.
I've got to stop drinking, I've got to stop smoking, I got to go to church to recharge my batteries.
I've got to take my daughter camping.
I've got to go camping and shooting with my son and my other daughters.
And so if you're asking what's happening, I'm going to recharge my batteries, get back to family, get back to God, and come back in 2023 harder than ever.
This is bullshit.
I think he probably will take a week off in November and December for Thanksgiving and Christmas.
Yeah, it's not going to stick.
Also, like, we're supposed to be right on the cusp of nuclear war.
Yeah, I know.
focus.
Yeah.
Just do your job.
Tell me what the tell me what's in your world.
You know who doesn't freak out like this? Other people who do daily shows.
Yeah, like, this is him.
Just be healthier.
Stop acting like this and grow up.
That's the other thing, too.
Like, I don't know, maybe I'm not cool and I've never really been that cool fair.
But I find it pathetic to hear, like, 40 year olds talking about counterculture.
Yeah, I know.
I don't know what it is, but like, as I've gotten older, the interest in whether or not something is culture, counterculture or any of that stuff, it kind of becomes something that maybe has a little bit of like an artistic interest to me.
Something that's like a subversive piece of music or art, maybe.
But like, I don't know.
A lot of the aesthetic trappings and a lot of that stuff, I think, is a little bit for the youth.
You can't be a rebel and have $100 million.
First off, that's not how that works.
Fugazi wasn't cool and also had $100 million.
They were playing in the basement of a dilapidated church.
They weren't doing Green Day stadiums.
Green Day cannot be a rebel and fucking do Madison Square Garden.
That's not how that works.
You kind of lose the ability to have credibility as counterculture.
You have to sign, like, a 40 page contract to do a show.
You're not a rebel.
That's not how that works.
When you have a CNN level studio that you're broadcasting from, it's kind of tough to make that argument.
A condemned building comedy show is a rebellious comedy show.
Beyond counterculture.
Fuck off.
It's a space where counterculturalism can really thrive.
Yeah, absolutely.
It might still be an incredibly mainstream show in a big totally.
That is very possible for that to happen.
But you're not going to see something that's wildly subversive at, like, the Laugh Factory or I know it's soft at Zanies.
Yes.
I don't want to poke.
Listen, hey, man, I was a countercultural icon when I MC Zanies.
Right? Yeah.
I get what Alex was saying.
And again, maybe I'm a square, but I cared a lot more about that when I was 19.
That whole idea of, like, selling out or anything along those lines, who cares? Barry Gordon isn't around anymore.
You're going to sell out or whatever.
But it is disgusting to think that if you and I right now, we're at any point in time, like, listen, man, as we sit here in our fucking hoodies and ten issues, like, we're the true rebels and not going outside, the rebels who are fucking hermits.
No, that's not how it works.
No, no.
I sit in a fairly comfortable apartment having overdo to do the dishes surrounded by buttons, and I am neither culture nor counterculture.
We don't even have room.
That's just how it works.
Basically, instead of, like, forcing yourself to get rest or whatever the fuck you're talking about.
Alex, grow up.
Grow up.
Anyway, Steven touches on an interesting question, and that is, why aren't you on Rogen? But you know what? You just mentioned something.
joe told me was on.
The show was two years ago, and it was one of the biggest shows he ever did with who was on the show? I haven't heard that.
It was a great comedian, really funny.
Tim, Dylan and Joe's like, yeah, we have a couple of months.
A couple of months, couple of months.
And then it's pretty obvious what's going on.
Just a little too much heat for Joe to have me on, which is fine.
He had courage about the vaccines.
He had courage about censorship.
He's been criticizing the power structure, but he's not as hardcore as Steven Crowder.
And and I'll just say it, but at least the overall defense free speech, and I just don't think Joe can handle it.
Yeah, what is it going to take for Joe to just be like, I'm done with this shit.
What is it going to take? I'm done with your fucking malign me for not promoting you.
Yes, he's a piece of shit.
Whenever you don't give him enough attention, he winds and tells you you're a piece of shit.
Fuck off.
Yes.
And granted, this isn't sneaky snake.
I'm going to gut them like a pig.
We should talk about his case.
Not quite that, but this is still kind of insulting.
And it's on a different show.
It's on a different show? Yes.
And he's saying, essentially, hey, listen, Joe's got some courage, but that man is a coward at heart compared to you.
Exactly.
You're the guy who's in a fucking sit outside of college.
Meme? I see you wearing that shoulder holster and I think there's a man.
Oh, man.
I think that the Maltese Falcon is around the corner.
So Alex isn't worried, though, like, about Rogan not having him on.
It's totally cool.
We're out of dinner about a month ago last time I hung out with him, and it's just pet peeve not to bring it up.
And I just said, man, it really helped me with this upcoming court case because the whole media is against me.
If I could get on there and explain things.
He just said, Alex, there's too much craziness going on.
Let's just get through this.
We'll talk about it later.
So I'm not really worried about it.
Obviously, I'm the big interview he'd want.
He even said, listen, you're like nuclear weapons.
It's a big deal to have you on.
But I'm not worried about it.
It's really a question for Joe.
I'm just asking because you talk about how you're hanging out with them.
Not only if not him, he has a bunch of friends who could have you on.
He has a whole podcast network.
Tim Dylan could have you on.
Dick was just me.
I'd love to grow it eventually with other people and be able to throw more support behind folks.
But right now, let me say it on the current scale, steven Crowder is a ten, alex Jones is a ten, and Joe Robinson eight.
And I'll take an eight all day over our enemies that are in a zero, of course.
And so I'm nothing but thankful to Joe for all the heat he's taken having me on.
No, you're more than that.
You're also insulting it.
You know what? That's how to give out the inside baseball numbers work.
But I'm just going to leave it at this.
I'll tell you off there if you want, but it's private.
The very same people trying to silence me.
I'm not going to get into it on here, but there's been some real harassment of Joe and stuff that's going on.
I know.
Yes, I know that's happened with him.
And I'm on that list as well, so I know we all deal with it.
Oh, man.
Joe's getting threatened about having Alex on, and guess what? So Stephen but Stephen doesn't care cause he's a ten.
He's a ten.
What a bunch of losers.
Yep.
It's tough.
It's tough to watch a show like this and not really feel sad.
Yes, this is sad.
It's not good either.
Like, I would understand if something had like, an ethos that I disagreed with, a lot of points that I didn't agree with.
But if Stephen Crowder was like, he had a spark of real funny in him, or if there was an interesting angle and delivery on stuff, if his co hosts were worth a damn as sidekicks, I would say I disagree with this.
I think it sucks.
But they're doing a show this just as bad from all angles.
Really bad.
Yeah, man, that is just so sad.
It's so sad.
All of you are adult men talking about how great you are to children.
That's better than Rogue.
That is gross.
I'm so much more of a big, strong boy than Rogan.
I have all the courage in the world.
So at the end here, this is the last clip we've got because I got to go to mug club, which is the, like, behind the paywall segment.
And Alex is like, you know who's a rebel? A guy with a mug club at a paywall and a cigar club.
What a rebel? The true rebels.
Right? And Alex is talking at the end about how he has to go to do his own show.
So he wasn't going to be on that for very long.
So I don't really care about what's behind the pay wall.
Right.
But before they leave, alex tries to troll the media into covering him.
This is really sad.
OK, this is an information war.
It appears to be flooding you with funding.
You're one of the only professional people doing top flight comedy and analysis.
It's better than the production on, like, these late shows that giant budgets, 20 times your budget.
People should flood you with support and more importantly, word of mouth.
Because unless the real currency we all want is to override the censors and to win the infowars, absolutely everybody should support Steven Crowder.
Who's got the 500 pound testicles? Well, Joe's only got joe's only got 400 pound ones.
I admire Joe's balls.
Okay, stephen, yours are bigger.
Bigger and even more juicy.
Well, gosh, you did say you've been drinking too much.
And part of that has to do with the fact that I have the under the cabinet microwave.
I've learned my lesson, all right? No, I made a gay joke so it goes viral.
Stephen, that's funny.
You said you have to recharge your batteries.
Alex Jones is a robotic homosexual.
All right, look, alex Jones talks about Stephen Crowder's juicy ball.
Gosh.
Yeah.
When do I get my 900 million? For what? This is funny to them, but when Alex has to tell his balls joke and then say it's funny, that's a bad sign.
That's not good.
No, I didn't know it was a joke.
My get or done back when I did stand up.
Was it's funny? Yeah.
After every joke, I would say it's less now.
I think things are less effective when you say, like, hey, I'm doing this so the media will report on it.
That's fun and sad.
But also the thing that makes it funny is that both of them are huge homophobes.
Both of them are like violently.
Is that what's funny is that they can dip into the into their they make a joke of talking about Stephen's balls because it is gay to them and they hate gay people.
Right.
But I mean, they know that we've just spent too much time with I don't know what people who aren't funny really find funny.
It's funny to them because they're engaging in a form of homophobia, right.
And to them, from the target or being hurt by homophobia.
So it is quite funny to them.
Right.
To them, it's a transgressive concept.
And so the idea of someone saying that would blow their fucking minds into laughter.
I get that, but I don't get it.
I don't get it.
They're the real rebels, man.
I think that this would have been just a ways, maybe quite a ways below, like Andrew Dice Clay in the 80s in terms of being something that's like rebellious.
I mean, I'm an elitist comedy, but I'm a comedian.
That's what you're supposed to be.
But I can still laugh at things that are sophomoric but you just have to be good.
There has to be cleverness, there has to be direction, there has to be intent or thought behind it or, you know, something along those lines.
I get what you're saying, but I think that from a construction standpoint, the joke is the media reports on this interview as Alex likes Stephens juicy Balls.
Right? The amusing image is the news running that headline, right? But the real joke is that the news isn't going to cover this at all, just interview at all.
I mean, you guys are the joke, right? It's imagining the ways in which you are tricking the media into a troll headline that doesn't come to play.
It is very funny to listen to these guys.
Imagine how they are outsmarting the media.
Yeah, that's very funny.
Well, it's all in their game of being the best.
Yeah.
So this sucked.
I don't want to listen to anymore stephen Crowder.
Never again.
This is brutal.
But one of the things that I found very interesting was that there is probably not that much difference between how he presents himself here and on his show in terms of this stuff.
I think part of that is because he clearly felt the ability to steamroll Stephen.
He even throws to two clips.
That was not hard.
Yes.
So I think there is a sense that, like, all right, I'm just going to do my show on his show.
Yeah.
He can't handle me.
No, he's got no chance.
I'll just be able to do that.
Then I'll call him a ten or Rogan's an eight and I'll compliment his balls be fine.
Yeah.
It is like kicking a choir boy and then patting him on the head, being like, you did such a great job getting kicked.
That was bad.
Yeah.
But there really isn't a ton of message discrepancy.
It is just kind of like, I've been wronged.
I didn't get a trial, blah, blah, blah.
They're coming for you.
Yeah.
Explain to me how a man can insist that he is both apologized and taken responsibility for his behavior and yet still be like, well, the family should get nothing.
That's a question for Alex.
And the mug club did not ask that.
We don't know the answer.
That's surprised.
The mug club does not do a lot of follow ups.
That's what I've heard.
That's what I've heard of Stephen.
And that's another reason why he can have message discipline and stay with the same thing he says on infowars is because Steven's not going to ask him.
I'm fucking barely even talk.
It's in no way a hostile environment.
Yes.
I would say that Rogan is a more confrontational interviewer than Steve.
Yeah.
Just because he'd be, like, to say something funnier about that.
Steven did the same thing that Greenwald did, which is, like, tried to offer answers to questions he was asking Alex.
This would be a good answer if you want to just take this.
Yeah.
He was massaging Alex's shoulders while he's doing it.
He was participating in being interviewed while interviewing.
Just said because he thought it would be a better interview, I imagine.
Probably.
Yeah.
Anyway, we'll be back, Jordan, but until then, we have a website.
Indeed we do.
It's knowledgefight.com.
Yeah.
We are on Twitter.
Is that knowledge underscore fight? I saw you tweet today.
Listen, it showed up.
The algorithm knows that I fucking hate Glenn Greenwald.
So it shows me Glenn Greenwald, and then I get so mad.
But I'm not on Twitter.
He's back.
He's not.
All right, we'll be back.
But until then, I'm Leo.
I'm Leo.
I'm DCI SCARC.
I'm wilford snippet snapped of the gripple PIBBLE.
And now here comes the sex robots.
Andy and Sansa, you're on the air.
Thanks for holding, Alex.
I'm a first time caller.
I'm a huge fan.
I love your work.
I love you.