A young fireplug of a lawyer got his teeth in Alex Jones and decided that this was something he'd like to gnaw on.
And, you know, so he tore through a series of people who were designated as corporate reps and then published their depositions online.
And so the haters we had a field day with the a corporate reps.
No one else that did infowars was willing to do it again.
No one wanted to have their deposition placed on video online.
To the ridicule of all the allocators.
Knowledge flight.
There are people there's a cult, there's something called Knowledge First or Knowledge Fight.
These people apparently live by loving the hate, Alex Jones.
And they bounce on every piece of video they can find.
Knowledge Fight.
There's a website called Knowledge Bite.
And these are a couple of bottom feeders who make their chops heating out.
And so they have episodes almost daily.
The corporate reps didn't want to be exposed to that again.
I guess I should say it.
I got my ass kicked.
Knowledge Fights.
Knowledge fights on.
Knowledge fights on knowledge.
Hey, everybody.
Welcome back to knowledge fight.
I'm Ben.
I'm Jordan.
and talk a little bit about Alex Jones.
Oh, yes, we are, Dan.
Jordan.
What's your bright spot today, buddy? My bright spot is I was on Marty and Sarah love wrestling this week.
Fun podcast.
Our friends Marty and Sarah Do.
Sarah is in Belgium, and so Marty needed someone to fill in.
And we had a fun conversation about my feelings about Bray Wyatt.
That's excellent.
I imagine that would be the main focus.
A little bit more about Bray Wyatt and then some talk about how I don't understand what the deal is with Orange Cassidy.
Well, that's fair.
It was a lot of fun.
People can find that over at I guess you just search for Marty and Sara Love Wrestling podcasts.
You know how to find podcast? I mean, if you don't know how to find podcasts, that's kind of an interesting thing that you have to find us.
Yeah, exactly.
Do you come here from north at US, tell you to check out these dorks and these losers? Did you download this bootleg from LimeWire? What's going on here? Yeah.
So what's your bright spot? My bright spot is shoes.
Dan, my wife, very beautiful person.
Lovely.
Love her very much.
Sure.
She's my favorite.
Found out recently that my shoes are garbage, as they almost always are.
Got me some new shoes and they're amazing.
Nice.
They're amazing.
I'm the fastest tennis player maybe there's ever been right now.
And if you fuck up, you can say new shoes.
New shoes.
Yeah.
You know what? All sorts of things can be just completely written off because you have new shoes.
Oh, what's even better, they're a little bit too big.
Just a little bit.
It's actually very comfortable.
But when you're running, that's an excuse.
But also, your feet are like goldfish, and they will grow to the sides of the container.
That does sound correct.
From what I remember in basic biology when I was about 8th grade.
That is what they said about Koi feet.
Let me take a look at those shoes.
These are different shoes.
I'm wearing the old shoes.
I don't want to screw up the good shoes.
Sure.
Yeah.
One time I got new shoes.
They were pretty bright white because they're new.
And I wore them to an open mic just because my older shoes had fallen apart.
Right.
And so I wore them, and I walked in and immediately sorry.
And Choxy and his buddy John McBride, the two of them were sitting at a table and they saw me, and they just started doing a run of jokes about my new shoes.
I love being comedian.
You don't get that.
It's just my favorite.
Yes.
I couldn't stop laughing.
Anyway, Jordan, today we have an episode to go over.
We're going to do some fun stuff, but you might have noticed in the intro there, we have a new special intro courtesy of DJ Danarchy.
Thank you so much.
Norm Pattis, lawyer extraordinaire, one of the premier lawyers, first Amendment lawyers, constitutional lawyers for shit bags.
He has a podcast called Law and Legitimacy.
And on a recent episode after the trial, he did a little bit of a breakdown.
Bad idea of what happened, how he was wrong, bad idea how the appeal is going to go great.
And he decided to bring us up.
What a terrible idea.
First of all, I mean, Norm, you didn't get the memo that you're not supposed to talk about us.
That's the rule.
That's rule number one there.
You just accidentally revealed a lot more than you wish.
Quite a bit.
He mentioned us in a bankruptcy hearing where he called us Knowledge First.
Right.
Which was great.
And I think we have a cottage industry out of making fun of Alex.
Fantastic.
And that was just good, clean fun.
But this mention of us is deeply problematic for Alex and everybody at Infowars.
Yeah.
And in case you could hear the intro and feel like things are maybe taken a little bit out of context for taking a beat yeah.
Here is the clip of Norm talking about us on his podcast.
And afterwards, I think we'll have a lot to celebrate.
And if there's one thing I've learned about Alex, it's that these are these were video depositions.
People love to hate him.
And so the haters we had a field day with the corporate reps and the corporate reps, there's no there there's no real organization.
So they testified about what they knew, and their answer to most things is I don't know.
Good question.
Really.
And that young man was able to persuade a trial judge in Texas that this was wilful failure, that the corporation had an obligation to produce a representative that could answer his questions because there had to be answers.
And so there was another deadline in Texas to produce a corporate rep.
We selected I selected a person from Connecticut because no one else did.
Infowars was willing to do it again.
No one wanted to have their placed on video online to the ridicule of all the allocators.
Because you know what? There are people there's a website I learned about called Knowledge Fight.
These are a couple of bottom feeders make their chops heating out, and so they have episodes almost daily.
They'll call me out.
They'll call this one.
I mean, I don't know if Alex is going to get a percentage of the royalties for the space he rented.
Good luck.
And so the Alex haters didn't the corporate reps didn't want to be exposed to that again.
So the Connecticut representative testified.
She didn't satisfy the fireplug or the Texas judge.
She testified in Connecticut three and a half days.
I called it the Gilligan's island.
Direct.
The guy had her up there, the lawyer for the plaintiffs.
Wait, the Gilligan that's three hour tour, not three and a half days.
Yeah, that doesn't make sense at all.
But that's norm, stand up chops coming.
Yeah, I was going to say so.
Norm, come on, man, you're showing too much here.
So apparently Brittany Paws got hired as the corporate representative because we everyone else was too worried about being roasted on our boat here's.
What's the most important thing? Like, okay, you know what, Dan? You kicked ass and you brought a lot of work into it.
But also the trials were the lawyers did a great job.
You know, like, your contribution was spectacular, but it was limited and it was shared.
In this case, Dan, you cost Norm Pattis personally $30,000, maybe less, because they had to hire Britney Paul.
That 30 grand is all you.
Yeah, it might be.
I mean, look, I don't want to break down quantifying things.
What is important is that there is a recognition here of a behavioral change that was made at Infowars, which is, prior to this, Rob Do was totally fine going in and being a Kangal hat wearing doofus, sitting in there, being I don't know how many did he do? A couple, actually.
Yeah, exactly.
And then Daria was totally fine in these depositions.
I don't actually think she's afraid of me at all.
I'm afraid of her anything.
But these people were not willing to do this and face the kind of scrutiny in the public eye that our podcast brings.
Literally, only our podcast brings.
Right.
And the other thing that it reveals, too, is that there are discussions about they know us being a motivating factor and them not wanting to be the corporate rep, which is fucking hilarious.
That means this conversation happened.
We need you to be the corporate rep again.
I don't want to do it.
Those two guys will be mean to me.
Those two guys in Chicago will just roast the shit out of me.
Good luck.
Royalties.
Also, normally we're commerce based.
He's really got to stop with this brain landlord joke.
Yeah.
He's been doing this too much in the aftermath of the trial.
Too much.
Like, I live right free in people's heads.
Sure.
I mean, it's fun and all.
Like, I remember the first time I heard it when I was maybe, like, 13.
That's a really interesting phrase.
Now it's a little bit especially when Norman said it, like, a hundred times.
It's getting very old.
And I think that it's evidence of him either deflecting from reality or not understanding what I and this show is about.
Like, I don't give a shit.
He is only serving the purposes of what I hope to achieve.
Yes.
Alex is a window.
Alex is nothing.
The sky and everything cool is out there after we get through Alex, not after we get through Alex.
In terms of him going away right after.
You understand? Exactly.
If you see the window, you can see through the window.
There's a tree out there.
Yes, Norm.
None of this lives free in my head.
I think it's hilarious.
Yeah, it's even funnier now that you it's too funny.
It's too funny.
So.
Thank you, Norm.
It's beyond a bright spot.
It's a revelation.
It is.
Because it is such an acknowledgement of how much gaslighting they've been doing to us.
It's physically impossible for them not to know.
Right? We've known that for a long time.
But what they knew, how much they knew, what it meant to them, all that stuff that we could only guess at that we can only guess.
And it kind of drives you mad because you're like, there's no way they put that much thought into it.
I think that's partially because you and I are our self deprecating people by nature.
It's like, Get off your fucking high horse.
These people don't care about you.
No one cares about you in your head.
And zero people.
You're gaslighting yourself along with them.
You think you're so important that they care about you, is my thought process.
That's why it was so shocking.
I'd heard that he mentioned us on the podcast, and when I was listening to it, I was like, what the fuck? That's all I had heard.
I had heard the rent free thing, so I was like, oh, to find out the second part is mindboggling.
Also, it is a bad idea to insult somebody when they have a DJ willing to remix that insult.
If you were in high school and there was a bully bothering you, but you had a DJ who was going to remix their insult, you've won, right? Yeah.
And if you have so little respect for the bully that whatever insult they're saying is funny yes, hilarious.
And do your best.
Good luck.
Thank you, Norm.
Yeah.
Anyway, we have an episode, like I said, but before we get to it, let's take a little moment, say hello to some new walk.
Oh, that's a great idea.
So first, Wilford Snipple snapple of the gripple.
PIBBLE.
Thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Wait, you can't donate to you well, now I can't use that as a name at the end because that's somebody else.
Now there's a walk blame.
So I have to come with a new alien.
Yeah, this is like a Twitter handle.
They bought it from you? Maybe.
Mind slum lord.
Wait, why did that one show up first in your brain? I don't know.
That's a question.
Chef says trans rights.
Thank you so much.
You're now a policy won't.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much.
And we agree.
Thanks.
Next rolly, boys.
Thank you so much.
You're an hour policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Next, Lucy Lawling on the trail.
Thank you so much.
You're now a PolicyWonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much.
Next, never expected to learn that Alex Jones thinks our last name is weird.
We pronounce it Pet ingill.
The gripple.
PIBBLE is silent.
Thank you so much.
You are now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Next, angela and Chase of House gripple PIBBLE.
Thank you so much for now policy wonk.
Here's how far behind sometimes you can really get it.
Really shortly after the gribble pivot and oops all swear he carries.
Thank you so much.
You're now a policy wonk.
I'm a policy wonk.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Now, Jordan.
Yes.
As you know, we've talked about this privately.
I've been having some insomnia type issues the past week, has been really tough with sleep, schedule, traveling, and I think it has a little bit of an effect on what you want to do, how much you can take on and what have you.
Sure.
And I found myself this week definitely having a like, I don't even want to turn on Alex's show.
I don't even want to listen to it.
It's frustrating.
I know I'm going to be bored.
I'm already exhausted.
I don't really want to do this.
And so I can guess what he's saying, and I feel like I'm just not interested.
Not hard.
And so I decided, hey, Norm talking shit about us covering deposition.
We're going through his whole show.
No.
All these people are afraid to sit in a deposition room.
Oh, no.
Today we have another formulaic objection.
So today what we're going to be looking at is the deposition of Don Salazar.
Okay.
The longtime writer and editor at Infowars.
One of the people who wrote some of the articles that were primary in the Sandy Hook conspiracies.
Right.
Someone who has a number of emails around the Sandy Hook conversation.
Yes.
Somebody who followed us on Twitter until we mentioned it and then he unfollowed us, ran away.
Goodbye forever.
This is from the Connecticut case.
Got you.
And Don is somebody who I've always had a little bit of a fascination with because I think he is a soldier, as they say in the I don't know what world, but gangland warfare world.
Yeah.
Got you.
Sure.
He strikes me in the same way as someone like a Darya.
And that is like, oh, you believe.
Right.
Or whether or not you believe, you believe in whatever the underlying mission is, you are going to follow orders regardless of whether or not they are sanctioned by the Geneva Conventions.
A lie.
And you believing some insane things are undistinguishable for you because whatever is motivating it is more important than its primary.
He is somebody who's written a lot of horrible shit over the course of his time.
He seems like an asshole, but he's also somebody who I've never heard talk.
I've never seen him in front of the camera.
He's not an on camera guy.
That's true.
And so I had nothing really to prepare me to see his decision, like, what's going to happen here? No.
It's afraid of him anymore, I'll say that.
For one thing, he doesn't strike me as savvy as I imagined him.
So his intelligence is not of the worldshaking variety.
He might be a perfectly smart person, but I don't find him in the way he answers questions and the way he processes what's going on to be all that like, remarkable.
Okay.
And then also he's 37, and that really bummed me out.
Right.
For some reason, I thought he was like 26 or like, I don't know, in the Alex Darren McBrien a range for some reason.
37 was about the exact age that I was surprised to hear.
Yeah.
And I was disappointed.
Maybe it's because I'm 38.
Sure.
It's like I can kind of whatever the landmarks in life.
Right.
They would have been fairly similar.
We would have been the same age at about certain times, experience certain things, world events from the same presumed level of maturity.
Right.
And that kind of makes me sad.
Yeah.
It would be less sad if he were on the front nine of life, so to speak, instead of the back nine is where he's started.
He's starting on the 10th hole.
And you're going, this is not going to end well for you, man.
The other thing too is, though, I realized how delusional that was of me because he's been there since 2012.
So the idea that he would be 26 is like, what? He started at 16.
This is ridiculous.
That seems like the appropriate level of writing he's at, though.
You're not wrong.
Yeah.
So this deposition is quite interesting.
It's taken by Chris Matty and yeah, let's just jump in.
Begins with some formalities and stuff.
And the first question, the first bit that you want to get into is how did you prepare for this deposition always my favorite question.
It's a great way to open well, and it always reveals that they didn't really do it at all.
What did you do to prepare for today's deposition, Mr.
Salazar? I went over a few of the articles that are in question.
Which article? I re read the FBI Sandy Hook.
FBI says nobody died at Sandy Hook.
And probably the first.
How big? Article that I wrote.
The first article, probably.
Sorry.
How big? Wolfgang.
How Big? Article that I wrote.
And that article was titled something to the Effect of Investigator Threatened.
Sandy Hook.
Investigator Threatened.
Something to that effect? Yes, sir.
That's it.
You reviewed those two articles.
Did you review anything else? I didn't go in depth.
I kind of just glossed over them.
That's pretty much it.
Okay, so other than launching all of those two articles, did you review any other materials in advance of your deposition today? No.
Other than Attorney Woman, did you discuss your deposition with anybody else today? No, sir.
You haven't communicated with Alice Jones that you're being deposed? No, sir.
You haven't communicated that to Rob Do? No, sir.
You haven't communicated that to David Jones? No, sir.
Okay.
You ordinarily be working today? Yes.
And you're currently employed by who? Free speechystemsinfoworks.com.
As this deposition progresses, you get the sense that maybe Adam should have done a little more to prepare for this interview.
There are basic elements of his timeline and surrounding context of his writing that Maddie can demonstrate, which Adan seems to think are like, undiscoverable secrets.
Right.
Also, I find it very strange and probably difficult to believe that Adan didn't talk to Alex or Rob Do about being deposed.
They work together.
This is in relation to a suit against Alex and the company.
And as Adan says, he was supposed to be at work that day.
It seems like he would have to come up with a reason he couldn't make it to work.
So I guess he must have just lied to his employer right off the bat.
That doesn't inspire confidence in him as a credible witness highlighting his willingness to deceive.
Yeah, I told no, listen, I didn't tell Alex or Owen or anything because I told him my grandma died and I had to go to the funeral, so I'm a reliable source.
Come on.
Let the record show that this guy is a liar.
I can understand if Adon doesn't want to say that he spoke with Alex about what he was going to testify as.
That would probably or even possibly give the impression that Alex coached him, but I don't understand what issues there would be with him just telling Alex about the existence of this deposition.
Alex would have to know that they were interested in talking to Adan since he wrote these articles that are involved in the suit.
I could possibly see a scenario where Adam was afraid to tell Alex that he was actually going to show up and talk to the lawyers, but outside of something like that, I have a hard time accepting that this didn't come up.
Yeah, it's possible, but it's just like it seems very weird.
I'm going to throw this out at you, okay.
If I was going to be deposed for anything and they had like six books I had to read and I would be like, okay, I'm going to make it through at least a full two or three of these books, right? I've got the time, there's the need to do it, and then maybe I can pass off the other three as being fine.
But Adon is only telling me that he skimmed less than 5000 words.
Right.
It's not like the articles are long.
Some of them may be longer than you think, but not that long.
Yeah, it seems really strange.
You would think that if you really wanted to be an active participant, you would go, you'd read the article, you'd figure out like, where the information that you were working from came from.
At least brush up on some of that so you can defend your process.
But yeah, you just skim some stuff.
Yeah.
So Adam started in April 2012 and as we know, the shooting happened in December 2012.
So he was pretty new there.
Yeah.
But before we get to any of that, we talk about what he was doing before April 2012.
When did you guys start working for Free Speech Systems? April 2012.
Where were you? I held three jobs.
I wrote for textbroker.com.
I also was a contractor for Quest Diagnostics.
I was also a Google search engine optimizer.
I worked for a contractor for Google called Leadforce.
It's somewhat notable that Don began his time at Info is only a short time before Synthany hook occurred.
He was a fresh new on the job reporter when this story started.
And as you can tell from this resume that Don is giving, he didn't have previous work experience that would make him well prepared for the role that he found himself in.
No the job at Quest is basically a courier position, shuttling samples from hospitals and doctors office to a central testing facility.
The job he had with tech broker is the sort of thing where he would get paid to write little blurbs for websites.
Sort of a freelance gig thing.
Sure.
This is where you might go if you want someone to write a paragraph about a lamp you're selling and you don't want to pay too much.
Text broker is also the sort of place you might go to get filler for a website that's designed for gaming affiliate link systems.
To give you some sense of the operation in their basic category of services, you can choose their low rate option, which has this blurb.
This is how it describes that service.
Did they write their own blurb using their service? They might have.
Okay.
Quote, I accept mistakes in spelling, grammar, and expression in favor of a lower price for writing, where you can just write what, random misspelled words.
You can make about 1.1 cents per word for that.
If you have to pay attention to spelling and grammar, you can make up to about, like, 5.5 cents a word.
Right.
To be clear, I'm not knocking the hustle, and there's no shame in this kind of gig.
It's just not necessarily the sort of writing work you do if you had in demand skills in that field.
And it's something that maybe isn't a great thing to be like on the resume for the job that he ends up in.
Yeah, I think heinlein got paid 1.1 cents a word at one point, but it was different currency wise at the time.
I don't think he's on the same level.
Right? I don't think so.
Hemingway got money subtracted for punctuation.
Yeah, too many commas.
The job at Leap Force is described here as an SEO subcontractor for Google.
More specifically, the company hires people to work at home and do repetitive searches to evaluate the results, basically to use as information for better ad placement.
It's a pain in the ass kind of job, and you can find tons of reviews about the grind and how it's really only worth doing as a side gig for some extra cash unless you can just turn off your brain.
And the people on, like, glass door talk about this as miserable.
Yeah.
I mean, no offense to a Don or anybody else working these kinds of jobs.
It actually does show quite a bit of initiative for him to have these three gigs running simultaneously.
That's impressive.
He's got a hustle.
In a certain sense, he's got a hustle.
I just don't think it's the kind of resume I would be incredibly impressed by if I were running a super important media network and I was looking to hire a reporter, editor of the news.
Maybe you take a chance on this candidate and you get lucky.
But Adam's writing and behavior are pretty central to the claims that infowars was disseminating.
That just lost them a billion dollars.
So it doesn't seem like this one worked out great.
When I worked at the coupon place testing coupons, that was my whole job, is I would go in there and I would test expired coupons.
I'd put the code into a website, and I'd click, can you buy? And they'd be like, no.
And I'd be like, you're goddamn right, no.
That was my whole day, right? Yeah.
At no point in time was I like, okay, now that I've finished this, I'm going to go work for the Tribune as a cub reporter.
That's not the jump.
Let's even go a step further.
It's not a cub reporter.
No, that's right.
I'm not the features editor at Tribune today.
Asadon will go on to describe his role immediately.
Was essentially he could write whatever he wanted.
There was no oversight.
It's going from Coupon cabin to being to write by hand in the newspaper, basically, while people writing it, while they're reading it.
So just make it up as you go along.
It's wild.
That's crazy.
Not best practices.
So now we get to Adam's educational background.
Okay, tell me about your educational background, please.
I went to the University of Texas for about a year and a half and majored in liberal arts.
Took several English courses there, and I also did half a semester at Austin Community College.
I don't know why you would even bring up that you did half a semester at a community college.
It's just confusing.
And it sounds like you're saying that you signed up for some classes and you just didn't finish them.
Austin Community College has 16 week semesters, but they also offer some courses that run eight weeks.
So it's entirely possible that Adan is expressing that he finished some of those eight week classes.
But if that's the case, he should have said, I took a few classes at ACC.
That makes me think that it's more likely that he signed up and then just didn't finish them.
Also, I don't know how it is at all universities, but typically liberal arts isn't a major in sort of a category of majors.
You wouldn't be a liberal arts major.
No, you'd be within the liberal arts.
I mean, in the early year that he did finish, maybe he hadn't chosen a specific major.
He was just taking the basic courses.
Yeah.
And you were drawn towards the soft sciences of humanities.
Yes.
That's fine, but I don't think liberal arts is a major.
I didn't go to UT Austin, though.
I went to a community college for a while, and I hated it so much that after the second week, I would drive there to avoid telling my parents that I wasn't going to school.
But I would sleep in the parking lot in the car in case they put, like, a low jack on your car? Exactly.
Just in case.
What, am I going to go in and sleep in the class? No, that's disrespectful.
I'm going to not go to their class and sleep nearby.
That's pretty good.
Yeah.
I did not put that on many resumes, though.
I didn't put it on there when I hired you.
Yeah, exactly.
So I'm a huge fan of education and the academic environment as a whole, but I do try to be as clear as possible that I don't think it's necessary for everyone to partake in.
You can be as smart and capable as anyone who went to college without any higher education.
And many folks I know bear that out over here looking at you, buddy.
There are so many hyper competent people who never went to college, and those people aren't folks that I would look at and say, hey, they should take some classes because.
They're doing just fine.
On the other hand, if you don't have any formal education, then find yourself as a highly placed reporter at a propaganda outlet where you argue that grieving families are actors and you're discussing your educational background in a deposition that about that shitty work that you did.
I might think that your lack of training or familiarity with the field that you're in is a problem and it could have helped if you would have taken some classes.
Yeah, to be perfectly blunt, I don't think that any amount of classes would have helped the dom.
Not that he's dumb or anything, just that I don't think that he's interested in doing the thing that he's doing.
Well, I don't think he needs to get better.
If you have the moral framework necessary to do what you're doing now, then you're fine.
Whether you're an expert at J school or not, you're going to do what you're doing.
Yeah.
You might just need a moment of revelation about yourself as opposed to classes.
Honestly.
So by this point, the deposition, we have a sense of what Adam's resume would have probably looked like when he applied to be a writer and editor at Infowars.
He had some freelance style writing experience, but beyond that, iffy credential, he had no experience in media or journalism and he had no education in the field, but he got hired anyway, and it seems like there might be possibly a reason why.
I liked Alex Jones.
And the message? Before you ever applied to free speech systems, you were essentially an audience member, correct? Yes, he was a fan.
Every time I learn more about how Infowars operates, I'm like, there's no way.
There's just no way.
It's usually a contest that people win and they end up working.
I guess that maybe is for more the on air folks, because given the razzle dazzle of an Infowars contest about writing, cause there's like no benchmark.
There's no like oh, here's good writing and here's bad writing.
You've just got the same Infowars essay contest.
Oh, no, I think that's the low rate.
Not worried about typos and spellings and characters.
1.1 cent.
Yeah, that's 1.1 cent a word.
So Mattie asks, what was it about Infowars that really got you interested? What Alex Jones show and the written content? Probably they're refusal to believe the narrative behind 911.
Okay.
Do you suspect the narrative that the mainstream media had reported concerning 911? What was that question again? Were you suspicious? I'm sorry, just let me finish my question.
I know you're anticipating what I'm going to say, but did you personally suspect the narrative that the mainstream media had reported concerning 911? Yes, I was suspicious of it.
So in eleven years after 911, that's a motivating.
I guess maybe whenever he got interested in it could have been gears prior.
So motivating factor suspicion about 911 and their refusal to accept the mainstream narrative.
What's your career path like? If it starts with, I thought 911 was an inside job, and then the next step is, I'm the editor@infowars.com.
That's a career path.
I saw employment because I was impressed with these people refusing to believe that 911 happened.
That is great.
We're told that is great.
So I appreciate this instinct on Maddie's part, and that is to go from this like, oh, you were suspicious about 911.
Why? Yeah.
Because in a deposition setting, that can lead to some interesting things.
And what in particular were you suspicious of? I didn't think we were being told the full truth about various parts of that narrative.
Like, can you go into a little bit more detail about what you thought the gaps were in what the reporting was? I could.
I suppose I didn't think that the planes should have been able to take down the buildings as they were taken down.
It seemed like a controlled demolition, which is a lot of people still believe, actually.
Are you one of those? That was probably the biggest one, especially with building seven falling and collapsing, controlled demolition style when no plane hit it.
So those are the biggest factors.
And did the fact that you felt it was implausible that the buildings would have collapsed the way they did cause you to suspect whether the United States government was involved in some way in the attack injection? Yes, sir.
Okay.
So this is a really interesting clip, because there's a couple of things happening here.
The first is really transparent, which is how a conspiracy theorist answers a question.
Adan is asked why he was suspicious about 911, but it's a conspiracy he hasn't focused on in a while.
So a lot of the talking points are a bit foggy in his memory, so he tries to give a vague, non answer.
Then Maddie asks for something more specific, and Ada basically it doesn't seem right.
And Building seven is a response, which is pretty soft.
Yeah.
The second thing is, something that will become important later is some of Maddie's questions develop.
This is something that Adon is suspicious about.
He has some inconclusive things to point to that he can use to justify these suspicions.
And based on having those suspicions, he just testified to Maddie that led him to suspect the US.
Government was involved.
This provides a clear example of Adan's thought process, where he's willing to take things that look weird and make him suspicious and use them to build up baseless explanatory narratives.
Hold on to this for later, because it will become clear how relevant this is to the matter at hand and how much of a mistake this was on Adon's part.
In reflection, yeah, maybe it doesn't, you know, lead to any direct consequences, but if you're analyzing this and looking at the way he describes his process and how he interacts with information, it's very damning.
That will become clearer later.
Yeah.
I mean, that's hard to I do appreciate one thing about Infowars employees that will never not be hilarious to me is that at some point, doesn't the lawyer have to go in and be like, before you answer the question, look at me to see whether or not I'm going to object? It in a deposition.
It's a different but in this setting, you still have to answer the question unless it's some other kind of objection.
But these objections are just, yeah, you can't be away, but I think you could just still say, like, I don't know or not answer.
Sure.
Just always look at your lawyer before your answer.
It's not hard.
Right.
Isn't that's what I would do? I'd be like, my answer is so when Adan got hired, he got some training.
Sure.
But it wasn't what you thought.
Yeah, it's not really training.
When you started at Info Wars in April of 2012, did you receive any training of any kind just to learn the back end systems, like WordPress and things of that nature.
Okay, so that training basically involved learning how to use the software programs that you are going to be using every day as an employee, correct? Yes.
Did you receive any training concerning the writing function of your job? No.
Did you ever objection.
A form? Did you ever receive any training during your tenure? Free speech systems concerning the writing function of your job? No.
Wow.
Have you ever received any training during the course of your employment concerning investigative journalistic practice? They train you more at, like, a fast food restaurant.
Yeah, I remember when I went to I worked at JCPenney's for a cup of coffee when I was younger, and there was an entire hours long thing about the corporate culture, the rules and harassment policies.
You had to sit in a room and watch videos.
At the very least, you had to sign something saying that you understood the rules of what they told you.
Yeah.
It seems like there's less oversight at Infowars than JCPenney's, man, if you have walked into any newspaper in the world and they didn't tell you first things first about the quote in house style, if they were just like, right away, my dude.
Also, I would say that every single job that I've ever had, at least the first half a week, maybe even the first week you're working with somebody else.
Yeah, absolutely.
You're trained Shadowing.
Yeah.
Because you can be trusted just to know exactly how to do your job.
And it's wild.
That does not seem to be the case here.
It is wild to not receive training on the job you are ostensibly doing.
They taught him how to post things on the Internet through WordPress.
Yeah, that was it.
You know what? It kind of makes me think of, like, some temp gigs I've had yeah.
Where it's just like, all right, here's how you enter this data go do it.
I don't give a shit.
I got other work to do.
What did he think that first six months, right? He had to have been walking around like, they know, right? They know I have no idea what I'm doing.
They have to look at me and know.
Maybe that's part of the test, though.
You have the psychopathic confidence there's no such thing as impostor syndrome.
Exactly.
Because I'm the greatest.
Yeah.
So you also got no training about what news to cover what you understood when you applied Infowars, that you were applying for an editor and writer position when you first started.
It sounds like one of the things that you needed to do was update news items on the Infowars.com website, correct? Yes.
And what do you mean by update? Kind of like, find news items and republish them on Info or with a link back to the original source, find news items that appeared elsewhere on the Internet, and then put a link to that news item on the Infowars.com website, correct? Yes, sir.
And how would you determine which news items to highlight on the Infowars.com website? That was subjective.
So basically, whatever I thought would be good on the website.
Did you receive any guidance or training on that in any way? No.
That's wild.
I know.
Words fail.
I just don't know how it's so nuts that, like, you have to think, like, that can't be true.
That can't be true.
But it could be.
It's the only place in the world where it could be true.
It could be true here.
And, like, the opening of a WeWork.
These are the only two scams where you can pull up having no clue what you're doing, and just be like, yeah, fuck it.
Wow.
I'm just making noises, man.
Yeah.
I don't know how to deal with that information.
I would have straight up quit so fast.
This is a scam.
This is a scam? Yes.
I would have just been like, or at least this is trouble.
This is a recipe for leaving aside anything about the ideology or anything about Infowars.
A business that runs like this.
I don't know if payroll works like this.
What are we doing? What is going on? That is the roommate scam.
If I was interviewing for that job, I would view it the same way as the roommate scam.
You know, where it's like, no, I'll move in with you and be a roommate, but I need $1,000 upfront to move here, and then I'll give you $2,000, whatever, or whatever it is.
I didn't know about that.
Yeah, it's a great scam.
It works for somebody, but it is the job equivalent of that.
It's like, hey, man, come on in.
You're a new editor? No.
I don't believe you for a fucking second.
You are trying to make me the CEO and then blame me for something.
I'm the fall guy, right? This is a bait and switch.
Here, for sure.
Yeah.
No.
You should probably and it was like, thanks a little less.
It was more loose back in 2012.
And now we learned our lessons, and we're kind of stricter about what we republish, and I'll ask you some questions about that.
But at the time you started, you could go to any website, select a news item that you thought your audience might be interested in, and publish it to infowars.com, correct? Yes.
Wild.
So we've learned our lesson thing.
You think that that's about, like, content, like Sandy Hook stuff, but it's not.
He explained later in a clip that I didn't cut that basically there are some websites that are litigious about repurposing their content.
Yeah.
It did sound like he was trained on stealing.
And so he's like, basically by trial and error, you learn that the AP doesn't like it when you just steal their articles.
Right.
And so you just avoid AP articles.
That's pretty sad.
In terms of the lessons you've learned are respecting intellectual property.
I guess it is analogous to learning about which dumpsters are good to get food from.
There's definitely certainly something along those lines.
They are nothing if not info record.
We info scavenge in the info war.
So I think that if you're in a position like a don, you always have to, whether you believe it or not, put on the front facing facade company line that you are reporting facts.
Yes.
You're doing factual reporting.
Doing the god's work.
Yeah.
Do you consider yourself to be reporting facts, or do you consider yourself to be writing your opinion? How do you consider the type of writing you're doing? Objection to form.
I believe it's probably you write the facts with maybe like a right leading slant instead of the left leaning slant, the mainstream media approach.
Okay.
So if I understand correctly, in your writing, you are reporting facts, but to the extent there's any sort of editorializing of those facts, you put a right leaning slant on them? Yes.
And usually yes, I think so.
And is that because you know that your audience is used to the right of the political spectrum? My audience and me? Yes.
Right.
If I started writing left wing manifestos, your audience will never know what the heck happened.
Right, right.
Yeah.
Well, I think the journalistic outfits, like the AP and stuff, they pretend to be objective, but they're not.
And we don't pretend to be objective.
I'm sorry, what? When you say you pretend to be objective, I assume you don't need that.
We wear our bias on our sleeves.
Sorry.
Not really.
No, absolutely not.
Alex's entire brand is he's above the left right parents.
That's the whole thing.
Yeah.
The right leaning slant of this is absolutely a betrayal of the central premise of Infowars.
But also quite obvious.
So not revelatory.
It's just embarrassing that Adan would phrase it this way in a under oath setting because Alex probably disagrees.
Yeah, I'm not right wing.
The hard part about these depositions is I always feel like we should really, really you know, no matter how basic a concept you think you're dealing with, you need to go further and further down.
What do you think a journalist does? Well, they tried to do that with Kit Daniels.
Right.
That didn't go well.
That was weird.
Yeah, good point.
And to be fair, I think that you could probably find some fertile ground in there.
Right.
But this is already 4 hours long, the deposition.
That's true.
Probably don't need to get down to like first principles.
Basic core concepts.
I would really like to get down to the very nitty gritty and be like, let's go with a glossary of words, my man.
I would love using this.
There's nobody in the world who would love if every one of these depositions was a Ken Burns documentary more than me.
Right.
Naturally.
That's what I want.
Of course you can't do it.
Other humans have other things to do.
I understand.
So Adon gets to talking about his research method.
They're good.
When you are reporting facts to your audience, I take it that it is important for you to accurately report what those facts are, correct? Yes.
And when you're writing about a particular topic, what do you do to educate yourself about the topic and the facts that you're going to convey? I do research and pretty much read everything I can before I jump into an article.
Where do the sources of information come from that you read? I do a Google search on Google News and also we'll look back at anything that Infowars has written and maybe look at a YouTube video or two, try to find various different data points to try to formulate facts and opinions on the subject.
When you are doing research for piece you're writing, you are doing that research exclusively from internet sources, correct? Yes.
Including Info or own previous material? Yes, sir.
That doesn't inspire confidence.
Wow.
My research methods are Googling things.
Looking at Infowars articles from the past and maybe some YouTube videos.
Yes.
Yeah.
This is the dream.
He's living the dream.
Isn't that what he's doing? Well, it's easy in a certain sense.
He doesn't have to do anything but occasionally Google stuff and then steal it.
I imagine that there is a lot of like you got to get this out fast because this isn't going to be interesting to people in 6 hours.
Sure.
So some of that is probably a hectic frustrating schedule.
I'm sure there's emails flying around, did you see this? Did you see that? Sure.
Yeah.
And then I also don't know how much he's getting paid because that doesn't come up.
So it could also be 1.1 cents a word.
And if that's the case, then maybe this isn't such a good gig.
But if he's making as much as some of the other Infores employees, I mean, holy shit.
Holy shit.
Get the fuck out of here.
Yeah, I wouldn't go back to Google Analytics either, or whatever it was he was fucking.
No.
Although he didn't even read these 5000 words that he needed to read for this deposition.
What confidence does that give you that he actually does any fucking reading? This deposition isn't an article that he needs that very seriously.
I read everything I can on Google.
So here's an editor now, right? Sort of.
Not really.
Okay.
He has a copy editor who reviews the work.
whenever Jamie White is available, he reviews your work? Yes.
And for what purpose does he review it? Typos, pretty much the end.
And make sure I got my I's and T's crossed and stuff.
So I's and t's you're referring to, like, no typographical errors.
Yeah.
Or words and stuff.
Yes, exactly.
He's essentially just proofreading, correct? Yeah, proofreading.
Okay.
Amazing.
He's not checking for the accuracy of what you've written.
Technically, no.
Well, certainly it's technically, no.
There's no way you could say technically.
They have, like, a whole conversation about whether or not anybody has ever done that in his time at Infowars.
And he mentions only one person.
There's this guy, Mikhail Falan, who isn't with the company anymore.
He now writes for the Daily Dot.
I don't know what the fuck his deal is, but he has managed to transition out of the Infowars stink into somewhat legitimate like he's actually writing somewhere.
Yeah, I bet he has an editor.
Yeah.
I don't know what his deal is, but he was there.
And apparently when he was there, he would point out things like, no wonder he got fired.
But Adon doesn't understand, like, that action.
Right.
He experiences it as like, oh, he was just doing that because he wanted to.
It was just kind of fun for Mikael.
It was like we were having a little game between us.
I would lie and he would be like, you can't do this.
And I'd be like, ha ha.
And then post it.
You get the strong sense that he didn't listen to the advice that Phelan was giving me.
Wild.
Yeah.
So he can just write about whatever he wants.
And apparently he has never been told not to write something.
Have you ever been instructed that you couldn't write about a particular topic? No.
Have you ever had a request to publish an article turned down? No, I don't think so.
This is directly contradictory to Alex's entire thing about how he told people not to write about we're done with this topic.
Got it.
So that's interesting.
And because I believe that email from Paul to Buckley, it mentions Ada.
Adan wrote something about this.
And so he would be the person who was told, don't write about this.
That would be the only person.
And so someone has their picture wrong.
Oh, that's not good.
So I don't know how you picture the workplace environment at Infowars.
The kind of like, coworker after I find out that nobody's even does don Salazar even live in the country? He lives in Austin.
Right, but I mean, there's no way to know based on what he's describing of his job.
He could be in fucking South America right now and nobody would have any difference.
I think that's probably part of why it's so easy for Paul to have worked there the entire time living in England.
Yeah.
But the workplace environment seems really cold and this bums me out.
During the course of your employment at Infowars, has your contact level with Mr.
Jones changed at all? No.
How often are you in communication with Mr.
Jones? In communication? I would say maybe going to the bathroom or something.
Say hi.
So once a week or something.
How often are you in communication to him about the substance of your working in force? Some of them, if ever.
This is bizarre.
Living the dream.
No, boss.
I want to do a cubicle every day.
I mean, he's worked there for a decade and Alex still doesn't know his name.
Oh my God.
It's inconceivable.
That is I don't believe that if that is true.
So rude.
Totally.
There aren't that many people who work there.
No.
How do you ignore one that close to you, that's banana, and somebody who's responsible for creating so much of the content that you use to lie on air.
Yeah.
Wild.
It's like that is impersonal to the point of being hostile.
Yeah, absolutely.
There's no way to experience that except as like, this is a clear rejection.
I'd feel like I was being iced out or something.
You've been there ten years.
It would feel like, oh, Alex has clearly tried to get rid of me.
Wow.
And then it just never happens, I guess.
Yeah.
You just hide out in your cubicle and just wait until someone notices you're there.
I go back to the forensic financial analyst and he's like, a competently run business should have this to this amount of money.
And when you hear shit like this, you're like, either they've got an absurd amount of money hidden in gold somewhere because they are hiding it from everyone, or this place just doesn't even know where money comes from.
Like, they just don't.
Yeah, well, they do have a very serious distrust of fiat currency.
Exactly.
Yeah.
I don't know.
It's a weird, weird picture.
If it wasn't Infowars, it would be like wonka factory nonsense.
Absolutely.
It would be like everyone's running around in costumes and like no what the fuck is this? When do you see Alex? Well, occasionally he calls the entire staff out.
We have to put on our elf costumes, and we have to do a little dance for him and then we go back to work.
I mean, that question wasn't asked.
Could be whatever you have to wear.
A little dance at Dancer.
You never know.
So we finally get to Sandy Hook coming up, and the question that's opposed is, when did you find out about the shooting? Mr.
Salzar, do you recall how you first learned about the Sandy Hook shooting? I believe I was at work when it happened, so it was kind of playing everywhere on CNN, the break room.
Then it was everywhere on the Internet.
And so given your job as a writer, I take it that you started following that coverage very closely as soon as it broke? Yes.
And you knew immediately that the Sandy Hook shooting was going to be a subject of Info Wars reporting, correct? I didn't know that immediately, no.
You weren't able to leave into it that this was going to be a major news story that infowars was going to cover? Objection.
No, I didn't immediately realize that until days after what came off of the news.
So at that time, like, two days after the event happened, I was like, okay, this is a big news event.
This is something to keep an eye on here because Adon is testifying that in this first month, he was unaware of an intent to cover the shooting at Sandy Hook as being fake.
And that timeline is going to be in trouble as information is revealed.
Yeah, but yeah, your response to that is, I think, very appropriate.
Like, it's very bizarre to imagine that you could see the shooting happen.
You work it in force.
You know how they've covered shootings in the past.
You were there for Aurora, which just happened pretty recently, and like, a couple of days later, you realize, oh, this is a big story.
What? It's very weird.
Either he's lying or he's insane.
Like, there's no other way.
I think it's lying.
Or just trying to give a softer appearance, too.
Yeah, we weren't taking this as seriously as we could or maybe thought we would, something along those lines.
There's no way you don't want to give the impression that you're like seeing this and getting excited for the coverage that you're going to do.
I can understand how that isn't the perception you would want to give.
Like, I saw this and I immediately knew this was going to lead the news.
Right.
Okay, fine.
Wow, whatever.
There's going to be a problem.
Yeah, but a couple of days, I would even be like, oh, it was a few hours afterwards when I realized it was going to be what it was.
A couple of days makes you sound like you're hiding underneath rocks.
Oh, true.
And the timeline is just completely fucked.
You'd say that about two days after the event is when you first realized that you would be writing about Sandy Hook.
Correct? I didn't think I'd be writing about it yet.
I was looking at different anomalies and stuff, so I hadn't really put my foot down that I'd be writing about it yet.
So I think the first time I did was when I heard the Halbig interview, which was I don't think it was immediately after the shooting.
No, it was in 2014.
Yeah.
So there was an interview that Halbig did, and we'll talk about that a little more later with the American Free Press.
And that was in February, I think it was February.
Maybe not.
Maybe December.
I don't know.
It was in 2014.
Two days, two years.
Same difference.
Right.
And so Adon wrote an article about Wolfgang's interview.
And that is true, but that amount of time is like, if you're pitching that as your timeline until 2014.
I didn't know I was going to be writing about this.
I don't think it's a big story.
That is outrageous, and you don't want this to be like the sort of the foundation that you're laying in terms of explaining what happened in a deposition setting, because you're going to directly contradict yourself repeatedly.
You know that authority experiment where they've got somebody and the doctors like, press the button and no groom experiment? Yeah, that whole thing.
This is one of the few situations where if you did that experience that experiment here, it'd be like, five minutes max.
Press the button.
Every time he lies and beg, they're like, It's going to get larger, and he might die on this one.
And you're like, Listen, I think I know how electricity works, buddy.
Press that button.
I mean, look, I don't know if that's one of those experiments that has been debunked.
Yeah.
Is that R1? Sure.
I know the prison experiment, wasn't that one debunked? More or less.
Problems with it.
But leaving all that aside sure.
There is such a frustrating path that this goes down.
Don is such a bad stonewall.
We'll get to it.
It is so frustrating.
All right, what you need to know for now is that after the shooting, adam thought it was real.
I'm just trying to understand in the immediate aftermath, what your perspective was.
Go ahead.
No, please.
I was just saying the immediate aftermath, my perspective was a school shooting happened, so I was on board with the shooting.
I'm sorry, what? When you say on board in the immediate aftermath and let's try and time this out within two days of the shooting, it was your own view at that time that children and educators were killed at Sandy Hook, correct? Yes.
I would have phrased that differently, but yeah, it is what it is.
I was like, I'm on board with this shooting.
Oh, man.
Strange.
Metty almost even gave him a chance to rephrase.
It.
He gave you another go at it, man.
So Don, his perspective on this is like he was only going to report on Sandy Hook if there were anomalies.
Sure.
I take it from your testimony earlier that you anticipated that you would likely only write about it to the extent you thought that there were anomalies associated with the shooting worth writing about.
Right.
Something that I found interesting and I thought the readership would find interesting.
Yes.
Okay.
And that eventually happened.
Correct.
Where you felt that you wanted to report on anomalies around Sandy Hook because you found them interesting and you thought the audience would find them interesting, correct? Yes.
Yes.
So we come to this idea of anomaly, and it's one of the words that Alex uses to sort of rationalize a lot of his coverage, but it is kind of a vague term.
There isn't really a concrete definition of this, and so in order to move forward, we try to get a definition of what is an anomaly.
That's a great idea.
Yeah.
It's helpful.
We're talking about anomalies.
I just want to go back.
Can you give me your definition of anomalies? Maybe something that doesn't really jive with the story.
So some fact that you believe exists that calls into question other facts surrounding the shooting.
Correct? Objection.
Why are you checking something that calls into question everything else? It's just something peculiar or odd that you really don't know what it is, what it's purposes, like I said, until you have more pieces.
Okay.
And in considering those anomalies when it came time to report on them, I take it that it was important to you for anything you published concerning Sandy Hook to be true and accurate, correct? Yes.
To the best of my knowledge.
Right.
And you'd agree with me that the shooting of 20 children and six educators is a horrible atrocity, correct? Yes, sir.
And so if you're going to be reporting facts about that situation, it's incredibly important to you that they be accurate, correct? Yes.
And your audience relies on you to provide them with truthful and accurate information, correct? Yes, sir.
And you understood at the time of the Sandy Hook shooting and your coverage of that shooting that the Infowars audience included millions of people across different platforms, correct? Yes.
And so you considered it a tremendous responsibility of yours to make sure that they were well and accurately informed, correct.
Injection yes, I would say so.
You take that responsibility seriously, don't you? Yes.
It's important to you that the sources of information you had concerning Sandy Hook be credible, correct? Yes.
So Don has repeatedly now said, yes, I take this very seriously.
It's very important to me that the facts and we're in for, and that's fun, but yeah, we have a sort of vague definition of anomaly, but at least it's something you can kind of work with.
Right.
I was surprised that the lawyer objected to Maddie really doing a really good job of rephrasing anomaly is something that doesn't jive doesn't jive with the story.
I appreciate his dictionary anomalies doesn't jive anteater groovy tongue like, I like the way this man thinks he's got it.
Don calls Maddie's, daddy out later.
He's hip.
He smokes a jazz cigarette in between.
So there's a phenomenon called motivated reasoning wherein you try and create an argument for something based on a conclusion that you already had.
Right.
You go looking for information, you succumb to confirmation bias.
You find information that supports your conclusion that you are going to have already.
Now, this conversation here with Adan and how he was approaching questioning the shooting has some of the hallmarks of that you might think, okay, immediate aftermath.
When I say immediate aftermath of the Sandy Jerk shooting, let's talk about a month.
Okay.
So December 14, 2012 to January 14, 2013.
Are you with me? During that period, did you develop a concern that the shooting at Sandy Hook could be used as a pretext for gun confiscation legislation? I'm not sure if it was specifically gun confiscation, but yeah, it was going to be used to curtail gun rights, I believe, yes.
That was a concern you developed within the month after the shooting that the fact of the shooting could be used as a pretext for curtailing gun rights, correct? Yes.
Was there a concern, to your knowledge, that Alex Jones shared? I believe so, yeah.
Maybe if you go back and see some of the episodes following the incident, alex might have been mentioning that concern.
I can't recall that it was a specific concern or not, but it might have been.
Was that a principal reason that it was important to you to question whether or not the shooting in fact occurred? Yeah, that was one of several reasons, yeah.
What were some of the others? Just trying to keep the media honest and trying to sift through actual news and not fake news.
That is a shocking admission.
I can't understand how Adam wouldn't recognize what he just said.
He said that principally one of the reasons it was important for him to question whether or not Sandy Hook happened was because he was worried they were going to use it to take guns.
Right.
That has nothing to do with the reality or falsity of an event.
No.
That is a fucked up thought process.
Right.
So here's what I thought, okay? I thought that people would exploit this tragedy to pass gun grabbing legislation, right? So I went out and I looked for the truth, and everybody who said that it wasn't, I called fake news, and everybody who said that it was, I called true news.
So obviously it's true, my man.
Right.
Thinking about it this way, that you're worried about them exploiting the strategy in order to push a political goal that you are opposed to, right.
Instead of supporting the political point that you are in favor of and engaging in the argument about it, wherein people are like, hey, there's this school shooting, we should probably get better gun regulations in place and common sense reform, instead of responding to that with like, well, no, I don't believe that that is an appropriate thing to do and here are the reasons why.
Instead you're like, well, they wouldn't have any argument if the shooting didn't happen, so maybe I should try and prove that, or maybe I should try and get people to insist that because that's a shortcut, that I don't have to make my argument.
And that's basically the way you could interpret what Adan is saying.
And obviously on some level, I'm fully aware that this is part of it.
Yeah, totally.
Sort of ideological and information model.
But to hear it on not trying to mask that in some way is very shocking and it strikes me as somebody who doesn't realize what he's saying.
Yeah, I mean, how do you say it out loud? Because you'd hear it then you'd hear it spoken into the world.
Maybe he's got one of those.
I believe his lawyer didn't just like, stop water on the computer.
Yeah, 100%.
That's a revelatory thing.
The lawyers should have a shot caller for these people.
That is an insane thing to say.
How can you say that out loud and not be like, oh, I get where we went wrong now.
Thanks, guys.
Listen, we had a great deposition.
I'm going to 100% of the wrong whatever it is you say is true.
I'm going to get out of here.
I'm supposed to give the presentation that we're just looking for the truth and ask some hard questions that no one else will and exposing cover ups and what have you.
No, you're just trying to take shortcuts and push your political agenda in a different way because you know that if you did it on the merits, no one would be interested.
Right? If I argued with you about the thing you want to argue about, I would lose because you're right.
Wrong.
So instead, what if I pretended that you don't exist and neither does anybody else? Just me, and everything I think is true? Yeah.
So that's good.
Good way to live the day of the shooting or the round there within the 24 hours time frame.
Dawn got an email, and this is an email where we get an appearance from an old friend of ours, likes to hide in the bushes.
Oh, now you know the guy.
Oh, Batman.
That's the guy.
Oh, boy.
John Rappaport.
Hang up that picture.
Rappaport.
He has sent an email to John Bound, who then has forwarded to a Don Sally.
Okay, exhibit number one, it should be coming up on your screen.
Do you see an email before you, Mr.
Salazar? In the from line is Jonathanjohn@infowars.com to you? Yes.
And do you see the date that this is Mr.
Whoever Jonathan is.
And your testimony is that you don't know who that is? That's probably John Bone.
How do you spell his last name? Bowne.
And who is that? He's a video producer.
Is he still there? I think he works off site, but I think he's still employed by Free Speech.
Okay, and you knew who Mr.
Raffleport was at the time, correct? I was barely becoming familiar with him.
Yeah, it's my first year there.
Okay.
And Mr.
Bound is forwarding you an email and an attached document that he received from Mr.
Rappaport on the day of the shooting, correct? It appears so, yes.
the document that was attached to the email is dated December 15, 2012.
And it says here, come to grief counselors over the hill, pouring into Newtown, Connecticut.
Do you recall reading this piece by Mr.
Rappaport? No.
No.
Do you have an understanding of what Mr.
Rapaport's view was concerning the Sandy Hook shooting in the immediate aftermath? No, I don't know what Mr.
Rabbit's view was.
Do you know when Mr.
Bounce forwarded you this email because he thought it was interesting and thought I might find it interesting maybe to republish? Do you know if this was republished by Infowars.com? I don't know.
It's a little weird.
I mean Rappaport's unhinged weirdo.
So the idea that he's writing blogs questioning Sandy Hook the day of or the next day regular.
Yeah, that's part of the course.
But the idea that John Bound has found this and thought, hey, you know who will enjoy this? Don Salazar.
That is a little weird.
Definitely.
If someone were to email me that sure, I would take offense.
Yeah, I don't think they would.
That'd be a problem.
There's something about adon that people know.
It's totally cool to send him weird shit about Sandy Hook.
Yeah, man.
I just feel like if I were being deposed by anyone and they asked me a question and I gave my response, and then they were like, okay, do you see this on your screen? Point to exhibit one.
My first response would be like, fuck, something went wrong with my answer.
How is that not your response? Right.
Like, the moment they go, did you say this? Bring this up? You'd be like, well, obviously I didn't say that.
Now I know that.
I didn't know that just a moment ago.
Oh, no.
Yes.
Something not a dawn.
He sticks to his guns and is presenting the idea that he did not know in the immediate aftermath that they were going to cover it as if it were really trying.
In the immediate aftermath of the shooting, that is the month following the shooting.
Is it fair to say that you understood that your coverage was going to frame Sandy Hook as a staged event? I didn't know that in the media aftermath.
you were not aware at that time, or you did not have a view at that time, that Infowars coverage of the event would frame it as a staged event.
Correct.
Yes.
So that is important in as much as we've now sort of laid the framework of what we're talking about, when you say the immediate aftermath, we're talking about that month.
Yeah.
And I think that's helpful.
I don't believe it on here, but I'm going to throw this out there.
Sure.
Don.
Earlier in the deposition says, why did I join Infowars? AHA, 911 was an inside job.
Right.
So your very first moment of joining Infowars is based entirely it's entirely around something being a false flag.
True.
You knew exactly how they were going to fucking you know that they're the false flag.
They're the false flag people.
Yeah.
They're the one stop shop for flag.
And you've just done aurora yeah.
They have just done all of their coverage about how that was fake.
And you were listening, we know.
No.
You were working there.
Yeah, exactly.
That's right.
Oh, my God.
Yeah.
So it's a little bit tough pill to swallow.
Yes.
I'm not going to buy that one.
And especially because obviously he said that the interest that you would have in reporting on this is based on seeing anomalies.
Of course.
And he started to see anomalies pretty fast in the immediate aftermath of the shooting.
Am I correct that you did become aware of what you considered to be certain anomalies? Fair to say.
Yes, sir.
How is it that you became aware of those anomalies? What did you do to discover them? Jackson I'm not sure if I received tips on emails or found videos on YouTube, but it was maybe a combination of the two.
In order to find videos on YouTube, you would have to search for something that you were looking for.
Correct.
A link is provided somehow via social media or email.
Yeah.
Okay.
Do you recall doing any affirmative work on your own to search YouTube or any other sites or anomalies? No, I didn't search the site.
I was probably provided with links to videos about it.
And you think those links may have come either through you viewing social media or through the writer's email? Correct.
Right.
Or on reddit.
Yeah.
Various places you can find links to YouTube? Yes.
Were you looking for those things? I wouldn't say I was looking for them now.
Okay.
Everything just fell into my lap, man.
All this information, these anomalies just kept popping up.
I wasn't doing anything looking for them.
They just I don't know where tips.
Yeah.
Social media.
I think this is who am I to not follow the story? This is the only episode, I think, of our show where if you just put Liz in my chair based on his descriptions of her job, she would be making she would be screaming.
I can't imagine anybody who works in media journalism hearing this and not being a fan, not being like, I will kill this world.
Nothing means anything anymore, right? I've ripped my hair out.
So many people who have worked so hard and just in the trenches grinding for one story, right? Months of research.
They've got people who actually go out there, fact checkers, who rip everything everything, or even people who do, like a lot of the behind the scenes totally facilitates good journalism and stuff.
I just kind of like, I don't know, maybe I just fall.
Somebody emailed me on Reddit, email me a link.
So I get paid six figures.
But there's also emails that come in that's true.
Like from Rappaport, naturally.
Or this other email from Rappaport.
Do you see that this is an eight page document and page one is an email from Jonathan to you with an indication that there is an attachment entitled Adam lands a mask.
Yes, I see that.
And you see that the email from Jonathan is a forwarded email again from Mr.
Rappaport.
It looks like it was sent from John Wrappers to John Bound and then John Bound forwarded to me.
Correct.
And the date that Mr.
Bound received it.
So the date that Mr.
Raffler sent it to Mr.
Bound was December 16, 2012.
Correct? I see that, yes.
Okay.
That would have been two days after the shooting.
I believe so, yes.
And if you scroll down in the document, again, similar to the last email we looked at, there's an attachment with a written piece that appears to be authored by Mr.
Rappaport, correct? Yes, sir.
And the title is two Movies, two Mass murders.
Yes, I see that.
With a subtitle that says The Dark Knight Rises in The Hunger Games.
Okay, yeah, correct.
It doesn't look like it's the subtitle.
It looks like it's the lead sentence in this.
Okay, all right, fine.
So Rabaport has sent this to John Bound.
And again, it seems like there's sort of a tunnel, sort of pipeline.
It does seem like there's a very developed clear pipeline.
Yeah.
I mean, the first one that John Bound sends me, and maybe if I'm not interested, I say, don't send me shit like, that weird, there's another one next day.
Kind of sounds like maybe this happens regularly.
Yeah, but look, Don doesn't know if he actually even read this.
Okay.
Fair to say, right? Yes.
You eventually did develop an interest in the nexus between the movie the Dark Knight Rises and the Sandy Hook shooting, correct? Yes, there was an interest in it.
And it's possible that that interest may have been sparked by this particular piece, which I can scroll down, draws a connection between the Batman movie, the Aurora shooting, and Sandy Hook.
My question to you, is it's possible that this particular email, which you received, sparked your interest in the nexus between the movie The Dark Knight Rises and the Sandy Oak shooting, correct? It's possible.
I can't say for sure.
I don't know if I read this article at the time.
But in any event, it appears that you received this email shortly after the shooting.
Correct? Yes.
It's honestly too bad for Adam that he didn't read this article, because if he had, he could defend himself here.
The conspiracy that Adan spread about Sandy Hook and Batman had to do with the name Sandy Hook appearing on the map in the movie Dark Knight Rises.
That was in an article Rappaport wrote on December 18.
But the one from the 16th, which is being discussed here since it was forwarded to a dawn, is actually about something else.
The Batman.
Part of this has to do with the Aurora shooting happening at a screening of Batman, and the theories about James Holmes thinking he was the Joker.
In this article, Sandy Hook relates to the Hunger Games.
I'm just going to read you here some of John Rappaport's brilliant work.
Please quote, we now have the boggling connection to The Hunger Games.
In that scifi novel and film, 24 children are picked to take part in a competitive national blood sacrifice killing ritual.
One child survives at the end, and 23 die.
20 died in Newtown.
And the author of The Hunger Games, Suzanne Collins, lives in Sandy Hook next to Newtown.
And this means this is just the kind of bizarre and insane opsecret societies are reputed to enjoy.
Ordinarily I would ignore this sort of thing and just call it a coincidence, but it's too improbable.
I can't prove the killings in Newtown were part of a kind of op, but I can't disregard it either.
The quote, coincidence is just too stunning.
And if The Hunger Games connection is real here, tell you what, then all bets are off.
The coincidence that Rappaport finds too stunning is that Suzanne Collins lives nearby, and the number of children who were killed in The Hunger Games doesn't match the number dead at Sandy Hook, but it's kind of close.
Plus or minus five.
Plus or minus five, there's a margin of error.
Yeah.
This is the kind of dumb shit that Rappaport was writing two days after the shooting that John Bound thought it was worth sending to Adon, who I almost guarantee did read it.
He may think it's in his best interest to not know anything about the article in this deposition, but the idea that he wasn't interested in this, it just flies, right far more.
Yeah.
Everything I've been able to tell about him from his work, far more ridiculous.
Fuck out of here.
I think I would have made it two sentences into that email before I would have thrown my computer out the window.
I've been like, Get this away from me.
I think the computer is scary now.
Or I would have told John Bound to stop sending me.
Bullshit.
Look, if it says John Rapper on it, I'm not interested.
Yes, do better.
Bound.
Where's Theodore at? Let's get him back in here.
So Adon, he apparently is not only a receiver of emails, he's a sender of emails.
He sent an email to Melissa Melton, who is a former employee of Infowars on December 19.
It's a little interesting.
Do you have this email before you, sir? Which is an email from you to Melissa Milton on December 19, 2012.
I see that here.
Who is Melissa Milton? She was a previous employee.
What was her role in force at the time? Video producer, I guess.
She wrote some articles.
So she was a partial editor.
Can you read the subject line, please? It says, forward Connecticut police radio, purple band Maskman one dressed as none.
And can you read the text that you emailed to Ms.
Milton? Look at this.
Sent in from a reader.
Don't know if you caught the show that day, but a caller said none gained entry to the school.
And why did you share that information with Ms.
Melton? It looks like I was going off of the email before it.
Well, correct.
We just probably interested in the anomalies.
So you were sending this to Ms.
Melton because you were interested in the possibility that someone dressed as a nun had gained entry to the school on the day of the shooting.
More of sharing a weird tale here.
It's a weird tale.
I mean, sure, I thought it was true, but then when you said it out loud back to me now, I think it was a weird tale.
It's a weird tale like that publication where Lovecraft's stories were originally published, submitted to the secret society.
Okay, so you sent a weird tale to Melissa Melton about a nun, someone dressed as a nun, gaining access to the school.
Obviously, this is because there was another shooter.
And that same day, something else happened at Infowars.
This exhibit, does it appear to you, Mr.
Salazar, to be a headline in the text of an article that was published on Infowars.com on December 19, 2012? Yes.
This is the article, I believe you attributed to a particular staffer, aaron Dykes, correct? Yeah, I think it was he that wrote this stuff.
Were you aware of the article at the time? It was published only when it went up on the website.
I was aware of when the readers were pretty sure I did.
So here's something that Maddie might not know or just isn't bringing up that makes this all a bit suspicious.
These two clips that we just heard on the same day, December 19, don is emailing Melissa Melton about a Sandy Hook conspiracy theory.
And Aaron Dijks is posting this article to Faming Robbie Parker.
The connective tissue that's missing is that Aaron Dijks and Melissa Melton were a couple.
They ended up leaving Infowars together, and they started their own outlet called Truth Stream.
Media and now have spoken pretty poorly about Alex, but are still lunatic conspiracy theorists.
They're married now, and Melissa has taken on Aaron's surname.
It seems difficult for me to imagine that you have Aaron actively posting the Sandy Hook conspiracy shit and Adon emailing his girlfriend other Sandy Hook conspiracy shit, and that doesn't translate to a group of people intensely interested in Sandy Hook conspiracy shit.
Yeah.
That, to me, is something that doesn't pass the smell test.
I used to be pretty good at pool.
And one time I was watching these two really, really good hustlers who accidentally wound up playing against each other like they fucked up.
And they were so good.
Like, after the first couple of games, they realized what was going on, and then they would just move so fast.
It would be like if there were four balls left on the table that they think you could run those out.
They just rip them off the table and they'd be like, next game.
Next game.
Like that.
If we were in this kind of high level situation, I think Adan would have been like, all right, you got me on this one.
Next question.
Let's go.
Next one.
We'll swipe these off the table.
I'm going to pawn.
You've won.
You've won this one.
I got to play the next game, though.
I'm down a lot of money.
Yes, I think that I would be very interested in that piece of information being brought as a rebuttal.
You know there are a couple, right, these people that you're communicating with on the same day about conspiracy theories about Sandy Hook.
I guess Adon doesn't necessarily have, like, a concrete proof that he was talking to Aaron Dijks about his article about Robbie Parker.
But how many writers are there at the time? Not many.
They all work in the same office.
Right.
I find it unbelievable that the two of them wouldn't have been at least in some kind of context.
I would go so far as to call that an anomaly.
It is anomalous sure.
Should that be the case? That's anomalous ironically, it sort of has the hint of a conspiracy.
Listen, I'll tell you what, that's a fact that doesn't jive.
That's for the truth.
So Don also sent Paul Joseph Watson an email looking for tips about a Sandy conspiracy article he was writing.
Do you have an email before you, sir? From you to Paul Joseph Watson.
Can I see that? Balls off the table.
Next question.
You got me.
Please, Paul, if you have the time, can you take a look at the article I have pending publishing on the back end of inflows? I did a little bit of research on the Sandy Hook Batman coincidence, and I've come to the conclusion that Sandy Hook was substituted for another name on the map.
So I think maybe you've got some tips or something you'd like to add or I think I should mention the article or a better headline.
Thanks.
Do you have a article that you are referencing? I think it's the one about Sandy Hook maps and stuff.
I mean, Batman.
Maps.
Yeah.
This is an article that you wrote in which you reported that a map that appears in the movie The Dark Knight Rises had a location that had been changed from South Hinkley to Sandy Hook, correct? Yes.
Okay.
Do you know if Paul Watson got back to you on this? I don't think he did.
He wasn't as interested in this story as I was.
You were pretty interested in this.
Yeah.
That's revealing.
I mean, we already knew that Paul wasn't down with this shit, but, like, for you to say he wasn't as interested in it as I was, the lie's, like, a real interest on your part, which doesn't look great.
Yeah.
So this is about December 20, right? Now, here is where things got a little bit confusing for me because there was an article posted on the 17th on Infowars about the map in The Dark Knight Rises.
And then there's another article that's an update of it.
That's the one that Don is talking about, I believe.
Okay.
I'm not sure if he wrote the original one on the 17th because they both have Infowars.com as the writer.
There's no attribution.
Right, but he said that he wrote the one, and obviously he's emailing Paul about it.
He wrote that one, presumably.
I would think he wrote the first one, too, but who knows? Yeah, I mean, that could have been just a fuck.
They could have stolen that one, too.
Who knows? Can't nail it down.
Who knows? What we do know is that when it did get published, the 20th one, someone else got a little update about that.
This is an email from you to the Drudge Report, correct? Oh, no.
Yes.
Drudge Report.
And the subject line that you wrote was bizarre.
Sandy Hook Dark Knight Rises connection.
Correct? Yes.
And you wrote, Infowars has exposed that a section of Gotham City was renamed Sandy Hook in the latest Dark Knight release, and you include a link to the story, correct? Yes.
That was a story that you wrote? That's the one I wrote, I believe.
Yes.
Okay.
And that story was written and published six days after the Sandy Hook shooting, correct? Yes.
And you then asked Drudge will help us spread the news of this very strange coincidence, correct? Yes.
So at this point, we have at very least, Infowars has a story about this Batman thing three days after the attack.
Then six days after the shooting, there's another one that Adon has written.
Now he's trying to enlist the Drudge Report to disseminate it more widely.
The argument that they weren't pushing a lot of this stuff and they weren't responsible for the spread of it, especially in the early days, it was very.
Out the window in terms of the size of the reach that Infowars has at this time.
Their active courting of Drudge, the largest link aggregator in the right wing, maybe all of yeah.
At the time, it was like the biggest was the Internet.
That, to me is like, really? Damning, that email is pretty it's a bad look.
Yeah.
I could not be deposed this way.
If you listen to the video of me being deposed, if this was me, it would just be like, don't read it on no, come on, man.
And I know I sent it.
It sucked up.
Because it's not like an interrogation where you can just confess.
Exactly.
Keep going.
You can't just be like, I did it.
Let's just move on.
Charge me whatever you want.
No.
We have more questions.
Can't we be done? Can I just go to jail instead of talk to you anymore? So the reason that this is something that would be interesting to Adam Salazar now.
You might imagine that the obvious answer is because if somebody who worked on Batman that had already come out had changed the name of this place on the map to Sandy Hook as some kind of a message.
And then later Sandy Hook happens.
It would lead one to think maybe they did that as a message.
There's this whole idea of predictive programming that is really big in Alex's coverage of stuff.
So the argument here, the shorthand is very clear that it's trying to argue for foreknowledge.
There's no other way to unless you're a dawn, you could argue that it's not.
Is he going to argue that there was a psychic power? No, that's a coincidence, man.
Oh, well, then, yes.
Mr.
Salazar, the reason you were reporting on this is because the fact that a map location in The Dark Knight Rises had been changed to Sandy Hook, caused you to suspect whether there had been some sort of advanced knowledge by somebody that the Sandy Hook shooting was going to take place.
Correct injection.
I don't know if that was my belief at the time.
I just thought it was a very bizarre, strange coincidence that I thought needed to be highlighted.
Why did you continue to be what relevance was it to your coverage? I think it's relevant if the name of a map changes on a movie when it's supposed to be something else and then Sandy Hook changes to Sandy Hook, and then something happens at a place called Sandy Hook in the same year that the movie is released.
Right.
Coincidence.
And so help me explain why that is relevant.
It seems and correct me if I'm wrong, that what you are inviting your audience to consider is that it's not a coincidence at all.
Correct injection of form.
I wasn't inviting the audience to consider that.
I was asking if maybe they perhaps thought the coincidence was bizarre to I think I point out the fact that the prop manager of the movie lived in Sandy Hook, maybe in one of the articles, or in town, Connecticut, which is the same place the shooting took place.
I thought that was all bizarre coincidence.
Yes.
I was only trying to tell the readers that it was a stage false flag.
I was trying to point out a bizarre coincidence.
Just so we're clear, here's the second paragraph of the article a don wrote and sent to Drudge.
Quote since that quote minor coincidence, we've scoured the Batman movies and poured over various Gotham City maps to find anything that could support the theory that the movies may have had hints of foreknowledge of the tragic massacre that occurred last week.
Because where there's smoke, there's usually fire.
Oh, my God.
What we found is interesting, to say the least.
It seems like this isn't quite how he's describing his writing in this deposition.
From the article, it sounds like they were studying these maps, searching for clues to prove that there was foreknowledge and that they found interesting stuff.
And where there's smoke, there's usually fire.
Seems pretty overt in its point, I would say.
Yeah.
And Ada doesn't point out that the prop master was from Sandy Hook.
He does bring up that there's a Sandy Hook in New Jersey, but it's kind of a non sequitur between heavy insinuation of a conspiracy and then this quote for those who are left asking, why would someone do this? Okay.
Alfred pennyworth.
Like Bruce Wayne says of an evil force in the Dark Knight movie, some men aren't looking for anything logical like money.
They can't be bought, bullied, reasoned, or negotiated with.
Some men just want to watch the world burn.
The article ends with this quote if you're enjoying spotting these bizarre coincidences and traveling down the road of curiosity with us, stay tuned for tomorrow's scintillating revelation.
Is the smoking gun needed to tie The Dark Knight Rises, the Aurora massacre and the Sandy Hook tragedy.
We guarantee it will leave you wondering exactly WTF is going on.
Oh, my God.
That doesn't really seem like someone who's just saying, hey, isn't this weird? Anytime I'm in a deposition, I just want to make sure that I've never written the word guarantee at the moment.
You say guarantee, you're fucking I think that it's an interesting approach that Adawn is taking because Maddie is asking, why is this relevant? Right? It's just something kind of interesting.
It's a weird coincidence, right? But it's only a meaningful coincidence if you're trying to argue X, Y, or Z.
No.
And this when I told you about this being an incredibly frustrating kind of thing, are we going to be here for a while? This seems to be a stumbling.
There are difficulties in getting Adam to admit at all that he was making a point.
Okay.
Adan, what do you do as a writer? I just throw words out.
I just say, Isn't this weird? Whoa.
Walking noodle doo.
But then you read the article, and I say we have a scintillating revelation of a smoking gun tomorrow.
Guarantee.
So anyway, it's just coincidence.
So it's really just the pointing out coincidence.
Okay.
That really is like to the extent there would be any salience to the coincidence, it's that right.
To find Sale, that the fact that a map location in a movie had been changed to the name of a place where a shooting later occurred could potentially be evidence that somebody involved in that movie had awareness that a shooting would later occur there.
Correct? Objection.
I don't know what it signified.
I just thought it was a bizarre coincidence that people should maybe look into okay.
Highlighted it for the audience because I thought it was interesting, and I thought they'd find it interesting as well.
It's just a bizarre coincidence.
It doesn't mean anything.
I didn't have any suspicions about this.
I wasn't trying to make a point.
Don come on.
Come on, man.
Unfortunately, he also had a Facebook account, and this happened.
I'm going to show you exhibit eight A.
You actually posted your article to Facebook and that's exhibit eight A before you, correct? I see that, yes.
And contrary to the testimony you just gave, which is you were just pointing out the coincidence, you included commentary there that called the coincidence very fishy, correct? Objection.
It looks like it says that.
Can you zoom in a little more? Yeah, that's the problem.
Yeah, I put very fishy, which you meant to so doubt about whether there was, in fact, foreknowledge on somebody's part of the shooting.
Correct.
I'm just pointing out that it's a bizarre coincidence.
I'm not trying to sow doubt really out that it's fishy.
Yeah, it seems like I'm pointing out that it's a bizarre coincidence.
I don't know if I'm trying to sow doubt.
I think that Chris Matty's delivery of that it seems fishy is just right on point, because that is the kind of thing that you could just repeat to somebody and you're shaming them.
Yeah, I wasn't trying to sow doubt or make this look suspicious when you said fishy.
Fishy.
Yeah.
I think that's one of the moments where Donald probably didn't think, like, well, you know, I didn't post anything on Facebook.
It is such like, of course you're constantly surprised that they're bringing this up to you.
You didn't research the things you did.
Right.
And you're used to working with a bunch of ding dongs.
You don't do anything you don't understand, like, how process of actual exploration might work.
I mean, it really does feel like he's like, how did you get that? You know? Like, no, it's public, man.
You can find it anytime you want.
Right.
Crazy.
It was fishy.
Mean, it's more of an anomalous word, really.
Have you seen fish? There's a lot of anomalous fish.
I'll tell you what, that fish doesn't jive.
So the next day after this adan is working on another Sandy Hook conspiracy theory.
Yeah.
On December 21, and this will be exhibit number eleven, you latched onto a different anomaly.
Do you recall becoming aware that an online movie review of a movie entitled Sandy Hook Lingerie Party Massacre had been published in the days prior to the shooting? Do you recall that? Yes.
And you referenced an exhibit eleven, but have not shown it? Correct.
You recall as you're sitting here without looking at an exhibit, becoming aware of and interested in the fact that somebody had published an online review of this movie before the Sandy Hook shooting? Correct.
I don't know about the review, but I was aware of the movie or something.
Somehow it crossed my path.
Probably some John Rapaport email, some dumb shit you saw on Reddit.
That lawyer should have been like when he was like, Objection.
You haven't showed exhibit eleven.
And he's like, correct.
Oh, fuck.
That means exhibit eleven is going to make my client look real dumb.
Oh, no shit.
Did you think that this movie was fishy? Yeah, so, yeah, Don's working on this article about the Lingerie Party Massacre, and there's some emails, these have come up in other depositions where Don is emailing the guy who wrote the review, I believe, and discussing how like, hey, there's a bunch of people who are spreading a rumor that you are maybe at foreign knowledge of the attack.
Sure.
And we think that's dumb, but we're going to write it anyway.
Oh, no, that's a bad idea.
Yeah, so it's always fun when in a deposition setting, you get to make someone read their own email.
Oh, don't make me read it.
And here's how it goes.
Don't make me read it.
And I'm going to scroll down to the beginning of the email and I'll just go down so everybody can see this one page.
And am I correct, sir, that you sent an email on December 21, seven days after the shooting, to a Ms.
Gonzalez? Is that correct? Mr.
Gonzalez? Yeah, Mr.
Gonzalez.
I'm sorry, Mr.
And your email reads, actually, can you read it for me? There is a vicious rumor that the date you posted your review of the Sandy Hook Lingerie Party Master on your site, a slash above.com, shows four knowledge or prior planning of the events that have taken place as of late.
At first, and I include two links at first, we thought this was surely ridiculous.
However, we're going to point it out in an article and we'd like to give you the opportunity to provide a comment.
Sorry, you said we're going to point it out in an article anyway, right? Yes.
I'm sorry.
Wonder if that's an attentional omission on this part of reading it, because the anyway, there really is a word.
Yeah, it shows like you're sending this person an admission that you don't even believe the shit you're going to post.
You're going to do it anyway.
Yeah, the NA is a shiv to your gut.
That is what the NA is for.
But I don't understand what the goal would be of not reading the word.
I mean, it's there well, because you don't want to read it.
Because anyway really makes you sound like you just shived somebody in the gut.
It's a weird instinct.
Don't make me read my own again.
I can't be deposed.
The whiny voice.
Don't make me read it.
I would just say, no problem.
Yeah, you read it.
You do it.
The email that he's sending involves a notion of foreknowledge because that's literally what he says in the email.
Yup.
So you might think that covering this story as Adon does, is an attempt for him to cast aspersions on the reality of the shooting and imply that the audience maybe should consider that there's four planning for knowledge.
Yeah.
Nah, man.
He wasn't making a point.
Sorry.
What? But the rumor that you were informing Mr.
Gonzalez of was that the fact that he had posted the review sometime in advance of the Sandy Hook shooting could be evidence that he was aware the shooting would take place, correct? I believe that's what I was questioning.
And you thought that it was surely ridiculous at first, right? Yes.
Why then, if it was ridiculous, were you going to include it in an article anyway? Because it was just another bizarre coincidence that I found interesting, that I thought our readership would find interesting.
And the reason that you thought they would find interesting is because you were trying to highlight evidence for them suggesting that this was an event of which certain people had four knowledge.
Correct? Objection.
I wasn't particularly trying to highlight that there was an event that people had for knowledge of more so that I thought this was a weird anomaly that people should keep their eye on and maybe read about.
Keep their eye on.
This is infuriating.
That is wow.
Yeah.
Fuck you.
This is kind of it reminds me a little bit of a child being like, I'm not hitting you.
I'm not hitting you right in your face.
Insane.
I mean, Jesus Christ.
At a certain point, just be like, if you're going to play dumb, you're playing the wrong amount of dumb.
This is dumb enough where I'm like, you're an asshole.
You've got to go way too far if you're going to try.
You've got to be like, Holy shit.
That is the first time that I have thought of that connection.
I can't believe I didn't consider that.
Are you kidding me? You know what? Honestly, now that you've brought that up, to me, that sounds like a crazy thing I did.
I'm so sorry.
Now you know what? It's weird that I completely unknowingly and accidentally speculated about that in the articles that you're asking.
It is crazy.
That's wild.
Or just, like, I don't know have an entirely open mind and be like, oh, yeah, that is what I was saying.
You're right.
That doesn't make sense.
Yeah.
I don't know.
Maybe that's a bad road to go.
I mean, there's no way to go.
This one's just very dumb.
Good way to go, but this is bad.
So Maddie asks Adon about, like, these anomalies and stuff, and actually this moment, it was revelatory for me because it was something that I'd never really thought about.
You yourself weren't convinced at this point that the evidence you were collecting established that somebody other than Mr.
Landon had four knowledge of the event.
Correct? Objection.
At the time, I was still kind of, I guess, trying to convince myself to put the pieces together.
So what were any of your coincidences to law enforcement? Did you no, I'd never thought about it.
Wow.
That if they took this stuff seriously, wow.
Why wouldn't they tell somebody in law enforcement? Why wouldn't they try to? I mean, obviously, if we don't believe any of this right? But that would be something that you probably have some kind of at least moral obligation to do if you took any of this seriously.
That's one of those things that when you're too close to stuff, you can't see it, but if you step back and you look at that, that's so simple, and it demolishes everything.
Yeah.
It's so simple.
It's so taken for granted by us because of how long we've been doing this, how much it's been repetitively borne out.
They don't take the series.
Yeah.
We just know that isn't even, like, a consideration.
Yeah, you're right.
It just does.
Like, what a great question.
Yeah.
If you really thought this, wouldn't you at least talk to somebody? Yeah, because it's very, very serious.
Well, the implications of this are earth shattering, so wouldn't you at least try? Right.
And you can be like, well, no, because the whole system is going to be like, well, that's not an excuse to not try, especially not if you're using somebody who is a former cop or whatever as your person.
Find somebody who's a former cop to ease it into them or whatever.
Dude's uncle is a former FBI agent.
Are you guys that stupid? Yeah.
So this next clip I really enjoyed this clip.
Okay.
It's a little longer, but it has to be.
And you were at this time aware that of allegations that one or more of the parents of Sandy Hook children were crisis actors, correct? Yes, I heard the rumor at that point.
Yes, you heard the rumor.
Did you believe it yourself at that point? I didn't really go into that so much as everybody else did.
Could have been a factor, but I wasn't really interested in trying to figure out whether they were crisis sectors or not.
You weren't interested in that? Not really.
It didn't really matter to the case we were trying to make or prove like, any of the bizarre anomalies that I was writing about.
Okay.
Can you let me know? And this will be exhibit number twelve.
Why on January 6, 2013, you attempted to establish an account@crisisactors.org? I'm not sure.
Why people listed on the site or something.
I don't know.
Okay.
You agree that zip number twelve is an email from crisis actors that is a website to you asking for you to verify your address so you can sign into the crisis actors website, correct? Yes.
About three weeks, correct? Yes.
But your testimony here today is that you don't know why you did that.
Well, looks like I was trying to investigate, see if maybe if they're listed as crisis actors on there.
I don't know what I was just trying to any avenue I can possibly investigate.
I wanted to do my due diligence.
I see.
Wow.
Your assumption is that you were trying to gain access to the site in the hope that you might be able to see if any of the crisis actors appearing on the website were the same as individuals who were family members of Sandy Hook victims.
Correction.
At the time, it looks like I was trying to figure out if any of the people involved in the Sandy Hook event were crisis actors.
That's what appears, yes.
Including family members, correct? I'm not sure.
Could have been anybody.
I might have been looking into some guy that was just interviewed and said, you know what? And what were the results of your query of the crisis actors website? Honestly, I cannot tell you because I do not remember.
Okay.
Really important information.
I got some expose level stuff, and Maddie makes another great point after that, and that is like well, I mean, if you'd gone on there and found somebody that was one of the Sandy Hook people, you probably would have reported that, right? Would have.
The fact that you didn't kind of shows that maybe you didn't and you didn't report to your audience that you didn't find it.
No.
Did you? Nope.
It appears that you said earlier today that you did not know why that assassin killed your wife.
Now, do you know why the day before you signed up for can an assassin kill my wife.org? I don't know.
I mean, look, it's a long time ago.
I don't know.
I think I was just looking to see how assassins are doing these days.
Are they making good money? What's their world like? Yeah, I've always wanted to interview an assessment, and as far as the day before it goes, I think that's just a bizarre coincidence.
Totally.
Yeah.
I got to go.
Oh, my God.
That's so fucking terrible.
Yeah, but that's a pure comedy moment.
I wasn't really that interested in the crisis actors stuff.
Three weeks after the shooting, you tried to join crisisactors.org.
Yeah, well, I guess I did do that.
There's just so many so many stepping on a rake moment.
It's bananas.
Wow.
So there's another conspiracy that was going around that has to do with the idea that there was a fundraiser for Sandy Hook that was published before this.
Right.
And so Don has to address this on January 13.
Well, you agree that you are the recipient of this email? Yes.
And descend.
Or Sean knows.
You know who that is? I do not.
Okay.
The sender Sean Noel in his email is encouraging you to go to a link where, according to the link, a Sandy Hook Relief Fund page appeared three days before the shooting, correct? Yeah.
That's what Mr.
Knowl seems to be pointing out in this email.
Did you do anything to investigate that? I might have clicked the link.
I can't recall.
Okay.
And showing you exhibit number 13.
fair to say that this is an image of your Facebook account in which you shared the post concerning this issue of a Sandy Hook fundraising page being created three days before the shooting? Yes, sir.
And you did that on January 11, 2013, right? Yes.
Oh, boy.
Again, you didn't do anything to investigate whether in fact a relief fund had been created three days before the shooting.
You just posted the link, right? Posted a link to Natural News on my Facebook? Yes.
Okay.
And you did that because, as you say, this was another coincidence.
Right.
Is that how you felt? The Google thing I wasn't too sure about.
Since I knew a little bit about how Google worked, I wasn't so ready to follow that.
How much do you know about how Google works? Anomaly.
You were prepared to post about it, but you were going to write an article about it, right? I was prepared to post it on Facebook for other people that might find it interesting, yes.
So that's interesting because he's willing to spread this bullshit that he knows his bullshit.
Yeah.
He knows that this is nonsense, but he's still more than willing to put it out as if it is.
Now, the interesting thing is that was a fun trap because you've got this email where this guy is sending him an email on January 13, and he said, did you research this at all? Maybe I clicked the link, I don't know.
He posted about it on Facebook two days prior.
OOH, that's fucking OOH, that's not good.
No.
Oh, that's bad.
There's a decent chance that this guy's emailing him about the article that Adon had posted on his Facebook.
The same article might have been what spurred this email.
Jesus.
And he'd already admitted that he didn't look into it.
He didn't research it.
One of the little pet peeves that I have, especially in situations like this, is whenever it's like you can't say it seems like that's what he's doing.
I'm giving you a thing that happened in the past that cannot be changed anymore.
It is done.
So this does not seem like he says this.
He said this, correct? Seems like it.
No.
So when they were talking about the Batman article that Don had written, he said that he thought, he mentioned that the prop master was from Newtown.
Right.
And that was not true.
He had mentioned that new Jersey, there's an island.
Sandy Hook.
The reason Adam thought that he brought up the prop master is because this became another big conspiracy for him.
So basically the argument or the theory that goes around is that this guy, Scott Getsinger is the name of the prop master.
He died in a car wreck prior to the release of the movie and prior to Sandy Hook.
Right.
So the theory that people had was that he was responsible for changing the name to Sandy Hook and that's why they killed it.
Exactly.
Because he knew too much.
Which sort of raises the question of why it was still in the movie.
Yeah, I mean, if they knew that he did it, but they also killed him for it and then they left it in anyways.
Right.
That seems silly.
And it appears that Adan was pretty into this conspiracy.
Right.
And so this is discussed a little bit here and I don't know, don't.
Boring as a dodger, let's say.
Am I correcting for sales or another email that you sent this one to Elliot Brown? Yes, sir.
And you see that it's dated there, january 28, 2013.
Yes.
And in this email you are asking him if he's free for an honest journalist question, correct? Yes.
And you're referring to yourself there, correct? Yes.
Even he laughed at that.
Exactly.
Fuck you.
And in the body of the email you ask him about the change in the title of the map in Dark Knight Rises, and you ask him about this gentleman, Scott Getsinger, who was the prop master, according to you, who passed away in a car accident, correct? Yes.
And so does this situate you in time, that the time when you were inquiring about the death of Scott Getsinger was in January of? Yes, it looks like.
And the coincidence that you were referring to, and we'll go back to exhibit number 14, this is the email to help Ranger Direct was that Mr.
Getsinger was associated with the movie The Dark Knight Rises and he was killed in a car crash and lived in Newtown, Connecticut, correct? Yes.
And you say what struck me as extremely odd is that this dude hailed from, you guessed it, Newtown, Connecticut.
Right, right.
And then you say at the end, definitely something fishy about it all.
What was fishy about the fact that somebody associated the props department with The Dark Knight Rises was from Newtown and it died in a car accident? Rejection to form.
I thought it was very odd.
Same year that this movie is put out and Sandy Hook is changed on a map, something happens at a place called Sandy Hook.
And what you were suggesting, were you not, was that Mr.
Gessinger's death was somehow due to the fact that he had knowledge about why the map had been changed? Objection.
Honestly, I did not have a theory as to why if he was murdered or killed or why he died in the car accident.
So I didn't really have an answer.
But it did seem like a strange anomaly worth pointing out.
So there is this infuriating thing where it's just the way that Don is presenting what Infowars does is like, I guess we're just a journalistic or media outlet where we post weird coincidences that mean nothing.
I find to be an offensive, just sort of characterization.
It's silly, it's fishy.
You are theoretically a writer, and you're trying to insist to me that words don't have meaning.
This is a problem.
More or less, yeah.
And so Maddie makes this point, and I think that this is important, and that is that coincidences don't mean anything unless there's a point to them.
No, you'd agree with me.
If something is a mere coincidence, meaning just happenstance, then there's nothing to note about it, correct? There's no relevance to noting it, right? Objection.
Well, there are big coincidences and little coincidences.
I think some of the big coincidences deserve to be noted.
Small ones, probably not.
And the reason they deserve what noted or investigated is because they signify that it may not be a coincidence at all, correct? Objection.
I'm not sure what the coincidence would point to, honestly.
It's just one thing that people have to look into on their own, what is relevant if it points to something, right? Objection.
Not necessarily.
I think coincidences can be highlighted without them having a point to them.
So your testimony is that when you're highlighting what you refer to as these coincidences, you are not intending to suggest anything about what they signify.
That's your testimony? I'm trying to tell the reader that this is going on.
It's kind of weird.
What do you think about it? I think at the bottom of one of my articles, I'm like, what do you think? Sound off in the comments below.
So just kind of bringing this to people's attention.
It's just what value is there, too? Coincidence? That's the question you have to ask yourself.
I think at that point, I'd be like, mr.
Salazar, I am now going to bounce a tennis ball off your forehead every time you say something about your job.
That's pants shittingly insane.
What are you talking about? Just coincidences, man.
What are you talking about? I mean, you know that time that Infowars ran a huge expose about how Carmen Electra's birth name was Terra Patrick, and she couldn't use that name because it was already a porn star's name associated with Carmen? Isn't that an interesting coincidence? That's a big coincidence.
So we investigate that one.
Not one of those little coincidences, right? I mean, it's.
Like, do you really think, like, maybe you would run an article about how some people have the same middle name? I mean, that's a coincidence.
What do you understand the word coincidence to mean? Yeah, no, there can't be.
I mean, I understand what you mean by big coincidences, little coincidences, but that is not a description of their meaningfulness.
That's insane.
Yeah, I'm not sure you do know what he means by big or little coincidence.
Actually, I'm not sure I do, now that you say it like that.
I know what I would mean by saying that.
What he means, I do not know.
And I certainly feel for Chris Matty quite a bit, because there is just a real attempt to be like, come on, you're making a point.
There's a point that you're trying to make.
Words have to have meaning.
An adon will not go for it.
God damn.
It isn't true, mr.
Salzar, that the reason you're highlighting what you claim are coincidences is because you want your audience to suspect that something like Sandy Hook, in fact, did not occur as has been reported.
Isn't that your purpose? Objection.
My purpose is to point out the coincidences and let the reader make up their own mind.
You have no interest in suggesting to the reader what the relevance of the coincidence might be.
That's your testimony.
I think I present the evidence, I gather it for them and allow the reader to make up their own mind.
Yes.
So we have one sort of coda here of the Sandy Hook prop portion.
And so just we'll ride this out here.
And then this is exhibit number 16.
This is your Facebook page, correct, Mr.
Salazar, in which you are posting on February 6, 2013, less than two months from the shooting, something from Intel Hub concerning Sandy Hook, and you post Google Scott Getsinger, correct.
Oh, my God.
And that's because you wanted people to discover the same nexus that you believed you had discovered between Mr.
Gessinger's death, the map in the dark night rises, and the Sandy Hook shooting, correct? Yes, I was pointing people to the anomaly.
The anomaly which you testified had absolutely no significance to you, correct? Objection.
I don't think I said it had no significance.
I think I said it was a bizarre coincidence that people should be aware of.
But that did not signify anything to you, correct? Well, it didn't signify that it was a staged mass shooting, but it did signify something very bizarre.
Bizarre coincidence.
What did it signify? It was just a bizarre coincidence that needed to be found.
For what purpose? We're not going to let this go, man.
Look into it so they can investigate it on their own.
So they could investigate it on their own and potentially discover that, in fact, it wasn't a coincidence at all, but that Mr.
Getsinger had been killed so as to silence him because he was aware that the change in the Sandy Hook map signified some advanced knowledge of the shooting.
Correct? Objection.
I'm not sure what they would discover, honestly.
It was very strange though, putting it out there.
I wanted them to google Scott Gensinger and see all the anomalies.
Yes.
Okay.
Just see what happens.
Just Google it and see what you find.
Maybe you'll find some of his other work from his storied career in other movies like The Truman Show.
Maybe that's a good reason to Google him, to see the work that he's done over the course of his career.
What's? His IMT page? Yeah.
Oh, boy.
I mean, it's infuriating.
Yeah.
I don't know Chris Matty personally as I know some of the Texas attorneys, but I get the sense that maybe he enjoys that back and forth a little bit.
It does seem a little bit like that.
Yeah.
There is a like AHA, how about this one? How about we try these words? Right? So there is a meaning to this for you, right? Coincidence that people should look into look into and find what? What? Come on, man.
All right.
Okay.
Frontal assault isn't going to work for you.
I'm going to go around the back.
Let's see about this one now.
Okay.
Alright.
So a lot of this stuff is fairly annoying, certainly.
Yes.
But there is some, like, positivity that comes in.
Unfortunately, it's positivity in the worst possible way.
Sure.
You received an email, did you not, in March, march 7, 2013 from Daniel Dupont.
Okay.
And Mr.
Dupont wrote to you, please stay on top of the story, no names of deceased to be released, et cetera.
The attack appears to be completely staged.
The public knows that they are being lied to.
And you wrote back to him.
Thank you for the encouragement.
Come on, man.
YouTube video that Infowars had published in January, correct? Yeah, looks that way.
Boy, I would regret responding to a random email like that at this point.
That would be like, I didn't have to write back to that.
He didn't give us a true moment, though.
A true moment of comedy, where he was like, yeah, I don't think I read that one.
He's like, let's see the reply that you sent to them.
Yeah.
Wow.
So now we finally get to conversation about Wolfgang Halbig and his role in all of this and how would dawn first learned about him.
One of the articles you wrote introduced the Infowars audience to Wolfgang Halbig, correct? Yes.
How did you first learn of Mr.
Halvin? I heard he was interviewed and I went and listened to the interview on American Free Press.
You required conducted the interview.
Not sure.
Did you recall when that was? Know, I'd have to look at the date on the article.
Let me show you what has been marked as exhibit 19 B.
Do you see an email from Bastian to you tomb? Astian you bet this guy.
And yes, it's legit.
Ask alex to bring him on as a guest.
Okay.
Basskyne is I have no idea.
And you understood Mr.
Bastian to be asking you to vet Wolfgang Halbeck, correct? Yes, it looks like that.
Yes, sir.
But you don't know who Bastian is? No.
So this interview on the American Free Press was released on February 11, 2014.
So the email from Bastian asking Adan to vet him came the next day.
It's probably not unreasonable to assume that Adan heard about the interview from this email unless he was closely monitoring everything put out by the AFP.
Yeah.
It's really good that Adan seems to not know who did that interview, because if he did, he'd have to say that it was Dave Gehari, a friend of David Dukes, who actually was the publisher of Jim Fetzer's book, Nobody Died at Sandy Hood.
OOH, Nazi.
Shit.
Well, and the guy who published that book that you're not supposed to really know all that much about, he was the guy who was interviewing Wolfgang.
How big that brought how big? To the attention of oh, man.
Of infowars.
Actually, I was looking around on Gehry, and he actually recently has made some comments about, like, I think I might be responsible for Alex and Wolfgang.
How big? Getting sued.
Yeah, maybe that's possible.
It could be you.
So even leaving aside who this interviewer was, american Free Press is a rag that was founded by Nazi and General White supremacist Willis Carter, which has a strange trend of Holocaust deniers as writers.
So it's not a great sign that this is where Adan was cruising to get new guests, particularly ones he's going to use to inflict severe trauma on the parents of murdered children.
Yeah.
Maybe do better.
That's not good.
A tip for depositions.
Ask how many exhibits there are.
Like, get as much information as you can beforehand.
And in fact, I would say even prepare, because then when you go in, see, this goes back to the first clip.
Yeah.
Prepare a little more.
You don't run into this.
And now let's go to exhibit 19.
Shim, you know what exhibits are coming.
That's what's important.
That's what my pro tip.
Sure.
Yeah.
Or, like, just be aware that you tried to sign up for crisisactors.org before you say, I wasn't interested in crisis actors, you really got to know what websites you signed up for that are exactly the thing that you shouldn't have.
So Don, having heard this American Free Press interview, you felt the need to vet Wolfgang.
Sure.
where Mr.
Halwick says down here in this paragraph, I think it's a scripted event that took place.
I think it was in planning for maybe two two and a half years.
Yes.
Okay.
And that was Mr.
Halbig's allegation correct? Yes.
Now, the idea that a mass shooting at which 20 children were killed and six educators were killed have been scripted and planned for two and a half years in advance is a serious charge, correct? Correct.
And you knew it was a serious charge at the time, serious charges.
And that's why you felt like you needed to establish Mr.
Halberg's credentials, right? Objection.
Wish anyone's credentials if you're writing about them.
But you'd agree with me that you did not do that in every article in which you reported what somebody else was saying, correct? I don't check credentials for everybody I write about.
Yes.
All right, but you did for Mr.
Housing.
Yes.
And the reason you did is because you knew that these allegations were particularly serious? Objection.
I thought he was bringing to the table some important information that only a school safety consultant could provide.
Did it occur here how families who have lost loved ones at Sandy Hook would react to an allegation that, in fact, their children were murdered in an event that was scripted and planned over two and a half years? Did that occur to you? Objection.
I didn't think about that.
Why would you? Yeah, I mean, they're not real.
They're not real people.
See, I am in Austin, Texas, working for Infowars, and they are not there.
Right.
It's solipsism.
Also, people might have heard what sounded like a gasp.
It was you.
Hiccuping.
I did not gasp.
I hiccup.
Yeah.
So the vetting process pretty light.
Almost like the vetting process to get hired at Infowars.
It turns out they're parallels.
You googled it.
Other than visiting the website, which you acknowledge Mr.
Halbeck may have put up himself, and reviewing the interview, did you do anything further to investigate the claims that he made relating to the threatening conduct of law enforcement officers and the scripted nature of the scene to hook them? No, I didn't.
I just published what he said in the interview.
Why? And you're aware that shortly after you published this article, mr.
Halbig appeared on the Infowars broadcast? Are you aware of that? I think I recall yet.
Probably a coincidence.
Yeah.
Bizarre.
So he did a little looking around.
Yeah.
Did a website that maybe how big? Put up himself? Yeah.
Well, I mean, listen to that interview.
If it's on the Internet, you can trust it.
It's the mainstream media.
He said bingo.
Let's go.
Let's do it.
It looks good.
Yeah.
And then a guy named Robert Keith sent an email to Info that said, hey, this guy looks shady.
Maybe check into his credentials.
Yeah, maybe don't do this.
And Adon wrote back to him and said, hey, man, it looks like he's got plenty of credentials.
Oh, my God.
You're being too unspecific.
And so Heath wrote him back and had a specific long list of things that were of concern.
Right.
We talked about this on a bunch of the deposition episodes because it's come up in the corporate reps and with Alex, so I didn't want to play it all over again, but we got this discussion about the email here.
So Mr.
Heath followed up in his email to you with the results of inquiry he had made online about Mr.
Halbat's past, correct? Here's that way, yes.
Okay.
And it seems as though he did, according to his email, quite a bit more than you did to investigate Mr.
halving's background correction, but it looks like he did ample research.
Well, all you did was visit one website that Mr.
Halbeck himself may have created.
Correction he may have created I think I did a little bit more searching, but I think it was mainly based off of that one website.
Okay.
You're talking to me earlier today.
Was that it was just the website.
Are you expanding that now to testify that you think you may have done other searches? Objection.
I don't recall what kind of searches I did for Mr.
How big's information other than that website, but it's possible that I did do more research other than what I stated I did.
I'd like to stipulate that I might have done something yeah, that makes you look way better.
Yeah, I did this bad thing, but I might have done I will say that if I were in a don's position and the lawyer asks, is it fair to say that this random guy emailing you did more work than you on the story you're doing? Yeah, if my lawyer didn't then object, I'd be furious.
Yeah.
That would be a position where no, you're getting hanging out to dry.
That's what's happening.
If your lawyer is like, yeah, answer that question, buddy.
So these emails come in warning about how big s credentials.
Right.
And as it turns out, I mean, how big just kept coming back on the show.
Yeah.
Did Mr.
Heath email to you in which he expressed concern that he was not able to find information concerning how big professional activities cause you to question whether Mr.
How big could be relied upon? I think the points he's bringing it up are valid, and, yeah, I think it probably maybe made me question I can't recall how I felt at the time.
Okay.
In fact, you don't even recall receiving this email, correct? It's been so long.
It's been nine years, so, no, I definitely don't recall receiving this email.
And you don't recall whether you raised mr.
Heath's concerns with anybody else at info force, is that correct? I don't recall doing that either.
Yeah.
If you had, do you suspect you would have ordered mr.
Heath's email along to whoever you wanted to notify about it? Yes, I probably would have.
Yes.
Okay.
whatever you may have done or not done in response to this email, mr.
Howberg continued to appear on Infowars after March 15, 2014, correct? I believe that's the case, yes.
And you don't recall whether you did any additional betting of Mr.
How big yourself in response to receiving this email? Correct? I don't believe I did any betting after this email.
Now, wow, that certainly shows that you care.
Mr.
Medi, I think you misunderstood our process here.
You see, what we did was we used him because his narrative bolstered our own credibility, and that was so we could make money.
Oh, no.
Now I see why we're in trouble.
And honestly, at the time, we kind of figured that if anybody was going to get in trouble, it would be him.
Yeah, we thought we were off the hook.
Yeah, we kind of thought we were going to be able to throw him under the bus.
I'm going to throw this out.
Screwed up.
We're not good at law.
I mean, based on their choice of lawyers, they really bad at law.
Yeah, fine.
So there is clear evidence that there were people who are raising concerns that a don had heard because he did respond to that email.
Yeah, that's an issue about Wolfgang how big's credibility.
But there were other people, maybe even Infowars employees, who were saying, you got to be careful here.
Other than Mr.
Heath, did anybody else ever warn you about relying on Mr.
Maybe.
I can't recall.
Possibly.
Do you know an individual named Robert Jacobson? Yes, Robert Jackson.
How do you know Mr.
Jacobson? He was a video producer for Alex.
Did your work intersect at Infowars? He's down the hall from me.
Once in a while, we'd chat.
When did he leave? In Cohorts.
Do you recall? Maybe 2017 or 2018 something somewhere around there.
I don't know.
And was he at his when you started in 2012? Yes.
So you were colleagues for five, six years? Yes, sir.
Did you have a friendly relationship with Mr.
Jacobson? Yes, I did.
Are you in touch with him today? Not really.
Do you communicate with him? I don't.
Did Mr.
Jacobson ever advise you of his concerns about relying on Mr.
How Big as a source for reporting that Sandy Hook was a scripted event? Mr.
Jacobson, I think, did raise concerns, but I didn't really regard them because Mr.
Jacobson has some wild theories about a lot of things.
Oh, he does? He has wild theories? Amazing.
Wild theories.
Just amazing.
Truly an incredible thing for a human being to say in the context within which he's telling it.
Yes.
He's telling me that maybe I shouldn't listen to this wacko about Sandy Hook being fake, but I don't listen because he's got weird theories.
He's a wacko.
Mike down for this because I get into what those theories are.
Oh, no.
And this is really unfortunate for a Don.
Your testimony is that Mr.
Jacobson raised concerns about Mr.
Halbig's credibility, but that you ignored those concerns because he tends to have wild ideas.
Yeah, he thinks Michelle Obama is a man, for one.
And you've actually posted on your own social media suggesting that Michelle Obama is a man.
Having I've gone along with that conspiracy theory? Yes.
You've actually posted a picture of Mr.
And Mrs.
Obama kissing and saying essentially, Happy Gay Pride Day? Correct.
I might have done that.
I don't know.
I don't remember.
So I guess you don't think that Mr.
Jacobson's view of that is quite as wild, right? I think I entertain the theory, but I don't espouse the theory.
In any event, you discounted Mr.
Jacobson's warning because you believe he held views like that.
Mr.
Jacobson wasn't completely credible in my opinion, but he did give the warning, and I didn't think much of it, honestly.
So the best way you can really interpret this otherwise, it's something that I couldn't even imagine translating.
But the best way I can figure is what Adam is saying is that Rob actually believes this thing.
Whereas I'm willing to post this trolling shit, post meme about it in order to push my transphobic and homophobic ideology, I'm willing to use something that I don't even come close to believing because it spreads the hate that I want to spread.
Whereas Rob is crazy because he actually believes this.
Right.
That's as close to making sense of this as I can.
Yeah, it does appear that he is saying that Rob is crazy for believing the things that I say.
Yeah, the things that we promote and make money off of.
You might actually believe this stuff, and that's worrying.
So see, the thing is, you got to see, Mr.
Maddie, the thing you got to know is none of us are actually really believe the shit that we say and Rob does.
So that guy's crazy.
I was invested in spreading Sandy Hook conspiracy theories and implying that it's fake because I needed to attack the event as a way to get around the obligation to make arguments in favor of guns being everywhere because of a liberal.
I have a kind of second order interest in it, whereas I'm actually just manipulating the audience into thinking these things are real, these concerns are real.
Again, in order to make money, rob kind of believes this stuff.
Wow.
It seems like that's one of the readings you could make of this.
I still know.
Well, there's another one, I think.
And that is that it's another rake in the face, and you're just sort of punch drunk from the rake.
You're like, I don't fucking know.
How am I supposed to respond to it? What am I going to say? Why didn't I listen to this guy's warning? Because I didn't.
What do you want? Well, no, how would Adan expect that Maddie has knowledge of this thing? He posted on Facebook.
Right.
He didn't expect that.
No, of course he thought he was going to get away with saying something that would be offensive to most people, this belief that Rob allegedly has.
And then they'd be like, oh, that is a crazy idea that Rob has.
Maybe you have demonstrated that he is not trustworthy, but instead, he gets confronted with you believe the same thing.
I mean, it is just amazing.
It's just amazing for a human being to be and it's even more amazing because Rob, when he was there raising these concerns about Wolfgang Adan, decided that the best course of action would be to make fun of him.
Oh, my God.
Your general recollection that he raised concerns about relying on Mr.
Halbig as a source for the claim that CNN hook was scripted.
I believe I brushed it off.
I might have poked funded him for saying that.
Did you report these concerns to anybody else at Info Wars? No.
Do you ever take any tips to have those T shirts or bumper stickers made? No.
Did you say that because you believed, in fact, Mr.
Halbig was right? I tend not to, like, throw my beliefs behind everything fully, so it's potential that he could have been correct, and I just know that it was getting under Jacobson's craw to say that he was right.
So I kind of threw that in there as a joke, but also half serious.
See, it's a joke, but it's also kind of serious.
Oh, my God, I'm kind of making this point, but it's also a joke.
I want to have entire plausible deniability about this stuff, but I also really want the benefits of people thinking that I'm serious about it when they're available.
How is it that a human being can lay out this clear a pattern of behavior that you engaged in that is so obviously everything wrong and not be like, Now I get it.
Right.
Well, just because, you know, going in, that what you already full of shit.
Yeah, exactly.
And I think that that moment of the constant banging your head against the wall, of, like, you had these things that you were bringing up about anomalies Sandy Hook, but you weren't making a point.
You didn't have a conclusion of the foreknowledge.
Like, if he realized the thing that was laid out about 911 at the beginning of the like, I had anomalies and it made me government did it.
Totally.
There should be a moment where it's like, Ah, fuck, yeah.
Absolutely.
That's what I want.
I just want that moment, like, with Norm dropping his bullshit to me.
That's the moment that I really want is when you have to finally admit that you're an idiot.
And I have boxed myself in.
Exactly.
I can't exist in this space and make anything totally.
You did this to yourself.
Yeah.
A decade of working at Info Wars causes no problems because no one gives a shit.
No one is monitoring your work.
I've never been asked a follow up question in my life.
Integrity and the point doesn't matter.
No, but yeah, when you're asked follow questions.
When you're in a place where people don't believe your nonsense, you can't do it.
It's hard.
Also, this was really funny.
I mean, it's not funny because the result of it, but being said, Don, is very funny.
Okay.
Up until relatively recently, you had a pinned tweet to the top of your Twitter account, which was a link to your first ever article about Wolfgang Halbeig introducing him to the Infowars audience, correct? I don't recall a pen tweet about how big, but maybe I don't know why I'd be publishing that on Twitter in 2019.
Okay, good question.
Showing you exhibit number 19 A.
Oh, my God.
This is the page of your Twitter account, correct? Yes.
Okay, and you joined in September 2017, right? Okay.
Yes.
And then you have a pinned tweet at the top of your account, which, according to the page, was posted on April 17, 2018, correct? Oh, my God.
Okay.
And you can see the partial headline there.
School shooting expert threatened over Sandy Hook.
That's the first article you ever wrote concerning Mr.
Halving, correct? Yes, that's it.
So at least as of 2018, you were leading your Twitter landing page with an article in which Mr.
Halbeig referred to Sandy Hook as a scripted event, correct? Objection.
It appears I pinned the tweet to the top of my Twitter account on April 17, 2018, and the pin linked to an article in which Mr.
Yes.
The article is about it's.
The one we covered earlier.
Yeah.
Boy, well, I guess I did do that.
Why did I post that article in 2018 and pin it in my top tweet on my account? Mr.
Medi, I'm starting to see a pattern of behavior here.
So you ask me a question, then I answer it, and then whenever I answer it, you pull out an exhibit proving the opposite, or at least something different from what I said.
Is it too late for me to blame this on them not training me? How have you considered telling me what your exhibits are before you ask the question? That was really fun.
Then I will be able to answer truthfully.
So we have one last thing that comes up, last line of questioning that has to do with Adon writing.
The FBI says no one was killed at Sandy Hook.
Right.
That article that was one of the most popular stories ever.
Drove a massive spike in traffic, went all over social media.
It was a huge thing for infowars.
And, yeah, it was all just based on one table from a report that Adon found somehow, I guess.
you cited a table eight from that report, correct.
You recall that it might have been table eight.
Okay.
And I'm going to pull that up for you.
That's 25 B.
And I'll acknowledge, Mr.
Salazar, that because of the way this was PDF is kind of partly cut off on the left side, but we'll be able to see what we need to see.
You recall the look of this graphic header? You included that in your article, did you not? Yes.
page three, to the Newtown row now, I can see that the N is cut off, but if we can just accept for purposes of this that this is the New Town row, you see that zero are reported in that particular row for murders and non negligent manslaughter for that year, correct? Yes, I see that.
And that was the quote anomaly you were reporting on, right? Yes.
But you didn't look in any other part of the report to see if the deaths that occurred in Newtown at the Sandy Hook shooting were in fact reported in another section, did you? I didn't think there would be another term for what happened at Sandy Hook.
I thought the murder would encompass the whole thing any further for other definitions or other places.
And you didn't look any further to see whether those murders were reported under a different law enforcement organization that had jurisdiction to investigate them, correct? I only was reporting on what the FBI was saying in this report.
Well, that's what I'm asking.
Good question.
This report wasn't just table eight, correct? There were other parts of the report.
Did you know that? Objection.
I figured there's one through seven at least it's table eight.
So we're on one through seven exists probably somewhere.
And you didn't think to look for table nine or table ten or any other tables, right? Objection.
I think my story was mainly about table eight, so I didn't go through the entire list of tables that the FBI has.
So I was listening to this and it just kind of struck me how clearly this demonstrates that there's no curiosity.
No, because curiosity isn't useful for someone like a don.
Like when your job is to write a story about a predetermined thing, curiosity is just going to get in the way.
In order to do the work that he has done and is doing, you have to actively not ask questions.
You have to actively not question events.
You're branding yourself in some way as like, we're out there, we're questioning things, but this is literally not asking questions.
It's stopping yourself from asking natural questions that one would have upon finding information.
It's wild.
I don't understand how they can't understand not that they don't understand it, but I don't understand how they can't see how transparent that is.
Well, what's interesting to me about that is I feel like it's very similar to why they're so susceptible to being trapped in these depositions, is because the way their brain thinks is they go into the forest, they get their apple, and then they go back home.
You could put an apple underneath a box, and I'm talking about this now.
In real life, you could put an apple underneath the cardboard box with a little thing attached, and they'd be trapped.
Every time they go in there, they grab the apple.
They'd be like, OOH, good apple.
And then they'd be trapped.
It wouldn't be hard.
They don't think clearly.
Well words.
All of the things they don't think them.
Yeah.
I just I wonder if it is just a thing of, like, no one cares in their lives, so why would they think that anybody else would see through the fake game that they're playing? Yeah.
If he did have curiosity somewhere with deep within him, I really feel like his answer to those would be like, oh, that would be a good idea to look for a table nine.
Right.
Ironically, I'm curious about this lack of curiosity, and that is absolutely not a healthy place.
Where does it come from? Yeah, but he really only was interested in that table because it made his argument.
He got it apple.
Yeah.
You only went to the one table that A.
Tipster pointed out to you.
Correction.
I only went to the table that showed their zero debts in New Ten.
Right.
But you had to have a reason to know that that's what that table showed.
And I think your testimony was that A.
Tipster had provided it to you.
Correct? It was either a tip or something I found on social media.
Yeah.
Okay.
And you only wanted to go to that table because that's the table that reported zero deaths, right.
That's the only table that pertains to the story I was writing.
Yes.
Well, the story you were writing reported that the FBI reported zero deaths in Newtown, correct? Yes.
And that's why the point is a table eight showing that it showed zero deaths in Newtown.
And what you were conveying to your audience was, this is an anomaly.
If there had been deaths in Newtown, you would expect the FBI to have reported them, correct? We're trying, yes.
Back down.
What you didn't point out was that the FBI didn't fact report them in a separate table in the same report correction.
Mischaracterizes the evidence.
You didn't point that out, did you? I wasn't aware that the FBI had reported the deaths elsewhere.
I don't know why they would not list the deaths where it says murders in UTown zero.
You don't know why they might do that.
Correct.
It seemed like it should all be listed in the table late and what did you ask or make any inquiry about whether those deaths may have been reported elsewhere in the same report? Correct? I didn't ask the FBI, if that's what you're asking.
You didn't ask anybody? No.
This is a dangerously uncurious and unserious person.
That's insane.
Yeah.
That's bananas.
I feel like he's now a completely unique person to me.
I don't know how this person exists.
How do you tie your shoes? My God.
So did you think that there could be a table nine or they could report it anywhere else? I don't know why they would.
You can answer that question, right? You can go be like, why would you? And find the answer things that you don't know if they aren't, like, necessarily in your interest? It's a dead end.
Yeah.
There's no reason to explore this because the only thing you could possibly find ruins the ability to get this for your purposes.
Which is what they won't just come out and say, right? Yeah, but it's pretty obvious.
If I looked any further, I would find out that I'm lying.
And I don't want to do that because I want to possibly deny that I'm lying.
I would get past the point of plausible deniability, and then we're in trouble.
Like these emails you keep reading back to me.
So, speaking of emails, I'm going to skip this next clip because it's long, and honestly, I only kept it in for one reason, and it's because there's an email that he sent to his cousin that was about these cyclists who are going from Newtown to Washington to, like, bring attention to gun legislation.
And he sent an article about it, and the subject headline was Fuck These Psychological.
That's very good.
I'll take that one.
Yeah, but it's a long clip.
We can skip it.
Yeah.
So the subject comes up as we're dismounting here of a documentary that Infowars had promoted called We Need to Talk About Sandy Hook.
And here is Adon's sense of what happened there.
You familiar with the documentary We Need to Talk About Sandy Hook? I believe I tried to get through it.
It was so long that I probably just got through 30 minutes worth of it or something.
Yeah, fairly familiar with the documentary.
Okay.
And you didn't have anything to do with making that documentary, did you? No, sir.
Did you promote that documentary on your social media platforms? I might have.
I can't recall.
Do you know whether Infowars ever promoted that documentary? I believe I wrote an article about it when it was taken off of vimeo or something.
No, other than that, I don't think we promoted it.
I just read about why being censored.
Okay.
Did you express your own disagreement with the fact that certain platforms had chosen not to publish it? Well, I did write an article about it.
I don't know if I express a personal opinion in that article.
Okay.
Did you know at the time that We Need to Talk About Sandy Hook documentary presented, to view that Sandy Hook and not in fact, occurred? I figured that was the central tenant of the documentary, but I didn't watch it in its entirety, so I kind of had to just guess that was what they were going for.
And you reported that in your coverage of the ban? I believe so.
Okay.
On December 2, 2014, inForest posted the video of this documentary on their site with the subheadline, quote, documentary blows the lid off suspected Sandy Hook coverup.
The article includes this, which sounds pretty laudatory a loose coalition of concerned citizen journalists known as the Independent Media Solidarity have produced an indepth, well researched documentary regarding the countless anomalies inconsistencies and discrepancies evident in the Sandy Hook School shooting investigation.
The video is a tellall, leave no stone, unturned work that coalesces hundreds of data points, which researchers laboriously spent countless hours compiling.
That certainly sounds like what you might write if the video was too long.
You couldn't even make it through the whole thing, and you can't even really nail down what the point of it was.
Also, the article includes this update a previous version of this video was removed from YouTube due to a copyright claim by Lenny Posner.
Posner is reportedly the parent of one of the children supposedly killed at Sandy Hook.
Reportedly and supposedly both in that sentence.
It's pretty over.
Go fuck you.
Wow.
If that's the article that dawn wrote, makes himself look quite a bit worse.
Yes.
Man, he should have watched the last ten minutes of that documentary, because they go, Hahahaha.
Fooled you.
And then we were just doing this to fuck with Rob Jacob.
Yeah, this is all the fuck with Rob.
So Maddie is done with his questioning, and unlike some of the other depositions here, at the end, the defense lawyer asks a couple questions.
And so the first one has to do with that only using table eight of the FBI.
Let's hear the stats.
There were some questions about this table eight at the time you reviewed table eight back in 2014.
Did you have any reason to doubt that the number for Newtown as zero was accurate? That's bullshit.
Adon absolutely had reason to question the interpretation of the table given here because the rest of the world was saying that these kids did in fact, die.
There is a direct contradiction here, and any curious person would see that table, and it wouldn't even really be a choice to question things.
It would just be a reaction.
You'd start asking yourself things like, how is this possible? Is there information I'm missing? What's the context here? Is it possible for both this table to be accurate and the shooting happened as was reported? The not questioning is actually a choice Adan is making, and he does that because if he scratched even an inch below the surface, he couldn't make the insane claims that he does make for a living.
He's woefully unqualified, and doesn't have the tools to be in the role he pretends to be in, which is that of a writer and reporter.
Yeah, that ability to turn off the instinct to question things when something conforms to your narrative while simultaneously yelling at your audience about how you're the people who question things, that ability actually makes him perfectly qualified to be an in house liar at Infowars.
Yeah.
So he better hope they don't go out of business, because there's not many other games in town.
Yeah, that's the way no, but they don't pay well.
No, see, the problem is, all right, I just misread it.
I didn't know it was table eight.
I thought it was table infinity, so, of course I didn't think there were one through seven.
This is all the tables? Yes.
I didn't think there were imaginary number tables.
Yeah.
Come on, man.
So here's the last clip.
The defense lawyer also has a question about his research that he did about the qualifications presented by Wolfgang Halbert.
Let's hear this.
Switching over to Mr.
How big? You don't have to have that open anymore.
There was some discussion of an email you received questioning his credentials.
Do you recall that? Yes, I recall it.
Now, when you first wrote about Mr.
How Big, you referenced one website, but was that necessarily the entirety of your research? I can't recall how much research I did.
I know that one website did probably provide a majority of the credentials that I credited him.
Is it possible you could have come across, say, Orlando Sentinel articles from the 90s referring to him as a director of security for seminal schools? Entirely possible, sir.
Could you come across articles in the La times mentioning him in the late 90s, early 2000s? Objection.
It's possible, sir.
This is fishy.
Oh, man, I love it.
Is it possible that you could testify better? Here, use this.
Okay.
Excuse me.
My own witness.
Could you do a better job? Let me give you an up.
Yes.
Jesus Christ.
It would be a better answer for you.
Wow.
Yeah.
If you had prepared for that, then you would have had that in the can.
Maybe.
If your lawyer knows that, then you should know that.
Oh, you'd hope.
Why is this hard? I feel like this is not that hard.
Yeah.
So we reached the end of this deposition of Adam Salazar.
And like I said, this peeled away a bit of the mystique around him and sort of, I don't know, a sense of menace that I felt about his body of work.
Certainly, I think he's defanged a little bit in my mind.
Yeah.
If the wizard of Oz was revealed to be a puddle of mayonnaise, that could handle a lever.
Maybe part of it was just because he was the one who was following us and then stopped following us.
Maybe that is kind of part of the menace.
Whatever the case, I feel like the way he answers questions, the way this is all processed, is very sad, transparent, and, I think unnecessary.
He didn't have to answer any of these questions.
No way.
Nope.
He clearly has an interest in the company.
Like he's a company guy.
I think we covered his deposition.
Certainly.
I hate paul Joseph Watson, but we weren't as cruel about that because he comported himself decently.
Yeah.
There is obviously more actions that Adam Salazar took in the past that are relevant to this case and that is unique for his position as some being deposed.
But there is such a refusal to accept reality and the like, no, I wasn't making a point.
It's just a weird coincidence.
Stop it, stop it.
Like, that stuff is a come on, man, you're a child.
It makes you lose a little bit of respect.
Even as a villain in my mind, you can't just be like, yeah, this is what I was thinking at the time.
I found out I was wrong and whatever right.
There's a way to do this that isn't completely disqualifying and he failed to know it is.
Like he was trying to half lie about everything.
Like, I'm going to try and obfuscate just enough.
Like, yeah, I'll say yes or no, but whenever they want to get me on something, I'll be like, I don't recall, or something like that.
Revelations of like it was my vested interest in questioning the reality of Sandy Hook had to do with my fear of them using it against the guns.
There's stuff like that that's just like, damn, you can't be real.
How can you be so slippery about a bunch of these other things and then just give that one give it away.
Give it all away.
Very weird.
Wild.
Anyway, we have a bit more where this came from.
Oh, yeah.
There's more deposition that will be coming up in the future because that's bottom feeders we got to do.
We love feeding on the bottom immediately after being called a bottom feeder to then talk about a Donadar Salazar.
It doesn't make me feel great, but there are worse things.
Sure.
Anyway, I mean, we'll be back with another episode in the near future.
Indeed.
But until then, we have a website.
We do it's knowledgefight.com.
We're also on Twitter.
We are on Twitter at that knowledge of the score fight and someone's been fighting.
No, we'll be back.
But until then, I'm neo.
I'm Leo.
I'm dzx Clark.
I run a cooperative in my brain where people are free to squat.
It's an artist's spaceship.
This is not really so much a thing where a charge rent barter is acceptable.
Right? I don't know what I'm saying.
Here comes the sex robots.
Andy and Kansas, you're on the air.
Thanks for holding.
So, Alex, I'm a person calling in my a huge fan.
I love your work.
I love you.