A young fireplug of a warrior goddess teeth and Alex Jones and decided he'd like to know on
Online
Again video
Find to the ridicule of all the Alligators
Something called knowledge first or knowledge fight people apparently
Loving date Alex Jones
Watch fight
A couple bottom-feeders who make their eating out
And so they have episodes almost
I guess I should say it
I got my ass kicked
Everybody
Alex
Jordan my bright spot is I was
Podcast
Needed someone to fill in
I imagine that would be a little bit more about Bray Wyatt
Somebody talked about
I don't understand what the deal is with orange Cassidy
I mean if you don't know how to find podcasts that's kind of an interesting
How do you find us
Exactly
Tell you to check out these New York City's losers Lake from LimeWire what's going on
My wife
Very beautiful person lovely love her very much
I found out
Recently that my shoes are garbage as they almost always are
Nice ceremony that I'm the fastest
Tennis player maybe there's ever been right now
All sorts of things can be just a little bit
Just a little bit when you're running that's an excuse but also your feet are
I like goldfish and they will grow to the size of the container from what I remember
In basic biology when he's about a trait that is what they said about
These are different I don't want to screw up the good shoe sure sure one time
I got new shoes
Why you no like is there new
And I wore them to an open mic just because I don't like my older shoes at falling apart
I wore them and I walked in and immediately sorry Aunt Roxy and
John
John McBride there's like I forgot we're sitting at a table and they saw me and they just started doing
Run of jokes about my new shoes
Halo
You don't get that it's just my favorite
Yeah I couldn't stop laughing
Anyway Jordan today we have an episode to go over we're going to do some fun stuff but you might notice in the end
Throw their revenue special intro courtesy of DJ danarchy
Stop that
Norm pattis lawyer extraordinaire premiere
Lawyers for cemented lawyers constitutional lawyers
For shitbags
Right he has a podcast called law and legitimacy and
After the trial he did a little bit of a breakdown
Battle of what happened
How he was wrong how the appeal is going to go great
Sure I'm and if you decided to bring us up and
What a terrible idea
But
That's the rule rule number one there
You just accidentally revealed a lot more than you wish.
Quite a bit I think he mentioned us in a bankruptcy hearing recalled
Knowledge first
Thought about
And I was just
Good clean fun
This mention of us
Is deeply problematic for Alex
And everybody at Infowars
You could hear the intro and feel like things are maybe taking a little bit out of context for the sake of the beat
USB clip of Norm talking about us on his podcast and afterwards
I think we'll have a lot to celebrate
And if there's one thing I've learned about Alex
It's that deserve these were video.
People love to hate
And so the haters
We had a field day
There's not there's no there there there's no real work
So they testified about what they do when they're in
Cuz I don't know
Good question really
And he would that be young man was able
Persuade to trial judges
But this was Will
Did the corporation had an obligation to
Producer representative
Could answer
There had to be a
And so there was a
Another deadline in
We selected iselect
Connecticut because no one else
It info
Was willing to do it
No one wanted to have their hair during deposition place.
Video on
Online
To the ridicule of all the Alex haters
Because you know what
There are people
There's a
A website I learned about
Knowledge fight
Haha
Bottom Feeders are art make
There
And so they have episodes almost
Daily Mail
Call me out
Call this one
I mean
Percentage of the royalties for the space events in there
Haters didn't didn't want to
I'd be exposed
I'm so the Connecticut representative
Fight you didn't satisfy the
Tire plug or the
Judge
She testified in Connecticut
Three and a half days
I called it the Gilligan's Island
Direct
The guy had a
Lawyer for the pie
Wait the Gilligan's Isle S3 our Tornai three-and-a-half day that doesn't make sense no
That's that's Norm stand-up chops,
So Norm
Come on man
You you're showing too much here early Brittany Paws got hired as the corporate representative because
Everyone else was worried about being roasted
Okay
You know what day you kicked ass and you brought a lot of work into it but also the trials where the lawyers that are gray
A job you don't like your contribution was was spectacular but it was limited and it was shared
In this case
Stan you cost Norm pattis personally
$30,000
Maybe I am 600
OU yeah might be I mean like I don't want to break down quantifying things what is important
But there is a recognition here of a behavioral change that was made at Infowars which is prior to this robbed
Was totally fine going into being a Kangol hat wearing doofus
Did you do a couple I can't exactly man
He's afraid of me at all
To do this and face the kind of scrutiny in the public eye that are podcast RingCentral are words
Only our podcast break right
And the other thing that it reveals to is that there are discussions
About us being a motivating factor and them not wanting to be the corporate
F****** hilarious memes this conversation happened
We need you to be the corporate rap again
I don't want to do it
Those two guys will be mean to me those two guys at Chicago will just just
Roast the s*** out of me wow
Wow good luck royalties
He's really got to stop with this brain landlord joke
Too much
In the aftermath of the trial too much like
I mean it's fun and all like for the first time I heard it
Like
Like a hundred times
And I think that it's it's evidence of him either deflecting from reality or not understanding
What
I am this show is about
Yeah like I don't
Give a s***
What is a
He is only
Serving the purposes of what I hope to achieve
Alex's nothing I have the sky and everything cool is out there
After we get through alley
But not after we get the relics in terms of play
Yo him going away the window there's there's
You see through the window
Yes I think it's hilarious
Even funnier now that you it's too funny it's too funny thank you Norm
It's beyond a bright spot it's a revelation is it is because it is
Such it is such an acknowledgement of how much gaslighting they've been doing to us like
It's physically impossible for them not to know right we've known that for a long time
But what they knew how much they knew what it meant to them all that stuff
That we couldn't we could only
Guess it.
We can only guess at any kind of drives you mad cuz you're like
There's no way they put that much thought into it I think that's partially because you and I are self-deprecating
People by Nature it's so it's like
Get off your high horse these people don't care about you and cares about you and your head in Opera people
Gaslighting yourself along with them
You think you're so important that they care about you is by is my thought process
That's why it was so shocking that like I'd heard that he mentioned us on the map
That's all I'd hurt
I had heard the rent-free thinks I was like to find out the second part
Is mind-boggling
It is a bad idea to insult somebody when they have a DJ willing to
Remix that until 8
And if you were if you were in high school and there was a bully bothering you but you had a DJ was going to remix their insults
U14
If you
So little respect
Or the belief that whatever insult their saying is funny
No good no good
Wilford Snapple Snapple of the crippled people thank you so much
Wait I thought that was me
Slumlord
Wait why did that one show up first in your brain
I don't know
Can we agree we boys
Lucy lolling on the trail thank you so much
Thank you very much
Never expected to learn that Alex Jones thinks our last name is weird we pronounce it
Gil
The group of people is silent
Journal about
Very much
Scribble kibble
You're so far behind sometimes you can really get it really tell
After the group triple triple
I'm a policy thank you
As you know we talked about this privately I've been having some insomnia type issues
The past week has been really tough with the sleep schedule
You know I think it has a little bit of an effect on you know what you want to do how much you can take on and
What have you checked and I found myself this week definitely having a like
Turn on Alex's show
I didn't want to listen to it
It's frustrating I know I'm going to be bored
I'm already exhausted I don't really want to do this
And so I kind of
Do you know I can guess what he saying and I feel like I'm just not interested
And so I decided a norm
Talkingshit about discovering download
No
All these people are afraid to sit in a deposition room
Oh no we have another formulaic objection
Looking at is the deposition of Adan Salazar okay the
An editor people who wrote some of the articles that were Primary in the
Sandy Hook conspiracy right
Someone who has a female's around these Hindi hooked on versation
Yeah somebody who followed us on Twitter until we mentioned it and then he unfollowed ran away
Distance from V Connecticut case and somebody who I've always had a little bit of
Fascination with
Because I think he is a soldier
As they say in the
I don't know what world Gangland Warfare
Yeah.
He seems that he strikes me in the same way as someone like a Daria and that is like a all you believe
Or whether or not you believe you believe in whatever the underlying mission is going to follow orders
Regardless of whether or not they are sanctioned by the Geneva Convention
You know you are believing some insane thing
Are on distinguishable for you because
Whatever is motivating it is more important than its primary horrible s*** over
The course of his time he seems like an a******
I've never seen him in front of the camera
Is not an on-camera guy that's true
Until I had nothing really to prepare me to do
To study literature like what's going to happen here
I was afraid of him anymore he doesn't strike me as
His intelligence is not of the world shaking variety
Play might be a perfectly smart person but I don't find him and the way he answers questions
Processes what's going on to be all of that like remarkable
And that really bums me out
For some reason I thought he was like 26
Or like
I don't know diddly Alex Darren mcbreen age range
Backstage that I was surprised to hear and I was disappointed
You know it's like I can kind of
Whatever the
Landmarks in life
They would have been fairly similar
We would have been the same age at about certain times row experience certain things world events
You know from the same
Presumed
Level of maturity
Stanza that kind of makes me sad if he were on the front nine of life so to speak
Instead of the back nine is where he start he started when you're going this is not going to end well for you man
The other thing too is there like I realize how delusional's I was of me because he's been there since 2012
So like
The idea that he would be 26 is like what he started at 16 to me and this is ridiculous
Writing he's at though you're not wrong
This deposition is quite interesting it's taken by Chris Maddie
Let's just a jump in
How begins with some just formalities and stuff and the first question
The first bit that you want to get into is
How did you
Prepare for this deposition
That's a great way to open
And it always reveals that they didn't really tell that much
What did you do to her
Fair for today's deposition mr. Salazar
I went over a few of the articles that are in question
Which articles
Why did the
I reread the FBI's Sandy Hook
Ibie says nobody died at Sandy Hook and
Probably the
First
How big article that I wrote
The first what article probably
Wolfgang halbig article whatever
Title
Something to the effect of
Investigator
Threatened
Sandy Hook investigator friend something to that effect
That's it
Your beauty has two articles because of you anything else
But I didn't go in depth but I kind of just glossed over them
That's pretty much it
Okay
Did you review any other
Materials in advance of your deposition today
Other than
Attorney Waldman
Did you discuss
Your deposition with anybody else today
No sir
You haven't
Communicated with Alex Jones that you're being deposed
No sir
You haven't communicated that to David Jones
Ordinarily be working today
You're currently employed by whom
Free Speech systems infowars.com
As this deposition progresses you get the sense that maybe add-on should have done a little more to prepare for this interview
Basic elements of his timeline of his writing that Maddie can demonstrate Wichita
Seems to think are like on discoverable secret very strange and probably difficult to believe
That add-on didn't talk to Alex or Rob do about being deposed
They work together this is in relation to a suit against Alex and the company and he was supposed to be
At work that day
It seems like he would have to come up with a reason he couldn't make it to work so I guess he was just lied to his employer
Right off the bat that doesn't Inspire confidence in him as a credible
Highlighting his willingness to deceive
Yeah I told my I told Anna to listen I didn't tell Alex her Owen or anyting
Cuz I told him my grandma died and I had to go to the funeral so that I'm a reliable source but the record shows
He was going to testify is that probably or possibly give the impression that Alex coached him
But I don't understand what issues are just telling Alex
But the existence of this deposition do know that they were interested in talking to idantity wrote These are
Articles that are involved in the suit
I could possibly see a scenario where a Don was afraid to tell Alex that he was actually going to show up and talk to the lawyers
Something like that I have a hard time accepting that this didn't come up
Yeah possible but it's just like
It seems very weird. You okay
If I was going to be deposed for anything
And they had like
Books I had to read
And I and I would be like okay I'm going to make it through at least a full two or three of these books right I got the
Time I've got the work there's that there's the the need to do it and then maybe I can pass off the other three as being
But
Adan is only telling me that he skimmed
Less than 5000 words right
Some of them maybe longer than you
You think but not that long
It seems really strange Mau if you really wanted to be an active participant
You would go to read the article you figure out like where the information that you were working from came from
At least brush up on some of that so you can
Defend your process
But yeah you just give him some stuff
Yeah
So I don't started in April 2012
I am as we know the shooting happened in December 2012 so
Pretty new
But before we get to any of that we've talked about what he was doing before
April 2012
When did you go to start
For free speech systems
April 2012
Where we going to rain Friday night
I held three jobs
I rubbed vertex
Kroger.com
I also was a contractor for Quest Diagnostics
And
Was that their job
Google search engine
Optimizer
I work for a contractor
Complete
It's somewhat notable that add-on began his time it in for his only a short time before Sandy Hook
Record he was a fresh new on-the-job reporter when the story started and as you can tell from this resume that done is given
He didn't have previous work experience they would make him well prepared for the role that he found himself a hoe.
The job quest is basically a courier position shuttling samples from hospitals and doctors office to essential testing for
Facilitate
Textbroker is the sort of thing where he would get paid to write little blurb for website sort of a freelance
Big thing this is where you might go if you want someone to write a paragraph about yourself
Much
Textbroker is also the sort of place you might go to get filler for a website that's designed for gaming affiliate link system
To give you some sense of the operation
In their basic category of services you can choose their low-rate option
Which has this blur but this is how it describes that service using their service
Quote I accept mistakes in spelling grammar and expression in favor of a lower price
For writing where you can just write
You can make about 1.1 cents per word for that
If you have to pay attention to spelling and grammar you can make up to about like 5.5 sensor work
Walking to hustle when there's no shame in this kind of gig necessarily the sort of work you do if you had ended
Man skills in that field and it's something at
Maybe isn't a great thing to be like on the resume for
You know the job that he ends up in a line got paid 1.1 cents a word at one point but it is
The different is different currency why I don't think he's on the same level I don't think so
Money subtracted for punctuation
Mama's
Leapforce is described here as an SEO subcontractor for Google
More specifically the company hires people to work at home and do repetitive searches to evaluate the results
Basically accuses information for better add play some
He's a pain in the ass kind of job and you can find tons of reviews about the grind and how it's really only worth doing as a side gig
Sportsmax for cash unless you could just turn off your brain
The people unlike Glassdoor talk about this is miserable
I mean no offense to add-on or anybody else working these kinds of jobs
It actually does show quite a bit of initiative for him to have these three gigs running simultaneously that's you know
Impressive
I just don't think it's a kind of resume Arby incredibly impressed by if I were running a super important media Network and I was looking to hire
A reporter editor of the news
Maybe you take a chance on this candidate you get lucky but
Adams writing a behavior pretty Central to the claims that Infowars with disseminating that just lost them a billion dollars so it does
Doesn't seem like this one worked out great
When I worked at the coupon place right
Testing coupons that was my whole job is I would go in there and I would test expired coupons I put the code into a web
Website like Alexa
Can you buy and they be like no and I be like you're goddamn right now
That was my whole day
Right yeah
At no point in time was I like okay now that I finish this
I'm going to go work for the Tribune as a cub reporter like that wasn't that that's not the jump
I'm not the features editor
Don will go on to describe like his role in mediately was
There was no oversight
It's going to it's going from couponcabin to being to right hand in the newspaper
Well people already make it up as you go along.
That's crazy it's not
Sup best pract
So now we get to add-ons educational background
Educational background
I went to the University of Texas for about a year-and-a-half
Major in Liberal Arts
Took several English courses are
I also did half the semester
Austin Community College
I don't know why you even bring up that you did half a semester at a community college
It's just confusing and it sounds like you're saying that you signed up for some classes I need just didn't finish
Austin Community College's 16-week semesters but they also offer some courses that run 8 weeks so it's entirely possible
Bullheaded on is expressing that he finished some of those 8-week classes
But if that's the case you should have said I took a few classes at ACC
That makes me think that it's more likely that you signed up and then just didn't
Also I don't know how it is at all universities but typically liberal arts isn't a major in
Category of Majors you wouldn't be a liberal arts major you'd be within the liberal arts
The early year that he
Didn't finish maybe he hadn't chosen a specific made realize just taking the basic courses
Humanity
Oh yeah that's fine
Would like I don't think liberal arts as a major
When I was I didn't go to UT Austin Community College
For a while and I hated it so much that after the second week
I would drive there to avoid telling my parents that I wasn't going to school but I would sleep in the Paw
Parking lot
In case they put like a LoJack on your car
Respectful I'm going to not go to their class and sleep
Nearby
That's pretty good
I did not put that on many resume so I didn't put it on
You didn't when I hired you
Education in the academic environment as a whole but I do try to be as clear as possible
You can be a smart and capable as anyone who went to college without any higher education in many folks I know bear that out
Over here looking at you buddy hyper-competent people who never went to college and those people aren't for
Folks that I would look at it and say it should take some classes
Because they're doing just fine
On the other hand if you don't have any formal education then find yourself as a highly-placed reporter at a propaganda Outlet Where You Are
Argue The Grieving families are actors and
You're discussing your educational background in a deposition that about that shity work
I might think that your lack of training or familiarity with the field that you're in is a problem
If you would have taken some classes
Yeah perfectly blunt I don't think that any amount of classes would help too.
Nobody's Dumber anything just
I don't think that he's interested in doing the thing that he's doing well
Moral framework necessary to do what you're doing now
Then you're fine whether you're an expert at J school or not they're going to do what you're doing
The moment of Revelation about yourself as opposed to class
So by this point the deposition we have a sense of what add-ons resume would probably look like when he applied to be a writer and editor
Infowars
He had some freelance style writing experience but beyond that if he credential he had no experience in media order
Journalism education in the field but he got hired anyway
It seems like it might be possibly a reason why
Why did you apply systems
I like the Alex Jones and
The message
Before you leave
Ever applied General systems you were
Symphony audience member correct
Yes
I just
You know everytime I learn more about how Infowars operates I'm like there's no way there's just no way
It's usually a contest the demands of working there
I guess that baby is four more the on-air folks
The razzle-dazzle of contacts
About writing
Cuz there's like no better there's no like oh here's good writing a bad writing you've just got the same
Infowars essay contest oh no
I think I was Advocates below rates
Not worried about
Typos in spellings and character
Maddie asks what
About Infowars I really got check got you interested
You
Alex Jones
Show in the written consent
Probably there
You know their refusal to believe that the narrative behind 911
Expo motive
That the mainstream media had reported concerning 911
What was that question again
Were you suspicious
Question
I know you're anticipating what I'm going to say but
Did you personally suspect
The narrative
That the mainstream media have reported concerning 911
Yes I was suspicious
In 2012 11 years after 9/11
That's a motivating in a whenever he got interested in this work
Yeah so motivating factor
Suspicions about 9/11
What's your what's your
Career path like if it starts with
I thought 9/11 was an inside job and then the next step is
I'm the editor at infowars.com
Spezza career path I saw employment because I was impressed with these people refusing to believe
The 9/11
You know
Yeah I appreciate this Instinct on Maddie's part and that is to go from this
Suspicions about 9/11
Why
Because
In a deposition setting that can lead to some interesting thing
In in what in particular were you suspicious of
I didn't think we were being told the full truth about
Embarrassed
Parts of that
Narrative
Like
And can you go into a little bit more detail about
What you thought the gas were in what the reporting was
I could have supposed
I didn't think that the
Should have been able to take down the buildings
As they were taking down yeah
Seem like a controlled demolition which is a
A lot of people still believe actually
Are you one of those probably the biggest one especially with Building 7 falling
You know collapsing controlled demolition Style with no blender
The biggest actors
Indeed
The fact that you felt it was implausible
That the buildings would have
Collapse the way they did
Cause you to suspect weather
The United States government was
Involved in some way in the attack
Directions
Okay this is a really interesting Club because there's a couple of things happen
The first is really transparent which is how a conspiracy theorist answers a question
He was suspicious about 911 but it's a conspiracy he hasn't focused on in awhile so a lot
Foggy in his memory
Three tries to give a vague not answer
Then ask for something more specific
I just got like it doesn't seem right in building 7 is his response
How to adjust pretty soft
The second thing is something that will become important later if some of Maddie's questions develop
This is something that add-on is suspicious about
He has some inconclusive things 2.2 that he can use to justify these suspicions
And based on having those suspicions
He just testified to Maddie that led him to suspect the US government
Was involved
This provides a clear example of add-on stop Prosser
That's where he's willing to take things that look weird and make him suspicious
And use them to build up baseless explanatory narrative
Hold on to this for later because it will become clear how relevant this is the matter
And how much of a mistake this was on add-ons part
In in reflection maybe it doesn't
You know lead to any direct consequences but if you're analyzing this and looking at the way he
Describes
He's processing and and how he
Interact with information he's very damning
And it will become clearer later
I do appreciate one thing about Infowars employees that will never not be hilarious to me is that
At some point
Doesn't the lawyer half
To go in and be like
Before you answer the question
Look at me
To see whether or not I'm going to object
UK
Unless it's some other kind of objection
Sympathies
Real you slept
You can't tell you happy
I don't know or not answer you know your lawyer before your answer
Isn't that at that's what I would do
My answer is
So when Adam got hired he got some training
But it wasn't what you think
When you started it enforced in April 2012 did you receive any training of any car
Learn the back-end systems
Like WordPress
Things of that nature
Accident Freeman basically involves
You know
Learning how to use the
Software programs that you were going to be using everyday as an employee correct
Did you receive any training concerning
The writing function of your job
Did you ever
Impression of Orem
Did I ever watch
Did you ever receive any training during your tenure
Free Speech systems concerning
The writing function of your
Never received any training during the course of your employment
Concerning
Investigator
Journalistic practice
Petri mewmore at like
A fast food restaurant
I worked at JCPenneys for a for a cup of coffee
Hours long
Think about like
The corporate culture the rules and like harassment
Maybe she had to sign something saying that you understood the rules of what
They told ya it it seems like there's a oversight
If you walked into any newspaper in the world and they didn't tell you first things first about the
Be quote in house style
They were just like
Right away my dude
Also I would I would say that
Every single job
That I've ever had
At least the first like half a week maybe even the first week
You're working with somebody else
Just to do just to know exactly how to do your job
Yeah
It's wild that does not seem to be the case here. Receive training
On-the-job Universe sensibly do it
You know like steak
They taught him how to post things on the internet
Screw weight WordPress
Yeah
That was it you know what that it kind of makes me think of like some temp
Go do it I don't give a s*** I got out of work
What did he think that first six months
Right
He had to have been walking around like
They know right they know I have no idea what I feel like they have to look at me and know maybe that's part of it
Test though psychopathic
There's no such thing as imposter syndrome cuz I'm the greatest
They also got no training about like
What news to cover
You understood
When you applied Infowars that you would be
Applying for a
Editor and writer position
When you first start it
It sounds like
One of the things that you needed to do with update news item
On the infowars.com website correct
What do you mean by update
Find use
Items and
Republished them on Infowars
When the link back to the original
Find news items that appeared Elsewhere on the internet
And then
Put a link to that
News item on the infowars.com website
Correct
And how would you determine
Which news items to highlight on the infowars.com webs
That was subject
Basically whatever I thought
Would be good on the website
Did you receive any guidance
Or training on that in any way
No
That's
Wild
I mean
I don't words fail
I just don't know how
It's not like you have to think like that can't be true can't be true
The only place in the world where it could be true
Opening of a wework
You know like these are the only two scams where you can pull off having no clue what you're doing and just be like
I'm just straight-up quit so fast
This is a scam
This is trouble
Leaving aside anything about the ideology or anything about it
A business that runs like this like
I don't know if
Payroll works like this but what are we doing
That is the roommate scam I'd like that and if I
Was interviewing for that job I would do it the same way as the roommate scam you know where it's like we're some selenite
I've got a move in with you and be your roommate but I need $2,000 upfront to move here and then I'll give you two
Dollars whenever wherever whatever it is you do
I'm somebody
But it is it is the job coronavirus like hey man come on
No I don't believe you for a f****** second trying to make me the CEO and then blame me
Also I don didn't need to get anybody sign off on posting things
A posting
News item
That you had
Eclipse from other sources
Did you have to get approval from anybody to ask
Republic
It probably and it was like thanks
A little less
It was more loose back in 2012 and now we learned our lessons and work
Kind of strict about Willie republish
I know ask you some questions about that but it's
The time you started
You could go to any
Website
Select a news item that
You thought your audience might be interested in
And publish it to infowars.com
Wild
So the we've learned our lessons you think that's about like
My contact like Sandy Hook stuff
But it's not
It's a l
Clip that I didn't cut
That
Basically there are some websites
That are litigious about rejecting preparing their content
Basically by trial-and-error you learned that like
The AP doesn't like it when you just steal their articles articles
Right right here
Sad like in terms of the lessons you've learned
Respecting intellectual property I guess I'll be right 80s it is analogous to learning
About which dumpsters are good to get food from you know there's there's definitely certainly something along those lines
They are nothing if not a raccoon
We info scavenge
So
I think that if you're in a position like a Don believe it or not put on the
Front facing facade reporting facts
You're doing factual reporting
Do you consider yourself
To be reporting fax or do you consider yourself to be
You know writing your opinion
How do you
Consider the type of writing you're doing
Direction to Forum
I believe it's probably
You ride the fax with a maybe like a right-leaning slant instead of the left-leaning slant the mainstream media
Correctly
In your right hand
You are
Reporting facts but you the extent there's any sort of
Editorializing of those facts
You put a
Right-leaning
Slant on them
Yes send it
Usually yes I think so
You know that you're already home
Use
Add to the write-up
Political Spectrum
My audience and me
I mean
Yes
Resume writing
You know left-wing manifestos
Your audience wonder what the heck happened right
Right yeah
I think the journalistic outfits like they pee and stuff.
Pretend to be objective
But they're not
And we don't pretend to be objective
I'm sorry what
When you say you should only be a ejected I assume you don't need it
You are bias on our sleeves sorry
Not really no absolutely not Alex's entire brain disease above the left-right paradigm
Right-leaning slant of this is absolutely a betrayal of the central premise of Infowars
Yeah but also quite obvious
Not regulatory embarrassing that add-on would phrase it this way and I
Underoath setting
Because
Alex probably disagree
Yeah I mean
I'm not really willing
About the hard part about these depositions is I always feel like we should really really you know no matter how base
Pick a concept you think you're dealing with
You need to go
Further and further down you know like just
What do you think of journalists
Does well they tried to do that with that didn't go well
To be fair I think you could probably
Find some fertile ground in there right but
This is already 4 hours long
The deposition that stroke-like first principles at the basic core concept
We like to get down to the very mitigating and be like let's go with a glossary of words my man what do you think
There's nobody in the world who would love if like every one of these depositions with a Ken Burns.
Do it other humans have other things
They're good
When you are
Reporting facts your audience
I take it that it is important for you to accurately report what those facts are correct
And when you're writing about
A particular topic
What do you do
To educate yourself about the topic
And the fact that you're going to convey
I do research pretty-much read
Everything I can before I jump into a
An article
Sources of
Information come from that you read
Google search on Google News and also will look back at anything that Infowars has written
And maybe look at a YouTube video or to try to find
Yeah I look at various different
Data points to try to
Formulate
Facts and opinions on the
Subject
When you are doing research for case you're writing
You
AR
Doing that research exclusively from internet source is correct
Including a warzone
Previous material
Yes
That's not
It doesn't Inspire confidence
Wow am I research methods are Googling Infowars articles count past and maybe some
Haha yeah
Yeah
I mean
If you weren't
If
This is the dream
You know like he's having the dream isn't that what he's doing well it's either
He doesn't have to do anything
But occasionally Google stuff and then steal it I imagine there is a lot of like
You got to get this out fast because I'm going to be interesting to people in
6 hours hectic frustrating schedule email
Did you see this did you need that I also don't know how much you getting paid cuz that doesn't come
So it could also be 1.1 sent to work maybe this isn't such a good gig
Has much as some of the other Infowars employee of that
Get the f*** out of here
Yeah I wouldn't go back to Google analytics either or whatever it was
Also he didn't even read the 5000 words that he needed to read for this
Deposition what conference is that give you that he actually does any f****** research
You need to take that very seriously everything I can on
Google Maps
Matador now
Right
Sort of
Not really
You're the cop.
Published
I send my work to
Editor Jamie B
If he's not there I'll just
I reread I'll re-read my own working
Is
Whatever Jamie why is available he reviews your work
Yes
And for what purposes
Typos
Pretty much zhiend make sure I got my
Byzantine cross
Yeah or are words and stuff yes exactly
He's essentially just proofreading
Correct
He's not checking
For the accuracy of what you Britt
Technically now
Give me cleaner
They have like a whole conversation about whether or not anybody has ever done that it is time at Infowars
And he mentions only one person has this guy Mikhail Salen isn't with the company anymore
Now writes for the daily. I don't know what the f*** is deal is but you
Managed to transition out of the Infowars stink
Into
Something somewhat legitimate he's actually waiting somewhere
Yeah I don't I don't I don't know what his deal is but he was there apparently
When he was there
He would point out things like they got fired
Adan
Doesn't understand
Like that action
Experiences it as like oh he was just doing that because he wanted to like it was just
He's just kind of fun for Mikhail you know we were having a little game between us I would lie and he
Be like you can't do this and I would be like hahaha I've been posted strong sense that he didn't listen to
So he can just buy whatever he wants
And apparently has never been told not to write something
Have you ever been instructed that you couldn't write about a particular topic
No
Have you ever had a request to publish an article
Come down
No I don't think so
This is directly contradictory to Alex's Tire thing about how he told people not to write about them.
Amethyst
So that's
Because that
I believe that that email from Paul
Tattoo
Mentioned something about this
I am so
He would be
The person
Who was told don't write about this be the only person
Someone has their picture wrong
Oh that's not good
So I don't know how you would picture the
The workplace environment it Infowars the kind of like
Coworker
I just
After I find out the
Nobody's here at the like
Desert Dawn Salazar even live in the country like I did lose in Austin
Right but I mean there's no way to know
Based on what he's describing of his job but he could be in f****** South America right now and I've nobody would have anything for
I think that's probably part of wise like
It's so easy for Paul to have work there it is time living in England
And I'm this bums me out
During the
Course of your employment at
Infowars
Has
War
Contact level with mr. Jones changed at all
No
How often are you in
Communication with mr. Jones
In communication I would say maybe
Opossum going to the bathroom or something say hi so
Once a week or something
How often are you in communication to him about the substance of your work enforce
7-Eleven
This is bizarre living the dream no boss
I mean
He's worked there for a deck
Oh my God
It's inconceivable
I don't believe that if that is true
So rude totally
Totally
There aren't that many people who work there know how do you ignore one that close to you now that's bananas
Somebody who's responsible for holding so much of the content that you used to lie on air
It's it's like that is
Impersonal to the point of being hostile
Yeah absolutely no experience at except as
Is being iced out or something I come in there 10 years and it would feel like I know Alex is clearly trying to get rid
Native made
Wow just never happens
I guess just wait until someone notices your
I go back to the forensic financial analyst and he's like
A competently run business should have this to this amount of money and when you hear s*** like this you're like
Either they've got an absurd amount of money hidden in Gold somewhere because they are hiding it from everyone
Or this place just doesn't even know where money comes from
Languages go
Yeah they do have a very serious distrust of fiat currency
Yeah I don't know it's weird weird picture and it would be like Wonka
Factory Montana
Everyone's running around like
Calling costumes I'd like to you when do you see Alex well occasional
He called the entire staff out we have to put on our elf costumes and we have to do a little dance for him
I mean that question wasn't asked could we what happened a little dance a dance
You never know
Get to Sandy Hook coming up and
The question that supposed is when did you
Find out about the shooting
Do you recall how you first learned
About
The Sandy Hook
Shooting
I believe I was at work when it happened so
It was kind of playing
Everywhere one CNN
The breakroom
Then it was everywhere on the internet
Give me your job as a writer I take it back
You started following
That covered very closely as soon as it broke
Yes
And
You knew immediately that
The Sandy Hook shooting was going to be a subjective Infowars
Report incorrect
I didn't know that immediately no
If you weren't able to meet Lee to Intuit that this was going to be a major news story that Infowars was going to cover
Injection
No I didn't
Immediately realize that now
Days after NFL
What am I
So
But that time like two days after the event happened I was like okay
What's the big news event
Now this is something to keep an eye on here because adonnas testifying that like in this first month he was unaware of an inch
The cover the shooting
At Sandy Hook as that being fake
I am that timeline is going to be in trouble
Yeah as information is revealed
Yeah yeah yeah response that is I think the very appropriate like it's very bizarre
Imagine that you could see the shooting happen
You working in 40 how they've covered shootings in the past
You were there for Aurora which just happen
The job pretty recently
I am in like a couple days later you realize oh this is a big story what
I I mean either he's lying or he's insane
Like there's no other explanation get the lying or just trying to
Give a softer
Appearance to say we weren't taking this as seriously as we could or May
Maybe thought we would have something along those lines but there's no way the impression that you're like seeing this and get
Excited for the coverage they are going to understand how that isn't the perception you would want to give like
Saw this and immediately knew this is going to lead the news
Okay
Find
Wow whatever this problem I would even be like it was a few hours
Afterwards when I realized it was going to be
What it was
A couple of days makes you sound like you're
Hiding underneath rocks
You'd say then
About two days after the Avengers when you first realized that
You would be
Writing about Sandy. Correct
I didn't think I'd be writing about it yet
I was looking at a
Different banana leaves and stems and really like
Put my foot down that I'd be writing about it yet so I think the whole
First time I did was when I heard the interview
Which was I don't think it was immediately after the shooting
No it was in 2014
So there was a interview that how big did not talk about that a little more later alright with the American free press
And that was in like February
I think
Banquet February maybe not
December 14th two days to years same same difference
Wrote an article about Wolfgang's interview and that is true
Amount of time
Is
Like that
If you're pitching that is your timeline
Until 2014 I didn't know it was going to be writing about this traffic is a big story
What is
Outrageous and you don't want this to be like the 3rd of the foundation that you're laying
Yeah terms of explaining what happened in a deposition set directly contradict yourself
You know that Authority experiment where you know they've got somebody in the doctor's like press the button and it'll grow
Like this is one of the few situations or if you did that experience here is that experiment here it'd be like 45 minute
That's Max
Press the button every time he lies in bed
Listen I think I know how electricity works buddy
I mean look I don't know any I don't know
I don't know if that's one of those experiments that has been debunked
I'm not sure I know the prison experiment
There is such a frustrating
Wade
Path that this goes down
Like it is
Like a Don is
Such a bad stonewaller
There is
I will get to it and it's so frustrating
What you need to know for now is that after the shooting
Thought it was real
I'm just trying to understand
You know in the immediate aftermath
What your
Obviously in the immediate aftermath my perspective was a school shooting happen
So I was
On board with the shooting
When you say I'm bored
In the immediate aftermath what's and let's try and time this out
Within two days of the shooting
It was your own View
At that time
That
Children and Educators were killed at Sandy Hook correct
I would have phrased that differently but yeah
I was what it is this shooting
Maddie almost even gave him a chance to rephrase it
His perspective on this is like he was only going to report on Sandy Hook if there were anomalies
I take it from your testimony earlier that
You anticipated that you would likely only write about it
To the extent
You
Thought that there were anomalies associated with the shooting
Worth writing about right
Something that I found interesting and I thought
Would I find interesting in
Eventually happy
Correct where you felt
That
You wanted to report
On anomalies around Sandy Hook
Because you found them interesting and you thought the audience
Yes yes
So we come to this idea of anomaly
And it's one of the words that Alex uses to sort of rationalize a lot of his coverage
Kind of a vague term
There isn't really a concrete definition of it
And so in order to move forward we try to get a definition of what is an anomaly
We're talkin about anomalies I just want to go back
Can can you give me your definition of anomaly
Let me something that doesn't really jive with the story
So some fact that you believe exists that calls into question
Other facts surrounding the shooting correct
Jackson
Odd
That you really don't know what it's the what it is what it's purposes like I said until you have more pieces
Geico
In considering
Those anomalies
When it came time to report on them
I take it that it was
Important to you
For anything you published concerning Sandy Hook to be true and accurate correct
Yes
The best of my knowledge
Right in
You'd agree with me that
The shooting of
Twenty children and six Educators is a
Horrible
Correct
And so if you're going to be reporting
Facts
About that
Situation
It's incredibly important to you that they be accurate
Correct
And your audience relies on you
To provide them with truthful and accurate information correct
Yessir
And you understood at the time
Of the Sandy Hook shooting
And your coverage
Of that shooting that Infowars audience
Included millions of people across different platforms correct
And so
You considered it a tremendous responsibility of yours
To make sure that they were well and accurately informed correct
Rejection
Yes I would say so
You take that responsibility seriously don't you
It was important to you
That the sources of information you had concerning
Sandy Hook
Be credible
Correct
Yes
Adan has repeatedly now
Said yes I take this very seriously to me today
Definition of anomaly but at least it's something you can kind of work with
Alright I was surprised that the lawyer objected to Maddie
Really doing a really good job of rephrasing
Anomaly is something that doesn't jive with the story
Appreciators dictionary anomalies doesn't jive
Like the way this man thing
Got it
Later
He said he's happy he smokes a jazz cigarette in between
So there's a phenomenon called motivated reasoning
Create an argument
For something based on a conclusion that you already had you go looking for information
Check new scam to confirmation bias inclusion they were going to have already
Now
This conversation here with Don and how he was approaching
Shooting if some of the Hallmarks of that okay
Any
Immediate aftermath and I'm talking about when I say immediate aftermath of the Sandy Hook shooting
Let's talk about
Okay so
December
14 2012 to January 14th 2013 with me
Enduring that.
Did you develop a concern
That
The shooting at Sandy Hook
I could be used as a pretext
Gun confiscation
Legislation
I'm not sure if it was
Specifically done
Confiscation butt
Yeah I was going to be able to check her tail gun rights
I believe
That was a concern you develop Within
The month after the shooting that the
Back to the shooting could be used as a pretext for curtailing gun rights correct
Yes
It was a concern to your knowledge that Alex Jones fear
I believe so maybe if you go back and see some of the
The incident
Alex
Mentioning that concern
I can't recall that it was a
Concern
It might have been
Was that a principal reason
That it was important to you
Question
Whether or not the shooting in fact occur
Yeah that was one of them
One of several reasons yeah
What were some of the others
Just trying to keep the media honest and
You know trying to
Sharethrough actual news
Not fake news
Shocking admission
Understand
Howard on wouldn't recognize what he just said
He said the principally one of the reasons it was important for him to question whether or not Sandy Hook happened was because he was
I was worried they were going to use it to take guns
Right nothing to do with the reality or falsity of an event
What is a
Bucked up
Thought process
So here's what I thought
Okay I thought that people would exploit this tragedy to pass
Gun grabbing legislation
I went out and I looked for the truth you know and everybody you said that it wasn't
I called
What's fake news and everybody said that it was I called Trunews
So obviously it's true my man
Thinking about it this way
That you know you're worried about them exploiting this tragedy in order to push a political goal that you are a
Supposed to write
Instead of supporting the political point that you are in favor of right
Engaging in the argument about it we're in people are like a
There's this cool shooting
We should probably get better gun regulations and relays and common-sense reform
No I don't believe that that is an appropriate thing to do and here are the reasons why
They wouldn't have any argument is a shooting didn't happen
So maybe I should try and prove that
Insist that
Because that's a shortcut that I don't have to make my argument by
Right I meant
Basically the way you could interpret what add-on is saying
And obviously
On some level I
I'm fully aware that this is part of it
Sort of ideological and information model
Yeah but to hear it.
Not trying to mask that in some way
Is very shocking and it's
It strikes me as somebody who doesn't realize what he's saying yeah
How do you say it out loud
Cuz you hear it then you'd hear it spoken into the world that you know maybe he's got one of those his lawyer didn't just like
That's if that's a revelatory thing I do lawyers
Color for these people like that is
An insane thing to say
How can you say that out loud and not be like
Oh I get where we went wrong now
Thanks guys listen
We had a great deposition
I'm in the 100% in the wrong whatever it is you say is true I'm going to get out of here I'm supposed to give
The presentation that were just looking for the truth and the hard questions that no one else will and right
Exposing cover-ups in
Trying to
This takes shortcuts and and push your political agenda in
A different way because you know that if you did it on the merits
No one will be interested if I argued with you about the thing you want to argue about it I would lose cuz you're right and wrong
So instead what if I pretended that you don't exist and neither does anybody else have him just me and everything I think it's true
Good
The day
Of the shooting or is it around there was in the 24 hours at time frame
Don't got an email
And this is an email where we get an appearance
It's from an old friend of ours
Likes to hide in the bush
So do you know the guy
He has
Send an email to John bowne
Who's Anna's forwarded
To Adan Salazar
Email before you
Mr. Salazar
In the front line
Is Jonathan
John infowars.com to you
And
Do you see the date that that
This is
Mister whoever Jonathan isn't it your testimony that you don't know who that is
That's probably John bowne
How do you spell last name
Bowne
And who is that
Video producer
Is he still there
Outside but
I think he's still employed by the precinct
Okay
And
And you know who's mr. Rappaport was at the time correct
I'm barely becoming familiar with him yet
Spirograph
In-N-Out
Mr. Brown is forwarding you
An email in an attached document that you received from mr. Rapaport
On the day of the shooting correct
Adam Pearson
And if we scroll down
The
The document that was attached to the email
Is dated December 15th 2012
Insecure come to grief counselors over-the-hill pouring into Newtown Connecticut
Do you recall reading this piece by mr. rap
Rapoport
No
You have any understanding as you sit here today without going through it what it says
Do you have an understanding of what mr. Rappaport
If you was concerning the Sandy Hook shooting in the immediate aftermath
No I don't know what mr. Edwards we will
You know one is bound folded you this email
Because he thought it was interesting and thought I might find it interesting Navy to republish
You know it was republished by infowars.com
I don't know
The little weird
It's a little weird
I mean rapaport's unhinged weirdo sound like
The idea that he's writing blogs questioning Sandy Hook the day of or the next day regular
Yeah that's
But the idea that John bowne has found and
Thought hey you know who will enjoy this a dawn Salazar
That is a little weird
Isn't it a definitely
If someone
Where to email me that
Altec fence
A problem
That be a problem there's something about add-on the people know
Totally cool to send him weird s*** about Sandy Hook
Yeah man I I just feel like if I were in being deposed
By anyone
And they asked me a question and I gave my response and then they were like
Okay can we
Do you see this on your screen Point Xavier want my first response be like
Bring this up you'll be like well obviously I didn't say that now now I know that I didn't know that
Oh no
60s guns and is presenting
The idea that he did not know his immediate aftermath that they were going to cover it
As if it were
In the immediate aftermath
Of the
The shooting that is month following the shooting is fair to say
That
You understood
That your coverage was going to frame Sandy Hook
As a staged event
I wouldn't say
I didn't know that in the immediate aftermath now
So you're telling me that in that first month
It was not your
You were not aware at that time
Or you do not have a view at that
That
Infowars coverage of the event
Wood frame it as a staged event
So important in as much as we have laid the framework of what we're talking about
The immediate app
Yeah I'm talking about that month
Yeah
I think that's helpful
I don't believe it on here but
Throw this out there
Adan
Earlier in the deposition
Says
Why did I join Infowars
Aha
9/11 was an inside job right so you're very first moment of joining him for his if they hire
Early early around
Something being a false flag
You knew exactly how they don't know that they're the false flag place
Let their the one-stop-shop
For false flag
Yeah I mean
Just done Aurora
Like they have just done all their coverage but how that was fake
No you're working there
Oh my God yeah
It's a little bit
Pill to swallow
Especially because you know obviously he would have in reporting on this is based on
John Cena Nopalea course
Any immediate aftermath of the shooting
Am I correct that
You did become aware of what you consider to be certain amount
Cersei
How is it that you
Became aware of those anomalies
What did you do to discover them
Jackson
I'm not sure if I receive tips on emails or found videos on YouTube but it was maybe a combination of the two
In order to find videos on YouTube you would have to serve
For something that you were looking for correct
A link is provided somehow
Bio social media or email
You recalled doing any affirmative work on your own
Search
YouTube or any other sites
Anomaly
I died in service
I was probably provided with limited videos about it
And you think those links may have, either through you viewing
Social media
Or through the writers email correct
Right around Reddit ya various
Various places
YouTube yes
Were you looking for
I would say I was looking for them now
Batman all this information
Belize just kept popping up
Yeah I think this is not follow the story this is the first
This is the only episode I think that Ivar show where if you just put Liz in my chair
Based on his descriptions of her job she would be making
Who works in Media or journalism hearing this and not being offended
Nothing means anything anymore right people who have worked so hard
I'm just on the in the trenches grinding right
Research they've got people who actually go out there fact-checkers and everything everything
Even people who do like a lot of the behind-the-scenes good journalism
It's kind of like I don't know I don't know
Six figures tomorrow
There's also email
Strip like from Rapaport
For this other email from Rapaport
You see that this is an 8-page document and page one
Using email
From Jonathan to you
With an indication that there is a
Attachment the middle Adam Lanza mask
Yes I see that
And you see that
The email from Jonathan is a forwarded email again from this to rapport
Look like it was sent from John Rappaport to John bowne and then John bowne forwarded to me
Correct
And the date that mr. Brown
Received it
Mr. Rapaport
Resent it to
Mr. ballen was December 16th 2012 correct
I see that yes
Good that would that would have been
2 days after the shooting
I believe so yes
And if you scroll down in the document
Again similar to the last email we looked at there's an attachment
With a written piece that appears to be authored by mr. Rappaport correct
Yessir
And the title is to movies to mass murders
With a subtitle that says The Dark Knight Rises in The Hunger Games
Okay
Correct
It doesn't look like
Sometime it looks like it's the lead sentence in this
Okay okay
Alright fine
Is sent this to John bowne
Is the first one that John Valentine's me and maybe if I'm not interested I say don't send me s*** like that
Weird another one
Next day sounds like maybe this happen
Regularly
Doesn't know if he actually even read this
Okay you're not sure
Courtesy
You eventually develop an interest
In the Nexus
Between the movie The Dark Knight Rises and the Sandy Hook shooting correct
Yes it was an interest in it.
Possible that that interest may have been
Bye
This particular piece
Wish
I can scroll down
Draws a connection
Between
The Batman movie
The Aurora shooting
Aunt Sandy Hook
My question to you is
It's possible that
This particular email which you received
Spark your interest in the Nexus between the movie The Dark Knight Rises and Sandy of the Sandy Hook shooting correct
It's possible I can't say for sure I don't know if I read this article the time
But minivan
It appears that you received this email
Shortly after the shooting correct
It's honestly too bad for Adam that he didn't read this article because if he had he could defend himself here
The conspiracy that add-on spread about Sandy Hook in Batman had to do with the name Sandy Hook appearing on the map in the movie
The Dark Knight Rises
That was an article Rapaport wrote on December 18th
But the one from the 16th which is being discussed here since it was forwarded to add-on
Is actually about something else
The Batman part of this has to do with the Aurora shooting happening at a screening of Batman and the theories about James Holmes thinking he was
The Joker
In this article Sandy Hook relates to the hunger
Games
I'm going to read you hear some of John Rappaport
Brilliant work please
We now have the boggling connection to the Hunger Games
And that sci-fi novel and film 24 children are picked to take part in the competitive National blood sacrifice killing
Ritual
One child survives at the end of 23 die
20 died in Newtown
And the author of The Hunger Games Suzanne Collins lives in Sandy Hook next to Newtown
And this means
This is just the kind of bizarre and insane op secret societies are reputed to enjoy
Ordinarily I would ignore this sort of thing and just call it a coincidence but it's
Too improbable
I can't prove the killings in Newtown were part of a kind of op
But I can't disregard it either
The quote coincidence is just too stunning
Headed The Hunger Games connection is real here then then all bets are off
Incidents that Rappaport finds two stunning is nearby and the number of children were killed in the
The Hunger Games of doesn't match the number dead at Sandy Hook
But it's kind of close
This is the kind of dumb s*** that Rapaport was writing 2 days after the shooting that you thought it was worth sending.
On who I almost guaranteed did read it
He may think it's in his best interest to not know anything about the article in this deposition but the idea that he wasn't interested in this
It just flies right everything I've been able to tell about him from his work
Ime mockery
I think I would have made it two sentences into that email before I go to throw Mike
Computer at the window ottoman like
What if it says Jon rappoport on it I'm not interested how about that
Yeah to better lb
Where's David at
So done apparently is not only a receiver of emails
Email to Melissa
Who is a former employee of Infowars
December 9th
That's a little ant
Do you have this email before you star witch
Is an email from you
To Melissa Melton
On December 19th 2012
I see that here
Who is Melissa Melton
Choose a previous employee
What was her role in it
Infowars at the time
Video producer splash
I guess you read some articles that she was a partial letter
Subject line please
Says
Forward
Connecticut police radio purple band mask men
One dressed as a nun
And can you read
The text that you emailed to miss Milton
Look at this end in from a reader don't know if you caught the showed that day but a caller said a nun game
Entry to the school
And why did you share that information with Miss Melton
Looks like I was
Going out to the email before
Well
Probably interested in the anomalies
So you were sending this to miss Melton because you were interested
In
The possibility that
Someone dressed as a nun
Had gained entry
To the school on the day of the shooting
Moriarty sharing of
Weird
Weird Tale
I mean sure I thought it was true but then when you said it out loud back to me now I think it was a weird Tales
Location of cramps
Secret society
Okay see you sent a weird tale to Melissa Melton about a nun on gaining access
Most of the school obviously is because there was another shooter
And that same day something else happened at Infowars
This exhibit
Is it pure to you
Mr. Salazar to be
A headline in the text of an article that was published on infowars.com in December 19th 2012
Yes
This is the article in earlier
That
I believe you
Attributed to a particular
Dapper Aaron dykes
Correct
Yeah I think it was he
Would you wear my uncle at the time it was published
Only when it went up on the website
Pretty sure I did
Here's something that Maddy might not know or
Just isn't bringing up that makes this all a bit suspicious these these two clips
So we just heard on the same day December 19th. His email and Melissa Melton about a Sandy Hook conspiracy
Here's a theory and Aaron Dykes is posting this article to fame and Robbie Parker
The connective tissue that's missing is that Aaron Dykes and Melissa Melton were a couple
Leaving Infowars together and they started their own Outlet called truthstream media and no spoken pretty poorly about
Alex
They're married now and Melissa is taking on Aaron surname
It seems difficult for me to imagine that you have Aaron actively posting the Sandy Hook conspiracy s***
I ended on emailing his girlfriend other
Sandy Hook conspiracy s*** and that doesn't translate to a group of people intensely interested in Sandy Hook conspiracy
That's that to me is something that doesn't doesn't pass the smell test
To be pretty good at pool
I used to be pretty good pool at one time I was watching these two
Really really good Hustlers who accidentally
Wind up playing against each other like they f***** up
And
They were they were so good like after the first couple of games they realize what was going on
And then they would just
Moves so fast it be like
If there were four balls left on the table that they think you could run those out they just rip them off the table lamp.
Next game next game like that
If
If we were in this kind of high-level situation
I think it down would have been like
Alright you got me on this one next question flipped out next month will swipe these off the table you want
Not a lot of money
Yeah I think that I would be very interested in that
Piece of information being
Brought is a rebuttal
Conspiracy theories about Sandy Hook
Zidane doesn't necessarily have like
A concrete proof that he was talking
Aaron Dykes about his article about Robbie Parker play how many riders are there at the time not many real working
The same office
Like I I find it on
Unbelievable
That the two of them wouldn't have been at least in some kind of contact that an anomaly
It is an obelisk
Ironically
It sort of has the hint of a conspiracy
So
Joseph Watson email looking for tips
Hook conspiracy article he was writing
You have an email before you sir
From you to tell Joseph Watson
Call Papa table
If you have the time can you look at
Can you take a look at the article attending
Publishing on the back end of Infowars I did a little bit of research into Sandy Hook
Batman coincidence
Was substituted for another name on the map
Maybe you got
Tips for something you'd like to add
I think I should mention the article or better by Banks
The article that you were referencing
I think it's the one about Sandy Hook maps and stuff I mean Batman Maps
Yeah
This is an article that you wrote
In which you recorded
That
Matt
That appears in the movie
The Dark Knight Rises
Add a location
That have been changed
From South Hinckley to Sandy Hook
Correct
Yes
You of call wasserman's back to you on this
I don't think he wasn't as interested in this
Stories hours
That's revealing
I mean we already knew that Paul wasn't down with this s***
But like
You to say he wasn't as interested in it as I was
Doesn't look right
So this is about December 20th
Right here is where things got a little bit can
Confusing for me
Because there was an article posted on the 17th
On Infowars about
The map in The Dark Knight Rises
And then there's another article that's an update of it that's the one that Don is talking about write believe
Okay I'm not sure if he wrote the original one on the 17th because they both
Have infowars.com as the writer tribution but he
And obviously he's emailing Paul about it
Presumably he would think you wrote the first 12
But who knows
I mean that could have been just a
It's like they could have stolen that one two who knows
Can't nail it down.
Someone else got a little update about that
Email from you to the drugs
Just read the Drudge Report
And Jacqueline
That you wrote
Was bizarre Sandy Hook Dark Knight Rises connection correct
Yes
And you wrote
Infowars has exposed
That a section of Gotham City
Was renamed Sandy Hook in the latest Dark Knight release
And you include a link
To the story correct
Yes that was a story that you wrote
That's the one I wrote I believe you
In that story was written and published six days after the Sandy Hook shooting correct
And you didn't ask Drudge
Will help us spread the news of this very strange coincidence correct
But this point we haven't very least Infowars has a story about this
Batman thing is after the attack then six days after the shooting
There's another one that add-on is written
The Drudge Report
Disseminated more widely the arguments
Responsible for the spread of it especially in the early days
It was very out the window in terms of
The size of the reap that Infowars has at this time
They're active cording of drudge the largest link aggregator in the right-wing
I am maybe all of
Yeah time it was like the biggest
The internet and that it's
That to me is like really damning
That email is pretty it's a bad luck
Yeah I do I could not be deposed
This weather if you listen to the video of me being deposed if this was me
I will just be like
Don't read it, and I know I sent it
Sucked up because it's not like an interrogation where you can just get fast
Let's just move on.
Let's just go to jail instead of talk to you anymore
Reason that this is something that would be interesting to Adan Salazar now you might have
Imagine that the obvious answer is because
If somebody who worked on Batman that it already come out
Wright had changed the name of this place on the map to Sandy Hook
And then later Sandy Hook happen yeah it would lead one to think
Maybe they did that as a message
There's this whole idea of predictive programming that is really big and Alex's coverage of stuff
So the argument here the shorthand is very clear that it's
Trying to argue for foreknowledge
Way to
Unless you're Adan You could argue that it's not
If you can argue that there was a psychic power no
Coincidence
Mr. Salazar
The reason you were reporting on this
Is because
The fact that
A map location in The Dark Knight Rises have been changed to Sandy Hook
Call YouTube suspect
Whether there had been some sort of advanced knowledge by somebody
That the Sandy Hook shooting was going to take
Correct
Injection
I don't know if that was my belief of the time I just thought it was a very bizarre strange coincidence that I thought needed to be highlighted
Why did you think she did it and what relevance was it
Your coverage
I think it's relevant to the name of a map changes on a movie you know when it's supposed to
Be something else and then Sandy her changes to Sandy Hook and then
Something happens
Place called Sandy Hook in the same year that the movies released
Coincidence
And so help me explain
Why that
Is relevant it seems and correct me if I'm wrong
That
What you are inviting your audience to consider
Is that it's not a coincidence at all
Correct injection Farm
I wasn't inviting the audience to consider that I was asking you
It may be they perhaps update coincidences bizarre to
I think I point out the fact that
The problem
Manager of the movie
Lived in Sandy Hook
Maybe in one of the articles
Newtown Connecticut
What should the same place the shooting took place I thought that was all bizarre
Was the stage X was trying to find out a bizarre coincidence
Just so we're clear here's the second paragraph of the article add-on wrote and sent a Drudge
Minor coincidence we've scoured the Batman movies and poured over various Gotham City
Define anything that could support the theory
That the movies may have had him to a foreknowledge of the tragic Massacre that occurred last week
Because where there's smoke there's usually fire what we found is interesting to say the least
This isn't quite how he's describing his writing in this deposition
Is Grace from the article it sounds like they were studying these Maps searching for Clues to prove that there was foreknowledge and that they found
Interesting stuff
And where there's smoke there's usually fire
Covert and it's point I would say
Yeah imma dog doesn't point out that the prop master was from Sandy Hook
He does bring up that there's a Sandy Hook in New Jersey but it's kind of a non-sequitur between heavy insinuation of it
Conspiracy and then this
Quote for those who were left asking why would someone do that
Alfred pennyworth Bruce Wayne in the Dark Knight movie
Some men aren't looking for anything logical like money
They can't be bought bullied reason to negotiate it with some men just want to watch the world burn
The article ends with this
If you're enjoying spotting these bizarre coincidences and traveling down the road of curiosity with us
Stay tuned for tomorrow's scintillating Revelation that the song The Smoking Gun
Needed to tie the Dark Knight Rises the Aurora massacre at the Sandy Hook tragedy
We guarantee will leave you wondering exactly WTF is going on
Oh my God what does really seem like someone is just in case Miss weird
Jesse's anytime I'm in a deposition I just want to make sure that I've never written the word guarantee
Such a f****** s*** hat
It's an interesting
Approach that add-on is taking Maddie is asking like
Why is this relevant
I just something kind of interesting it's a weird
Jaguars eat
And this
When I told you about like this being like an incredibly frustrating kind of a while
This seems to be a
Stumbling
There are difficulties in getting add-on to admit at all that he was making a point.
What are you doing the writer
I just throw words out
This weird
Revelation of a smoking gum tomorrow
He's really just a Pontiac
To the extent that would be any salience to The Coincidence is that
Define salient
The fact that
Aim application in a movie had been changed
To the name of a place
Where is shooting later occurred
Could potentially be evidence that
Somebody involved in that movie
At awareness that are shooting would later occur there correct
Production
I don't know what it signified I just thought it was a bizarre coincidence that people should
Maybe looking to
Highlighted highlighted it for the audience because I thought it was interesting and I thought they'd find it interesting as well
It's just a bizarre coincidence that doesn't mean cuz I wasn't trying to make a point
Come on come on man account
Did this happen
I'm going to show you exhibit a a
You actually
Posted your
Article
To Facebook
And that's exhibit AA
Before you correct
And contrary to the testimony you just gave which is you were just putting out the coincidence
Including commentary there that called the police sentence
Very fishy
Correct
Injection
It looks like it says that can you zoom in a little more
Yeah that's the problem
Yeah I put very fishy
Switch you met
To sow doubt
About whether there was in fact
Knowledge on somebody's part
Of the shooting correct
I didn't I just pointing out that it's a bizarre coincidence I'm not trying to
Showdown
Really itchy
Seems like
Pointing out that it's a bizarre coincidence
No Doubt
I think that Chris Mattie's delivery of that it seems fishy
Is just right on point
Because like
That is the kind of thing that you could just repeat to somebody
I wasn't say I wasn't trying to slow down or make this look suspicious when you said
I think that's one of the probably didn't think like
I didn't post anything on my Facebook
Such like of course you're constantly surprised
Put their bring you it's up to you
You didn't research the things you did
And you're used to working with a bunch of Ding Dongs and I'll do anything you don't understand like how
Processive
Actual exploration might work
How did you get that
You know like I know it
Public
Stickman you can find it anytime you want
Crazy shemane
Anomalous word reader
Doesn't jive
So the next day after this add-on is working on another Sandy Hook conspiracy theory
December 21st
And this will be
Xzibit number 11
You latched onto
A different
Banana
Do you recall
Becoming aware
That an online
Movie review
A movie
Entitled Sandy Hook lingerie party Massacre
Had been published
In the days prior to shooting you work all that
Yes and you referenced an exhibit 11 but have no
Donut
Correct
You work all as you're sitting here without looking at an exhibit
Becoming
Aware of an interested
In the fact
Dad
Somebody get published an online review of this movie before the Sandy Hook shooting correct
I'm about to review but I was aware of the movie or something somehow it crossed
My path
Probably some
John Rappaport email is on Reddit
Butler's in a bad language
Correct
Oh f*** that means exhibit 11th going to make my client look real Dumbo no
Did you think that this movie was
Fishing
Add ons working on this this article about the lingerie party Massacre
And there's some emails these have come up in other deposition
Where Don is emailing the guy who wrote the review I believe share and discuss
Somehow like hey you know there's one people who are spreading the rumor that you know you are maybe at foreknowledge of
But we're going to ride it anyway know that's a bad idea it's always fun when
Deposition setting you get to make someone read their own email
Scroll down to the beginning
The email and I'll just go down there but it's use one page
And am I correct sir that
You sent
I'm in email
On
December 21st
7 days after the shooting
UA Miss Gonzalez
Is that correct
Mr. Gonzalez Seattle
Mr. Gonzalez
And your email reads
Ashley can you read it for me
There is a vicious rumor that the date
You posted your review of the Sandy Hook lingerie party Massacre on your site base / above.com
Shows for knowledge or prior planning of the events that have taken
Place as of late
Likely to links
At first we thought this was surely ridiculous however we're going to point it out in an article and
Would like
Give me the opportunity to provide a common
In an article anyway right
Wonder if that's inattentional Omission not as part of reading it because the anyway there really is
Is a word that shows like
You're sending this person an admission that you don't even believe the s*** you're going to post you're going to do it anyway
Play is a shiv to your gut
That is what the anyway is for I don't understand what goal would be of not reading the word I mean
Cuz you don't want to read it cuz the anyway really makes you sound like you just shipped somebody in the gut
Bebe
Weird instincts don't make me read my already but I would have me again I can't be deposed the whiny voice
Don't make me read it
Arrest me to email that he's sending
Involves a notion of foreknowledge
Because
That's literally what he says in the email
So you might think that covering this story
Liza Don does
For him
Cast aspersions on the reality of the shooting
And imply that the audience maybe you should consider that there's
For planning for knowledge
Not Manny wasn't make an appointment
But the rumor that you were
Informing mr. Gonzales out was that
The fact that you had posted the review
Sometime in advance and the Sandy Hook shooting
Could be evidence that he was aware of the shooting take place correct
I believe that's what I was questioning
And you thought that it was surely ridiculous at first
Right
Yes
Why did if it was ridiculous
Where you going to include it in an article anyway
Because it was just another bizarre
Coincidence that I found interesting that I thought I
Leadership would find interesting
In the reason that you thought they would find interesting
Is because
You
We're trying to highlight evidence for them
Suggesting
That
This was an event
Of which certain people had foreknowledge correct
Objection
I wasn't particularly trying to highlight that there was an event that people had foreknowledge of more so that I
I thought this was a weird anomaly that people should keep their eye on and maybe
Read about in F
Kind of it reminds me a little bit of a child being like I'm not hating you
This
I mean Jesus Christ
At a certain point just be like
If you're going to play if you don't play dumb
You're playing the wrong amount of done like Isaac so
This is dumb enough where I'm like your f******
Can plan your an ass off you got to go way too far going to try
You got to be like
Holy s*** that is the
First time that I have thought of that connects I can't believe I didn't consider that honestly now that you brought that up
To me that sounds like a crazy thing I did I'm so sorry now you know what it's weird that I accidentally
Speculated about that in the articles that your ass that's why
Corey Blake just
I don't know I entirely open mind and be like
Oh yeah that is what I was if you write that doesn't make sense
But I don't know maybe that's a bad road to go pick a good way to go but this is
So Maddie ask sadhana about like these anomalies and stuff and actually this MO
Moment for me
Something that I've never really thought about
You yourself weren't convinced
At this point.
The evidence you were
Collecting
Established
Somebody other than Mister Lana that had foreknowledge of the event correct
Dakshin
At the time I was still kind of
I guess trying to convince myself
Put the pieces together
For any of your coincidences the law enforcement did you
I'd never thought about that if they took this seriously
Somebody at law enforcement why wouldn't they try to I mean obviously threatened to believe any of this
You know that would be something that you probably have
Some kind of at least moral obligation
Yeah took any of this seriously that's one of those things that you when you're when you're too
Close to stuff
If you can't see it but if you step back and you look at that is that's so simple
Edit demolishes everything. It's so simple for granted by us because of the like how long we've been
Doing tonight how budget
Repetitively born out rat take this seriously
Like consideration
Great question
If you really thought this wouldn't you at least talk to them about it because of
Very very serious implications of this are earth-shattering so
Wouldn't you at least try
Right I need to be like will know because the whole system is going to be but yeah
Well that's not an excuse to not try especially not if you're using somebody who's a former cop or whatever is your purse
Find somebody who's a former cop till like
Easier into them or whatever text Uncle is a former FBI agent
Come on come on
Come on
So I really enjoyed this class it's a little longer but
It has to be
And you were at this time or where
That
Of allegations that
One or more of the parents of Sandy Hook children
At work racism
Actors correct
That's the rumor
Did you believe it yourself
I didn't really go into that
Is everybody else did
Benefactor
But I wasn't really
Interested in
Trying to figure out whether they were crisis actors or not
You wanted
Not really
Didn't really matter to the
We're trying to make MerCruiser
And I'd like
Tentativas are anomalies that
Writing
Can you let me know
And this will be exhibit number 12
Why
On January 6th 2013
You attempted to establish an account
At crisis actors. Org
I'm not sure why
You to look into people listed on the site or something I don't know
Got
You agree that
Number 12 is an email from
Crisis actors that is a website to you
Asking for you to verify your address
So you can sign into the crisis actors website correct
Yes
If
Michigan
But your testimony here today is that you don't know why you did that
Looks like I was trying to investigate
See if maybe
Wondered maybe if they're listed as crisis actors on there I don't I don't know what
Yeah any Avenue I can
Possibly investigate I wanted to
Do my due diligence
I see you are wow
You are
Assumption
Is that
You were trying to gain access to the site
In the hope that you might be able to see
If any of the
Crisis actors
Appearing on the website
Out where the same as individuals
Who were
Family members of Sandy Hook victims correct
Dakshin
The time it looks like I was trying to figure out if any of the
People involved in the Sandy Hook
Event work
Crisis actor says with a yes
A track
I'm not sure
Urban anybody
Might have been
Some guy that was
You know
Interview
What were the results of your
Query of the crisis actors website
Honestly I cannot tell you because I do not remember
Okay really important information I got you got some expose level
Stop and Maddie makes another great point after that in that is like well I mean if you'd gone on there and found somebody that was
Was one of the Sandy Hook people who probably would have reported that right would have
Kind of
The fact that you didn't
Kind of shows a baby you didn't
You didn't report to your audience
Find it
Nope
It appears that to you you said earlier today that you did not know why that assassin kill
Killed your wife now
Do you know why the day before you signed up for can an assassin kill my wife. Org
I don't I don't know
I mean I look as long time ago
I think I was just looking to see how is Essence are doing these days
Are they making good money what their world like
Interview
And as far as the day before it goes I think that's just a bizarre coincidence
Oh my God
Terrible
Pure comedy moment
Be like I'm really that interested in the crisis actor stuff
Three weeks after the shooting try to join crisis actors
How do I say well I guess I did do that there's just so many so many
Stepping on a rake
Bananas wow
So there's another conspiracy that was going around the house with the idea that there was a fundraiser for Sandy Hook
Published
Before the shirai Ryu
Dawn has to address
On January 13th
Well
You agree that you are
The recipient of this email
And
Descendre Sean Knowles you know who that is
I do not
In this email is encouraging you to go to a link
Where
According to
The link
A
Sandy Hook Relief Fund
Paige appeared three days before the shooting correct
Mr Knowles seems to be playing out in this email
I might have clicked the link I can't recall
And
Showing you exhibit number 13 a
Thursday.
This is an image of your Facebook account in which you
Shared the post concerning
This
Issue of a
Sandy Hook fundraising page beam
Created three days before the shooting
And you did that on January 11th 2013 right
Yes
Oh boy again
You didn't do anything to investigate
Weather in fact a relief fund has been
Created three days before the shooting you just posted the link
What's the link to Natural news on my Facebook yet
And you did that
Because did you say
This was another
Coincidence right
Is that how you felt
The Google thing I wasn't too sure about since I knew hug a little bit about how Google worked I wasn't
So ready to
Follow that
How much do you know about Google
Anomaly
You were prepared to post about it but you weren't going to write an article about right
Posted on Facebook for other people that might find it interesting yet
That's interesting because he's willing to spread this b******* that he knows is b*******
Is nonsense but he still more than willing to put it out as if it is
Interesting thing is that was a trap
Because you got this email where this guy sending email on
January 3rd
13th music did you research this at all
He posted it on Facebook two days prior
That's not good that's bad
Emailing him about the article that I don had posted on Facebook that has has been with spurred this email
Jesus didn't look into it he didn't research it I mean
What are those little pet peeves that I have in especially in situations like this is whenever it's like
You can't say it seems like that's what he's doing
I'm giving you a
In the past that cannot be changed anymore
It is done
So this
Does not seem like he says this he said that
Correct
So when they were talking about these Batman articles written
The prop master was from Newtown
He had mentioned that the New Jersey there's an island Sandy Hook
The reason
Adam thought that he brought up the prop Master is because this became another big conspiracy
Hymn O
So basically the argument or the theory that goes around
Is
That this guy Scott getzinger is the name of
The prop master
He died in a car wreck
Prior to the release of the past
So the theory that people had was that he was responsible
For changing the name to Sandy Hook and that's why they killed exact
Because he knew too much ryra which sort of raises the question of why it was still in the movie
If they knew that did it but they also killed him for it and then they left it in anyways
Appears that add-on was pretty into this conspiracy
This is disgusting little bit
Here and I don't know
How tall is is is
Boring as a Dodger
This is
Am I correct
Salazar another email that you sent this one to
Elliot Brown
Yes sir
And you see that it's dated their January 28th
Yes
And in this email
You are
Asking him if he's free for an honest
Journalist question correct
Yes and you're referring to yourself they're correct
Even he laughed at that exactly exactly
And in the body of the email
You ask him
About
The change in the title of the map
In Dark Knight Rises
And you ask him about
This gentleman Scott getzinger Who was the
Prop
Master according to you
Who passed away in a car at
Incorrect
Yes
I inserted this situated in time
That the time when you were
Inquiring about
The death of Scott getzinger was
In January of 2013
Yes it looks like
And the coincidence that you
We're referring to
And we'll go back to your
We'll go back to exhibit number 14
This is the
Email tell Furniture Direct
Was that Mr katzinger
Was associated with the movie The Dark Knight Rises
And he
Was killed in a car crash
And lived in Newtown Connecticut correct
Yes
And you say we're struck me as extremely odd is that this dude hailed from you destitute Newtown Connecticut right
And then you say at the end
Definitely something fishy about it all
About
The facts
That
Somebody Associated the props
Department with the Dark Knight Rises
Was from Newtown and it died in a car accident
Direction
I thought it was
Marriott
Same year that this
Movies put out in Sandy Hook is changed on a map something happens at a place called Sandy Hook
And what you were suggesting
Was that Mr guest singers
Steph
Was somehow
Due to the fact
That he had knowledge
About why the map have been changed
Injection honestly I did not have like
Theory as to why
Getsinger
If he was murdered or killed or why he died in the car accident so I didn't really
Haven't answered
It did seem like a strange anomaly where the pointing out
So infuriating thing where it's just
The wave add-on is presenting his like I guess we're just a journalistic or media
Coincidence
Yeah that's
I find to be a defensive
Just heard of characterization
Yeah it's silly
Yeah it's fishy
You are theoretically
A writer
And you're trying to insist to me that words don't have meeting
This is a
More or less
Yeah and so Maddie makes this point and I think this is
Important and that is that
Coincidences don't mean anything unless there's a point to them
Agree with me
If something is a mere coincidence
Meaning just happenstance
There's nothing to know about it
Correct there's no relevance to note again
Right
Productions
They're big coincidences
Little coincidences
I think some of the big ones and does
Deserve to be noticed
Probably not
Or investigated is because they signify that it may not be a coincidence at all
Correct direction
I'm not sure what the coincidence would point you honestly then
What do the people have to look into on their own
Is relevant
8.2 something
Bright
Injection
Not necessarily I think
What's can be highlighted without
Them having a point to them either
So your testimony is that
When you're highlighting what you refer to as these coincidences
You are
Not intending to suggest anything about what they signify
That's your testimony
I'm trying to
Tell the reader that
This is going on and kind of weird
What do you think about it
I think at the bottom of one of my heart
What do you think
Sound off in the comments below
People's attention
It's just what value is there to coincidence
That's the question you asked yourself
I think at that point I realized Mister Salazar I am now going to bounce
The tennis ball off your forehead every time you say something about your job that's pants shooting Lee insane what are you talkin about
Coincidences man what are you talkin about
Carmen Electra's birth name was Tara Patrick
Isn't that a coincidence
Not one of those little coincidences I mean it's like
Do you really think like maybe you would run an article about how some people have the same middle name I mean that's a cool
What do you what do you understand the word coincidence to meme
I mean I understand what you mean by Bitcoins is little coincidences but that is not a description of there
I'm leaving fullness
That's insane
I'm not sure you do know what it means by big or little Clinton cuz I'm not sure I do now that you say it like that
I would mean by saying that means I do now
I certainly feel for Chris Maddie quite a bit
Because
There is just a
Like a real attempt to be like
Come on you're making a point
There's a point that you're trying to make words have to have meaning and add-on will not go for it.
Salazar that the reason you're
Highlighting wood
You claim are coincidences
Is because you want your audience to suspect
That's something like Sandy Hook
In fact
Did not occur
As has been reported
Isn't that your purpose
Objection
My purpose is to
Point out the coincidences
And let the reader make
You have no interest at
In suggesting to the reader
What the relevance of the
Coincidence might be
That's your testimony
I think I present the evidence I gather for them and allow the reader
To make up their own mind yet
So we we have one so Dakota here of the
Did Sandy Hook prop
Portion
And so just that will ride this out here
And then
Exhibit number 16
This is
Your Facebook page
Correct mr. Salazar
In which you are posting on February 6th 2013
Less than two months from the shooting
Something from Intel hub
Concerning Sandy Hook and you post
Google Scott getzinger correct
Odd
And that's because you wanted
People
Discover the same
Nexus that you believe you and discovered between Mr getsinger's death
The map in The Dark Knight Rises
And the Sandy Hook shooting correct
Yes I was wanting people to the anomaly
Yunomi what you testified
Had absolutely no significance to you correct
Injection
Said it had no significance I think I said it was a bizarre coincidence that people should be aware of
But that did not signify anything to you correct
But didn't signify that it was a staged mass shooting
But it did signify something very bizarre
Coincidence
What did it signify
It was just a bizarre coincidence
It needed to be done.
For what purpose
So they could investigate it on their own and potentially discover that in fact it wasn't a coincidence at all
But that mr. getsinger
Have been killed
So as to silence him because he was aware
That
The change in the Sandy Hook map signified some Advance knowledge of the sheathing correct
Direction
I'm not sure what they would discover
Honestly it was
Very strange.
Putting it out there
I wanted them to Google Scott Gunslinger and
See all the anomalies here
Just see what happens just Google it see what you find
Maybe you'll find some of his other work from his storied career in other movies like The Truman
Maybe that's a reason to Google
What is a page boy
I did I don't know I don't know Chris Maddie personally as a no
Some of the Texas
But I get the sense that maybe he enjoys that back and forth a little
A little bit like that yeah
Meaning to this
Hey Quinton is the people should look into look into and find what what
All right you're not going to okay frontal assault isn't going to work for you I'm going to go around the back with me about this one now okay
So a lot of the stuff is fairly annoying certainly
But there is some bike positivity that comes at the worst possible way
You received an email
Did you not in March
On March 7th
The 2013
From Daniel DuPont
And a few
Please stay on top of the story
No names of deceased to be released etcetera the attack appears to be completely stage
The public knows that they are being lied to
And you wrote back to him
Thank you for the encouragement
Mothman
YouTube video that invoice and published in January correct
Yeah
Looks that way
Play I would regret responding to a random email like that
At this point like that would be like I didn't have to write back to that he didn't give us
True moment though a true motive comedy where is like
Yeah I don't think I read that one is like
Let's see the reply that you said yeah
Wow so now we finally get to conversation about Wolfgang halbig
And his role in all of this and how Adan first learned about him
What are the Articles you wrote
Introduced the Infowars audience to Wolfgang halbig
Extract
How did you first learn of mr. Howell
Heard he was interviewed
And I went and listened to the interview on American Free Press
Your interview
No I got to look at the date on the article
Let me show you what is Ben Marcus
Exhibit 19
You see an email from Ronald bastien's you
Tom Bastian
You got this guy and
Yes
It's legit ask Alex to bring him on as a guest okay
Nuketown.
I've no idea
And
You understood
Mr. Bastian to be
Asking you to that booking hounded
Yes it looks like them
Sumter 1014
So this interview on the American free press was released on February 11th 2014 so the email from Bastian
Asking add-on to wedding came the next day
It's probably not unreasonable to assume that add-on heard about the interview from this email unless he was closely monitor
During everything put out by the aafp
It's really good that add-on seems to not know who did that interview because if he did he'd have to say that it was Dave Gahan
Harry friend of David Dukes who actually was the publisher of Jim feathers book nobody died at Sandy Hook
Not the s***
Well and the guy who published that book that you're not supposed to really know all that much about he was the guy who was interviewing Wolfgang halbig
Take the broad how big to the attention of
Infowars Hellboy
Actually I was I was looking around on Garrity Harry and he
Italy has made some comments about like
I think I might be responsible for Alex
And Wolfgang halbig getting suits
Yeah baby
Even leaving aside who this interviewer was American Free Press is a
Supremacist Willis carto which has a strange kind of Holocaust deniers as Riders
This is where Adam was cruising
To get new gas
Particularly ones who's going to use to inflict severe trauma
On the parents of murdered children
Maybe do better
That's not good
A deposition
Ask how many exhibits there are like
Get as much information as you can before hand
And and in fact I would say even
Prepare because then when you go into this goes back to the first clips
I'ma let's go to exhibit 19 ship you know you you know what exhibits are coming that's what's important that's what my
Approach
Sure
Ora or like
Just be aware that you tried to sign up for crisis actors. Org
Before you say I wasn't interested in crisis actors what websites you signed up for that are exactly the thing
That you shouldn't have
So I haven't heard this American Free Press interview
He felt the need to of that
Showing you exhibit 19 again
Where mrhaliboot says
Down here in this paragraph
I think it's a scripted event that took place
I think it was in planning for maybe two
Two-and-a-half years
Yes
Okay and that was mr. how big's allegation correct
Now the idea
That a mass shooting at which 20 children were killed
And six Educators were
Have been scripted and planned for two-and-a-half years in advance is a serious
Charge correct
Crap
And
You knew it was a serious charge at the time
Serious charges
And that's why
You felt like you needed to
Established mr.
Talbots credentials right
Objection
Anyone's credentials overriding.
But you agree with me that you did not do that
Article in which you
Reported with somebody else was saying correct
I don't check credentials for everybody I write about you
But you did
Yes
And the reason you did it because you knew that these allegations were particularly serious
Injection
I thought he was bringing to the table so important
Information that only a school safety consultant
Supervisor
Did it occur to you
How
Families
Who have lost loved ones at Sandy Hook would react
To an allegation
That in fact
Their children
Were murdered
In an event that we scripted and planned over two-and-a-half years did that occur
Objection
Think about that
Play why would you
Yeah I'll be there they're not real but they're not real people say I am in Austin Texas working for Infowars
And they are not there
It's a solecism
Also people might have heard what sounded like a gasp as you hiccuping
Baby you did not have
So the wedding
Process
Pretty light almost like the vetting process to get hired
It turns out there's a parallel here
Other than visiting the website
Would you acknowledge mr. how big man
But I can sell
And
Review me interview did you do anything further to investigate the claims that he made
Relating to the threatening conducted law enforcement officers and the scripted nature of the scene to go to bed
No I didn't I just published what he said in the interview
Why
And you're aware that shortly after you publish this article
Mister how big
Was
Appeared
On
The
Broadcast
I got a call yet probably
Bizarre
So he did a little
Looking around
Go to the website that may be how they put up
Self get well I made listen to that interview
Let's see what looks good
A guy named Robert Keith sent an email to Infowars it's at 8
Maybe checking his credentials a little bit
Cynodon wrote back to him and said
Hey man it looks like he's got plenty of credentials to unspecific
And have a long list of things of concern
We talked about this on a bunch of the deposition episodes cuz it's come up in
Rap song with Alex
I didn't want to do like play it all over again
But we got this discussion
About the email here
Followed up
Is email to you
With
The results of
Made online about mr. habits past correct
Is that why yes
And it seems as though
He did
According his email
Quite a bit more than you did
To investigate mr. Holland's background correct
Directions to insulated more but it looks like he did a research
Well all you did was visit one website that mr. helping himself may have created correct
Direction
He may have created I think I did a little bit more searching but
Think it was made mainly based off of that one website
Earlier today was that it was
Adjust the website are you expanding that now to testify that you think you may have done
Other searches
Injection
Recall what kind of searches I did for Mr howland's information other than that website but it's possible that I did do more
Search
I'd like to stipulate that I might have done something that makes you look way better
Might have done I will I will save it if I were in add-ons position and the lawyer asks
Is it fair to say that this guy with random guy emailing you did more work than you on the story you're doing
If my lawyer didn't then object I'd be.
A position where I would
You're getting hanging out
To dry that's what's happening if your answer that question
Emails come in warning about how big's credentials
Right as it turns out
Albert
Coming back on the show
Did mr. Heath
Email to you and Matthias
Expressed
Concern
That
He was not able to
Find information concerning
How big is activities
Professional activities
Call you to question
Weather mr. halbig
Could be reliable
I think the point is bring it up or valid
Yeah I think it probably maybe maybe made me question I can't recall how I felt at the time
Okay
Don't even recall receiving this email correct
It's been so long it's been nine years so no I definitely
Don't recall
Receiving this email
And you don't recall whether you raise mr. he's concerned with anybody else that enforce is that correct
Recall doing that either
If you had you suspect you would have forwarded your email wrong to whoever you wanted to notify about it
Yes I probably would have yes
And
Whatever
You may have
Done or not done in response to the email
Mister haldi continue to appear on Infowars
Aftermarket
15th 2014 correct
I believe that is the case yes
And you don't
Record whether you did any additional wedding of mr. how big your cell and response to receiving this email correct
I believe I did anybody after this email now
Boss that certainly shows that you care I think you misunderstood our process
Siri see what we did
It was we used him because his narrative
Bolstered our own credibility and that was so we could make money oh no now I see why we're in trouble
Honestly if the time we kind of figured that if anybody was going to get in trouble to be out
Screwed up we're not good at law
I mean
Based on their choice of lawyers
Real bad at law
Yeah yeah
Is clear evidence that there were people who were raising concerns that add-on
Had heard because he did respond to that email how big's credibility
But there were other people
Maybe even in fours and please who are saying you got to go to be careful
Other than Mister did anybody else ever warn you
About
Relying on District how big
In your reporting on
Sandy Hook
Maybe
And I can't recall
Possibly
You know an individual named Robert Jacobsen
Yes Robert
How do you know mr. Jacob
He was a video producer for Alex
Did your work intersect
At Infowars
Is down the hall from Mesa
Once in awhile WeChat
When did he leave Infowars
Miami 2017 or 2018
Somewhere around there
And when she Adam boards when you started in 2012
Collies for
By 6 years
Yes sir
Did you have a friendly relationship with mr. Jacobson
Are you in touch with him today
You communicate with him
I don't
Did mr. Jacobson ever advise you of his concerns
About relying on Mister how big as a source
Or reporting at Sandy Hook with a script event
Mr. Jacobson
I think dead raised concerns about
But I didn't really regard them because mr. Jacobson has some wild
There is about a lot of things
Oh he does he has wild theories amazing
An incredible thing for a human being to say within which he's telling it
Yeah he's telling me that maybe I shouldn't listen to this wacko about Sandy Hook being fake but I don't listen cuz he's got
Weird cereal wacko
My job for this because I get into what those theories are
And this is really unfortunate for add-on
If your testimony is that Mr Jacobson raised concerns about
Mister helbig's credibility
But that you
Ignore those concerns because
He has
She tends to have wild ideas
Yeah I think Michelle Obama is a man so
I'm in
Ann you've actually posted
On your own social media
Suggesting that Michelle Obama is a man having
I've gone along with that conspiracy theory yes
Actually posted a picture
Mr. and mrs. Obama kissing and saying
Essentially happy gay pride day correct
I might have done that I don't know
So I guess you don't think that
Mister Jacobson's
View of that is
Right
You sure
I entertained the theory but I don't
I don't let spouse the theory
In any event
You discounted mr. Jacobsens warning
Because
You believe he held views like that
Lizards
Completely credible in my opinion
He didn't give the warning and
I didn't think much of it honestly
So the best way you can really interpret this otherwise it's something that I couldn't even
Imagine translating
But the best way I can figure is
What add-on is saying is that
Rob actually believe that thing where is I'm willing to post this like trolling
Post about it in order to push my transphobic and homophobic ideology
Something that I don't even come
Close to believing
Because it spreads the hate that I wanted it
Whereas Rob is crazy cuz I believe
Close to making sense of this as I can
That
Rob is crazy for believing the things that I say the things that we promote make money off of
Might actually believe this.
Either thing you got to know is none of us are actually believe the s*** that we say
And Rob does that guy's crazy
I was invested in spreading Sandy Hook conspiracy theories and implying that it's fake because I needed to attack the
Give that as a way to get around the obligation to make a human's in favor of guns
Being everywhere the liberal I have a kind of second-order interest in it
Where is I'm actually just manipulating the audience into thinking these things are real these concerns are
Rob can't believe this stuff
It seems like that's one of the readings you can make of this
It's another rake in the face
Punch-Drunk
From ber
Why didn't I listen to this guy's warnings
Because I did what do you want
Adan expect
That Maddie has
Knowledge of this thing he posted on Facebook expect that
Something that would be offensive to most people
This belief that Rob allegedly has and then it is a crazy idea that Rob has
Stated that he is not trustworthy he gets confronted with
You believe the same thing I mean it's just
It is just amazing it's just amazing for a human being to be
Amazing because
Rob
When he was there
Raising these concerns about Wolfgang
It decided the best course of action would be to make fun of him
Your general recollection that he raised concerns about relying on mr. how big
As a source
The clean that Miss Bessie Nico prescript
I believe I
Brushed It Off
I might have
For saying that
Did you report his concerns to anybody else that Infowars
No
Do you recall saying in his presence
That you wanted to have T-shirts and bumper stickers made
Printed on those t-shirts and bumper stickers
How big was right
Have those
T-shirts are bumper stickers made
No
Did you say that because you believed in Jackman how big was right
Not to like throw my
Beliefs behind everything fully so it's the principle that he
Could have been correct and I just know that it was getting under his under Jacobson's craw
To say that he was right so I kind of
Threw that in there
As a joke
But
Also have serious
Repeat the joke but it's also kind of serious oh my God I'm trying to making this point but it's also joke
I want to retire plausible deniability about this stuff but I also really
I want the benefit to
Five people thinking that I'm serious about it when they're available
How is it that a human being
Can layout
This
Clear a pattern of behavior
That you engaged
That is so obviously everything wrong
And not be like
Now I got it
You know going in that what you're doing is full of s***
I think that moment of the constant banging your head against the wall
All of like
You have these things that you were bringing up about anomalies yet
Can appoint you didn't have a conclusion about the foreknowledge
Like if he realized the
Thing that was laid out about 911 at the beginning
Avi like abbyland anomalies and it made me
Totally
It just there should be a mowers like
That's what I want
Dropping his bulshit like
To me that's the moment that I really want is when you don't have to finally admit that you're an idiot might have boxed my
Myself in space and make any stuff
You did this to yourself
A decade of working at Infowars
Causes no prob
Speaker
Monitoring your work going for a follow-up question my integrity and the point doesn't matter
When you're asked follow-up questions when you're at a place where people don't believe your nonsense
You can't do it
It's hard now
Also this was really funny
Because
Result of
Being said that Don is very
Until relatively recently you had a
Pinned tweet to the top of your Twitter account
Which was a link to
You are first
A article about Wolfgang halbig introducing him to the Infowars on his breath
I don't recall 10 tweet about how big
But maybe I don't know why I picked up the thing that on Twitter in 2018
Are 2019
Showing you exhibit number 19 a
I say this
The
The page of your Twitter account correct
Yes
Okay and you joined in September twenty
17 right
Okay yes
And then you have a
Ken's tweet at the top of your account
Which according to the page
Posted on April 17th 2018 correct
Yes
And you can see the
School shooting expert threatened over
Sandy Hook that's the first article you
Ever wrote concerning
Mister help me correct
Yes that's it
At least as of 2018
You were
Beating your Twitter
Landing page
With an article in which
Mister how big
Refer to Sandy Hook is a scripted event correct
Objection
A side
In the Tweet to the top of my Twitter account
April 17th 2018
And the link to an article in which Mr halbig refer to Sandy Hook
As a script
Yes the article
Is about fix the one we covered earlier
Boy
Welive
I guess I did
Guess what did do that
Why did I post that article in 2018
Kennedy's Mike top
Tweet
On my account I'm starting to see a pattern of behavior here so you asked me a question and I answered
And then whenever I answer it you pull out a
Exhibit
Proving the opposite or at least something different from what I said is it too late for me to blame this on them not training me
Have you considered telling me what your exhibits are before you ask the question
And I will be able to answer truthfully 831 last thing that come
Adan writing the FBI
He says no one was killed at Sandy Hook
Write that article that was one of the most popular stories ever drove a massive spike in traffic
Wet all over social media was a huge thing for Infowars
Yeah it was all just based on one table
From a report that add-on found
Somehow by guess
Inure
Barnacle
In which you reported that the FBI
Had reported zero murders
In Newtown for 2012
You cited
A
A table
From that report correct your call that
It might have been table
Okay that's 25b
And I'll acknowledge
Mr Salazar that because of the way this was PDF
Iscar partly cut off on the left side but will be able to see what we need to see
You recall this
The look of this graphic header
You included that in your article does not
And if you go down to
Page
The Newtown row
I'll concede that the end is cut off
But if we can just accept
For purposes of this
That 0
Are reported in that particular row
Four murders and not negligent manslaughter for that year correct
Yes I see that
And that was the quote anomaly you reporting on right
Yes
But you didn't look in any other part of the
See if the deaths that occurred in Newtown at the Sandy Hook shooting weren't back reported in another section did you
Jackson
I didn't
There would be another term for
What happened at Sandy Hook
Murder wood
In compass
Don't think so
Any further four other other definitions are there other places
And you didn't look any further to see whether those murders
We reported
Under a different law enforcement organization that had jurisdiction to investigate them correct
Jackson
I only was reporting on what the FBI was saying in this report
Well
That's what I'm asking you questions report wasn't just table 8 correct there were other parts of the report
Did you know that
Objection
I figure there's 137 at least of
Sabal lakes around 137
Exist strawberry somewhere
And you didn't think to look for Table 9 or people 10 or any other tables right direction
Think my story was
Mainly about table Aiden so I didn't
Go through
The entire list of tables at the FBI has
So I was listening to this
And it just
Kind of struck me how clearly this demonstrates that
There's no curiosity
Because curiosity isn't useful
For someone like a dog
Like when your job is to write a story about a predetermined thing curiosity is just going to get in the way
In order to do the work that he has done and is doing
You have to
Actively not as Quest
You have to actively not question event
Your branding yourself in some way as like that we are out there you know we're questioning things literally
Will you not
Asking
It's stopping yourself
From asking a natural question
That one would have upon finding information
It's wild
I just I don't understand how they can
Like understand
Not not that they don't understand it
I understand how they can see how transparent that
What's interesting to me about that
Is I feel like it's very similar to why they're so susceptible to being trapped in these depositions
Is because the way their brain thinks is
They go into the forest
They get their apple and then they go back
Back home you know like
You could put an apple underneath a box
And I'm talking about this
Now in real life
You could put an apple underneath the cardboard box with a little thing attached and they be trapped every time they go in there
The grab the Apple there be like go to Apple and then maybe try
It wouldn't be hard
They don't think
Clearly
Well
Words all of the things they don't think them
Yeah
I I just
I wonder if it is just a thing of like
No one no one cares in their in their lives so why why would they think that anybody else would
The see-through the thief
The fake game that they're playing
If he didn't have a real City
Innate somewhere
With deep within him
I really feel like his answer to those would be like
Oh that would be a good idea to look for a table nine ironically I'm curious about this lack of curiosity
I am at where did it come from
Yeah but you really only was interested in that table because it made his Arkham
You only went to the one table that a tipster
I pointed out to you correct
Injection
I only went to the table that show their zero deaths in Newtown
Right
Have reason to know that that's what that table showed and I think your testimony was
That
A tipster had provided it to you correct
It was either attempt or something I found on social media
Okay
And
You only wanted to go to that table because that's the table that reported
0 deaths
That's the only table that
Pertain to the story I was riding
You were writing
Reported that the FBI reported zero deaths in Newtown correct
Yes
That's why I
When is the table light showing that it showed zero deaths in Newtown
In and what you were conveying to your audience was
This is an anomaly
If
There have been deaths in Newtown you would expect the FBI to Live recorded
We're trying
Back down
Went out with that the FBI didn't back report them in a separate table in the same report
Scrubs election
Mischaracterize of the evidence
You didn't point that out did you
I wasn't aware that the FBI had reported the deaths elsewhere I don't know why they would not listen
The death squared says murders in Newtown 0
You don't know why they might do that correct
It seems like it should all be listed in the table a
An inverted you ask
It will make any inquiry about whether those death may have been reported elsewhere in the same report correct
I didn't ask the FBI if that's
Address
You can ask anybody
Dangerously on curious and unserious person
That's bananas
I feel like he's now
Completely unique person to me
I don't know how this person exists
Like how do you get how do you tie your shoes
My God
So did you think that there could be a table 9 or they could report it anywhere else I don't know why they would
You can answer that question
You can go be like why would you even find the answer things that you don't know
If
They are
Like
It like
Necessarily in your interests
It's a dada
There's no reason to explore this because the only thing you could possibly find ruin the ability to exist
For your purposes which is what they want just come out and say yeah but it's pretty awesome
If I looks any further I would find out that I'm lying and I don't want to do that because I want to possibly deny that I'm
Past the point of plausible deniability in trouble reading back-to-back
So speaking of emails I'm going to skip this next clip because
Is long and honestly I only kept it in for one reason and it's because he was an email that he sent to his cousin
There's about the cyclist who are gone from Newtown to wash
Intend to like
Bring attention to Ghana
And you sent an article about it in the subject headline was
F*** the second
Saudi subject comes up dismounting the Earth
Documentary that Infowars had promoted called we need to talk about Sandy Hook
And here is a dawn sense of what happened there
Familiar with
The documentary we need to talk about Sandy Hook
I believe I tried to get through it was so long that I
Probably just got through
30 minutes worth of it or something yeah
Familiar with the documentary
Okay
And
You didn't have anything to do with making a documentary did you
Did you promote
That documentary on your social media
I can't recall
Infowars ever promoted that documentary
I believe I wrote an article about it when it was taken off of them
Jimmy H something
I don't think we promoted it
Read about how my God be censured
Juran disagreement
With the fact that
Platforms had chosen not to
Well I did read an article about it I don't know if I express my personal opinion in that article
Did you found
Know what the time that
The we need to talk about Sandy Hook
Documentary
Presented The View that
Sandy Hook back to curd
I figured that was a central tenet of
Of the documentary but I didn't watch it in its entirety so I
What kind of hats
Guess what that was what they were going for
So can I and you reported that in in your coverage of the van
Eliza
On December 2nd 2014 and forward posted the video of this documentary on their site with the sub-headline
Documentary blows the lid off suspected Sandy Hook cover up
The article includes events which sounds pretty laudatory
Quote a loose Coalition of concerned citizen journalist to known as The Independent Media solidarity of produced an in-depth
Well research documentary regarding the countless anomalies
Inconsistencies and discrepancies evident in the Sandy Hook school shooting investigation
The video is a tell-all leave no stone unturned work that coalesces hundreds of data points
Which researchers and laborious Lee spent
Countless hours compiling
That's really sounds like what you might write if a video is too long you couldn't even make it through the whole thing and you can't even really nail down with
The point of it was
Also the article includes this update
A previous version of this video was removed from YouTube do to a copyright Claim by Lenny Posner
Posner is reportedly the parent of one of the children supposedly killed at Sandy Hook
Reportedly and supposedly both in that sentence is pretty over
Go fuc yourself
And he should have watched the last 10 minutes of that documentary cuz they they go hahaha and then
So Maddie is done with his questioning positions
Defense lawyer asked a couple questions
Answer the first one has to do with that
Only using table 8
There were some questions about
This
Table8
At the time you reviewed
Back in 2014 did you have
Any reason to
Doubt that the number for Newtown a0 is accurate
No
That's bulshit
Madonna absolutely everything to question the interpretation of the table given here because the rest of the world was
Did in fact die
There's a direct contradiction here in any curious person would see that table and it wouldn't really be a choice to question things
Reaction
You'd start asking yourself things like how is this possible is there information on missing what's the context here
Is it possible for both this table to be accurate and the shooting happened as was report
The not questioning is actually a choice
Adan is making any does that because he's crashed even an inch below the surface he couldn't make the insane claims that he does
Make for a living
He's woefully unqualified and doesn't have the tools to be in the role he pretends to be in
Which is that of a writer and reporter
That ability to turn off the instinct to question things when something
Conforms to your narrative while simultaneously yelling at your audience about how you're the people who question things
That ability actually makes him a perfectly qualified to be an in-house liar it Infowars
So you better hope they don't go out of business cuz there's not many other games in town
CCC the problem is all right I just misread it
I didn't know it was
Table8
I thought it was table Infinity
Course I didn't think that one through seven imaginary number
Also has a question about his research that he did about the car
Qualifications presented by Wolfgang halbig
Switching over to mr. how big
There was some
You have to have that open anymore
There was some discussion of
An email you received questioning his
Credentials
Do you work all that
Yes I recall it
Now
When you first wrote about mr. how big
YouTube
One website
Necessarily the entirety
Your research
I can't recall how much research I did I know that one website did
Probably provide a majority of the credentials that I
Is it possible you could have come across
Say Orlando Sentinel
Articles from
The 90s
Referring to him as a director of security for Seminole schools
Tomorrow if possible
Could you come across an article
In the LA Times mentioning time in the late 90s early 2000
It's possible
This is
Fishy I love it is it possible that you could testify better here
Here use this
Excuse me my own witness
Could you do a better job let me give you an update Jesus Christ better answer for you
Wow
If you would prepare for that then you would have had that in the can maybe
That's if your lawyer knows that then you should know that
Oh you know I don't know
So we reach the end of this deposition of Adan Salazar and like I said
Play a bit of the machine around Tampa
No it's sense of Menace that I felt about his body of work a little
But my mind The Wizard of Oz was revealed to be a puddle of mayonnaise that could
Handle a lever
Yeah
Maybe part of it was just because he was the one who was following us and then Sapphire was maybe that is kind of part of the
Yeah the minister felt but
I mean whatever the case I feel like
You know the way he answers questions the way this
This is all processed is very sad
Transparent
I think I'll necessary you didn't have to answer any of these questions help
Nope nope he clearly has a an interest in the company
How many guy like
Paul
I think we covered his deposition that certainly I hate Paul Joseph Watson but we weren't is cruel about that because
He comported himself decently
This
Was
Get out there
There is obviously more
Actions that add-on Salazar took in the past
That are relevant to this case
And that is unique
For his position
As some being deposed
But
There is such a refusal to accept
Reality
In the like. Was making a point
It's just a weird coincidence
Stop it you're a child it makes it makes you lose a little bit of respect even as a
The Villa
Whatever there's a way to do this but isn't
Like we we just qualified again he failed to reach text a
Like I'm going to try and obfuscate
Just enough like yeah I'll say yes or no but
Whenever they want to get me on something I'll be like
I don't recall or something like that that message
Vested interest in questioning the reality of Sandy Hook had to do with my fear of them using it against like their stuff
Damn can't be real how can you be so slippery
About a bunch of these other things and then just
Give that would give it all away
Anyway we have a bit more where this came from there's going to be coming up in the future
Cuz that's bottom feeders
Immediately after being called a bottom feeder to then talk about Adan salad Salazar
Doesn't make me feel great
There are worse things
Sure I mean
Another episode
In the near future
Someone's been
But until then I'm Neo I'm Leo I'm dzx Clark
I run a Cooperative in my brain where people are free to squat
Artist space sure right
Where is acceptable right
I don't know what I'm saying
What the sex robots
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work