Holding
Alexandra Thurston color I love your work
We are Goodwill dudes you like sit around drink novelty Beverages and talk a little bit about Alex Jones
It is much like a
Customer service representative
You read making friends and influencing people
So f****** annoying I understand gym
So annoying those tricks that people do art you can just see through them so easily all those
All those little light influence
Strict
Solenoid
Most people can't afford to pay attention a little bit
You just become aware of them and then
You know you want me to
What is that because
You know a lot about
And I can't see through his b*******
Well that's fine I'll help you out
Arnold Palmer Lite
Arizona's
23 fluid oz
Almost the size of a wine bottle 608 great love it
Iced tea lemonade
Delicious good summer drink
Muggy out in the shop
I like doing the weather report up top
Telling everyone how muggy and
Voice that is outsides crazy
I'll tell you right now this is some good ice cream
It's good but it's not
What's going on out there Mike be
Thank you for joining up with
Ewok what's up out there Mike W
Thank you so much for doing everything Winslow is
The guy from
Police Academy
Call Mike
I didn't know you guys were friends
I met him once in Columbia Missouri as well
I don't remember it going well
Today
So if you emailed us your your address
Hopefully it will show up
Open your mail I am
Fingers crossed
Put a note in there rain today
Jesus Christ where do I have paper what's going on
Well I've already mailed
Mail it out Dubai
Alright fine
Hotmail you notes later later
From 2015
People then go back and listen to what we've said what we written what we have exposed
Understand that we do have our finger on the pulse
We do understand how the elite operate
Are sure would beg to differ
People will go back and listen to this
Two years later we're like yeah
And no no not at all
And no sir
Span of October 4th
Thirsty
Forever
Publicly that we have an episode 2
Covering Alex Jones's further coverage of the events in Charlottesville
We recorded
The evening of Trumps
Latest Prescott
Almost simultaneously
Yeah and
The hearing is a press conference everything
That our analysis was good
In terms of what we had in front of us and how Alex Jones is about a lot of stuff with
Add a contact of
Basically mirroring Alex
On so many fronts
It became a thing where
That's what we need to talk about
Episode itself would have been dogshit
So I don't like that's the reason for not putting it up
But
I've been having a lot of thoughts
I just want to say that
Really quick
I feel like
I kind of know what's going on here with these white nationalists
And I see
What's going on are they looking for something I'm not saying that I know as much as even
Deep deep deep sleep study
I'm not saying that
Of what's going on and the direct
Some things are going
And it's bad
I predicted on the last episode
We were going to see
The Isis like insert
Please come together
I meant immediately there was that guy
In Oklahoma who got arrested with 1,000 lb
Federal Reserve building
Course
That's literally
Absolutely
You can't do that whole thing
I'm right where they are
That's for real for real war
Yeah and it's it's scary and I'm terrified and I hope that
My fears
And why expectation
Predictions are off
I don't know we'll see
But I had one thought
That I want to share with everybody and you Jordan
I know you were looking at me very accusatory
I think this is actually a good
And I think it's something that should
Good talk
This is a mega good and bad song
Is bittersweet
It's a bittersweet
There's a massive difference between
People on the left
Be alright then gone
White nationalist
What's the Nazis
The biggest difference
What's that I see beyond
Very obvious
Are the people on the left specially activist
Engage people
A place of love
They operate from a place of love
And trust with each other and vulnerability
There is
A part of it that is
Usher
Goal
A shared objective
Videos Unity
And is
I get taken care of and so do you and so does everybody else
Damn there's a freedom to be what you are
Gay people can just be gay trans people can be trained
And there's a vulnerability in living
Who you are public
And there's something that brings people together about that
And creates community
So when you see these organizations
These hippie leftist organization
That protest
Often you'll see people who stand arms
2 arm
Together different
And they care about each other and that's great
On the right
It's beer
It's fear and paranoia
And that is not
Sustainable
You see what's happening even within the Trump White
Everyone's turning on each other
It's constantly happening because they
Come from this place
Of conspiratorial paranoia
This fear this fear of someone trying to squash them
It's on Meredith
It's this fear of whiteness being eradicated
Or whatever version you want to fill in that Gap
That beer
Makes you fear everyone else
Even the people you're so
Supposed to be in lockstep
So
Even though we see these disparate white nationalist groups coming together
And they're doing some damage
There is a part of me that knows full well
They're going to
To turn on each other cuz they're going to start taking each other or fed
They're going to come to a point where they're like
You're an infiltrator
There is
Cannibalistic
These sorts of organizations
Can't really
Make the sort of loving Coke
Lisa Vaughn
The people
Supporting each other
Ansel
That's my positive feeling
Right now unfortunately
About it is
That Wendy's conspiratorial paranoid
Type of Tendencies come out
It often leads
To explosion
So
There could be
Some really negative
Flare up
And what have you
But they'll never
Will never be able to work
Work together well
I'm at the plaza
I think
I don't know it's cold comfort and I don't think it's that great but it was something that dawned on me when I was
Going over some of these stories
And watching
Footage
From the
From the demonstrations
It's like it's terrifying but at the same time there's a there's a pitiable ass
When you see them interact with
With each other
I agree
Type beat right
It might be it might be something very small but
They that wait on the heart
Well
I agree with you like whatever
So I
Advice of Menifee
People who
Here's what we got to do
We should
We should talk to them
If you have somebody that you know who is
Engaging with his alright bulshit unfortunately know where this is going
And
I got a lot of Infowars back
Did you forward me that email there's a
There's a good bit of it but it's not encouraging
But it is anymore
It's just ironic to
I've spent the last
Pretty much year of my life
Fighting against Alex Jones only to be
Related to it
Whatever I'm talking to him
I don't want
I want him to
See what's wrong
Because I believe he's a good person
This is not good
I know you think you're following through with your princess
But
Twisted by this
Nonsense
Just for a second remember you're not a
Or not the apologist
Them and they just can't do that
Seaside is all Jews should die
So I'm going to go with we're fighting out of love
If you're apologizing
Apologize
For Nazis
To be in the middle if you're apologizing for
No no
The part that you know
A lot of people have made this point already but
The weekend you can cast
Decide very easily the argument that
There are good people who are
Just with them
Yeah no arguments
I've been to 100 protests in my license
Anytime there were Nazis
Airplane people
Open like I'm getting the f*** out of here
If you're surrounded by
Maybe you're not
Terrible right one of the two
Cuz even if you do care about Southern Heritage so much that you feel like you got to go to the protest
The only two options are leave or then demonstrate against
The Nazis being a part of your protest
Those are really the only
To socially active
Responsible
Things you can do
But be that as it may
Let's not dwell on this too far cuz
The simplest way of putting it
Is
Not everybody who voted
Now they are
Now it's time to
Look in the goddamn mirror the one who's on the side of
Good luck
Good f****** lakay
I don't want to talk about this anymore and
Proventil
Which I don't see happening cuz you now on vacation
We were safe to go back to the past
I go back to 2015
Be going over the 4th to the 6th
Guess what
On 4th David Knight hosted we don't have to talk about that s*** at all I'm looking forward to all the stuff
Not talkin about
That's my favorite part of the show right now
Not talking about it that's another one of the win column for us
Big old weigh
Here's how Alex Jones Watson start
This is the beginning narrative
The kickoff
I also in the fourth hour Paul Joseph Watson
This morning
And
This motherfukers wearing my dress
Endorsement
It's hurtful.
You may have to lose your eyesight
Your existence
So you don't know where that
But that's based on
I can't be happier that were in 2015 Dance For Us in 2015
Arise
Best trendy
May we live here in perpetuity
Alex Jones saw some sort of
I don't know probably
He's ready he's ready
Vonnegut
Like one time
And that's all he knows
So that's all he's doing right now
But this is
Aji sauce
Some British version of a show that's like My Strange Addiction
I like that one of these shows where they follow people
Pretty bizarre
Cuz even plays part of it on the show and everybody loves a freak
It is there worshiping these people pouring Drano in their eyes
They're showing that there are people who believe that they should be blind
There are people who believe they should
And cut off their arm
Supporting anybody
I don't know
If you want to if there's an argument
So small of a population because I'm not sure I need to have an opinion
But I don't want to
Stop the Elsa want to say that
Trendy's are not worshiping them
That because that's
That's the same thing as
GB like
That's going to a carnival and having the guys they look at the bearded lady especially the ones that are like I eat my bed
There's a conversation about that
What is the copycat is not becoming
Like a carnival Sideshow s***
No I'm not super thrilled with that but
Then again about sucking 33 year-old man I shouldn't be
90s local Broadcast News
You're in your eyes could that be happening to your kids
If if the local news guy was really obsessed with globalists into trendys yet
So Alex
It's going to be 1000 degrees by the end of the
The week because they're globalism
Thanks 16 will be everybody's
The trendy
Worship blind making people blind do I have you
These on that for like days
It's ridiculous
Give other stuff
The other other narratives he wants to get to
This one's kind of interesting
Alex Jones shows
Alex is way ahead of the curve my man
This is about 20 years ago about linguistic
Okay
And European is wrong
Members of the
UK and German and French government the last month
On television articles
Because it's Europe has white people
And it's good they're all about to be gone
Northbrook
So you are
I said you mean where
A woman
I love that played
Eva
Eerily
Specifically
You might as well as that black dude
He was actually saying
Do you mean that video you sent me right right
I agree I look up
We wrote the story a little bit
In terms of like Shakespearean language
Adjustment a lady who is cheating on her husband and everyone knew it modern
Pornography
Exactly what is 15
Fruit that is great until like the crnkovich is come along and stuff like
But
He's right there
I think it might be right around the corner
I think they might show up around the
Who's Rodger Stone
They're all their ears perk up
So I'm pretty thrilled to that I didn't know that Alex Jones is on the cock tip
Literally
I'm excited
You're not going to like this next clip
Cuz it's one of the three times
Eight-and-a-half months
That I've labeled a clip
Wolf
So get ready for that
Let's baby exasperated
Can you be homosexual
Already out
There are cases of it
Drugs the
The degeneracy the mutilation is
The idea that will Embrace us
Didn't like the
Like the Greeks will this is just repetition of what that homophobic
Pastor said on the show like 3 weeks ago or whatever
Chronology
This is just an example of literally repeat
So
But that that's part of the Wolf
Vet like
I knew that you were
I knew that your answer was going to be what he deflected from immediately after
We just got a nice it's a little frustrating but it gets so much worse
I'm civilization because the globalist are developing high-tech reservations
Cultural degradation
The globalist
Elysium basis
Seminar on artificial Islands
You don't get onto those things when you buy into any of the stuff
Is a cultural poison put out there to neutralize
Well
Do you sing
The first weapon
Cover for a whole bunch of different
Racially-based
Caucasians
Wait
Are so closely aligned to Africans
What
You can sneeze we got HIV black person it
What about the year relationship
Let's talk about reality
That's a
That's a misunderstanding of all the things all the way at
Simultaneous
Also also even his argument of like
Gay people destroy civilization if you embrace them
That's why the globalist have no gay Utopia
Right I guess three of the cultural degradation
Yeah he argues the globalist
Superhero
He also argued that globalist like f****** each other
How do you not know that
Fine
Can have a conversation about that
Jon rappoport
That's why
Reagan crack into the black community I will not put
Whatever whatever
But oh boy
If I understand this correctly
White people are resistant
Hib
But
Designed specifically just
For Africa
Understand DNA
He does not even come close to it
The studies that have been done have shown that there is a
Incredibly higher-risk
In Black communities of HIV
But the reason is generally it's because of poor resources in communities
The systematic differences of
Shittier education
Because we
Deflective Public School Systems
Deteriorate
And just access to healthcare
Those are the things that are the main drivers of the wrist
And intravenous drug use
Things like that also
Artifacts are in it
Hit his
You get why I marked that
That's a big oof
Wow Let's talk about reality
Great
That's such a great punchline to that
But really
Yeah really what he said so he said
You can sneeze on a black person and give them HIV
Damasio book
A hell of a sneaky
If you got
TV
Just jumping on somebody
Into their face
Maybe maybe
Are 28 Days Later
I think he thinks it is
Alex's
Redeemable
Sneeze on the black
Immaculate Palace Moline the homosexual community
Sort of I don't know people on black
People but he certainly
Genetically
That's fair I think that's fair but what you need to know is what Alex doesn't it
Around most cases
With with with the group above the Ku Klux Klan
Ku Klux Klan is in their dialectic
Used to just create
PetSmart
But they recall my mobile
Going to give you free stuff
Show me on the doll where Al Sharpton
Unless you
And that means every race every color every crate
Good
Pay for abortions
Alicia
Maryland
Holler at you are
Tolerate
Cultural
Notice how they're saying
Facebook at 50 different sexual preferences
And the future you will be asexual
Wrong creatures
Under the UN plan it is not all that matters.
Um puts out a plan where they're like we're going to make people asexual dronebot
Totally
This is pretty
Eat ya in the
The
Plan of the globalist
There is
Really convolute
Very much so
Workout
And if the global if they're the ones who really hate black
There
They're just doing a bad job
How so
Well
I mean if you really hated black people
Any better plans as opposed to
Building up the KKK as a
False flag for white people
People also black people to hate white people
Power up the black lives matter
You forgot a piece of the plane
Director
And then they train people to get mad
Red
Is the late nights
He wasn't an MC
You drive around in a big ass convertible
He would
F****** Spin and it would be an amazing
Departament galten came over
If you got to do a different
Some Arch globalist
Tricked him
Well because
Rap is an amazing art form
So Gore Vidal
Unfortunately
Let the men dressing differ
The point there
Is that Alex loves everybody
He wants to get across wow invalidating the
Entire point
Those of us who love
What a dick
Oh you're just saying all the things you hate about black people
What makes you uncomfortable that black people is all the globalist
It's a really sneaky way to be a bigot
It's not that I hate
I just hate all the things
But it said the globalist make him do that
A little bit
On this show also Alex explained that people are Pepsi is using baby parts
Flavor their sodas
This is not true at all
He screams about that a little bit it wasn't a big enough deal in 2050
Get sued by Pepsi
No no no no
What there's no statue
Limitations on that well know there's enough
Truth to what he's talkin about that he probably couldn't get sued although it's a wild misrepresentation
What's going on
There isn't like a development a flavor development company that
Has subcontracted with
Pepsi in the past
They use
Cloned
Endometrial kidney cells
Or something like that
From elective abortion
In some of their res
So
There's removed from
Actual cannibal
But there is enough truth in it that I think Alex
Could get away with not getting
But he's straight up line
Cuz he wants his audience to think when you drink Pepsi there's f****** babies in there
So
You know what
He has a lot of Truth
Despite what we say for hours on end
He's got a lot of Truth backing him up but he has a problem
And that be that might be that he is too much
Behind them
Fantastic
I found out one of the biggest reasons why under such government scrutiny right now
Is because of whistleblowers documents things like that
I've got to the point where I can't even respond because
They will arrest
And you're afraid of no
Plumlee folks in Benghazi and all that and Colonel Shaffer
I don't even want to know
Horse anymore
Bro
Will control the whole future that's why they're so brutal
Not backing down
Whether you're FBI or CIA or
Politician or an arrogant
NFL football player
False reality
Slow poison
The Shield we respond to see if we notice is a titrate the dose
Talk to guard what is it in different compounds all known
Prostate function he'll never fails
20% off
I've been listening to Alex Alex Jones everyday for a month
Whiplash
I was impressed
Also
Brookside with the NFL football player
It's not I don't think so cuz I don't think it was
2015 Midview started his
Is the public
Protester
He might have still been an activist but
Daikumedia paying attention to what I don't think was in 2015
If you're saying an NFL football if you're staying in
Arrogant NFL football player
That is
Quote
Book Subway
Apparently racist
Very race I don't I don't know what was going on exactly that point but he always talked about how much he hates the NFL
Because it's such a
Distraction from globalist
Some stuff like that
But I'm willing to believe that that was a vague non-specific thing I don't know I'm not entirely sure
Still racist
But boy is that amazing
First of all
He is too many
All these whistleblowers
Giving me all of the same information
Yeah it was a coup
Yes it was a false flag
I don't need proof
Purple Penguin
I don't want any
In the degrees of May
Frost guard
That's pretty amazing
You got a lot of s*** coming out of you
Because got to poop
So
Yeah I have anymore
Reservoirs coming up to him
I want I want this clip
Okay good but it just it's delightful
Cuz you eat in this nightclub
A the Liberals
And the Dum Dums like us
Fallen for the globalist
To a certain other group dum dum
And it's it's pretty fun
Let's find out it's a total false reality
People don't know what they're talking about
Repeat
Because they have nothing
They're totally in the hands of a
I can't tell you how many people
I'm coming over the years with Nigerian scams and other skins
OU falling for one of those scams
MMA even invest in the fraud
And then down the road will never speak to me again
Because they can't admit they got screwed over
I didn't learn from it
Successful
It's their family as their clubs are cool nobody can stop them
There
2 Chainz
A couple of important first
Buck is he doesn't talk about it all the time but the fourth time you talked about the Nigerians
Prince bububu Austin bar
I don't know if that's the next stage of the scam I think it's a one stage
Second
Let's take it easy line
But let's pretend he's not
But he knows for people who fell for the
Yeah
Tumor
Your Friends Are
He knows more those are just the ones who won't talk to him
Anymore
A lot of people
What you don't know is that he's not on air is volunteering at a very tech-savvy nursing
It is a place where really old people
Exposed to the internet and email
To not answer email
Wow
That's that my only Theory
To want is Alex's lying to
Buckley
Buckley it still talking
Buckley second third and fourth ex-wife
Destroying Buckley marriage
I'm so
This whole investigation
Isabel
Figure out where Alex Jones
About the 2016 presidential election
Right
We get to check in
Who who who
You're in the truck yet
Cuz
He hasn't been up to this point
Let's see where's had that on
I would support Trump more if he
Paul and I really like Carson
I can tell he's really a good man
He's so good
Inoculations
He's super smart
But he's I know people like this so good
He wants to help people so much
Then he just can't believe the system crap they're bad
And
I don't want us there really smart loving hardworking people on average
The most successful people I know are Seventh-day Adventist
But they still will do what
You know a lot of Seventh-day Adventist
We tested on
They volunteered for
Including some cases to be killed
Basically
Because I thought that was christ-like I mean
My mom Workforce
Dallas
Point
Nashville TV show
Steven Trump
It's just that
Tearing
Values
The other way if you then just start saying the state's perfect
He said
Carson
I really do like Cruz, he's got some better leadership qualities
I like trains
I guess you were asking callers
What
A lot more
Who was somebody like
Does not include
That's where he's at
Long diatribe about Seventh-day Adventist I don't know why
Text job history
His mom works
Pr4 The Seventh-Day Advent
But wasn't
I don't understand I don't care to unpack it like once we already have been placed the CIA dentist
Story
Add 26 smartest boy in Austin, Texas
Country who knows
Who cares
It's all made up
We talked about
We can't nail down these
Because he always talks about like all my family is in the
Your CIA dentist dad also
He assigns whatever job he needs to one of his family members
In order to make some sort of connect
Listen to what he's talking about
I don't believe
Three quarters
The Avengers part I believe 100%
I love it I love that Ben Carson
Is a
Good man
He's a
Find man
He's a bit tyrannical
Totalitarian
A little bit but he's a good man
He just thinks the government is good for everybody like also I figured it out
I figured it out
Ben Carson
Very very
Super smart
The pyramid
It's filled with green
Are the same. Pyramid
That weren't
It's built by the
That could be
Well guys
You'll never know how
Mediocre that joke really was he found the guy who organized
The
The United right rally on Alex Jones twice
On the show and he's like
We're taking down these Confederate statues next thing raps take down the pyramids slaves built
Go.
Love it
Slaves built some of some of them yet
A joke
I know
But you're very interested to know all that you can about these global
To announce to you finally
Finally
We've got some
I'm f****** specific information
From Alex
About the global
There's some stats
Okay
Weird
Descriptive
Numbers
You're going to find out in just a minute
And so they all have their special Garden for special drug their clean vaccines
Got their own food trucks around Jets their own everything in line they're all
7000 people on planet
In their own words are aware of this
And they just totally try to just get ready and they're all very scared in the elite
For the Earth
Population
Populations to the plants
The truth is your control
Promise all this power by your masters
When it gets down
The deeper level of statement
100 million
Wait but why what's up
He's talking directly to like
Douglas Taffer
Yeah like a PA
Going around like okay
I'm afraid of this guy so I will set up all these
Population
Jones
They're not going to give me the life extension
I'm not going to
That's great
Their staff
Their nature is not going to change as they continue
You complete
You're not
By the system okay
That's cool
Some of these people and they know that
What are you doing
Because let me tell you these people start turning against their masters real quick
I spiritually have announced that I'm not part of
Hands off
Older sub Corruptions
Before
Sublevel where I wake up and I'm in their hands
What's this is the master seduction of humanity
The Bible is run by an ancient powerful entities with super advanced intelligence
Call
To be developed and deployed
Envisions the double-helix of DNA Invision Envision science
Social engineering
Charles Darwin his cousin Alex
I don't think that makes Iraq
Wow you were freaking out
What are you Siri
Play there's a super intelligent
Slowly drizzling out
Futurize Technologies
Servant
Yeah
Like global
Google downloads
Love the hyper-intelligent demon
Which book of the Bible is that I don't remember
Are you talkin about how you guys met
Need to give up all of your local religion
For the superintelligent guys catch up
Established
Make sure that you're not bothering each other
Is my basic Point again
Just to reiterate
Super intelligent living underneath you at all times
He's going to start getting Charles Darwin to think about stuff
I love this I love that he believes that human creativity and Innovation and progress
All this stuff but can't believe the people would come up with creative ideas
Understand it's only
It's only Superstar how to be a demon
Huge parallel between what
I just heard it
A huge parallel between what do you say
About how
They're Masters don't care about you
You can't change their nature
Alex
Personally with his
Yeah
Line by line that's what happen
Paranoia is exactly what has happened
Damn right now
Paranoid mindset that tears apart every
Look even look at it like I mentioned
The Trump Administration is being sort of the microcosm of that
Can staph look how quickly people just show up and leave
Still haven't
Norfolk
Shows back up
Occasionally now but clearly is on a
Real real Longley
In the episode that we
Tell recording didn't put out
When he's interviewing Jason Kessler the guy who organized the United the right rally he accuses him of being a pet
Right I mean there is Jeff they complete destructive
A force that's within paranoia
Evil
Itself from within
Right
Will Shakespeare
Dragonlance
The end of everything that's important
On October 1st
Let me see is there anything else that I worth talking about on this episode
Distributive not Nigerian prince
Oh no this is worth talking about
He takes calls for a long time on the show
Think about Trump
Call
Raptor
Fantastic
You have no idea
He has no qualms using people's fake names
Respect
But be that as it may. Call not work.
But now we get onto October see
It's kind of ground
I think October 6th is a really big day for Alec
Nephew
But
If the musical
It's going to go away better than the Spider-Man free shows on Broadway
The undoubtedly
I will get to he's in a weird place and then something
But he's mad about guns
White people
Anyways I want zero gun laws
Doesn't track we have a pretty clear statement of his position
Viva vegan
No gun law everybody gets everybody
Are we check government program that gives everybody
Absolutely
Serious about that about that
Okay new pet
Everybody can have a gun
No gun laws
But every gun is stamped
Brought to you by Obama
Everybody everybody gets a gun
You just have to give it to us
We stamp them with with
I'm not into it
Background check
Text chat like that
I don't think it's great just because you know that people can get guns illegally
Doesn't mean you should
Lags all the rules about like
Alright no nuclear proliferation laws
Rogue nations are going to end up getting nuclear-weapons eventually
You know why even try
From getting it
Background check
For that guy who is
Convicted of domestic violence
Multiple times you don't want anybody looking into that because those guys
Main people who kill people
75% of the people
Terrorist attack
You're being bigoted against
That's what the back.
At the end of the day it would save so many more lives if
It was just like looking
Into whether or not
Dude
Unfortunately unfortunately I don't think a lot of those things
Can show up on background check
Convictions that happened for domestic abuse
Incident
Through the roof so unfortunately that might not be effective but yeah I agree
To get a f******
From a breeder
Over breeder
Like
From like a pound or something like that she was giving 50 bucks
I got my cat just showed up and gave him money
So what
Keep one of the eyes
That's why you're Pepsi
Okay so much better than everybody else
With dogs and cats if you go to Humane Society you just give them likes
D-box
To cover the shots
I know what you're trying to say it's also
There's this reason that
Yeah
Like I said in a weird place
He's faking a lot of
Protocol ailments
On this episode
He might be like a kid trying to get out of class
He actually has feelings
The first one where he
He really hams it up
About what he's feeling
This is one today
I mean I know I guess
Because
All this was coming
The old-timers were hundred percent right
But now it's all here
It show
Criminal
If you say it's not drama it's totally
Occupied country
They are
They hate everyone
They are the Pierce come
The corporation
They're going to hurt everyone they hate everybody they are stroking
A lot of a Sienna be like watching some guy with a big pot belly
Peter
800-pound wife
And people on the world Hip-Hop star
I physically get it all
Because they turn people into such scum and nnn people
I physically important
Only physically threatened
You always talking about he's just talking about all the
Videos that he watches of black people beating up white people
Featherstone Worldstar
He's just talking about how scared he is about lightning
That makes him physically ill
It's a nice reveal that he comes to at the end there that that's what's making them feel that way
Guitar
I've had tons of
Contacts that last rough
To speak coherently throughout
On a live broadcast
Comment
Blind Pilot
So all the other stuff is very standard Alex Jones
We just mention that they put her in the vaccines
Stuff like that
Explain danhauer
You can put cancer
Vaccine
No it never really gets into
Do the specifics of it but if you really look into it but the only thing
Think you really can be referencing
I is Vape
Presence of simian virus
I would realize
Some of the cell cultures that they used in
In the preparation
The polio vaccine
Between 1955 and 90
I've accidentally they didn't know this
But it led to a very high rate of mesothelioma
And increase rate of bone
Tumors
That
Was
Statistically
Hire it statistically relevant compared to
Xenon
Right
A lot of times he's really misrepresenting and just talking about
Temple side effects
That are natural or you
It is inflating stiff
In this case what he's doing is talking about
Bad science
Didn't get caught
We didn't know any better
The ended in 1961
So
Told you it ended Dan
That's because
Proto infowarrior
Was around in 1960
51 was it
One of Alex Jones has previously
No
Entire time
Neuroscientist
No somebody found this out
Stop it
A leaker
And then they stopped
Publicly
But this has been Declassified
No there was a study and there's a study 1991
5 a.m.
Anticancer research
Association
That
It's 1999
You know
Set timer
Sometimes they f******
It's
It's not some sort of terrible plot the conclusion of the study
The conclusion of the study that they found is
The data suggests that there may be an in
Increased incidence
I'm certain cancers among the 98 million persons
Exposed
Contaminated
Poliovirus in the United States
Further investigation
The clearly Justified
Even in the studies that they've done
There is no causation
Necessarily that is ascribed
It's probably it looks like this is probably a player
And not in that
So what I'm saying is it's not evil globalist
Science in the fifth
Yeah
Where do you think
Wawa
Super intelligent
Demon
Exactly
Hyper-intelligent
Throwing up because you
You scared what's going to happen to white people
Random is next episode of fakes
But he's going to throw up again
What do you think the American people can do to stop please
Prom queen
I almost threw up
Good morning that bad right now
One time and I went to the CPS meeting and watch the judge
Take the kid from the family for no reason
Ducks shop in chest get worse from here it's so over-the-top
Covert
Alright Nikki and public
That's
That's some real next level
Absolutely
I'm so in this next clip Alex wants to brag about Amanda
He is after faking a panic attack
He's going to throw up
Listen this is genuine
I truly feel this
Listen
This is totally genuine
I really feel these
I filleted don't believe that heals anything
Fear and paranoia
You lies about a fight
And the guy was
Phlebotomist
People on here what you doing down the street
Establishment
I bet you're a little leftist you don't want the right way
I'm more or less
I'm going to walk out of here
Oh I see you're not so tough now you think I'm one of these people been here all day
Let's go
Just looks like
What do I do what I do
I just was telling that story about being really manly and not getting into a fight
Why did I do that he had no idea and then
F****** 10
15-second pause
Skip another break after earlier
Best stories
Not true
I don't have that story
The point of the story I believe
Is that there are people in the world
But he also knows
Kansas Granby and everybody up
He's got to let him know that he will beat them up
Otherwise they'll think that he would
Only want to fight him because
The globalist minions
Power Trip
But the reality is
Then Alex knows
Victims
He doesn't want to beat up victims
Kind of does
I really wanted to beat that guy
Or if you did that story the reality of it is
Very
Yeah yeah
Sounds like Alex
Probably
I would assume
And they were like
Calm down
Get your
You're being really
It's very difficult to have my bar
Yeah
You you and your friend want to come fight me outside I hate your ass
Elsa fight you I'll kick your ass I see you're one of these controllers
You're just drunk drunk
You're drunk your globalist
Alex
I am on the left
But you are further less than 11
Far to the left of me
Where did you get that table on top of a bottle of Jack Daniels
Where'd you get that where'd you get that thing that pours out a shot at a time
Did you get it from a hyper demon
Cyberdemon
Intelligent demon
Technology
Dolphin
Galt
The devil
Deceived the devil every night when he goes to bed
Bulbulay
So yeah that didn't
This next
I'm going to tell you that I only have
A small awareness
But he's talking about
It's very complicated
I didn't have time to look into it
I had enough time to look into it enough to know that he's lying
I'm keeping this in
The show
What a cocky prick
Kia's
And at the end he says
It's very telling
About his beliefs about vaccine
And that's the reason I got to keep it in even though
Camp
Fully unpacked
GnRH for you
Which is
Will get yours down the other side of the Sun
In feral animal population
A similar approach
31-day spur the development of long-term birth control options for human
This looks incredibly promising
William Swanson director animal research
Cincinnati Zoo in Ohio
To get their resources of already response in animals
Dumb gringo
I want to stop right there for a second
This is a anytime he brings of Gardasil you only mentioned
In the context of Hispanic
Which is very weird cuz it works for everybody
Because he's racist
Okay because he wants to use it as a way to take potshots at
Maraza
Because he thinks Our Gang organizations
RH is the thing that he's talking about
Gonadotropins releasing hormone
And they were experimenting with
In terms of being able to
Create sterility and animals bunch more effectively
Just like spaying or neutering
Yeah and also it was
Something that I believe was discussed as a means of birth control
They could be applied to humans
Because
One of the things that they found in the study
Was that it did
Make the animals in
Infertile while their treatments were going on
But then as soon as 9 months after
IV treatments for ceased
All of the animals in the studies regain their
Infertility
Yeah out of 10 were infertile during
I am at 9 months later they were
Just okay
The birth control pill has a
Effective male birth
Great is that to it again it's not perfect and that's why
Hasn't been used
Humans and it hasn't developed for them that it's
It's a study that is interesting but maybe not Apple
And it's not
What I was down says it is
About like I said I don't
I don't fully understand all this
Sauce and I know Alex doesn't either cuz he's just reading off like a daily mail art
So
Anyway
Block
At this is hit GnRH that's when I got
Bio weapon
I've seen the show on other next
Nope trying to get blind
Cuz I only read the first
I only read the first line together hours
Response antibodies
Releasing hormone GnRH required by mammals to turn on the pathway
Trickblox in the first trimester
Inducing dear contraception
Go knock on Heaven show no effectively work
Are both male and female birth control
He doesn't understand any of these things that he saying either completely
He's the blocking of the GnRH it's already you're only use
Using it while you're
Sing
The blocking of the GnRH
This allows
The sperm and egg
From being produced
And from being accessible whatever however you want to put it
So he's been so in the first trimester
No it's
Before
It's before that call TriMet
Misrepresented
Get some how about a portion which it's not
Process
He's not doing a good job defending
He's not doing a good job reading the article
Use a booster shots every few years
Biologist Bruce hay in the California Institute of Technology
GnRH
That win
Interactive Rochelle's oh that sounds like
Turn the muscle cells into Auntie GnRH
That's turn your muscles into cancer
Spell Sparky
Because muscle cells are some of the longest lasting in the body
They continue to search for 10 years
From autoimmune disease
Reproduction not kilkee
We love you so much
We care about you and your family so much
I have to be cynical and evil about the I bet
That right there at the end was the reason I wanted to
Keep it in because he he shows his cards a little bit there
And that he believes that side effects that happen naturally insert
Small subgroup
Are the
Vaccine working
Which is really
Dumb
Insanely.
So I just wanted to
Do that
Childish
Bulshit moves
Cincinnati be like
Dismissed it out of
That's awful
Cuz he doesn't understand what he's talking about he's just
Speculating and saying everything
Autoimmune blah blah blah
And he's misrepresenting like
Science books
He's choosing
One word that he understand
And out of the lungs
Considering that he doesn't
She's playing like
Match this with whatever word you do
How to say words like
He's doing the positive thing but with
Basically is what he's doing there
I mean like
The stuff about
Putting
Stuff inside virus shells and stuff like that that's
Pretty common
No that's how you do
Yeah that's not that's not out there any hole
Actually understand any of the words involved
Escrowed
At this point
Everything Changes
Up till this point everything is Ban Alex faking illness who's talking about being manly
A couple of really stupid narrative
Coming in
Coming in hot
It's point of the show
Big big time
I have never had a deer in the headlights experience this crazy cuz I really
Drudge
And then he's hiding over there in the shadows right now I'm not kidding
Conspiracy theory
Is over there
Heart attack can you just walk over here behind the stage you're not coming
Stop saying it's
1puglife
Take a note
April Fools
April.
Supposed to go to rebroadcast
Oh my gosh
Alright well I'm not going to be aggressive and turn the lights on over there and in the document
I'm definitely going to have to
Alex is tumescent
That's the weirdest
Like schoolgirl
Wow this is bamboo
7 years ago me and Matt Drudge
With Helen Hunt
And she is taking it and all
That's why I Drudge.
It gets worse Alex's fan Bush it gets worse
Sandra Bullock
Anyways
Maybe
God would that be all right
Oh my God
What I look like Buckley when he walked in
Flabbergast who is that
I tell you
He's got a lot of he's got a lot of class
Anyways I was already super Roundup today I've already had too many DNA for assisted
I'm at the I'm not been drinking
Since last Thursday
And
I don't have any
Recall on tranquilizers
Equalizer.
Because I'm Starstruck right now
I have like
You wasn't there
Guess what
He wasn't there
What
I'm getting used
Avenue just it's believable
Is definitely in the house
Man
Regular Alex was disgusting but
Weird and that like I've been a good boy I haven't drank since Thursday
F****** open microphone
Publix up dude you see at the bars every night like
Haven't drank in 3 days
Too pretty big for me on water
Too many
A worried about the
DNA Force like a a pet pillars
I think of the brain for
Probably what you meant to say
Is just supposed to keep your DNA from untangling
Something's not working
He's in the studio is very rare
During the break
With a mic
Add so he's not on video but he's on my
You give
He gives a bit of an interview and he says I'm really dumb
And we'll get to that in a second
For those of you who don't know drudge is one of the most popular people in the world
With no sarcasm
But much display
Because his website
Is one of the most
Traffic
Internet news aggregators in the world
One of the problems of it
Is that
He is a
Partisan hack
Super
Conservative dill weed
Publishers are not
A lot of them have
Let's say
He was big on that Swiss boat
For truth
Situation with Carrie
I'll be on that I'm either
You just everything anything anti-hillary
Everything anti-clinton
He's been a huge part of because
He came to prominence
As one of the first people reporting to Monica Lewinsky
With Oakland
That's why he broke
International,
But before that
He was just
A guy who ran a gossip
The Drudge Report was just a gossip site
And that
Ethos
Still Remains
Even though he's
Supposedly a hard news
Breaking reports kind
It's still a gossip rag
But for very serious issue
We've seen it brought up over Court Daily Mail
Cuz a lot of
Bulshit
Drudge Report
That doesn't help
Play some nice pop ups
Little Ted every now and again
When we went over the dentist Montgomery investigation
About how much b******* that was
Alex being excited The Drudge was reporting
Not
True so there's one example just from our history
Of him by shooting the bad
Also you super big into it has been
Super baked into the birther
Situation
Upholstered for Joe Arpaio with his birth certificate
No just some of the examples of
Horrible things that use perpetuate
Joe Arpaio
Should be on.
Also
They're pushed me Hillary is sick
Narrative really hard
He also pushed the
Bill Clinton's love child story it's gossip
Except your say and what have you
And I'll say that this first
Clip is about
The only piece of it
That could be
Construed as real
And it's not
Husband and wife
They were going to ban words
Has the left have they gone collectively insane on on a
Kontrolfreek
Bentley
Supreme Court Justice over for me
Which one are you
They've got the votes copyright law out of there
They're going to make it so headlines
Was it Kennedy Court Justice
To my face that it's over
They got the boat, which means forever
How many more moons does sun rises BBC in real life
Horizon soil amount
People to be saying with his attitude I'll get on with my life in my greatness
No you can't
They're claiming you're taking their words this is insane and you had the Justice Stephen Breyer said we need to look at it
He thought some of these other decisions
And the Supreme Court
Decides you cannot have a website with news headlines linking across-the-board
Was it Ruth Bader Ginsburg Alex accidentally
Like nine months a year after this
He's like the conservative one
On an item not saying it's
Scalia
Hello
Clarence.
So I
That's all.
I mean ice
At this point
I mean right now I'm asking that because I I'm afraid of
F****** zombies I watch Game of Thrones earlier
We should check
I think I think what
Maybe
A Supreme Court Justice
Was telling Drudge
What you do is done
Inasmuch as
Call you can't take headline
What you traffic in
Is lying about story
Lake George is really good and it gets a lot of traffic because
Chico's me fine stories
I meant put the manipulative headlines on the link
Boost traffic to the
Two places
Right and it makes it makes for inability to control it because a lot of the time people don't follow the links
Read the stories
And because he misrepresented
I'm so happy
And sometimes it's not outright statements it's the you know
Statement?
We can get around that
Is it the case that
Wonder Alex loves him so much that
Alex's ammo right there
I mean Alex Jones came up with
He came up on drug
Like drudge has been doing this for
For twenty years as long as Alex has been broadcasting
So it's always been
Of Alex's awareness
It's always been a piece of wood
His
What he respects in journalism
If the same way that Andrew
Will Andrew Breitbart
Before he ever started Breitbart
All of this stuff really links back
To Drudge
And his willful misleading people
With
And I would say I don't either
Talk to Clarence Thomas
So I don't know what he actually said to Drudge
And what drug is misrepresenting but I'm guessing the
People's intellectual property will be protected
In a better way
Then what you do with it
You will be able to be sued
Ford
Manipulating people like this
I'm not too worried about that
Cuz I don't want people doing stuff like
It's freedom of speech
But at the same time
Propaganda
Yeah I'm very against propaganda because
We seen the effects of
Just a rule like hey
If their headline is this
Splinter with their head
Bright
That's it
All that all that because that's
Exactly what salve
What time is this
This willingness of
People
To just read a headline and then
Just like Alex saying
You're plenty of time pre-show
I'm only a broadcast
You're talking about it on there
Kill Everybody
Crazy at 9 to 5 job and I read more of it than he did
Write any predates
Well yeah I know
Just
Okay
I want to make sure that work
The reference that are
The thing I want to drive home though is that
George is really the
The central
Spoke in many ways of this week
Because
His his
His Empire and is important
It's the culture have really run
Concurrent paths with Alex Jones Infowars
He's he's been more successful he's much bigger than our
No their contemporaries
Time they have run
Similar paths
Same place as Trump
At the same time Breitbart
The publication
Are direct offshoot
Bright garage
Android
Consistently linked to them which gave them
The platform and the audience
But they never would have had otherwise
He is responsible for mainstreaming and creating and popularizing
So much of this dangerous
Why based
Right-wing media
And beyond that
He's created
An Atmos
Sphere where everyone knows
Baby if you get on drugs
It brings you massive trap
So a lot of people have tailored their approach
In order to
To try and get linked on drugs
Which
Don't f****** keep yourself for a second
If that hasn't informed
How
Mike cernovich goes about his business
Power jack the Soviet goes about his business
They want
Create things that drudge will linked to
As opposed
To creating things that are true
Because they know there's a massive upside in it
And don't think for a f****** second The Drudge doesn't know that
It's all it's all a f******
Manipulation
Media game
That drug is making millions
Because all he has to do
Please keep upkeep
On his very shoddy site where all you have to do is sit down
And write write a note 20 headlines a day that are salacious
4 / the news find things you can misrepresent
You're done
He doesn't do
Do that personally
I don't know what it looks like now but like they've there was a piece I read for my 2011
Him and another dude
Wow yeah because it is the simplest thing in the world to do
Right and I mean he's his it's not like he's
He's putting a lot of grass
Design people to work on
I'm saying negative things about him because I take you to s*******
But at the same time in the same way that I say Alex Jones is a good broadcaster
I want to see
Grudges
Brilliant
Brilliant guy
In terms of picking the stories and presenting
Eat the pudding is in the eating
The fact that
Millions of people go to his website
Everyday
You can't do that if you're not really good
After I believe the term
But I saw some on right that I was he's the best wire editor in the world
Oh yeah that's great that's a great line
Curator of
Things in order to make a specific point
But the point isn't necessarily real
He's had to redact so many fun
Walking things in the past
He's let people down horrible pad
Create
The he's created a lot of that
He's definitely Amplified
That to a level that
If you have somebody who's your Protege go create a site that explains
With Italy makes
Right wing
Propaganda
Italy link to it
To get them more trap
You're a Yeezys like this weird conservative
Kingmaker
It's in the same way that
Those
Energy
Anyting where the Fox News
People
Rodger Ailes
The same thing is true of the drug
You like what you were saying about the Drudge Report
And like like Breitbart
Created Breitbart while still working with drugs
So the whole thing is
Feedback loop
That's exact same thing with the game that Alex Jones plays Lester
Successfully
With sending Mark Dice out to make a video and then reporting on that video
So it is all just
Miss representation of Truth and fact
For specific goal
Specifically
Big picture
Destruction of reality is
Well that's it that's by-product of it
But the destruction of the
It really seems like that's what he's mostly about
Say really really really hate
And I think a part of that is I mean I don't want to bring it down to some like
You're a misogynist if you don't like Hillary but
I generally
Do you think that
Especially back in
In the days
When bill was
There were there was a lot of hatred of Hillary that was just
She's the first lady can't you just get a nice dress on and go to a party
The fact that she actually had an agenda
I mean
Not that other path
First ladies hats
But
She was very vocal
Choose forceful about her opinion
Easy target for the
F****** monsters in the
It's like Newt Gingrich in those
Yeah and I think that a lot of the hatred
Come through that and
From internalized
Misogyny where people are like
Hey
You just let your your husband go bang all the
These people you're a weak woman
It sort of s***
And I think the Judge is a victim of that mentality along with the lies that we've already shown Larry
Nichols Towing
Like all this is in the same ecosystem
Really really f***** up
That all of these people
Are so connected and it's so clear
What they're doing
So let's get to this next clip
With a Drudge
You know what
Beggars of thought
They don't
I have any ideas
Is trying to
Kingsdown
Like Trump isn't doing anything
He's just tearing down everything that Obama
Progressive tax
Is something that they're just
Continuing to
Teardown
What fer
These guys
What Nixon
Really
Is there anything
Things that they
Built
Like Network that's impressive
Ethics and consequences out of it it's pretty impressive
No I don't know
I don't know
Just like in argiope
Government
Nothing ever come up
It seems like everything always
Just goes down for
Or backwards
Yeah
I don't know I can't think of anything right now there's probably something somewhere but who cares
Next clip we get to
To see what
What drugs
Facts about the candidates
Is drag
Any form of success
In the pole is because they
I don't know I'm very pessimistic
I'm very pessimistic
With the dreaded brain
In the in the jar in the Oval Office once known as Hillary Clinton
Who is hypothyroid
Anybody who is 17 years old who is hypothyroid
Ladies and gentlemen
Do it has to be her VP is whether it's Antonio or the other
San Antonio for the other Castro from San Antonio
After seeing NDC giving her a Time
Hillary's back
And she's back for real
Means to you or me what it means to me I got a long history with these people
They play dirty
A civil action
Thought that's very misrepresented
In 1997 The Drudge Report reported that incoming White House assistant Sidney Blumenthal beat his wife
And was covering it up
Read the story the next day and apologized saying that he was given bad information
But Blumenthal filed a 30 million-dollar libel lawsuit against Drudge
After four years Blumenthal drop the lawsuit saying that the suit of costing tens of thousands of dollars in legal
He agreed to pay $2,500 to drudges Los Angeles attorney
Foretravel cost
Claiming The Drudge was quote back
Unlimited fun
From political supporters
Who use tax-exempt Foundation
The individual rights Foundation led by conservative activist David Horowitz
Paid drug is legal fees in the Blumenthal author
A federal judge noted in the judgment
The drudges quote
I'm not a reporter a journalist or a news gatherer
He is as he admits himself simply a purveyor of God
So
Even though there was a bad outcome to that suit and terms of you didn't actually get pain for libel
Is a purveyor of God
Yes
Is legally
Clinton suing him
I think you wanted to say that thing about the Supreme Court
I think that's about it
Etiquette mostly at
Like just showed up
He's just doing a drop in 5 minutes like what's going on
No I think there was something else going on in Austin at the time something by conference or something I don't know
I'm not entirely sure
Michael Savage
The show around that time
I think he's just trying to get to
Get stories out
To demonize people
And scare people into falling in line with the right
Hypothyroid
Brain in a jar
It's not even scary as his lies about the Supreme Court
Isn't that a fish song
I was thinking more Futurama
I was going to I was going I'm happy with
The president
If Nixon can come back to become
Futurama I think Hillary has a shot
Meant to scare
Conservatives is the idea that the
The out of
Control liberal Supreme Court is going to Outlaw even the ability to
To publish a headline
It's all part of this
Internationalism
He's walking on the globalist ip2
Like for real
He spends about 5 minutes of this time
But he's on
Just being like Alex you are the best
I love you
You get it
Yeah of course he's on
Globalist
But you asked
The beginning of the clip
Is he on Trump and no he's not
This point
Or at least he's not expressing that on Alex's show
I don't think I don't think the marching orders have been given out clearly from Russia
For all these people to fall in line
And sports
That's kind of depends what I'm getting at this
Pretty much
And we get like
We just saw today
Daily Stormer got taken offline
Apricot hacked by anonymous
What a shock
Yeah
Russians really love suck
It goes back to that stuff that we were talking about when we went over the interview book that he put out the talked about
The way to subvert a country
Especially America is to support any Fringe
Groups specially racist
Extremist
And that's clearly what's being done
Bucking obvious
I'll be
All these assholes
They were they were primed for it of their own volition
I'm not saying that it's in trap
Matter anything like that I don't think that Russia made them do something
They didn't want to do or blackmailed them or anything like that they were already ready
Need to do it and they got tricked
Tricked by Propaganda cuz they're propagandist
Comes out
The truth and so
Anybody who agrees with
There's an added piece to it
That's how you move a propagandist in the direction you want them to go by adding ly
Absolutely so here is another
Here's the other thing
That I think garage was there to do
Is there scare people
So why this next
Is really weird
There's so much going on world
Obama now is talking about Australia
As pundits to say let's just take him
If they really come out in the frontal assault on Gunn
It means I think they're trying to start a civil war
It just seems like insanity I mean they may
Well cuz they're all armed
Themselves they don't have to worry about challenge Hillary Secret Service
Your secret service dismiss them
Security around you
Hillary
I dare you
Take your secret service away Obama
Take It All Away leave the White House unguarded Obama
Obama
What would happen in 30 seconds
Both of those people would no longer be on planet Earth
To drop drop our security measures
For what
This thing is very real and I don't see how it's being taken seriously
Except for the sick
You can't underestimate the sickness of the American people right now
But what you were confused
So
His point
Clinton
For Obama
Security detail
Would murder them
And he's probably
One of them
Isn't he saying that basically
If the live didn't have any protection
The Wrightwood murder
Yeah that's kind of exactly what I hear them saying and I'm confused as to why he thinks that makes him in the
The subtext of what he saying but he is also using this
The Second Amendment
Do something
I'm just saying that the people who love the Second Amendment
Notoriously violent
The thing
The thing there too is more the
Canard
Obama wants
To take your gun
I'm so they think that a reasonable argument against that is you have guards
You have guards protecting you
So why are you saying that I can't protect myself
And the problem with that logic is no one is saying you can't protect yourself
They're just saying
Victor
We should I get background checks for weapons
I don't
Get it I understand
We've been over this
I support people
Rights to have guns
Right
I can see every piece of evidence that Alex Jones brings up
In terms of the fears about people taking their guns
I look into them in they're not accurate they're not true
This Lion of like
You want me to put down my gun but you have guards
It falls so flat it's so
Defensive
It's so
Built on nothing
Yeah
I don't know what else
I mean
There though is
Imagine afraid of
When
We're just like Halo
What time's the background
Like what would they think was happening if we actually did come take their guns
Well I think we will never know that we will never know because that's not good
Of course not
Do you know what it's like
Steve threat
Of Obama
Saying like you know we should have background checks
It's waiting.
Some stuff like that
In order to cut down on raids killing
Things and stuff like that domestic
Situation
I'm getting out of control
Go buy a gun and kill your wife and next
Let's see if we can find ways
To respect people Second Amendment right
But at the same time make the world safer
Cut down on rash violin
All I hear is take away my gun and they react
To the point where
It's for the next like 3 days tries to start a hashtag disarm Obamacare
Campaign tries to get a medium out there
The reaction that most people have two literal Nazis Gathering
They're like
Calm down
Bad guys are both sides you don't know what's in the
It's utter lunacy the reaction
The perceived threat as opposed to reasonable reaction to realtor
Right that's the threat you would respond like that to the threat
We're making
All black
People in Judaism
You should get the f*** out
I don't understand why you don't think
Like
I have every right
You believe that everybody but me
And people who look like
Break even an episode we're not going to release their the we had a clip of Millie Weaver who was there in Charlottesville
Is there a lot of them or just White
And Alex and Alex responding an agreement like that's not okay
You're if that's where you're at
You need to you need to look at
31 Moore clip of Drudge
Look around you if you're surrounded by Nazis
A little bit of information
Before we listen to
On the next day's show
Is furious
That everyone is reporting
That you had a weird with Matt Drudge
So far time is a flat circle
You're running out of time
But I'm
Time is Olive
We are all time
Don't say that you can do tomorrow
Time is a flat circle we're running out of Hillary's ahead of a jar
The Supreme Court has told us
We can't use headline
Pretty weird
Listen to this next clip
I think it justifies why anybody would think that this interview was f****** weird as s***
Cuz this is dumb
Well I'll say this week until name for start coming up
Was
Designed to be confused with their Eliza
Was the Enemy at the time
ResCare most likely
You get the depositions going you get the president under oath
You fight with a chain
Most likely
Boehner decided we're going there
Those Cities Burn
We're not going to do it
Aisa
Isis
To be confused with their license
You know these words
House
So he can't even keep it
It's Islamic State in Iraq and Syria
ORS or if you're confused about the isoparts Islamic
Iraq and the Levant
So I mean it's all.
All of the name
Vets
That's like
It's like a weird
Wait so you know the collective Batman
That's what does 60s
Yellow
Yellow is a lot
Melo Melo
Carmelo Anthony will be going to the next like that's just made-up nonsense
Stupid obviously
Like what happened with the pinto
What the f***
But the other thing is I think that he couldn't even keep a straight face while saying it cuz he knows I'm full of shity
I think that he's
Obviously just spitballing nonsense
I think that he want the audience to think he's not
But he is so
Like he's above the Joker
I think that
I think that he's tricking Alex up
Believe in 5 minutes flattering him as lip service in order to make sure that
Alex
I'm in spreads nonsense like a there Lysa
Is Bruce demonized by ISIS
Is demonizing
Aisa
So then Obama's like hey
Where was The Writers Workshop
Cuz I could have done better
This is evidence that he does not have a big staff
Is just he's running on field
So that's that's about it for the 6
That they called
Darrell Issa
Make fun of Darrell
I thought the Darrell Hammond was named Johanna
With me
Hammond Indiana
I love you tell you I could do this all day
Good but let's not bring this to the end of
Legit no development
Pasta where we were in terms of his opinion store Trump
But I do believe that we're starting to see the forces come together
It weird
Comes on cuz it is rare pokes his little
F****** head out of his Miami condo
Gives interviews that's very strange
So it's a pretty big deal
I think there's consolidation that we're seeing
And on the heels of
Alex is very clear pro-russia pro-putin
Stances that he was making
In the days just
For this
I see I see trouble I see trouble
No definitive conclusions
But I see trouble
It's going to happen
To beat we're going to have to find
When we find the day
We're going to have to cross-reference it with
It's something else going
Find the day I might not be able to record for a week or so
And just
Dance around like a lunatic pour over everything from before that figure out
Like exactly what was going on with all the players involved
Find out what happened on Drudge Report the days before Rodger Stone
Find out what Trump has said
I very like read all of his
Appearances from the days before that
Cuz there's something I mean
I'm at the point where I don't believe
That he just decides who likes Trump
And I don't believe it's coincidence
At all
Not anymore
No I thought
Let's not make any rash conclusions
Of course the Russian narrative is
Because it's happening
Concurrently with the present where there's
The Mueller investigation
All of these
Going on like my first thought is
Of course
We are going to be more likely
Play the sea Russia ever
Right even when we're going
But God dammit this whole thing
Coming on
Resin and
Yeah yeah yeah
I've kept a running
I mailed it to have influenced
I nailed it
I agree with you and I believe
We've done
As best we can to push back again
Willy-nilly jumping in
To that conclusion
And like I said I think that there's something going on and it doesn't necessarily mean
Oggi's
Bentofu
But it's clear that he likes Buddha
Before he likes Trump
Anybody else
And that's not nothing
Helix
Ram's Horn
Seems like it
That seems like
You know what I like more than Rand Paul
Or website
Noteflight.com
Are you check that out we have links
To stop with a lot of
Things on there also there's a button
The support the show
Can give us us money
We would appreciate it
You and you can
Jerry Michael Williams
Backing up
London
The great Michael
Exactly
That rival Spaceballs
Cash register
Which will be opened if you donate your show
White liquid fabric
These chop
Also you can follow us on Twitter at knowledge underscore fight
Knowledge
Listen to it
Tell everybody
Do you know
Tell the people
Hopefully you can find us on
Facebook
You can check us out there
Beyond that I don't know what else we got
The world is a
Massive nonsense and violence right now
Pikachu
Would never come out of the mouth of a John Rappaport I'll tell you that right now
Time is the flats
You think the John Rappaport speak to that poetically
We've already got the CIA
Sorry
That makes me so angry
Alexandra Thurston color