Alexandra Thurston color
Bricknowlogy beverages
Drones
Maybe maybe a lot
Is there a reason people would listen to that other than just liked
Two dudes
Hatred of Alex Bell
No
There is to know about Alec
The show was just we don't know if neither of us have any idea what's up with him
No it's neither of those thing I know a lot about Alex Jones
We are going to
To be doing
Stated time travel episode
Cuz
Donator has requested
Us not to do so so we get to take a break from our normal rigmarole bulshit
And get into the good stuff
Phuc yea
Take a second to talk a little bit about the events that have
Transpired
I in the world of Alex Jones
Since we last recorded
Not sure why
A video went viral
Fantastic debate last night you and I
About whether or not
That was real
Then a lot of people seem to think it was
My position on it is it's
The argument the people have that it was fake is that a guy
Ends up throwing the coffee on
Is a wrestler
Is not enough to convince me
Not at all
Thrill is because
Empire video
He is trying to pick fights with strangers on
Someone throwing coffee on him is kind of a reasonable outcome
Further
And
If he is a wrestling promoter that
Could mean that he's hired to
To do that or could just mean
He's the type of guy who
Willing to start some
He's a weirdo
Possible
Play it up as he got hit with like
Fiery hot coffee
So it's either boiling hot coffee
Adrenaline is so jacked up
From like
I know I'm going to try and pick a fight with
With the stranger
Bored
It was tepid coffee
He's the guy from us play
I don't encourage people to assault Alex
I think I still think it's funny
But I don't think it's the right things
To do
Is much better
Construct is b******* world
How I would respond
We haven't
We don't have enough information
Vision yet to confirm
Nor deny whether or not
So I am going to give a
But you can do that if you want but we're holding off on it
Condition
Hopefully he's not fake
Call Mary mobile
Just to make sure that his name is out there it is
Yeah it's gotten out there
We don't have a scoop
Do I'd like to give an updated policy
For someone who has donated
Donate generously
He has request
If you want
Not even foreign policy walk at all
Level of policy wonk
Might be you're officially a
Protocol one
Thank you very much for donating you can go
There we go now
The business
We are going to
To be going over
Episode
Of Alex Jones
This show from January 7th
Because
We got a new policy walk who donated on the time-travel level
I like to give a shout out to him
So Charles got in touch with me it is
To cover a specific app
Episodes but felt it was a long shot
Because it isn't 2011 it sort of outside of the
The database that I'm pulling from
Yes I did
String
Doug Ducey
Deep-diving
I don't know
YouTube
Some poorly labeled
Episodes
And I found this episode
God I did cuz this s*** is wild
He's at all what happens
But you're going to love this ride
You know it's the
The beginning of the year
Everything is good
Coming around the Sun
The Earth has survived
Looking in
See what was going on in the world
At that time
What is Alex Smith
It wasn't a big news big news day around
One of his primary narrative
Is about supposed bombing
They took place in
The day before
Supposed cuz I looked it up I found an article about it
From the article
A message
Incendiary devices that were mailed to
To Maryland State office
You complained about Homeland Security roadside
Estate
According to a government official with access to information on the investigation
Maryland employees suffered slightly burned fingers when they open
Packages containing devices
That set off a flash of fire smoke and sulfur
Zoe
It's f***** up
Because they were being sent
Martin O'Malley's office was one of them
Directions to the Maryland Department
Transportation office
So it is backed up
People are sending
Maybe offensive thing
But in the end it wasn't a big deal cuz they were poorly constructed and they ended up just slightly burning
Zoo
It's not the biggest deal in the world
The full-on bomb or was it like
The guy was sending
Was it was it like
Shootout bang here's what I would say about that
If someone were trying to
Descend
Aunt bomb
It would be counterproductive to include
Because that would
Soap
Tumi
It was kind of a flashback
Tension
A company is at
I don't think it's necessarily the biggest deal in the world
He was angry about signs
Here's a quote from the note
Report
Suspicious activity total b*******
You've created a self-fulfilling prophecy
Please man but like to see something say something say
Sovereign citizen
Alex
We got to
Little bit of a take on this
About whether or not it's fake
Kathy's dealing with
Yeah
Huge bong
He's dealing with it in presenting it as like this
Is
Very serious
As opposed
To flashback
Give
Has too many whistleblowers
.
And that's the real Mark of this
Housing almost no news on this
I'm going to step in
That
Attacks
Real terror attacks
Like a dinosaur
Police
And have tried to release it
So Alex is
If you want to parse what he's saying there
He think there's not a lot of media attention being given to this
And the reason for that is one of two things
Either
Very helpful
There's a 90% chance that either real or fake
There's something entirely new probably space
I don't I don't
Schrodinger's cat that other 10% means
It could be both same time absolutely
So
Just a good sense of like
His analytical skills
His career
Which is great I love it he's been on the air for like 17 years ago
I'm a bath
She's got is
And weird language
Truism
But
Luke most of this episode is pretty weak
It's pretty soft
Like I would say
Two-thirds of the episode
Is
Entirely ignorable
And that the other third
Is outrageously amazing
Covering a ton of stuff
He breaks down how like
Is admitting the fluoride bad for you
To talk about
Carnival
But
This is super fast
Because the
These episodes
Are full episode
They don't have the commercials taken out
Like the rebroadcast
Dude that I
Okay
To hear what he was advertising in 2011
Before he
He got really successful
Because now
All his commercials are for basically just his product
But in 2011
He was still working on
2 pecan Ave
Oh s***
Super f***** up
And here is the first one
Wild
Introducing electronic cigarettes
There's no flame no secondhand smoke
Commercial
There's a new way to smoke
First of all starting a commercial with smoke
Sol Vape
Brandy cigarette
Commercial
Cuz we never lied.
Commercial is where we're starting commercial stuff
I'm so blown away by this commercial
Episode Alex wants to celebrities a little bit
Here's his take on somebody
Some names were going to record
So I'm he's lying
Does he does he give it a week research Texas long as it takes
Really were talking about 30 to 45
Slime
But
Back then
That's a pretty restrained version of Alec
True now I don't think Brad Pitt is a fan
I don't think so I don't know
Put it on Sandra Bullock
Call Bell
Surprising
To me though.
To hear like
Nowadays modern Alex
Would be talking about Angelina Jolie drinking blood in ritual
The fact that he's like
Illuminati movies
Like that's
Crazy
Talking about
Mr. and mrs. Smith whenever they finally got
Ring 11
I think it's because
You heading up like you an issue
Baps to Irvine
A river runs through
Right possibly
Not good I made a real big deal out of how much I loved 7 years in
Tibet when I was younger
I don't know if I stand by that Proclamation
I remember being
Pretty good what's the one where he's on the ship after he gets them really really long hair
No no no it's not
Another commercial
Anonymously
Dot-com
Define compare Realtors anonymously
Do that
Well 14 like something he would say
But it would be about
It wouldn't be for like
Do you know
75 bucks or whatever
Do you know what I think he missed his calling
He's good if you didn't have the baggage of having listened
Hunter the voices glass
Sugar instantly clicks into my head bigotry
Soho
Home game.com
I looked into this a little bit
We're living in now
Perfect
I've booked into the protocols of the Elders of Zion
It makes me what it is is a website where they have a bunch of Realtors who are paying for their service
To be linked up with
People
To get
Leaves and
Propose
People
Give their experiences by product
Stop
Is it
I know that's what you think
A lot of the responses are
Home games.com is a waste
Sometime I received a lot of fake emails I do not recommend
Anyone using the service
Here's another one
I have had home game for 3 months
I've done
6 quote-unquote proposal
Weather the prospect
4info
Not one has even opened my
Proposal
Rejected it
Never even even open
I think it's a way
That's pretty much the trend of
Alex Jones is just Hawking weirdo scam product
Yeah Alec Baldwin
Be happy with the web
Website
Vapes
Damn home owner home
What is the weather supposed to be
Ritsuko Realtors
Realtors who signed into
Use their service
A house or supposed
Go to home game
To be matched with these Realtors
Who are paying
Of whatever
The service
Extremity
Who's running home
I don't know
Venture capitalist
Vince Venture scam artist
But I would assume
Who's on the show
The other is Charlie is
Naughty real name
Apparently
White House
Charlotte Charlotte
Charlotte iserbyt
So one of the things that she wants to talk about is that
Intentionally Reagan was dumbing-down the school
Debatable
Everyone is a globalist
Just basically
Her conception
She wants to talk about the group called The
The council for on National Power
Which Alex believe she is going
Boson
The show as being the right-wing version of the Council on Foreign Relations
Okay
Getting the
The dark side to our lights
Very much so Alex
Trying to push her down that aisle
Desert
How'd you goes off in Aldi's
Bizarre directions
VeggieTales a long story about how
To get every buddy
CMP and every Republican
Congressperson
Politician
Do I join her to get out of the UN
And no one responded to her and that proves that they're all globalist
It's while
Is herpes
Yes
Dew point
Congratulate yourself
If it's not a real date clips
Cuz she keeps order going down weird path
Screw in 2011
Rodger now
Have to do.
Train right now
Play the Soviet Union
Crazy
This is the 20th anniversary of the Soviet Union
That in 2011
Edward merging with the Soviet Union
V
Secret Cove
Yeah which we all know did not
Gotcha
She's she's out there she's Wild
I swear
I don't know
She's not it
I don't have any
She's ever been on Infowars
Episode
I think Alex would prefer to
Pretend he doesn't know sheet
Best Buy
Cuz it exposes a lot of host
But
Isaac
We need
8 like Nora Ephron
You should get those
Two together like
What is it
You got hey
Like
There we go
I'm sorry I can't hear you over the Executive
I don't think it's there there cuz Kerry Cassidy I don't think that she is a hateful person I think
I am maybe she is I just don't have enough information
Alex is Sophie
Callahan
Cassidy
Do you want Cassidy dammit I can't I couldn't remember if it was Kerry Cassidy or
The Alex Jones
Is
Not afraid
Really make
Clear
That he is a front for a goal.
In-N-Out now being like well he doesn't talk about it
Ever now
He doesn't talk about what
DC and the Genesis
Communications Network
He doesn't talk about how Midas resources
Is owned by the same company that
Sindicate to show
Gcn
Right never talked
You needed to hide
Nearly as much
And on this show they have a straight-up
Commercial for Midas
Important
Specialist
Postal Services
This detailed report will provide you with
If you read the report
Get the facts
What is it
Play that number
Free Walking Liberty silver half-dollar so what are you waiting for get the fax and called Midas resources
Toll-free at 8
And remember
Let's see if this is still an operating phone number
You better remember to say your on the
This is freaking me out
Are you a business pick up
Saturday I don't know what's right off of that
This is going nowhere
And what are we going to do we want silver
I just want to see if a number with your real I also will I know his voice
And automated
So he has his own
Message
Alex
Really thought about that commercial and what it was illustrative
There is there's
Basically because it's
To retard
50 Cent
Kind of
10 CDs for a penny operation
I theme
It seems good but is a scam
I still owe those people like 7
$7,000
I probably do
But the good news is that we were doing it when we were like 12
Select on 12th
You can't find a contractor or anything like that
But
Be that as it may
Calls in 2011 than he is now
He clearly has a little bit better attention
But
He gets this call
Exposes him
Terribly
And I don't think you realize
Alex Waterbury
Real quick anyway
And I don't really want to put any more money in the bank through hands I was wondering if you could recommend a good local bank
Local bank
Call Bank in Armada
Research
Looks like
But you can pull up
Texas Top Texas
Which ones are the best customer service
Local credit unions are great
Visual advice
Bulshit
Is it bites with Google it but
This guy is calling
If you believe the things that he professes to believe wouldn't have a
Pretty good under
Understanding of what banks were globalist
And which ones were cool
That's bulshit
And where's that
Loophole scam going on
Of course
I don't like to give people Financial advice
Is b*******
He plays commercials on his show for a gold silver sale operation
Is not fine a
It is life advice
That's fair
Your life by this rule
Buy gold
Constantly talks about like Financial collapse
The dollar is going to go
I believe
Could be interpreted as Finance
I don't know
Leave the financial cyst
Chick-fil-A
Google whether or not the world is going to end about 2 or 3 weeks at the end
Summer of Rage
It's right around it
It's my favorite season
Right before the fall
That's a good one
Because the leaves change
Lottery
Beautiful colors
Just like angry just like Alex
So
Up to this point replacing weird commercials
Super weird
This Mix commercial
Made me blurt laugh at the office
I was sitting there listening to it and everyone stared at me like
But because I was blown away by
I'd first volcano
It is a real thing
I can't believe the problem it's
Purporting to solve his real
It's just layers upon layers of
Volume
Bite down on this one cuz it's that weird
Going through the roof and that means
Powerful Secrets
Make the perfect
Stop
Hi georgia.com
Under any
George waiting outside but don't hide it underneath the park
Seems too good idea given the circumstances but that's cuz you're a fool
You don't understand what I've done
Look if you're that good I can maybe you should write another book that says
How to hide your book from people trying to shut it down
This is about making weapons
About like
Noah shirts
Is legally dicey
Don't hide them
In your underwear
Don't do that
No
Hide it in the zoo
So why stay on the topic
While we're on the topic of gun
Fun stuff I wanted to
To bring this up
I just saw an article that came out of Stanford study
Just came out
Alex always talks about how more guns
People more safe
It's a philosophy that people on the right really believe in they believe it's that good guy with a gun
Sort of mentality of course
And
How's Revis off
States with right to carry concealed handgun laws
Experience
Increases and violent crime
To Stanford scholar
Stanford law school professor
You found the states that adopted right to carry laws
Have experience
To 15%
Violent crime
In the Ten Years After in a
When over f****** data for a deck
Information
Be found
And compared them to
Right to carry
Have you found
Entirely
Well Countrywide crime has been going
Has been going down
So
If you see a long increase
You're f****** up percent
Increase
That's a 10%
On top of
Decrease
20%
That comes from this analysis
That's fine
Let's just illustrative
Mythology that RG
4shared
AIDS from Stanford
Liberal bass Samurai
Of course
Take your guns away. Even though I acknowledge that that is entirely true
I still don't think that people should ever go
I just want to be clear
In case there are any Alex Jones
They know how to hide them
I also like violent criminals
Coming for your guns because gun prices are so hot I like that that's the presentation of it it's not that like
The government is coming violent criminals who are just like
I wish I could
You get a gun but I can't afford 130 bucks off
Can't afford it I got to go commit a peony
But yeah
That commercial
Now I want you to I want you to know looking for a gun
Why would you go to summer
House has a lot of guns
That's just bad at that's just a bad idea cuz generally you can assume that they haven't read the
Facebook
Do no not every gun owner knows where to hide gun
So they're just going to have it in a safe
Or something
Very good
As weird as that is
There's another commercial coming up that
Even weirder
A lot
Call wants to tell you about a superpower that we do not know the globalist
Alright
Yeah
I mean
What kind of deal they can actually control
And stuff like that you know things that happened
Around volcanoes with a lot of these
You know
Poisonous gases infused fumigate from or whatever these volcanoes in a lot of wildlife starts dying off
Call line
So go both can control volcanoes
Understand
What exactly
I know I know a lot of wildlife around volcanoes
Houses that are really
But the globalists are causing
To be released
I don't understand what you don't understand
Also who is who's killing all the
Top of the Rock
Because the dove is
And they cannot handle that I'm just
Eliezer
Spitballing
Like maybe that's what they're doing
People can't even get any information about volcanoes.
I don't know probably
He still thinks the volcanoes are made of paper
The globalist just taught the Earth that's how they talk
You're dumb
Nobody's more of a snowflake
Always
Everything
Culture
Olive Garden
PCH least a pyroclastic
These commercials are f***** up but they're also on some level strategic
Navigate talks about the economy falling apart and
Commercials
On this episode
He talks a lot about how
The government is
For you because
There was a
Somebody came out where
People were trying to push
Lowering the amount of fluoride.
Send the public drinking water
Alex
To be like
We now know it's bad
But the reality
Of any
So a little bit of fluoride is not really all that
From all the research I've done
But
Not
Doesn't matter how much it take
It's always good to know that
Always good for audio evidence
Good stuff
Take it all should not eat on hamburgers
We know that
Bone broth
Come on
Like I said
Taste like chocolate according to Millie Weaver
Play one episode about fluoride
This message
Realtors.com
Do cyclists absolutely free
Fluoride
$50
There's the emergency
Crumbling
Fluoride in that
42nd commercial like four times
Make
But the reason that
There's a cowardliness on Alex
Who's part is that there is a plausible deniability argument
Yeah of course I advertised for this because
All of this stuff
The solution to
Which is not true
He wants to make the money
And his narrative
What products
Give him money
Filter fluoride
So I don't know why
A lot of those systems are charcoal
It's like the water runs through like charcoal beads or whatever in heavy metal
Absorbed by the charcoal
I don't know I don't know it's fully and I don't
I don't know what big Berkey is up to but I will tell you I know
She's up to
Crushing small Berkey
Starbucks
Big Berkey
Alex still sells water filtration
But they're not big Berkey
Like he has
The all of these products
A lot
That's not around anymore
Vapor Galaxy
With the yelling
Let's make that
How can we make vaping more annoying
Salt Lake
Because I
That's that's not going to set the world on fire
I think that what
He does
Has done
Is he has these products
Like the water filtration
And he's not making a good enough margin on it
Another company that's a little bit easier to exploit
A pushes harder
And get the better profit
With whatever
I think that's probably
Or I guess
Get the name
Of course they
Her name is Big Bird the interview
Various
But before we do we got one more commercial
Advice
Nuts
This is so crazy
I like it
But it's
Did this also made me Boardwalk
Diamond
Map turtle
Against
America today
Is awesome
But I should tell you that diamond gusset is a jean company
They self
I'm looking it up as we
We speak
Course you have open
Gossett
No
Arkansas
I love love songs
Here's a review from SP
I'm looking for a fact
A f
Not female Factory male Fear Factory
I like the
If you order online company is zero customer service
They're incapable of providing for Creek
Exercise
Manufacturing
All sizing Is Random
I have.
Their slogan is good luck lose weight
I've ordered multiple are the correct size
Mark 35-3-36
38 or 37
Seems to be random
They also refused to Hansel like pants
To get you the correct size
So basically this company is incapable of providing the correct
To the customer
I don't know but I also take
I love this place
There's another one from Eric
Not the guide
What about Rock Hill
Received
I love this place so much
It's my favorite thing they don't even provide return shipping now I get to pay $13 to return the pants they charge
I will never waste my money here again
You shouldn't either
Why would you give the pants to somebody else instead of waist 30
Dollars
Cortez customer service
Ordered three pairs of genes although really wanted a pair of their Defender G
They did not have my size in comprender so I ordered their Orange County Jean
But I made a request in the notes section that Arie
Really want the defender not the Orange County I have to take it make an adjustment
Received the jeans but never heard from them regarding my request
Then within 10 days they advertise
Well it so happened that all three pairs that I ordered were now on sale
I called them and asked if they would refund the difference between what
They said they cannot do that
I will return the order and get my money refunded for the whole order
Lost because of customer service
By the way
They refund the difference
This is one of the
They have grown like they have
God I love God
Everything
From Diamond gusset
Serve.com from now on
Hard to believe
Keep in mind I have a cycle on my washing machine the customer service representative
Discernible
Informed me that they haven't never
That is
Forever meaning in the entire company history including the time this person probably didn't work there
After watching amazing this is possible
And the person is work there as long to know this
And they would look
At my expense
30-day guarantee on the website is a complete lie
Chicken look up
This is
Bisra Benjamin not Benjamin Button
I wouldn't recommend Diamond gusset they lost my order and kept me on the phone for 20 minutes to figure out what happen
Weather in American company
Batman's
They need to get organized
I love it
God
That's amazing.
Still in bed
Let's be on
If they move their Factory down south
Maybe they make a higher-quality product
Maybe they're suffering from American manufacturer
I don't know
But that song
Is a banger
Alright
So here we go
I do want
CD and t-shirt
Diamond gusset
America
So here we go we're getting into it
Now
Everything is going to be
Insanity
History
No it's not random it's just
Bizarre
In 2011
But
Every week
On Friday
Do you have a guy named Bob chapek
Come on the show
Google search
Man killed in exactly
We figured it out
So he's apparently on every week and he is a Republican
Involved with Reagan
Gubernatorial
That he was involved in World News
Insight
And what have you
We just had this interview with Charlotte
And about how
Reagan wanted to dumb down
Schools
Probably
The CMP
Is full of globalist
She wants to get out of no one
I think she said some bad things about Phyllis Schlafly
Metallica
Cannot stand for
A big slap Leafly
Plant
Slightly flawed
What's a good dessert chapli fan
The first interview as a single
Instagram
They probably f****** fit when they
Alex is having this interview and
Bob
The phone
He's been on hold for like 5 minutes
When are they go to him
Because the interview with Charlotte rampling
To get Bob
On the things
The cheese saying about Reagan
His
First-hand knowledge
Wild
I was involved
In the
A good material
Ronald Reagan was in
And I know a great deal about him
A lot of reasons
And I know a lot of things that
I'll never say on radio
Because it got me killed
Really looking for me
There's no way it's going to be
Alex
Vet your guess
You know this is going to be a nightmare
You think you think it's
It might be
Conception of what is about to happen
Okay he's got some right
Stuff that he'll never say on the radio but he's about to say it on the radio
Cuz Alex
Huge scoop
Videos bullied his weekly guess
Into divulging
Get ready for it
Because
It is going to shock
Okay Mike down
This is going to be shocking
Reagan was a homosexual
During the late 1930s and early 40s
He was making
What we would call today pro-communist peaches
It all goes in
It was part of the reason
Dad he had as many roles as they had
The movies because he really wasn't a very good actor you was doing sexual favors in Hollywood
The Reagan wasn't
Actor Arya
Are you kidding me how do you say
He was the Bruce Campbell of his time so the reason I wanted to put the mic down wasn't because I was afraid of that be
Anything like that
How long of a pause
Alligator was at
Was gay
Alex legitimately
Probably thought
To say that
It literally
Be something like
Really
Came
Juicy gossip
Was you like
What do I do
I do
Is there be two till they're on the other line
So you might be asking
Turn yourself at this
How's Bob
What what information
Is he bringing to the
That is not correct
No I can't confirm or deny that but that's not what he's bringing to the Alex Jones Show
Is what Bob has
Information
It just freaks me out the power of that knowledge
Styrofoam
And I was also called
By his girlfriend before he married Nancy
Now this is making me sick
A movie
He's all film film of Reagan and banging a dude
We're going to get two more specifics on that.
I'm fine with what I'm fine with both or either
The game hero
We're going to get to all those details
Cuz Alex
How to deal with it
Because at this point cliff deal with it
Beer
This could get even you and me right now listening
At this point
In 2011 Alex Jones
It's not a fully committed devout
Bigot like his show is not
At this point
The Beyond
The dog whistle hate speech
I think
But how we respond
Is very different than he would now
He would scream about all kinds of s*** and how it proves pedophile Etc
But the fact that he's like
Warming
Rough
Language that I don't like interview like if he was that way
That's everything that's
Tacky
Not necessarily horrible
Kind of more reasonable man worth
Stop at the same time
Because he's not that outright screaming about different people
Straight white Christians we're under attack
Really know how
To deal with
He doesn't know where
You should go with it and so he keeps asking Bob
Questions
Illuminate
Yes
But we'll get to all the details
That you might be curious about as this goes on
I think we should leave a review on Alex Jones's website
About how
If you take all of his
Pills
For a few years
I don't think
You're a smart person
Because you think that there's a review section on Alex website
Bear
Look at Amazon
So now then
It is one that
Hazel eyes that I know of
Didn't do this
And
Another store
Earlier on
No
Germany
Quite frankly I was never in Berlin and it wouldn't let me go to Berlin
No reason to do that
At a private showing
And most of the people here there I didn't even know
By Invitation Only
Was this a group
And dumb
Well that's all
Deborah sorry but I learned before that
Girlfriend
That's right
Still alive not
He was probably be
Are late 80s or 90s now
So confused
That
Is my favorite thing
Also
Okay
If I understand this correctly
Goes to his mailbox one day
Gets an RSVP
Absolutely
Female vs male male
Eagles
To this party
Rockville
Have sex with another man
Let's not be too specific about what the film is cuz it.
This point all we know is that the film
How can firms
And at the party
Is a cross-section of
These are the things that we know
You know most of them
Why would this be a party
Beyonce
Theater
Is there a home to properly watch
Baguette really rich
He refuses to say unequivocally
This was an attempt to blackmail him
And he says that it's not accurate to say that it's conservatives who were just
Disgusted
Bizarre
Possible
I watch that
Yet so Alex
Bang
I did Point Alex
Realizes that
He's coming into some of the same issues
In terms of like he's talking
He's hearing a story be told
He doesn't really know this
Specific
What was the tape
Lowriders
Willard Willard
Wilford Brimley
Mustache
Alex asked for more specific
Dangerous
No no
Now
The woman with him
Who used an artificial device
Do what they did
That's not gay
I was trying to call covertly but not by a talent intelligence
Agency
Unbelievable
Reagan like that place
I love
This Alex Jones
This is weird
Unexpected
Awesome
Beverly
Episodes back
Think about how
One of the reasons that I feel so passionately about how much I hate
The current Alex Jones
Is because there is a place for this sort of thing
You still full of s*** you still pushing narratives that are based on lies
A
It is
What's the weirdest thing I heard there was Alex
Given the very reasonable position of
It's downright bordering on sex positive
Strap-on
Easily could have been like
Kind of like
West Coast Circle
Possible
It's funny and it's great
I just hit this
Bums me out just based on
Who is Atman
Watching Reagan
We're not even close
Done with the Bob
Does not make you gay
No not at all
So everybody like the last
Coffee throwing out
We are getting coffee thrown on him
Get picking fights with strangers on the street
Because they don't realize globalists
What's that
It's so depressing
6 gears
That huge of a
Bummer
It really is kind of the same
Course at the Rattata
For everybody
Like Point how many of us
Can actually talk to her parents
Liberals
My parents are strong liberals out there in Austin
Families
Conservative they've always been Republican
Bright
Christianity means
What you do
This level of
Insanity from that
Weird
It came on in degrees
And especially with
The youth I believe
Including up to like 30 year old
Rat
Protecting my own age
I think that a lot of it crept up on people through
Differing
There was a lot of Subs
Refuse like with gamergate stuff
Men's rights activist
Like those
Communities
Became portholes
Two radical
Through
Real rampant distrust
Any liberal
Movement in the liberal ideas
The idea of a
The George Soros is
The trick everyone into
Cultural Marxism
Lego sorts of things
Or implicitly apart of gamergate
As much as
They are so
Based on
Being anti-semite
I am so I think for a lot of people don't think your parents
Necessarily in that bill good but a lot of people
Dvn
Coming
The end result that we have now is not what they
Expected when they started that Pat
They thought it maybe maybe semitism is a little bit out of line
Maybe they are asking for too much
Actually not want equality
I'm fragile male ego that kind of makes sense why someone would get
Not realizing it
Stop there you're going to end up
Being an anti-semite
But you know what it's a clear path
He's a very to the idea that maybe Hitler was just a failed artist
Possible
Like
All it took was Gamers to be like
I don't like
Journalism ethics
Tonight
A gold star for one of his paintings and then we would be fine it's possible but I think the bigger issue
It will be
Park
On looking back
This. Of History
Black mark
History
People especially men
Did not listen
Into women in terms of gamergate
Especially
Stop the fact that people
Turn such a blind eye
Kind of hip to what was going on
But I certainly didn't act out enough
I didn't speak out
But history will show
When they write books
And some people probably already have
Write a maze
You mean the guys who follow Trey Anastasio on tours
I remember reading
What the name of
But
The debate
Interviewing
People after World War
Who are always just
It was a it was those guys over there I heard about those knots
Seaspray we were always
Like everyone is good
Everyone else is terrible
Go to one of those places
And you will see so many
Now who are losing their jobs and all that s***
Know that they were
We were f****** around
It was a joke
Narrative is already even
Complete disaster
The organization in the rally and
In Boston is going on as we record this
Today
Optimism
Trulia beautiful
Do wrong later tonight
You know
They still haven't released the guys who beat the s*** they still haven't
The s*** out of Dion
They are
And they have address
Who's Patricia
Who's the snowflake the hundred
The people who went
To the police station
To say hey
We took down
F******
Bulshit
Confederate statue
Somebody in his
To do anything
F*** the whole whole narrative that the Liberals snowflakes are all that
No
Yeah yeah yeah
It's not hypersensitivity
Something is morally repugnant
You know there's a lot of
Unpack
In terms of
There's a lot of foreign
Issues
Equally repulse
Something we should
Maybe take a look at wheel do a good enough
Job
Uno
Around the world
We focus on Alex and unfortunately that means
Can't talk about how terrible other governments are
Outside of let's arz
And Russia
Turkey
F****** turkey
He-Man
Isn't which one was was
Who was it that was
Plymouth
Flynn was the one who's working for tomorrow
Yeah cuz I was more based out of Ukraine
Can you say that's it
Alex wants
To know when Bob saw the film
Here was this whenever you were shown this film
Late 1970s
Early 1980s
That doesn't Inspire comp
What if it was a late night
Seventies an early night
1880s
Reagan was
Either president or just about to
Yeah
So
Get around around the store
Somebody invited Bob Chapman
Of the president
Yes
I would say
Think of all the positive feelings
Oh I was invited to this
So cool
Happy to watch the
The president getting
Alright
I don't even think they gave him a reach-around
You know what I'm saying
But like
Do you eat the nail kind of on the head I think
With your first piece there that is
Given the timeframe
Sibley important figure
So-vi
Involved
Is like
Only have a decade
Late 70s early 80s
10 years
You would remember
Very clearly
That would definitely that would be my 911 that's for sure
Question the entire credibility of the story
If it was me
And let's say
I get invited to parties
I see Trump getting paid
I remember there was
Two clouds in the sky one bird flu B like he would have
Total Recall
I would still remember exactly
Because he's afraid
Spell whatever
I bet Trump
Olivia's
Who cares
This next clip
Are we getting two more about the nature of the screening
Again
Screaming
Who is Ali
I know already
How did you know
No way no way
Settlements important
They got me there and
I really didn't know what the content was going to be
I don't think so
Yes
How old
Quite frankly can't remember
That's a good question
I would say older
Hahaha
Is there anything else Bob you can hear the frustration
Thought
We're standing on the precipice
I don't know
I don't know what it would be some sort of drug running operation inside information
Stop baby
Well I mean
Involved
Dealing with Nicaragua
Alex
Really like I said
This whole time you just does not know what to do
He's really struggling
To figure out what to judge
Do you have nowhere to put his
Disgust really
Angry public bigot
Breton can't just be like
Clear
This guy is a queer
Have to figure out like
What is it about this story that I'm mad about
Yes
But here we go
As like this
Republican
When I was six years old
But it's not even doing something
Freaky
It's
Trinkets
I know you know all these people
You were friends with
How to compute that
Hollywood ask
Film
Why were you invited to this meeting
Because I was going to do a couple of other people who are invited
No they just said his
A very interesting film
And that you should come and watch it and
I know these people.
And that's what I found out
And they sent to me afterwards well what do you think I said well
I'm surprised that I'm not
And then I told him what I had learned from somebody else he is before
And
No these four people
The ones who I knew who was there who I knew who they were
Very conservative people
But there are other people there I didn't know so
Around 4:11
And
I like him
I am is a very nice person
Apparently
Timmy socialite
That's just the way it turned out and you know
Another southern California for 36 years
He would find out things like that about people
Normally find
I want in Indianapolis Indiana
It was a pretty wild lifestyle in California and New York City
Lot of pagan automatically Southern California well I guess
San Francisco Hillsdale
Beautiful
Los Angeles
Willie
That seems to be where he's Landing
It's bad
The film sex
So he doesn't know what to do here
Weird Hollywood lifestyle
I don't approve of it I'm not condemning it I don't know what a guy and a girl dude spot.
I love
Summary of like
I didn't know it was going to be
My friend said is a very
So we thought and afterwards they asked me what did I do
I thought there was some third act she was like what are you
Right what do you think
Just my opinion but I did not know that
Already has the girlfriend for the pastor's told him this already
My girlfriend
Did the girlfriend didn't tell him
That he was gay the girlfriend said he likes getting picked on evolve time there was no
Differentiation
He probably heard from
From the girlfriend that he likes
Maybe a finger in the ass
Opposed
You just like
Let's get weird
Should have tried it immediately
Tonight right
Yeah
Grow up Bob
Your a****** that turns you
I don't know but fine
Alex is not
Sure what to do
He's judging California but them being like
The Willy like I don't like
Let
Amateur
At this point it does not know what he's
Ian is next clip
He sort of makes clear that
In his defense
That's a weird ass pic to be told
So weird
Now that's a weird
Huge scoop
Conspiracy
Communist could be Bohemian Grove
I did instead
Regularly had on the show just dropped in with life
Reagan gay
Golden
Just drop that I shouldn't be talking about this it'll get us killed or whatever
Even if
Walter Cronkite you're not going to be like
Well I've got a plan for this one
I think
And Alex's shoes I could kind of roll with it
Serious that's true best
Can to ask questions
Isaac
Revealing that Bob
Does not have a good grasp on.
Details
Barring any other
Any invitation to a party that I might get in the future but like
Without employees
I don't believe him
These details don't make sense
The vagueness of
His inability to answer
Pictures that are very simple
When did you see this
Bratz why were you there
It's all just
So vague now I imagine this tape
As being like the room
Play Rocky Horror
Touche
Alex
It kind of shows a little bit of his cards
The real
But he is pretty bummed out
She said Bob that one time that's
Way to go Bob
I don't know I think it was for blackmail
And
I think use politically later
Rainbow Rocks
I really don't know there
It was fine
Republican
Workaround
A superhighway
I don't think so but I do believe have to have a
Yeah at this point H is not development
2011 that was not a piece
Please go to worldview
It's possible that he just doesn't think
He's not as frenetic a broadcaster at this point
But the new information that he has about Reagan
You Don't Have You released
Iowa
I don't care places 202 me
I'm more interested
There were these parties
The people watching
Know that to me is much more
Where do you get
I don't know I think it's probably has come and gone
Anymore
We got screwed
Gcn
Sounds good career
Play engage enough kind of thing
I was very very prevalent in I live there in the 67
How long long time
End of the 90s
And so I ain't I saw Lots I lived in Malibu for years
A lot of time
Beverly Hilton
Play all of Los Angeles pets
Lysol
Lots of people
Nothing surprises me
I don't see how she could not
I have known
It's much easier
The other evidence I had
Something I've talked about in all the years
My personal experience
Beatbox
I thought you were
He was on the edge
Oh man
That is in
Same disappoint
Also I love you
I love
Turn of that
Clip
Alex
They can use animation with black and white
Clips
Maybe it's
Bob's response
So that
I don't matter
I don't have any other
So that's the end of a Alex interviewing Bob
About this
But there's a Cota after he's done still on the phone
It gets really boring
There's no more risk
Is it go up from reggae
You gay
God
So they go to commercial
And then they come back
Browning mobile.
Washington
Bobcat
There's a film scanner
Westside
Homosexual prostitution
Bush
Everybody takes the field trip
Washington's backup for you
Winona weather
I should have said anything that
It sounds like that's just the way it is
Fake laugh
Send a famous a nice guy
But
Everybody has their while many people have pugs Liberties that
Different than others
But
It was quite an experience living for 36 years in Southern California
Moving on
Yeah thanks for your memoirs
Google get me killed
Time does Cowboys handle
Planet is a is a
Since he was like seven
Member
Of Alex
The team for likes
Lego G
Prisonplanet was the original
As I recalled good I believe
DaVita cases prison planet was the original website
Infowars
Oh okay Paul Joseph Watson
Editor-at-large
Boats
Twitter handle
So
I don't know I don't care about him at all
But
It's going to be a great time travel question
What's up if you could go back in time and murder
Watson would you
It'll be the same conversation about Hillary
He's not going to commit
Make him feel less scared of everything
LOL
Seems to motivate Paul Joseph Watson Twitter
Extreme degree
Spear of every
Resume Ronald Reagan and secretive organization
Screening
They don't want people that's what they're going
Let me be clear
I'm going to see Reagan get paid you want to come on with
I asked you would want to crash
Let me
Perfectly
Cordially invite you to
A screening of a video of
LBJ
Getting up eggs
There will be hot dogs
There'll be food and drink
I really want a chili dog right about now where I'm at
If they said you know food and drink will be taken care of
The private sector will be much more likely to go
Interesting film
You should see him down 7 days a week
What you doing go see baby driver
Do you want to go see it no
But I'm not
Arcanine
See you later
I can't see your film of LBJ getting pegged later
I'd like to say
I knew that this was something that had happened
But I did not know the date
Being pinpointed
I was
A great Delight
And this is a real fun
Escape from
Thank you so much
If you'd like to send us back to a particular date
You can do so by going to
No it's right.
Your website
You click the sport the show button
Have you donated
Time travel level
You cannot go back and see what the f***
And also just so you know where website
Yep
That's correct
Samurai
Then go and check us out just knowledge fight
There
You like it when people
Something along those lines
Joseph scoop
That was
The six-year-old Alex Jones scoop
Yeah absolutely twenty-year-old Harper's magazine
Are the Washington forty-year-old Bob Chapman
Yep
So
To make it big on this one
This is
Indeed
Did you know what actually
I did a little bit
Idea of this group of people who are at this deprived
Soiree
I can't figure out
Videos
In preparation
Okay good but I'm not able to test like we've all been watching a lot of tacos
Episode sure
People are
Pornographic episode
I like I like my women over art
Right I cannot figure out who
16 of them are
But I found out
One of the other attendees
Okay
This party watching
Dixon and headaches
Get that pack
All the time
Similar age folk 100% what day is been around the same area
I believe so yeah
Hard to say
He has dentures
Oso
Okay
Alright
I'm making all this up John rapport
Go get pegged
Alexandra Thurston color