Alexandra Thurston color
Dance
I want to engage in the bed but my nose really a shape
As of no energy for trip
Did you know a lot about Alex Jones true
What's the fun
Sourpuss Jordan
Shut up family
Arctic
Thought it was great
It's kind of like a Canfield 50/50
You know that soda
It's good situation is awesome
Other awesome
No it's not weird never doing
We have an announcement to make
Earth-shattering
Is on the evening of
September 9th
Determined
We will be doing our first-ever live show
At at North bar here in Chicago Illinois
It's essential
That you come out
Because
In all honesty
No idea why people listen to
Eoto
Noclip no furthermore
No idea what I'm going to look like live
No I think we're just going to do the show
Will sticking around of the show there probably be some stand-up involved you might do a bitter to
Subway
Party afterward make a night of it it's going to be great time
But the more details will be forthcoming but I wanted to let you know now playing at the
The dance party is the remix
Made of Ludacris
With Alex Jones
I will be okay with that we love our somalis
Songs of course
Please
If you are inclined to come it'll be a good time and we couldn't use all the walks we get there
Chicago
Treatment Argo insulator National hub
Somebody out and have them go about 20 minutes
Ravenna and we'll just have fun maybe maybe limit that
If you need to
Briggs
Delight forever that would be a miserable time
Tinder date
Bring me that's what we should do we should do a policy
C-walk singles
All of our followers
I don't know
I wouldn't phrase it that way
Speaking of people who deserve to breed
Terrible translation
I want to backup out of
New policy walk what's going on out there Manuel
Thank you for joining up
Welcome to the fold Manuel Noriega this one I can confirm
Is the freezing point or sister from way back
Mixed person onboard what's up
Thank you very much for joining up
Oh I thought you were going to go with the R&B sensation
Chinmaya
Ghetto Superstar
Wood
Endorse National Treasure
Not just endorse
You truly Inspire him anyways we are
Howcast laureates
Don't look at me
So also all the time we are grateful for you the person you are and be
You your name
Ewok yourself you may do so by going to knowledge fight.com and clicking Leesport
The show button
Also I'm going back in time on a 2011
That was wonderful time
Find out what else
You could do that there as
You had a butt
He sent to you and you sent me a picture of how terrible I am a mailing things terrible
Put buttons
And you will be pleasantly surprised to find
Taped to ship
Forest envelopes envelopes
Is a nice transition accidentally Exodus out of context drops
Emulator
I mean I would want that to happen
Just don't have her genitals cut off
Hours for shoulders right there
That was just weird
Confuse the hell out of me doing with scissors nearby
Bottles of Superman
Keep scissors away from him
Stubby one
Throw my elementary school
In 2015
Do what the f*** happened to Alex Jones
Back in
To sign up with Donald Trump
We made no progress in terms of Donald Trump
But we did discover that Alex Jones is
Firmly in support of Russia
And Vladimir Putin
Scary
In the last
2 months
Of 2015
He has not changed
Disposition from
I like what Trump says
But I don't trust him
That's what he said for a very long time now
And that's where we begin that's where
At the beginning of today's investigation
Which will cover October
October 11th
He does not trust
Because Trump is
Billionaire
Fronted by
Hey call me
A front for
Consortium of Russia
I was with mob
But
He does
He's not his dad
Absolutely
He doesn't wear a shirt sometime
Amazing picture of Alex
From this last Sunday
In 2017 he broadcasted without a shirt on
Really f***** up
Giselle Wolf Blitzer filters
Wolfis Wolf's like Master roshi from Dragon Ball
Bio-reference mist
Start on October 7th
If you were call
Matt Drudge
In the house
Is that a good portion of the stuff that I cut out
Is Alex Jones replaying
Clips from The Drudge interview
And talking about how important
That he had drugs on him
Is ballet the whole
Timer
Exactly
Is right over here
2 makeup
Paper cutting that out of the episode
Encompasses
Is everything
That Alex really wants to say about drugs
It's chickening how much I like Matt Drudge
Is undoubtedly an
He's helped us more
He's helped the country more
He's done so much good it's sickening
For doing the town for the satellite anyways and TV stations
Under contract
I love the ramshackle it's already happened
Denville New Jersey
Get the phone call
Goddamnit Terry sell college
Is calling
Any positive adjectives he just uses his regular
Appositive
Monsters pedophile
Also Matt Drudge
Who's the coolest person I've ever met that's got to be tough news for
Joe Rogan
Charlie Sheen
Can't think of the other celebrities that hang out without
Be quiet
All the things that judges
Doesn't seem cool
I-don't-want-to-talk-about-it
The Hat
Used to wear that
Fedora hat
Used to be against a very cool
He's rich
It's kind of cool
Condo in Miami
Oh that's super uncool
Supreme Court in the future
What
That was a
Let's go out going all the way back to Will Smith
Wait is that part of wild wild west or does he do more than more than once.
Dog
Dammit
Nothing to mess with
Canfield rip on the strip
Been screaming out where we love to last hit
Alright that was fight live shows
I could also
The entirety of wild wild west acapella
All donations
The body of the show
On the show The First
Cousin interview with
Who is the economy
Zookeeper
Saying that
That's Harvey Dent
You keep saying that
Economic collapse
Which was the company that was involved
Yeah
Dripreport
Oh man
We figured it out his Studio isn't Austin
All right so he's on
A month ago on the show you said that the claps
I'm going to come within days
It did not
Here is his updated
The pope very interesting 11 dimensions
Can we look back at the last major piece which I also call a megaphone pattern higher high
Exit the higher high
East Prospect
I've been playing on your show now.
I'll probably late next year or early 2017
You're a scientist when it comes to economics
We don't obviously know why they come at the pit but that's what I said myself
Outcomes
What's happening
You know this is a time where were
That's pretty interesting theory he has
Two data points that they're drawing from 2008 and 90
Via
I love
You can see their these high
And then there are these Lowe's in
And they keep getting higher at
And lower regulated causing these bubbles
He's like no
If the Pope
It's a bad omen
Very that
School of Economics the people we got to rethink a lot
Freakonomics
They
Made a follow-up call
I believe in statistics
Is known as an
Inadequate
Because
In 1965 Pope Paul the sixth came
The crashing
Came to the United States
7 time
He came in 1979
And 1999
None of this is all of this
None of this is covered
Newborn for half
Benedict 2008
We got that one there
In 2007
He was
He wasn't offering
This time April of 2008
Siri
That's when Nazism
Started
Spreading throughout the United
Possible and this is where really dumb economic theories
Spreading throughout Alex Jones's death
Like I don't understand how anybody
He literally has to datapoint
That's it
This is a graph that I've shown lots of people love
Visual aid
And here's when the pope visited so as we
Also
Balls shrivel up on cows
When the pope is it
They will drink
The balls of your
Dum Dums on his show and allows them to
With these idiotic predict
Keep going
You know why you
Cuz he likes to play that game too
Here is one
Yeah he has equipped the plays about of Obama
And stuff like that
Obama gives
The speech about how
We need to
Tubi
Committed to our principles
People who
Hi
Won't give an inch
About this issue as
Absolutist
Gun safety measures are somehow
An assault on freedom
Communistic
My m
And stay in power for
Trevor something
I mean the crackpot conspiracy theory
Ratified by
Elected officials and the other party
On occasion
Machete wants
Obama
Janelle Gibbs
Global
Works like that
Grandma's how big bang
Tuesday leaders
Here is golden
Admittedly Obama's only been out of office for 8 months
Recording
So we don't know
But
He's not made moves to become the Secretary General of the UN
Unless you ask Larry nickel
Larry Nichols
Shadow um
Set a reminder
By the dark un
I'm sorry I did Skip Along so fast but I
Excited to get to
So I want you to not talk
Because we need to study this
This clip
Is fascinating to me
I had to scroll back and listen
Do it a couple times
Because
Describe it is the anatomy of a bad comedy
Like he's trying to upside funny
Okay his support staff isn't playing along
I'm soaking
He's trying
He's trying to
Get some juice working
And it's not anywhere
This is probably about
2 minutes long
Eddie just bailed
A bail is spectacular
So here we go
Serious news
Actually
Killary
He's not sick
She doesn't have 6 months to live some bugs her
She's fine
In fact this was her just yesterday
And was having some cocktails
Some Prophets
Someone else running for office
But she stood up to him
In a very very dramatic
I will
Filthy rich off all the
I want to come here real quick I didn't plan
Is vaping really hard
Is a video from The Dark Crystal 30 wants to play
Are.
He's like
All right got to keep
Describing what I think will make this funny
Spoiler alert they don't
Play Drake
But even if they had
This is such a long walk
To get there
Workout
Wonderful
Class Warfare
Here you have it ladies and gentlemen
Amazing footage
Incredibles
You're going to
Who's going to have
And other are there that they're marching
She was laying on a couch
Just relaxing her feet
From
Hangouts show on the road
Hahaha
Democratic supporters
The Beautiful People
You can tell the girls
Asurion.com
4 / 0
Let's continue Us Predator
Brown Jug
Audio of Hillary Clinton talking over video from The Dark Crystal
That was just a clip of Hillary Clinton speech
2 minutes
Setup 46
I don't know where
Play the wrong
You're totally right
During the break
Score
Absolutely like me
You didn't look
One thing that I've learned from doing a lot of stand-up
As long as
Do not at all
Like just never happy
That's what was supposed to happen
Gorgeous
Alex Jones
Incapable of
Humorous that's what I'm talkin about
Even if it had gone perfectly it wouldn't have been funny
If you have any chopped
You should be able to try and bring some funny into the middle
Spice it up
Something embarrassing
Hillary isn't
Was I supposed to say
Alex
She's fine
We all know that.
Discussing her successor
She refused
Amazing
Obviously Democrats and Republicans
Class Warfare they'll Eat the Rich
Joe Biden
Yeah why wouldn't because part of Larry Nichols narrative the Joe Biden was is angling to drive to
Open create a caliphate
And be the king of Muslims
Who should be most angry about the
Tragedy
Even they aren't this bad
We commit crime
Yeah we are
You're not a part of bad comedy 31 line we do not cost
So if Alex
The little racist
And then he talked about boots
Which is fun
Always
Get disgusted by
Racial stereotypes and racial comments
And pushed incessantly
Biracial
Nope
And this is a real culture of enslavement
Wow
Anybody who wants to own a company
B b b b b suppress black people
MTV
They're sure pushing all this death culture
University of Pennsylvania professor
Aneesa beutler
Call presidential
Strong
King believable it's not nearly done either
You can't
Rhetoric
Literal
Why would you use that as your comparison in this
Rhetorically
It's dumb
About boots
That are somehow we've been to
Well I mean
You can fly suasticas
You can fly Chinese flags you can fly
McDonald's Flagstaff Easter Bunny
I need
Go to jail
So far
Comedy
It continues give only there was a coon of the Year award Professor Butler
Response to another
Lincoln
Class Warfare
If somebody
Suzanne
Does that mean someone wearing
Punk rock boots
People wearing them
A lot of them
I was in high school I wore all sorts of cowboy boot tennis shoes
Music
Other skaters
Just not knowing what these symbols mean
People parading around
Martin's Indian School
Yeah I got it
Got it all right
Got a phuc
Going to be asked if you're not see
Going to get your ass kicked by skate
Yeah also sorry that there was some jumps there
Problem with my recording I don't know what happened there was a little glitchy
Some sixteen-year-old girls wanted
We got the point of it
Over 150 sixteen-year-old girl
I guess
Having a Confederate flag doesn't make you a ray
Discounting out of whole cloth it's like
Vista set
Of people
Confederate flag
The percentage of that
I'm going to go with 9
Whatever it is
I'm not sure if it's that high but I'm sure
Sure it is
Whatever the number is it statistically relevant
Oh yeah over the general population
In the same way with Doc Martin
Statistically relevant there's more.
You should be judged on those stereotypes
Unless you have
Confederate flag
Today
Proof is on the defendant in that particular
Interest
So
On the last episode
Alex Jones
If he had gone to his head
He was being
Approached by a shooter
He would lie to him and say that he wasn't
Christian
Wildly again scripture
Jesus and the Bible
Very clearly say
It's me or you pretend you don't know me I will pretend I do not know you in front of my father
Is a myth perpetuated by
Certainly least the Columbine watch for sure
This episode
Episode
Caller
What we say
You are way out of line saying
Is really f*****
I can't believe you would say that
Alex is like
Alright
You're right you're right
Sorry sorry
As long as I don't have anything from the call
But in the end is like look I'm so honest
That I'm even honest about my lying
Nice save
But then he says this
Which I think is it
Incredibly telling
This next clip is like something that
I don't think he knows what he's saying
Because he's making
Some of our arguments for us
This is literally off to be weird out of Alex Jones's mouth
Well that's awesome
We get to do this
Of news and information
Wrong
Yep he's right
How your call surgery call
What are the reason
He has that town is he
About music
But I wasn't back to episode
He says that are wrong
I hear a bunch of times but he says things that are you misspeak
All the time
The only difference
Is it he's blaming like I look everybody else would screw up more than me I don't have a teleprompter
I think we screwed up
Weight loss from him
I mean
Actually probably also also this
This game is playing where he's like I misspeak
Stuff like this is actually a really generous version of
Because the truth is that he's lying
It's not that you miss
Legitimately
And intentionally lying about what people
Blur saying
What liberal causes if you are on the right
Red handed in Ally
You will absolutely
There is no way that you'll be like
Oh yeah yeah
My bad no time for introspection dr. Jones
No thank you
The dentist
The CIA
Cuz I was
Does not have a doctor
As opposed
2nd
Who has a
A PhD in
Good trivia
In case you're out of the car
The bike down 45 minutes
There's not a whole lot more in there we need
Need to get to nothing
Squeeze out of that
Chestnut
October 8th
The stretch of time where Alex Jones
Is doing a
Honda of impression
Bombshell
He's trying to put together a real
I think he wants to get on SNL I don't know what's going on
But he does long impression
And this is the first one
I think
It's supposed to be an impression of
How
From space
I think that's supposed to be
We can beat them
Freaked out about in Congress that's why they said
MSNBC
Every week
Discredit yourself Republicans
In 2001 Space Odyssey
Don't do that Captain please stop
Letchworth fish
Really
Want to do that
I tell you you're going to lose you
Are Momo's
Bilderberg
New York
How is your day going I don't know
I just like that at me over just like that
I think that the daisy thing there has to be some
He's trying to give like
A message to the boys back home or something like that I don't know
There's no way
The song
A member of the 88
You don't know who I David Rockefeller
Is it is it
Hopalong my darling Build Me Up Buttercup
Okay
Can you woo woo woo by Jeffrey Osborne
Next clip
Being a f*****-up
Depression
Start a hierarchy of things Alex Jones like
Breaking in this area we learned that Alex Jones like something more than the
He's in the middle of
This is really weird
You doing the top 10 Center
Galveston
Stunning
Kiro
Kanye West and all these stupid stunts
Kanye West is stupid
Is stupid
Game of Thrones
This is the false culture
It's so good
Potbelly pedophile
Stop playing around
I just can't take it anymore
It's so sick
It showed
Degenerate
Guitar
You just have to
Anything else
Never be more clear that you just filling time with random non-sequiturs
From his like catalog of villain
The boy
So that is one part of the hierarchy
I'm guessing you would never reference
Guitarist
This guitar is race pimping
If we find out what Alex Jones likes even more
Then not Randy Rhoads playing guitar
Can live in peace
Either not political
Impala ancient
Judaism
I know all that
Israel's wrong turkeys
America strong
Who's not wrong is Russia
. starting
Respond
I'm not giving up
Do you think that if you just watch Russian
Intellivision
He just wants Russian media you would definitely
I mean you could describe using them as a sort of
You don't have given it up to the goat
Pro-russia umbrella
Which should be
A big red flag for what we know ends up happening
In a few months after this point
Yeah yeah
I don't want to I don't want to pull any sort of like
American Nash
Nationalism
Like that
If you are a politician
Serious right
Debate stage
So earlier he was on the show talking about how the pope is going
To bring an omen
Beforeitsnews
Is going to bring an omen of
To talk a little bit about economic collapse
But he wants to tell you how he
He's right
All the time
Essence back to the show and realize
Is that what he said was
What what's interesting is in this clip he pretends but he's only ever made one
Prediction about financial class which is great
How dare you associate with Alex
Conspiracy
This
A couple years ago
Any
We're just covering
We told you forced inoculations were coming
They haven't
Coming up
Before we go any further
We are offering
Free specials right now
Water filtration systems
To confirm that we no longer have big Berkey in the house
Company
Play Justin the time that we've been covering
Alex Jones has shifted his prediction about economic collapse at least
3 *
It started in the summer
He's pretending that years ago he's like
The collapse is going to come into winter 2015
I guess what
Didn't
So all this is wrong
It's factually wrong this time
It's intellectually dishonest
Reframe to say that
August talking about reality
Really
Horse vaccines are coming
Guns from violin
Criminal
I'll be there in Mesa
Clearon vaccine
But you don't f****** know
On the 8th
On October 8th
We're like I just got forced inoculated
Larry Nichols dropped by the show on October 8th
Details Alex
But she almost died
Because of some shots
The real serious business
Chops don't blame shot
You have lung cancer and in the f****** video that they play with in the documentary
You smoking a cigarette
I don't disagree with that and I'm not judging anyone for their choices
But if you want to talk about
Xvid why to you in terms of health
And you're smoking
Cigarettes with lung cancer
Maybe it's on you baby you are really unhealthy
And I'm drinking
Faygo
IFixit Larry Nichols is probably in the clubhouse for worst dude I've ever heard of
Like even worse than Alex Jones I think Larry Nichols sucks way harder
And we need to call him back
I get some point cuz I
The list of questioning
Questions
Piling up
Yeah
My contacts list
Looks good
Give me a text it's probably a house phone it's probably a house phone we do that
I'm so in this that in his first clip of Larry Nichols
He
Continues the Infowars tradition of making a ship prediction
Phrased delightfully
It's like a down-home
All shucks
It's kind of affliction
Free prediction
Sucks
Kids and everything in it
Remember When
Benjamin Netanyahu
That Obama was setting up
Yeah you don't outside caliphate
Yep
I'm sure as we all know
Sunni and Shiite
Are getting along great
Right now
Team up under Obama
Thunder
Personally led to bombing in murdering so many
Are the the problems with
That 30 seconds of Larry Nichols
He is not a duck at this point and his prediction has not come
HonorBound
To now become a duck
He has been taking a lot of
Duck-billed faces
Human bills on their face
Is to get these bills off of our faces
They're right
I love that unfrozen
In caveman lawyer as
Now your daughter no more guilty than my client
To be a duck
Frozen
Here in Beulah
Now I'm not
Now let me tell you
That we talk
Ferret
Civil non-civil facetory
International asset forfeiture
On this show
He comes
More Muslims
He does this
His big narrative that he's coming to pitch on this episode
Is super weird
Larry Nichols has
Completed his transformation
Not into duck
But into a
Beer Chain Letter your grandma might sing
Ridiculous Bowl
It's about his friend who was a mechanic
Keep that in mind that it starts
Muslims have no more fitting
Mechanic is fit
Text Mai Tran
Dieter
Owner
Your dealership
Flags
Is war flag
Mica Battle Flag
Obvious
Al-Qaeda flag
No it's not
That literally fighting out
Yesterday
And
With your permission
It's risky for the people that saw it you know that
Nope
Danger
Caliphate
He goes on to say like
Government won't do anything about it
Cousin
This is nonsense
This is a gossip story
Alright
Sure first question
You are a member of Isis
Successful owner of
Three major dealership right right
Yeah
Even though I know I'm supposed to
Flag all the time
Chase down another car and I raised it like the skull and crossbones above in case someone thinks
Vacation Olympic
That you're like you going to Isis territory or something like that
Yeah I think it's just like when you get pulled over
You just open up the
Stration but I got a little bit
You go along now Bo
It's the stupidest talking
Story I've ever heard and let's imagine a scenario where
It is true
I don't care
In the same way that Alex
To have a Confederate flag
Some Flags is distasteful
Sure
I'm fine with it I don't care
I don't think
Having a nice
That you are a part of Isis
Write a Sandpoint
My friends had when we were 18
No but we had a flagpole out front
And we had a
P o w m i a flag
In the service
I don't know
Like it doesn't mean anything
There's also that
Nichols has no details
And I just
It's just
Grandpa fear God
Flagpole
And what we would do it
Steal other people's
People short
Khaki shorts
To the top of the fly
May have been a Nickelodeon show
Camp anawanna
We hold you in our heart
What do you think about you
Make us one of art reference
When I get to hang out with Donkey Lips
Budnik
Remember the girl's name there's a true Madness
Salute Your Shorts
5 years ago maybe 10 years ago and
No
Pete doesn't
Does all you dorks
Even the first run sucks
It's kind of fun to go back and watch a video
It's a fever
Yeah it's like a hallucinogenic
Kind of shell
This is this writing
No way I remember being a huge fan of
Were they all become lifeguards on the beach
That was a couple episode
Leah Remini
What's on
But yeah she was like her dad
Beach Club
Probably
Squad Warfare
Larry Nichols
On the beach house I don't know
Versation about
Just emailed the state of the world
Ends of advocating for something that I never would have thought I'd hear him say on air
This is something they like
It's hard for us to get surprised listening to Alex
But this this clip legitimately surprised
Talked about
That they can just have two states
Control
Once it was back under control
I never would have thought I'd hear him legitimately just straight-up say that
States
Pretty far
That's pretty
That's out there even for Alex
I think so yeah
Feel like Alex
Is leaning towards
Secede
Like it's be unspoken thing at ever at the end of every set
All of our
Country run by globalist
Weezer
But we should rightly probably something
It is kind of weird
What article was
Is he
Tatoosh your lawyer say
That the founding fathers
Song about conversation
Somebody have a cough
Original lawyers
Oh okay I thought they came on the show
Cuz he linked to an article
I don't know
I didn't look it up
I don't believe it
Everything way that I don't believe he's only made one prediction about financial collapse
Listen to this show there's so much that I have to say
And then just move along
My spot
Otherwise
Letsjerk
Will get really pissed off
But
As long as the episode last
Recorded in real-time while I research
Better be a terrible show
And will not be what we do
Just a384 hour-long episode marathon
Larry Nichols
Says something
Also surprised me a little bit
Immediately
The couch
And remember I have
Well I just called a little problem
This is real
It's not
The grossest thing
King of
Anita Hill
Very obviously he was sexually harassed by Clarence
Thomas when she work for him
The right-wing attacks
Aggressively
Years later even
Clarence Thomas's wife left a voicemail for her
That was demanding an apology
She thought it was fake and called the FBI
Found out it was real and
Considers an olive branch
Okay
Alright
But you guys are crazy
You better go
You're my husband
Public apology
Olive
Trying to start
A dialogue
You always negotiate from a position of
Straight up murder ink
Looked into this in a long time
Clarence Thomas
Situation
Anita Hill
Was what caused David Brock
Become a liberal
There is so much
Backroom evil
Character assassination going on
This woman who is just
You know saying
Was sexually harassed
And she
Absolutely was
Who put this pube on my Coke
Also Larry Nicholson
I don't believe that he hung out with Clarence Thomas
In the same way I don't believe you was talkin to Bibi Netanyahu
I don't believe any of that s***
Also we talked over
But In that clip
What's the first time that Alex Jones gives up
Did Matt drudge was talking about Clarence Thomas
Because he's like Larry Nichols brings up Clarence Thomas
Alex like Talk Talk giveaway
Give them all up
Donald Trump
Start of the two sources if Donald Trump
So good the end of October
Still no development in terms of trump
Nothing just wait I forgot
We have something big we have to talk about
Nope nevermind
Bronchi
Ron
Alert alert
Don't look at me like that
October 9th
And there's only one clip to play but something
Nothing to discuss
It's another one
This one
Supposed to be Dracula
Peter Gunn
Two plus two equals five
Jojo
Question asked
Truly
Or Count Dracula
Have a strong will for one whose only live one life
There is nothing
There is no world government
Vehicle cameras
There is no
That are not 40 million illegals pouring into the United States
That's not on
To not
Do not
Awaken
Trust
Bosch
There is no organization in power
Power does not seek power
You are becoming sleepy my dear
Show me Annette
If you still talk about Van Helsing
Truly
Tympanic
Yeah that's what it is
Eclipse of these things cuz they they aren't worth it
He's there was a yoga class
Didn't allow white people in
I don't care
Just don't
I don't care at all
But
I don't have it
F*** I forgot to get the eclipse
Sucks
That sucks this one was big
He literally says
Winning executive fights checks
Imbalances
That is a dictatorship
I would love to throw that Clipper right in his face
Right about now
The big thing that's going on is
Obama
Pardon me
Confirm nor deny that it is
His middle name
Ipecac
Pajamas
Shooting in Oregon
Before that's a little bit
Before is going
To meet with
Families and going
To pay condolences
Whatever
Like a good present
Something
President Taft
You know if you were a good president
You would want to be a symbol to the nation
Even if you're not nest
Sara Lee running everything like a dictator you are still a symbol of the American conscience
And the America
Spirit
And so if there is
Yes you should be there
To make sure that everyone is together
Everyone realizes
What's going on in everybody decides
Time to f****** fix it
Or
You could go on TV three days later
102 102 102
That's good.
There's good and bad
Amazing
Is only even what like
Really pissed off
How much
Murder he was doing
I was really mad if I just don't want us to bring it
Sure bring back Obama's
Because Trump is so much worse so much worse on the murder run
Literally ever
Refract 100%
The front totally there is no there is
0 upside down
To Trump being president unless you're really rich
Shouldn't theoretical tax breaks accounting
There is no upside
Well I suppose if you're an oil exact you do get
National Park
So whatever
F*** it is you want now you calm down and have a cigarette calm down I just
We just heard Obama's voice and it triggers me is like when all we had to work
Sorry about I got triggered and I'm sorry
I'm sorry
Paul Joseph Watson
We're not listening
Have a nice little chat and I realize that the two of you not like each other
They seem to be miserable being in the same room
He is not like any of Alex's jokes
He is just little looking like
This guy
Which
I kind of agree
They
Presented as
Obama is going to Oregon to feed off the desk
To go feed off The Souls of the Dead
But here's the thing
If you really think about it there's no
Nothing Obama could do that would
When in the situation
Cuz if he goes they're going to use the argument you just use
Why wouldn't he the president how could he
How could you be so heartless
Does not show up at the shooting
What weather the victim not black enough or something like that
If you hate somebody that much
There's no there's never going
Nobody propaganda trap
The only thing to do in that situation is ignore it and I'm glad that most
People do
But
Alex Jones
Send
Jakari Jackson
To Oregon
And the wrapping it up
As like there's going to be a protest
The Obama you're not welcome here
Stop trying to
Split these deaths
You think there's going to be 10,000 people there
Which is based on a Facebook event
So good reporting
Turns out there's more like a couple hundred
And they're at
A place that
They think
Obama is going to land at
They don't know
He doesn't end up liking there
Add it's just walking around
Good deal
Like a microphone and another one is a young guy with a Halo
Prism shirt
They're all from out of
They all came in
To say Obama you're not welcome in this town
It's very weird to me
It's very strange that you have these people
Speaking for that town because of their hatred of Obama
Anyway it's terrible the audios bad and
There's not much
Not much going on with it
But it does
Because of
Damned-if-you-do damned-if-you-don't
Playset Obama into
And the fact they spent money to fly
Can bigs into carry out there
For nothing
Except
Or ride the rails
Like
So also
Also
Very aggressively
And I saved you
Bears mentioning
Because those dudes suck
So
That's the end of the night
No show on Saturday
And we get October
Which is the the last day we're going to be covering
This is going way too fast
I don't know what's going on we're only an hour
I feel like
It's been more
Yeah this is weird
We have covered
A lot
I don't know I feel like we've been digging around
I feel like what is going on how many Clips do you have
We're World lipstick
How are we on this man eclipse this fast
Bananas
Something is wrong
Nothing wrong
No it is I just checked the time
Feel like we're in a wormhole
Clips
Last
I guess
Vamp
So
I don't know what he's doing here
I'll be honest
T-shirt with the agenda
But he says something that I do not agree with
About a celebrity
Also see if you can guess who the celebrity is before he says his name
La
5 years ago
Mario Lopez
California
But the illegals can create
Just huge amounts of crimes
So hold on
Roman Polanski
No
Celebrity
Apparently they committed $5,000
In Los Angeles
Call Mark Wahlberg
Okay are you going to Borgess
Alright
The game show host
I'm going to go for the rare 24
On the set of the Antiques Roadshow
Correct
Celebrity Charlie Sheen
There we go
Hollywood lawyer
Well I don't know if he's telling the truth he comes off as credible
But I know the inside of Holly Road and I know I've been told the exact same thing with some of the biggest stars out there
That's a great that's great Randy
Is a lunatic videos from his RV
Mountain Dew starkiller's out
Mustafa needed Casa properties
But the bigger issue that you got in trouble for beating his wife
Defraud
Keeper in Santa Barbara by using an invalid credit card to pay it
$10,000 bill
The Frog
Court case was dismissed they paid most
3 years of probation
In addition to 240 hours of
Free service for it
Didn't they flee the country though Montreal a little bit later
September 2010
Got charged
Burglary
After they find the guest house
They claim that the Hulk
God dammit
The Music Hollywood situation where you like
They're good
Right around the
And then
Then they were squatting
Signature
Warrants for their arrest issued Court
Where are they were arrested for
Under the immigration and refugee
Claiming that they fear for their lives
Because of these starkiller's
Stuck around
For permanent resident status
You know you lived in Montreal but was briefly arrested for not checking
Non-resident
Court of Canada and America
He's an illegal immigrant
Vermont
Origin
You can get through customs without them noticing
Again
Love doing it.
Is very real
100%
I am going to have to arrest you you f******
A few days later after he was detained by US Customs was released and allowed to remain
Though he is still subject to arrest
Should you travel to another state
Billy Burke
Bernie Sanders
Black mouth shut up that's what I would guess
I know it's the stock killers that coming out tomato
Seems credible vote
Which is right in line with Alex Jones is picking cuz look at all the
Prediction
To the loudest
It said on his show already
B e d
Harry dent
Himself
Larry nickel
Now we get to add one more to that list
A Leo zagami
Leo zagami
There's a gay Lobby in the Vatican
I got all that stuff cuz I don't really care and it's terrible
In the clutch
With a s*** prediction
How is it going is it going
What's the next big shoe drop
I'm getting award Awards
Why
Okay that's because two years ago the Scandal started five years ago
Jesse's going to
Staind
He's coming
Norfolk
So that's pretty
Isn't that
If I recall it was
Bananas
Who resigned
Wackadoo
Premise
Flushes out as the clip goes on is that
These
The pope into a position as opposed to like a lifelong
Okay
Can shuttle people in and out there will be multiple living popes
Eventually they'll be a council of Pope
You know that's actually a really
Time in the
The Pope's fighting
That's just one of those beautiful things were like
You guys know that your religion
Thinking about you guys
Seemed really silly to all of us
Bulshit out of the gate
There's a black pope
Multiple popes
Well he saw that movie with the order
I love that movie
I kind of agree it was like a secret
Sossaman
Shannyn Sossamon she's the one man to man
She's the one
Accepting that 40 days and 40 nights when are mad that makes her orgasm with
Look up rose petal
Hollywood Homicide Hamilton
Harrison Ford
No idea
Noise
I lost track of Josh Hartnett around the
He was in Penny Dreadful
Very thrilled for
It wasn't it was
Stockman
What's
God damn it I don't remember
This whole investigation
August 2015 investigation
Is
Figure out where Alex Jones decided Trump
Is cool
For the time those covered he's not really talk too much about you
How many months
Close to 5 months
Started in June
Close
He doesn't really talk about Trump
Choosing stuff on the 11th
Is there like a larger context
Because if I call
This insulated what's going on in the world
Every single day
Everyone's talking about Trump Ad nauseam
Being weirdly restrain
Billions and billions of dollars in free
Because everybody was just like
He's in Albany
We'll look at this silly dumb f*** nominee thank God we got him so our other most hated candidate
Will finally become
Can president
Nope
Because of the complexity of your dumb f*** media
Times we've been over that I'm glad I'm glad MSNBC
The greatest
Conservative columnist of our time
I don't know
Then we live in a weird funhouse mirror of the world
That must be what's going on
Like this
That they're actually sick
Successfully doing
Is absolutely destroying the Earth
Like this like they're getting rid of all the regulation
They're getting ready to sell off our Nash
They're getting rid of all of these like the EPA is even allowed
To use the word
Climate change anymore
Like they're killing
Yeah but all of the failing at
Expect
Tacular Lee
You're just like well maybe we can
Can get through this
Like maybe we can
Maybe we actually can get through this
Trump should be
The
Absolutely
Just like football gear
You're not going to repeal that
It's just
It's too big
Actually
Yeah it's helped so many
Funny people
That you're not going to
Take it back the same thing is true of a lot of these regulations
And it's not going
Like our next
Just going to go and they're back on
He took a lot of them took years in the first place
Cruiser so strongly against
Even though they save lives
Protect the environment and s*** like that.
Businesses to work in
Who's going to save people
From their greedy selves
Clean water
EPA
Understand
Be just
Sincere level of sociopathy
And the worst part is
I can't understand how it is we don't have the ability to focus
Just long enough to
We all know Flint
We've all known this
For forever
Huge
To do something
That the internet
Focus for a f******
Internet focus for a week
To fix like the pipe in
Infrastructure
Couple billion dollars
Probably more like 500
He has a billion
Five bucks
Fix-It I mean
Put
I think that's overly simplistic but all of them
All of these GoFundMe for surgeries and all
Whispers
You bet your ass that's what we do
But it's
It's wrong to do that
It really is
Free market
Donated
So much money to the Chicago
To the Chicago Publix
It was amazing
Unfortunately
That's just
Wait for them to be like
It's all about
One argument but the other argument is
You can't you can't rely on these lofty principles of
Care of these things
Hey so if there is the possibility
Schools
Is it emergent
The right thing to do if you have the resources to do it
I agree so
All those things would be taking care of it a perfect world because they're not
Sometimes
Need to be a perv
Forgeworld to have
Functioning
Expression
But the whole point the whole point of us
Susan so we can go to school
So we have wrote
Don't even have a
Auctioning
System
Do any of the
What's
I don't know all I'm saying is
Is Texas
From the Union
Extorted
But you don't
The feed and then we're like
All right come on
I guess
So
The founding fathers
Kieron the Oggy
August October 11th
Only inasmuch as
It's not surprising at all
When you look at all like the same person wrote it
Donald Trump
Colin Ford
As if Donald Trump worth 5 billion dollars
Drug cartels
I hope so remember that
And then they act like that's weird
Mother father
Mishawaka schools
Nobody
So you
I found out the Trump have a gun
He won't have a secret service
I don't know actually
I'm glad you brought that up
Cuz I think these
Scarier
Probably going to happen
When is malicious
I bet you are going to replace the Secret Service
Protecting
If I were watching a TV show and the development
Crazy right-wing nut ball president
Isn't power he loves the militia is he
He keeps saying positive things about them when he shouldn't be
Next episode
The Secret Service
Can't protect them anymore cuz they run out of money
I'm going to guess that episode end
On a dark note where the militia step-in
I like will do it for free cuz we're keeping the oath
Alright
Terrible
Prediction
Bethany Alex Jones Leo zagami level four
I'm not predicting it I'm just saying the appropriate for our world is becoming a
Dystopian fiction
Ridiculous
That would be so
Like
You wouldn't help but laugh
Like it's a tragedy
This is a tragedy that that could happen but at the same time
Really you're going to get a bunch of
Weekend
Paintball players to follow you around
I think you're under selling some of these a militia types
You need to look into these
Little bit
People in that World War
Credit for car
There are
Weekday
Rifle
I don't know how to put it.
Don't know what's going to happen
Alex Jones
Love gun
Love answer you would think
Maybe
Finding out the Donald Trump has a gun
Is going to be what pushes him over
You know what that actually does
Alex Jones love guns so much
He says everything irrational in the world in defense of God
It would make
$0.06
That this is the
The turning point
To the point where he had himself
Love the sky
What's interesting is
At the very end
Where he is talking about the media coverage of the head
And I remember
Does breathless where it's like
Reminder shouldn't be a prison
I think it's
Our responsibility to give it up for him
Absolute from a different perspective
Signed up with Donald Trump
I will just
The fact that your ass
Asking me that question
Trying to play war games about to reveal
Figured it all out first off I would assume that there would be balloons
Waiting to come down like an election night
Second
You would be
Giddy like you would look at me with so much
Are you leaving in right right
Neither gets a gun
And I'm going to go with no well let's see actually a caller calls in
3 minutes after this
And ask him what he thinks about Donald
New York City
Are on the air
Hey Dallas how I change the New York City
Are you from New York
Call Grace
Donald Trump
Is he the real deal
The question is a new world order but if you can answer that for me
I have to judge a tree by its fruit
Americana
I don't completely trust
I think she might be
President
I just have to give him the benefit of the doubt but
Regardless
He's now
What I'd call the Tea Party
And so they want to destroy him in name
Do to try to her.
Truth
Watching very closely so I think
Frustrating
That's the same thing
There's no progress
Come on so this is ridiculous
Because we have to pretend there's progress being made when there's not
There's a couple things we can take from the does the first time use the word America
Americana guy
That's kind of big
And then also you say
I don't trust him but that doesn't matter
Please freezing
With the same things he said this whole time
Slightly differently
So there is warming
But it's still the same message
I like what he says I don't think I can trust
I don't think he's trustworthy like it or not
He's saying things that we have
To defend
Give me a prediction
Does it go from this like
Tepid
Throated 1776
2.0
You can't ask me that cuz I know some
Something
I can't answer any questions
The next week or so of the show
The come down the line
He's not going full throttle
I don't know.
This is really starting to f*** with my head
I don't know what he
He's doing
Yeah
It's super weird
This is the 15th episode of our investigation
B nut
That can't be true
This is just such a
So much edging
Nonsense
It's driving me nuts
And I'm mad about it now
I used to be like
This is interesting
Now I want
This to be over I want him to f****** support Trump already
Cuz I kind of
You know what
I kind of understand why
He's going to eventually
Or or way worse
Yeah
Magical elements
The real reason was going to be something out of left
I had a 6-hour dream and now strumpet 1776 to
The end result of
Based on the
The month that I've listened to in the lead-up
I know what's going to happen
The end result
Behind the scenes
Is going to be someone lies to him
Yeah that's it
Sort of been operating off of
Or least need suspicion
We've had for a long time
I don't know anymore
I have no bearings
Kirby Millennium episode
People
Every single day
Crazy Andy
Alex has no intention of supporting Trump
Same way I have no intention of becoming
Indeed
31 more Clippers
The Parting Shot Alex painting humility
Disgusting way
I don't want to be the leader
I have to
I just cannot get up here and not tell you the truth go f*** yourself
So
I don't want
Look
I don't want to be there
I want to hear cuz I'm so awesome
Awesome
Truth all the time
I have to
I can't not
And when I'm wrong
Listen
I called myself out for
I was so wrong
Everybody knows that two years later even though they knew I was lying
It comes true and I was like see I told you I wasn't
I never lie
Even when I do
Sneaky
I'm lying all the time
So if but
I'm a liar in
In a good way
Is there
Come to the end of our investigation Chung
Furious
A very subdued
Furious but
Furious nonetheless
I don't know man
This episodes only like an hour and a half and I apologized episode
But to be fair I'm thrilled
Cuz it's the weekend
I think one of the issues
You know if this if this episode it happened
2 months
We would have really been able to pee off on all this stuff
We've already gone
Is just like it just
You said this is so much edging
F****** do it
We got to figure
We got to figure some of this
Something's Gotta break
I don't know
Cuz the next next investigation we're going to record is over the weekend
Like two weeks
Makeup
I want to find
Target
To figure out
This same
Will-they-or-won't-they this is a f****** doctor house and Lisa Cuddy
I want it
Fine fine
Tonight
Wilson
Cast no Wilson doctor Wilson
I never watched
Sean Patrick
Chicago
Dead Poets Society who cares
The other side
No. Sean William Scott he was not Dead Poet Society
Anyway
If you'd like more of the show
If you'd like
To find out more and go to our website at knowledge fight.com
You can subscribe
We are also called knowledge fight on I-10
Yeah we didn't make a we didn't make
Different store on.
Go to Facebook
Checkers
Send an email
You are
If you want to
Not a policy
Undercover Boss
Just send you one
Gmail.com
Listen you may get a random size pan as well
And patriotism
If you would like to Port Sherlock we said that in the past a bunch
Autotrakk.com sportshow button
We really do appreciate it makes a big difference
Doing alive
Show September 9th
Determined
Probably some good simultaneously 99 at 9
September 9th at 9 that would make the most
But that will do a handstand
The pope will also be showing of the black pope will be there
I got to put out a feeler
Larry Nichols
So you know one guy was not going to come
I told you I don't know if
I've only seen one that I've ever seen
He could be a puppet
I have no idea
A creature from Sesame Street
Could you give me
One more thing about him that probably piss
Pisses me off the most
No
Are you like that
Dude
I swear to God
Doesn't stop running this better
I am
Cardinal sin
Not even like it I gave you nothing you work with
Do you know whose fault it is though
Go fuc yourself
Controlling
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work