Alexandra First Time coloring
Novelty beverages
Yes before we go in
Alright are we open
Just for one though
Question
The follow-up I'll allow it
I want a question
Do you know a lot about
I do
Nobody
All right there we go
What was your fault though that was the follow-up that my
Have to bring it up guys
I wanted to bring this up and I didn't tell you before we started recording cuz I think
It's fun and I don't do stand-up anymore
Make a note
Reservation
White people
It buzzes your your little
So whenever I get up to
Text like you when you texted me
I got a little buzz
But it also doesn't
If you haven't moved in a while
Like an electric shock
And it work
That just has like
Do you want have a cigarette
Remind me to go take
Fake cigarette break
Let's go in my lungs but helping my legs
Compromise we all got them
Right
Just be lung cancer
Indeed
Is alright
Bi-fold of the policy wonk
Thank you for joining up
That was our Make-a-Wish wasn't it
That's exactly what just happened right now
Also I need to do this
Because I think I falling behind it
Terms of our foreign policy wonk
We have a couple in the last week
And I think I might have
Given one
A foreign policy wonk status but I can't remember
So I'm just going to go through all of them
I already did but anyway
Thank you very much
Now that I'm doing this
I think I've done this all already
I'm still up in my head that I can't remember
I also
A foreign policy
Stop
Alright
Reminder vinall in repetition
But I want to make sure that we got everybody covered
I'm not good at monitoring my email
Like I don't know why I'm included but it's like
Reminder if you if you up your donation we will give you another uniform
I don't want to be one of these guys
Become a foreign policy wonk
And the people come through
And I just forget
One of those guys one of those guys
So many kickstarter's
You can see the guys
He said listen
You're going to be a foreign policy want but
They never fall off
There's so many people who do Kickstarter
And stuff like that
Just lying and cheating people
Is definitely
Hallmark of capital steaks are real low for your most
People's creative Kickstarter
Those are like to give a shout out to
Set me a nice email I really appreciate it
Informed us that to Alex Jones
Is wrong
About Sweden
Which we already
We could have guessed that but I have always wanted to marry a woman
Until
Almost is coming off as a cliche
No she's real she's real.
Look up women named Sonia
Mortal Kombat
Right us I'm convinced
I just
Don't really give a sheet
Twitter Bots got 2000 hundred
In my life where maybe I'm an old man
I know that the the rest
Wrestling fans of the world
Don't like Johnson
Cuz he wins all the time
I don't care
Cuz I get to hear his theme song
If you win
What's his stats
Exactly
Corn
Blaze episode
Still doing preamble
Everybody's already stop listening by about the World At Large
One main thing
I'm starting to become
Incredibly
Concerned
About
Joe Rogan
This is something that our friend far-out friend of
The show has a while back
But
His most recent Gap
I was Peter Schiff
Who's someone who
About on the Shelf
He's one of Alex Jones's favorite economist
Went on Joe Rogan show and I listen to the first like
2 hours of it
Just talkin all this b*******
About how he moved his business
To Puerto Rico to avoid federal tax
Believe that
The minimum wage should be nothing
Because if you don't have the skills to earn a high wages
It's your fault
It's all these ideas
Children should work in Coal Mine
Course they can learn skills
Cuz their children they don't have to
It's about exposure
Aldi's
Libertarianism and I don't know what Joe Rogan
Cuz he's had a
Ring
Of these alt-right libertarian ding dong
Mixed in with you know you're
Your Joey Diaz is in
The standard SP has
Because
Was not challenging
Peter schiff's ideas at all
I was just
Signing off on them all that makes sense
Why does no one talk about this
Wow
A lot of people do it your new fan base is going to
Quite a bit
You know it's weird
I was watching
The livestream
Put some super male Vitality on a burger and just ate it
During Peter Schiff
Might as well
Yeah you might as well
He seems
Smarter and yells last
But he's becoming Alex Jones
You think so wow
Did that is something that I would send Joe have in common
That could be
Humping the wall
Pretentious
What do you think Tom Brady
Chop chop.
Your argument would be
The entire NFL basically
Sports
Not allowed time to gets back
Therefore he is safe
From the CTE
Anyway
Anyway my point that they wanted to make is I'm deeply concerned about this growing in
Spreading disease
Really worried that
Joseph
Incredibly impression
They look up to him as a icon
If it's a way that I looked up to Adam
When I was in
Junior High
High school you know
I'm concerned about them being
Exposed to Peter Schiff
Talkin his ass off
For 2 hours
More or less unchallenged by Rogan
Or at least when he challenges him
Really
It's soft
It's really kid gloves
Movie kind of stuff
Heavy never even get to the park
Or really discuss the fact
That
Peter Schiff believe that taxation is a crime
Against people
Does he lives in Puerto Rico
Alright well then we should
Allow him to have roads
Where
All the stuff
That's what I if you don't want to pay federal income tax
That is fine I reckon
Decision
Anyway I'm pissed off whatever
I will deal with it in my own way
Probably
Drinking tons of is black raspberry sparkling water you brought over
!
It's like a it's a
Like the Steven Soderbergh movie The End
At the Disco
Discussing the August 23rd 2017 episode of The Alex Jones Show
That was Wednesday of this week
We are
Can I call an audible during the show is that possible
The rest of the night for us
Call inaudible roughly 15
18 seconds I can probably
For about 4
6 hours
Directions
The present
Dad visit episode stocks on a number of levels
At least
Three or four moments
No one
I Really Deserve Summit a
And unfortunately we're probably going to have
Talk for a minute about Joe Arpaio
But we'll keep it to a minimum
Alex Jones
Alzheimer's
Digress
Brought an idiot
What video
Going to use that that was in reference at Morehouse
Did I hit a regular covers
Justine
That was a reference
To Trump
Speech that he gave him Phoenix
Trump has Alzheimer's
Who is Steve
Even though even like doing that f******
Broke at least three or four different
Like he had a public official audio
Thousand on the list
Yeah well
I tried to stammer my way through that like I was Bob Newhart I f***** it up
So he talks a bit about
The speech
To start things off
Donald Trump
Incredibly riveting
I can't turn away
This is the Ultimate Reality Show
He's doing the best job in the economy around Santana stand expansion
Automan
I watch live last night that our Plus
Volley after volley of Truth against watch them fly at at just
Before the speech in Phoenix
Everything they say about him is what they're doing
Was
Bikers rally against Trump
From 300 yards away of bikers
Bikers for Trump
And then it was but they wanted to make it look like everyone
Going
Beyond any level of Lies the Soviet Union or anybody ever else North Korean propaganda has
Nothing on this
You know when North Korea when they're like hey those bikers they don't like Kim Jeong Hoon
That's
Stop believe from everything I can tell.
Character
Groups
Trump when they were for it was also in the context
Is there being a lot of groups
That we're going to protest
And there were some that were coming to support
And so the article
Itself
I had to do with both sides of the
The demonstration
Alex only reads headlines
The size of his rally wasn't equal to the size of the protester I don't care
Protesters wasn't equal in size of the Rat don't care
Did you see me
His rally size
Is 0
Guy who opposed
Every time there's been a rally you post that image
Do the Cavaliers
Celebration
Didn't realize
He presented as this be outside of the Trump rally
The Cleveland
Cavaliers NBA Finals celebration parade
Cubs
World Series champs
Yeah I got to read that
Apparently
For every rally
And conservative ding-dong
Still don't catch on
Hilarious
I read an article about him
I'm just a sports guy if you look down my feed you can tell I'm f******
People
That's that's the only thing I care about
Here's my question
U-Save the jury
Are you still out on
Because there was a little bit of a cut
There I don't know why it goes a little glitch in the recorder
With increasing the truth
The jury's still out on
Alex is married she doesn't spell it out on this episode
Narrative is the Trump is trolling people
By saying he's going to raise the troops levels
And then pull them all out
He's trying to
Trickmaster
Into a false sense of
Security
And then he's going to pull the rug out from under his globalist
Yeah so that's why the jury's out
Hey by
Jerry not out
Really grasping at straws
Number two
I mean he knows that it's bad
That's what it really me
Alex knows that the idea of sending more troops to Afghanistan
Is bad he can't
Support it cuz he has a long documented record of being against war in Afghanistan
Everything that the bushes clintons and Obama did
In terms of wars
He's going to be
Very exposed
He's going to have to be against
Right and I don't think he's ready
The jump off that train yet
Lot of people keep saying you don't know how is Alex going to turn
And my response
No Dodgers
I don't think they're Rodger stones are real bellwether
Especially when you see Rodger Stone
Anyway
Alex says that he's going to go over
All of the clips
From Trump
I'm assuming
He plays too
He plays one
How long was the rally 7077
Okay so
You might be right if you were saying sex
Replace one where he says of the media is really f****** awful
I'm in episode
Any plate
Yeah
Joe Arpaio is on
How is he not in prison you might have been Skyping in for prison
That's a better question but
Before he does the interview with Arpaio B play the clip where Trump is like
Do you guys like Sheriff Joe
So you place those two clip
But he keeps saying I'm going to play all of them we're going to get into it I'm going to do some analysis of it but
Secant
I think he's
He's drunk
Oh
Alright Isaac H I think Alex
Either drunk
Or in the middle of a manic episode
Orbo
And I'm leaning towards bow
You'll see the behavior on this episode
Is quite different than usual
Even for 2017
There is
So much ranting
So much losing track of where he is
And the way this episode
He's exactly like the March 30th
Episode where he was wasted off his ass
With the exception of
He doesn't have Rob do sitting next to him in a jacket waiting to leave
To the four ways to learn
At least
Alright but before we
Because it's a 3-hour show
The buzz is going to be different throughout
He's just good worked up drunk
As I I believe
You want to talk about the globalist
Course
Spiderlite
World weather creating a false reality
And then having
Just going
In some groups for the week
Dumbest
The most helpless people
Presentation of the news
A good meeting with Alex
But I would like to say
That the exact same thing as being done by Trump with all of the box
There've been a couple of new studies that have come out following a lot of these thoughts
If you really look at it it's
It's pretty impressive
Body clear Oregon
Innovation made the rounds
Wanted
The one that was
Do it
All of this
Pixar from
28 or whatever Showtime
That was part of an investigation that followed the people who have
A name and then ate numbers after their names
Naming protocol
There's a lot of really f***** up stuff but
Totally right
But about the wrong
Trying to manufacture
The appearance of
Consensus
And a green
And people who fall Twitter
Stupid
And that's very true
Think of these
Bots are real
I am. Believe me
People who do
Well you can
Concede
See the things
That likes the telling
For me is
When he said
It's the group's
People in your life
OU
That's another reason I think he's drunk and that's what they're always really cuz I think that's the
This is
Zetas
Deep distrust for anyone who knows
The idea of knowing something
Is expensive to pay
People who think it should be
Versus
Empirical evidence
Is always going to be more confident
Certainly
Then faith-based people will always
Playing the confidence people have
Always the same people who strongly approve
Who denied
They just released the the Harvard study where they're like
Climate change
70s
More like
So much money
Whichever one
Thinking in
Space space
Carbon tax is that Al Gore
Globalist Mickey
Spider-like globalist
Let's go back to the spiders
Are in the WikiLeaks
What spiders do
Flies
There
Webs
What is this
Check out the suitcase
Idiot
You guys
Spider has a bit of a New Jersey
I don't know
I mean come on
I don't even know what to do with that
Well I think that
Already I'm on he's drunk tip because
He's talking about spiders
I've noticed that when he's in these moods
Then whether it is just a harsh man
Sodor
He's drunk there's a lot of projecting
What's being done
And the idea of tricking people and stuff like that manufacture
Consensus
Stuff that he does a lot
Until what are you talkin about
Trick dumb people
Are you doing
You can't possibly think of.
He either
Literally no way
He pitched
Purple Penguin
For six months
Plus
Any mail
But there's no way that if he had
If he had faith in his audience
What do I do
I've met most of our listeners
You said you had faith in his
Department
Senor pronoun
That's what's going on
Fair enough
What I'm saying is
I'm confident that if anybody was looking for the show
Looked up the purple
Stop
Easily see that
We are telling
The truth about it
Alex Jones
Totally confident knowing that his audience
Will either just blindly
Trust whatever bulshit he say or if they do look it up they'll look it up on zero
Or WorldNetDaily
Mlgc
Instead of digging a little bit cheaper finding the primary source
So
I mean
He's projecting like crazy and do spider voice is
Distract people
Jingling keys
Yeah yeah
But fake cry
Little bit later
Would you cry
This is it goes into Alex's victim
Complex
With who or what
The news
Toupee
The New York Times
We have
I'm here
Letting you know you're not insane when you see their wall of Lies
You know there's other people that recognize as well we are solitary
The joint
Yeah the first thing obviously is
First of all it's not true the 10 billion dollar contract
But if it is
Shmoney
Echo Bluff
Hit up your boy
Right I think that that's trying to harken back
To the eye
The Google dualistic narrative
I think it's going back to that cuz I think that was 10 million dollars to
His narrative
It's b*******
Billion dollar contract
2 News
Selective checkout 2 News
But like the movie blank check
Tan Luxe
Not great nevermind
I was going to say he's awesome he's not
He wrote a song about that
That was not great
Alex is also
This is more projection
The idea that they want you to feel alone
Like that because obviously benefits
People
Like if you go into normal society
And just regular people and start saying things
That you heard on Infowars
Thank you believe that
People are going to
Naturally get away from
They're going to like
This is a weirdo
Person
Speeds be the isolation
And that may we talk about this in the past it's called stuff
It's it's just
He's doing that
I'm saying this is what
To feel you to feel like no one else likes
Trump
You're not alone you got us
Recurring
Themes throughout all of the all
And it's a throughout gamergate throughout all of this stuff
It is
People who are isolated
And that is always the narrative why the internet
Is all of these people who are isolated
And creating that
Horrible bigotry and racism
That is really built out of their own into
Insecurities
Women of color people
Their bodies of
Spiders The Wiz
Avaz
You think I can't Alex's
From
Is insecure fear of spiders
I mean look if he's afraid of spiders good on it
I understand
Spiders are where
They're really weird
Spiders are
Another not let me tell you about it
Hello story
Got to go tonight
Stone
Some pig
Wizard of Oz
Alex
Really expresses
Basically just how excited he is to be relevant
But what comes out of his mouth but it is
Coming up
Has receded
Literally literally
Comeback
If there are literal Goblin creatures
That is all I would
Are you sure
I saw a literal Goblin I would shoehorn that into any and every conversation that I was going to
Cocktail party
Oh I just saw this documentary on little Goblin creature
No
I need to make a documentary about these little Goblin but I can't cuz I can't
Can I please have 10 million dollar contract
Make it afternoon
Jimmy news
So
Have you heard
Love it
I love it that people are talking about me
Which kind of makes you think that no matter how bad an idea it is to hitches
Along
Stop the other way around
Even though even as much of a bad idea is that is
He loves it
It's even if it's negative
Idea of being the number to EDD
Anime
Is
Proposition
If you're up
Power or
Number of enemies
The number one enemy at Infowars
Boyfriend
Oh yeah
Yeah I think so
People are talking about him being investigated by Mueller
You bet you thought I was on the
For out of the periphery
If he's even in the
Anyway that's a debate for another time
Yeah I don't know what
To do with this clip I can't really set it up I don't
I don't know what to do with
Enjoy
You got to be lowered first before you can even be
On the level
Evil
People seeking power
I have fear
Gods
Power trips positive
But it's only the image of the universe you have in your mind
Image of God
Understand
You are not that thing that you can
I have a path for you and you will Attain
Is falling
This is eaten coming
So much depends on the desk lamp
Beautiful
So I made that bed that long pause
Is just like him
Staring like
What
Try and explain to I wrote down as much of that as I can and I have no idea
Karlos Williams
To get that out or otherwise I couldn't sleep otherwise I could not sleep
I just be staring at Twitter refreshingly
Who's going to f***
Call me out cuz
I know it don't want the beginning of it is upside down
Minos Road
Jesus you're going to be
The beginning part is about that narrative that he has that in order
For the globalist
To attack you they first have to bring you down
Make you impotent
Them stuff like that
I have it done
Do you is not clear
No but it is
There's
Context clues we can take
I guess
Destroy you I'm guessing
I don't know
So then
Whoever what else what other questions do you have
Does God
Taking power
As of God
Right
Right right
It's the image of yourself that you are not like that
Haha
You are like the
And then there is
Nope
I'm starting to think I don't know what
The image of or is
Not here's what I want to believe
Because I'm kind of into it and it'll be awesome if Alex
But I'm thinking maybe what he's saying
Is that we aren't are flashing bodies
Okay
To think that you are your fleshy body
But what you are is actually a spark of the
The divine
In a pretty how town
With you, all right
No I think it's
I think
That I might be bringing others my own stuff to is but it sounds like it's almost
Like a gnostic
It's almost like the devil that he's talking about is the
The demiurge
They created the physical world that
Retracting
If you want to go
Planet
Might not even be about the global it could be like
If that's true
Holyshit
Not though it's not because even this is a drunk and sucking an
Talking about fidget string together whatever words are coming out of his mouth
Beater half thoughts
It feels like he is having a manic episode
Because he is
Stringing along all of these words which are
Utterly incapable of keeping up with his putter
Do they sound like you trying to get to
Sounds like he has an idea
I may be as the colonel of 1
But be that as it may it take Saturn
And I hear this
We're just getting ready to figure out my license
But because I absolutely have to do this and other people have to do it
Why
Piles coming on December 1st
Fox News
He'd been convicted in prison
What
We got the info to Trump as well
Federal
Baseball
About
Did not even know that this was happening because
Infowars.com
Drudge Report
And I said
Lawyers looking to Pardon for you and it almost happened last night
Really about
Back-channel the president
In Congress
Who's fighting for this Republic
Fearlessly
Who is committed
I said Fearless I don't a psychopathic murderer
He fears he's not good enough for this
Now I think Federal
Centigrade
It doesn't on air
And just
Every
Essence of his
Is just drained out of him
I want him dead I wanted legally
I wanted to I wanted to go over the stuff about how awful Joe Arpaio is
But the last time
Threw up
So
He's a true
He's a true f****** monster
He's a
If he is
Second pardon John Wayne Gacy
Cares at this point laws aren't real Only the Strong Survive and murderers
Everything always
Whatever the f*** is goddamn Arpaio
Presided over the Maricopa
Maricopa County Police Department
Was was
I demonstrate the worst pattern of racial profiling in our country
Brief history
He was told repeatedly by judges
Cannot racially profile people
And he consistently refused
Any of his
Beyond
He's a murderer he deprived are human rights
You give people moldy food
Conditions in prison for
For twenty years for a gram of coke
F****** mass murderer
Serial killers
Didn't come close to
To each other that's the definition of serial killer
Doesn't have to be like within
He's responsible much like Sheriff Clarke for
Tons of
Negligence
And Beyond negligence related deaths
In his facilities
If you want to go listen to the dentist Montgomery episode
We talked about it
His officers
I got
A cop for entrapment
Cuz they convince someone to create a pipe bomb
A fake bomb attack
On Joe Arpaio
In order to boost his chances of re-election
Yep entrapment isn't the officers of the Maricopa County
Sheriff's Department
Had bought
Bee balm equipment
There was record
Other conversations telling this guy
How to do it
Ended up serving like 9 years in prison because of it before he got free
Sophie
The serial killer is
They're smarter than lawn for
And when you are like they are logged
Realize that there was a higher power
I'm smarter than myself
Yeah
F****** monster
Is
Obama
Federal judge
Sounds great but I would like
Obama
I would like a small claims Obama
That would be a daytime show
Yes
Federal
Lowering yourself so I can do it to you
If you talk about backing it up
Bounce bounce bounce
The other thing I needed to bring up in my clip is that Alex says
That Donald Trump
Call Joe Arpaio when he found out what was going on
Yes
The Narrative is Alex
Totality is the Jerome corsi wrote an article about it
Drudge
Reposted it
Donald Trump heard about it
Call Joe Arpaio
And said we're going to take care of this
Whatever
When I was on the show
He flatly contradicts
Not in a correcting way
But he literally says
Donald Trump call me
Nobody from his campaign called me
So Alex is just making that up
Yeah even cuz you been Psychopaths
Serial Killer Joe Arpaio
Which is which is the only way that he should be referred to
Unwilling
To go along with that
He has every reason to be absolutely Trump
The interview with Raquel talk about too much
Just sucking Trump's dick on
He just talked about how I'll never leave him he's the greatest
There was only one really funny barbwire Alex's
Like what are you 80s
Bring that up
So also revealed
Also fun Tamara Alex's I claiming is going to start soon
People that will also come back
A little bit later
This next clip is a little bit of a longer Ram
He get the spirit gets in
And
I think
What starts the ramp is thinking about having
Kids
I think
Stuck in his craw and why he ends up launching on this
I believe it's like 4 minutes
There's no way I could
Rolling
But I want to remind you
Live the reason
He probably feels like he needs to
To have kids
Because he does.
Disgusted in this clip in the context
Text of like
Islamists
Some stuff like that
It's because he wants more white children
Do they talk about birth rates
Some stuff like that. In this clip but he does a lot
Yes
When he talks about having kids
Bread but when he talks about having more kids
Them stuff like that
It's it easy to fall into the Trap of
Nothing like I just wanted a big family and not. But that's not what he's talkin
He's talking about
Responsibility to have more
For kids which is what whitener
Has not diminished
So here is the beginning of the long clip
Will deposit if we need to but
Feel absolutely
Because
Absolutely
Believe
How desperate Straits are in
I love him so much the more children
God.
Grommet
Civilization as a toy
Like a clown car
Worry about
I want you to be with them in their ugliness and their misery and I know it
And I understand
This is not the time to hedge bets ladies and gentlemen
This is the time to get on your knees
As God got an erection
This is the point
Unless you threatened with death and work that day
Infinity fight
Alright
We got a new level of Public Accounts
Books
Bible
One-time to get
Going through it
Beaches garage
Get me
That contradicts what you said
Earlier
You said you were winning
And now you're saying that you're losing
The score is never clear but you should be on your knees
How can I find that will
I think we do have bingo
Magic the Gathering
To come into your heart
Wannabe
I Want to Be Free of this scum
Football game
No that is what you're trying to
You just kept survival
This is survival
What did glitterbug
Me and my family
The world for me to love
God
What's Genesis
Excuse
Almost there
Little separation between the rest of life
In-N-Out
Great equalizer
Doesn't transmit forward
I don't know what that is
The evil drug Transit forward
Weber gets ahold if they're cold
That's local
Straight up like
What is dead may not die
Even I forgot that was at the assembly
What was the alternate name of the working title that Kevin Spacey movie
Slightly shortened
I thought you meant
K-PAX recalled I promise I'm going to play all the clips
That if I were judging that as like a wrestler doing
I would say you need to tighten
I would say
Turn off track a little bit
I know you're got a big match with the Undertaker coming up
Right foot
You just
You're going over to Medi
Too many derivation
We can't have you in the ring
In 45 minutes
Can't you can't handle
You just
You gotta
Give it
Get a teleprompter
Scripture
Bullet point
That might help cuz it has
Chevy has on his desk
Doesn't understand any
That what what other bullets
If I were
Organized
Now this
Is a great game
Bullet point
The devil
Is that number one
Sup board
The nature thereof. Bullet point
The door that we got to get through the devils
Comenity screams at all the time
Let's play
I don't know that that's the
That's a lot of rambling on sensitive on
Refills convict
I really think that's
What's going on there
Also
I'm going to start making Bingo cards
I don't know if I'll be able to do one for this episode but
Absolutely
That'll be alright that'll be our next
Can send out 20 yeah yeah yeah put it on the patreon
You can download your own PDF 07
Sorry baby
To make a bingo card
No priest
Is Alex Jones not believe in a handout
Globalist
The only rant
That we're going to be covering on this episode
The
The Marquis had
Headlining
Iran
I believe nothing
He's got nothing
He's car I think
He's drunk
I'm not sure might be hungover
Something like that
But
He's got this interview with Steve pieczenik
The 2nd hour
Joe Arpaio
I'm just going to yell about the
Good
It seems to be one he uses a lot
But
Write what you know
People seem to listen
We should scream about the devil for the first hour of the program from now on
Or Bingo car
What would you go with
What time
You are my attic slick
We're just going to do karaoke for the rest of the lyrics to Blood Sweat and Tears great song
Heidi Heidi ho.
Sweet Roll
But what am I big karaoke songs
By Blood Sweat and Tears
You're just Great Horn Rock
But at the end
He freaks out the leasing
Freaking out
But
Zoom karaoke I'd run up
Someone in the audience
And screaming in their face
To add to the theatricality I would fall down on the stick
You are very good at karaoke
That's what happened
I'm going to do karaoke at Roadhouse bars
Central Missouri that have
Really cheap
Big lot of Sloe Gin and hang out with Hillbillies
But
One thing I liked about a lot of those hillbillies
Like my boy La Monte out there
Central Missouri
Feel it in the air
But I worked with
I just got out of the joint
Call me baby boy all the time
My hillbilly friends from the past
At one of the things that I liked about them was Dave
We're country
But they were not racist
It's not country
It is next clip Alex.
Explain why he thinks people think he's racist
He's wrong
You should not try
Explain.
Any sensitivity
President
Diva quotes
Those are quotes
You know
Episodes
See all the racist cities at
Racism
Because he always complains that no one
Five clips
Make claims about him
Spirit clips
Slow
Maybe it's
Or at least new to me
Instead of saying that's what I
Thing like that
He switches into talking
So it's it's like soundbite was in in the 90s or whatever
It's almost a
Disqualifying term before it set
If you say always
That means
Is that it
Focus Group
Truth
But the connotation
Of the phrase
Makes you feel like oh well they're just making it
Yeah
Which is crazy because what I mean like
Can you describe Penguins or anything like that is anything but eight
Is a Confederate flag is about his
History
You know all of these different waypoints that we've had over
Are all the same definition of talking
I think that you talk
Turns out a lot of people are on the same tip for a while
Goose because
Cuz the way it may we talk about it like that
Like what we've descended into now everyone's into one thing for a week and then we move on to the next
Because everyone's talking about
Through
People having arguments on Twitter and stuff does almost naturally just conclusions that you come to
I find that a little bit distasteful to but
Think I have the same perspective on it Alex does
Cuz I don't think
Global it's doing that I just think it's
Slightly hivemind
It's just a lot of people are kind of dumb
Bluetooth lady something are you liking it
Becomes their opinion
I don't know complicated but
I like his understanding of what
MSNBC
Erasers for
Sure doesn't work and there's going to be penalties
That's why they think I'm
Yeah
No
Yeah Alex
Baby
Come on
Even you got another better things that he said about Obama himself
Could be like
This is what race
Suspend
His dumb ass fans
True
Speaking of another for me to say wife
And black people are more racist
Deserve it
Speaking of another race
Rodger Stone
All-in-one good
We give it up
Even these monsters agree
On. Good stuff
Rodger Stone and Alex Jones
Open favor of legalization of marijuana
Goodbye
Talking about Rodger Stone
I wanting to push
For legalization of marijuana
He believes that if
Trump gets on board with that
It will make everyone
Which I got to tell you
Some people be like
Great you did what Obama Started
But I don't think people will just destroying what Obama did
Look over all this other stuff you've done that
Horrible people for the military
Unilaterally for no reason
One of the most bananas thing
I love the that on Twitter
Then everyone was like why are you doing this
Even everyone in the army
Yeah where the services
How about Double Down
What what else
Just like
Let's do something
Let's just throw something out there today but spoke the business
Unfortunately has a very serious effect on a lot of people
Brookton sale
It's a distraction
Even if that is
The intention of it
It feels bad for us to say that cuz it Doesn't minimize the effects it has on
The point
Cliche now is
Is that
If
If you're not willing to serve in the military
That anybody should or shouldn't
Yeah you know if they volunteer you know
F****** get out of their way
Call say
I'm here we're all on the same
It's fine
Mirror
Not like
Cuz I hate this
Marijuana
It won't
CNN MSNBC Rodger
As if I need to go on your shows they have yours
Story of the Year Pierce Morgan
Quotev
But I don't care what his hottest
Cuz you're lying by Rodger Stone
Totally
Just for fun
I'd like to remind everyone that the reason the Rodger stone with bands
From these Network
Call Danna Navarro
Roland Martin
Contributor
Quota hires
Navarro was borderline retarded
You called her and entitled Diva B
Said she was dumber than dogshit
Beyond
I hear you said that Fox News
Contributor Allen West
Is an arrogant know-it-all negro
Rodger Stone also mocked
Contributor Charles
Hamburg was paralyzed and driving accident
When he was in medical school by telling him to
The quote stand the fuk up
I suggested you wanted
Ashville Ohio O'Reilly's
He called
Contributor Fox News
Contributor Herman Cain Mandingo
Just around it out with
Sexism
He said
Megyn Kelly has a nice set of Cam
Because he's
Horrible
Horrible person
Those are good reasons
That's not even like
The full list
Twitter yeah
Busey's Coronavirus
He's been on television and call people
Other I don't remember all the people that he's I called people mediocre Negroes
Stuff like that
He seems to love calling black people Negroes
It seems to love calling women b******
Mocking
People for
You know
He likes going on TV and revelling in his
Monstrous Behavior
Next clip
Awesome
Because this
Is what I would call
A sales pitch
Okay this is like Alex
That you really think that he's about to go to a sales pitch
Isabel
Haha
This time he's doing this is like this caught me off-guard
He would have cost me over for sure
This is Iverson level
Hugo
Level of deceitful creatures
Chimeras for you
Last night
Leafly
Yesterday specialists
We are skeletons
Because I've got to have a sales meeting at the shower
So first of all I think we talked over
Because it's a subtle thing
I think I want to go back to try and make my point
But also are you see there is always extend
That's another important point
The
These are terrible awful people
And then there's a little bit of a brief
What that's when he's got to get into the sales pitch
But he doesn't
And then he gets into
A sales pitch
That's the part that's remarkable to me
Elizabeth is beginning like 15 seconds again
Hey tell me you don't think
That went he actions
Alright let's get to tonight or last night's clip
That's where the sales pitch is supposed to go
Deceitful
Right here for you
You're right
Yesterday
Zigzag
I'm so bored with this dumbass
I think he's going to
I'm so bored
I'm just
Picking these tiny little motorcycle that's weird
Maybe it is for everybody I apologize by waste
So
Alex wants to make a metaphor about the fires of Liberty
Burn the rug
That's a great metaphor
It's super pain
But I want to I'm going to spoil what he ends up saying
Because I think it's important to really bring this into polka
He says that
Are going to
The globalists are going to run to their castles
And those castles will be
Weather burned in their oven
Speed test
Basically
Not great
We're going to be there
There's a couple unfortunate pieces about
Never say that
About somebody
Usually a bad idea
Don't do that
Especially when Nazis are on the rise in America
When it's very clear
That your worldview is
Globalist
Equals Jew Banker
Add stuff like that
So when you're saying these
Globalists are running to their tassels
What most people
Especially the bigots
Get it
In the audience
That
Those International Jews
And so when you when you then refer to it as oven
It is very very
Bad
Take Claire dogwood
Yeah
So clear if you're not if you're not paying attention though you're like
That's just how it is
Dumbass rhetoric
When in reality that is signal to all of his
Nazi followers
Cuz it sounds like
Cover it
Immediately after
Like it might just be
Be something that came out of his mouth
But make no mistake
That is not
Like I don't
Think that
There's a hundred other ways
If you want to say they're going to be burned
Play
Or something like that
Things people are not burned in oven
Except in one
Very specific
There is one other specific
Another one
Oh oh yeah
Not related
That's definitely try to know that
Even with all that put to the side
Is f****** torture
It is so awful
Enjoy enjoy literature major
On fire
You the fire extinguisher Kohl's robot
Golf in your own
Close up
And we'll burn down these evil people
Before
The heavens a week in a time of Ezekiel
Turning away the tyranny
Like in Ezekiel
Ladies and gentlemen
You saw that Eclipse you see how beautiful this you know that
Strong
Strong because of the eclipse
Also it was pretty cloudy in Chicago
Not that impressive
Although I
I did make a good joke with my boss
Really need glasses
Cloudy out I looked up at it I'm not blind yet
I hear that happens like the day after
I don't want to tell you just get cross
Never looks at me
This next clip
Thought is
Weird
Peter than that
No cuz that metaphor wasn't that weird
Like the fires of Liberty getting out of control if you try and put them out
I think I could make a better metaphor if I wanted to
But still super weird about that and how bad he is
The metaphor
Out of nowhere saying oven
Right that's the word
But this clip
I don't I don't even know I don't even
Know-how
They're going to be like three or four parts
Famous episode that I just don't know how to tell you
I don't know what to do
So I just have to play with
Don Lemon
Images
What is a lawyer did
He wants to resign
President
You said that
Believe
We should talk to one person
What does put you in here all alone
And with liquid was coming on later the sheriff
Do you want to thank us for helping the president
It's not about it's about the story
That if you can get to him
Know something's happening he will research
Globalist play the part of collect
One-sided
They're coming
And we are bracing now
Gcnlive.
Shout out at the end of a
He's got to get stuff out off his chest
That we've accomplished more in the last
Two years that we have in the last hundred
Is f*****
That is so f*****
Because
What happened in the last hundred years
Civil Rights Act
New Deal
What else
What is
What have we accomplished in the past
What is Trump and the Patriots a screwed-up to the false group that Alex
Thanks as a present
That's what
No
Of course not all of the strictures of Global's
As we understand what Alex's
Believe
In our previous episode
None of them know and if Trump really did want
To do what Alex
What he would have done immediately.
The fat
Like if you was the person that Alex Jones thinks
He would have bought it at the side
That's the biggest thing for the
Globalist
Hawking wingdings
Is the idea of a federal bank
Needs to be checked
Because all this national debt isn't real
Have you audited
You find it all these Baxter's
Then we should put them
Well the Federal reserve's
Really the Federal Reserve
The idea of
The Federal Reserve
I'm starting to actually
Think that Alex Jones might vs Auburn
I found a clip from 2015 that makes me
But he might really actually be on that
I call it will get to it eventually in the investigation
But a caller calls in and
Explain the idea of Maritime admiralty
Dialysis
Okay I'm confused as to what he was
He was talk
Secret people
Like scammers
Campaign office
This is something we've talked about before then
Turn off
MN riots
The Originals
And then
But all the leakers would put us two years from
Campaign whenever Rogers Hornsby sing the people in the white house we're almost fired
The man who legally can get nowhere near the White House
You can get as close to the lighthouses in Kansas
CNN
Reince priebus
Tenure
Don't overlap at all
This is just a convoluted narrative that Alex has a globalist
Inside were trying to trick
Trump loyalists
Into quitting
And then they do not jump he's like
Let's just not
Which
We're dealing with so that probably would have
Yeah probably anybody's office
Doesn't burn like Trump fired you ignore you
That is a description
Jen of one of the most disorganized
Chaotic
Backstabber
Awful Administration
I can possibly imagine
To even
The reality
That's terrible
Yeah we probably shouldn't
Allow them to have any
Kind of government
Do you know what
Even if they are
Real fuk up
They're screwing up
Creating a ministration
That's okay
And every possible respect that literally
Not one thing they have done
With any sort of cop
Implement any of that
These are the dumbest people
In the history
Of American
Jordan I can tell you one thing
What they've done
That is not terrible
That is not created any
Babies that don't have souls
Now listen to this next clip
No infinities
Never
No no
Yo no no no no no no no no no no no
No no no no you will not get control
You will not win you will not tell everybody you will not deform everyone
It's a person
They're like
This for pericecal izle
Imprint
They just take on
Program
And just go around power trips
Artificial synthetic sociopath
As opposed to our homegrown socio
Once which they want to cut off its virtue
He's no chewing on Kanis
Innocence is the window into Xfinity from mind of God
Ever seeking ever-lovin ever
Wishing
Set trailcal he mailed babe
You know that's how you really
Radicalize your audience
The mainline people
Who opposed
Political ideas
Want to kill your children
They would run through a kindergarten with a hatchet
Which I want to say is maybe a stab at the Juggalos
And I don't appreciate that
So their symbol is a guy running with a hatchet
Oh okay
Publix
Redhatter
In the movie The Patriots
I'm guessing based on his reading level
So
Well he was fake crying so maybe read where the red
Could be
Thor Bridge
To Terabithia
Other children's books
The other day don't hold on hold on
I know you're chomping at the bit there
We need to unpack this very important piece
The way
In that clip
Leads me to believe he
Big
That's a lot of people who disagree with him
Are clones
I kind of feel that way
As if like
He's not talking about a hypothetical future
He's talking about these
Synthetic will walking around even a metaphorical description
640 baby
Even said like
They got five parrots
But they don't have souls
Like wait but how many parents do you need
Vitro fertilization mean you don't have it
Multiple genetic material coming out of his idea if we took his logic to its
Don't have a soul
Yeah
How else would you get that synthetic
Senzo feedback
Sociopath
Chicopee state
Bet you believe
Woodmont would disagree with it
The devil the devil is real
And he's doing all kinds of clones running around all over the place because they have five
Oh my God this is
Open the WikiLeaks
All people talk about it was on the show
So much more The Source here
What
Best
Like this
Is the type of ship
It's like every every article you see
Dislike
How did Trump people feel about Trump now that he's ruining their lives and they don't even know it
It's like here's what they feel
Anybody disagrees with them is trying to murder
Them every single point
Or password
The point of
Can you talk to these people because they think you're trying to
I would never never operate in the same I'm still willing to even talk to
I will give everyone the benefit
Until proven otherwise
I don't like descending into that we can't talk to the other side
Stop
But I do believe that a large
Portion of the people who won't turn on Trump
Despite
Mounting evidence
The Russian ship being
Mary real
And
The fact that he's just going
To destroy
The entire country through his
Ego greed
Siphoning off money to his own businesses
The siphoning off money all the kleptocracy s***
Right so but like they will never turn on it because
They are indoctrinated into this called
Essentially
Globalist
Why
I'm particularly offended by Joe Rogan jumping on board with a lot of these people who are in The Alex Jones
Yeah as it were
I understand he wants to give a fair day in court to all sorts
The people but
If Peter Schiff was on
Let's say
There's no way we would allow him to say the things
But he says
Without at least pushing Back 40
Considerably on these
These ideas be faulty economic ideas
Well if we had a monarch we would spend a week
Prepping
We would have
We would have everything
He regularly
It's about weed
Charts
We would go through all of this
Because we care I'm probably try not to talk about his dad
I think it would be hilarious
Oh yeah
The point is my point
Is this even if we're going outside of our
That we follow along
Even the mainstream
GOP people
Even whenever they give us this
Dislike Trump is reach the 60
4%
The proofing
The GOP will still vote 48
Percent for
Right
4 / over the
This is what we used to be
It will still be every GOP voter voting for
Exist as a
Positive
There's no
Republicans are for
A non-existent
They are just
They are just filled with I hate this
And they will use any rationale
Justify their
But I don't think it's fair to say that and not say that it is
True that most Democrats would just vote for any Democrat also
Makes it okay because obviously
Lee Trump is
Then any political alignment is that same block step walking
Specifically blaming Trump
A bottle but I I just think it's
Do you know it's important to be fair
There's a lot of
Just
You know
Mindless
The other side socks our side is great
Another kind of problem
Rissa
Especially when party systems in the world today
I think that is
Not entirely what I was
Was talking about
Hey I was talking
More about
Rather than it being a
Party
It's more just
This is that right ideology
No
I think you're wrong.
Is very malleable
They fall in line with whatever fits
The most important pieces of their ideology which is
Don't give stuff
Two people
Diane lower taxes
But that's all
Negative
Call a.j.
Remove
Well then we don't get that way
Rationalize any of these dumbass
You know Obamacare is bad
The rationalized with
Just because they hate Obama
Just because they want to tear down
Wage was like
Minimum having a minimum wage
Employee
Because
Hey you know what
Say you want a job and you want to work for $3 an hour
UPS
You don't have the power to do that
Because you can't it's against the law
So if you want to have that if you want to have that
In our world what you get is $0 an hour cuz you can't have a job but if there was no minimum wage
If you could get that $3 an hour job
You be making $3 an hour
It's all stupid
Is that
His conception of taking away the minimum wage which we know is a negative
He's trying to make it a positive for everybody
This is a game for you
You could get $3 hour and 20
Again that's just a rationalization for their
Hell-bent
Destruction of the new deal
Like that's all they really want
The Rings upon dreams upon reams of history book
Explaining
People are so f******
Dumb
Process
Will just always come up with some sort of alternative or something
Written
Heritage Foundation
Only ancillary disproves a small tiny little bit of this if it even does that at all
We have our own special
Gotcha
What about like that
They don't
Believe in anything
Well
They just don't want any of this s*** around because they hate
But now I'm deeply concerned because there is there is
But
University party
Has come to prominence and now
The Tea Party is kind of absorbed into the larger Patriot movement
Whatever you want to call
Because there's a lot of there's a lot of
There's a lot of moving pieces with it but they're all sort of coming
Together
Draws them all together is a really anti-government
Release anti federal government
Stamps
They're like the witch of Liberty hard libertarian
The Liberty people the Patriots
Even the alt-right
There is a Peter Schiff
But if there is a
Complete believe
That the federal government imposing anything on you is
Some sort of a crime or violence against
It is as that gets absorbed into the GOP
And becomes the mainstream of the
Conservative side
You you look at a really dangerous proposition
Do you know Prince
Nipples is almost better to that
Straight up
Destruction
How do you run a campaign where one person is like I think the Federal
Government to do nothing
Brooklyn
I have some ideas
Right
What you do how does that argument work
I don't know
The federal government doing nothing is really the best
For you
That's the argument if you're trying to run a campaign on no I'm saying or down the government debate end up
Working cuz the person
On the other side
Just forced to take the position of
Federal government
Whereas logical position is
Federal government has its problems with there's some things we need to work out in
There's so much.
It would never
Ever ever be possible
Were it not for federal government intervention
Yep
Like
Dirk carry the load of this larger population
Urban centers existing
Astronomy
Beginning
With Federal invest
Higher leaf
The federal government
Search
Play technology the Arts
Culture
The Civil War is not going to
Canan
State score
You know north-south any
Cities versus
Imagine it like if I will I will never take up arms against La Monte
God dammit
I know if we switched even though you know like
Ancient classical times
It's
All of this stuff
So much would just
Destroyed and lost
Without some sort of unifying federal government
Chicago is
It would be
Jackson
And they calling for anti-government
The most anti-government
Are the ones who are going to die
Maybe
That's what they have there is a death call
Call I don't know. You sound like out
Run through your daycare
With a hatchet
So
I don't stand by that new.
So in this next clip
This is fun
Cousin
How do you know what
I'm just
I'm just a f***
Done
I'm just so f****** done with
These people
Get started
Babies with no stove
So this next clip with five
Alex Jones
Gets mad
Which is hilarious
Pretty fun
A butt
He starts getting into it
Start making jokes
And you can't do that.
That's not good you can't tell from the audio
What is on Skype
And you can see him laughing
The Intern
Steve pieczenik
He gets on the bike
For the first time
Strongly disagree with
Looking for a way out
Again the same lies and McConnell deserting him
This is a test controlling the narrative
I kill a lot of people
Hey dude
Ordered killed yourself
I want
I want to do stupid
Steven looks like
Reality
Fake laugh
I'm sorry
Yeah
It's okay go ahead
I don't think anybody really
How is this okay
It's okay for anyting anywhere anybody because this is us Steve pieczenik
Maintains his space in the order
Just Mindless sycophant
Able to trick Alex into believing all these counter-coup narrative
Some stuff like that
Whatever Alex goes off on
Whatever the f*** that was
Just laughing is me a big like
And then almost immediately transitioning into the point
Which I actually kind of agree with some of the point is we don't need to listen to none of him
Talking about how
We can we cannot
Duplicate
Continue it
Sending more troops is a really terrible idea
That's clearly it's clearly the work
It worked into
It worked
In 2011
Burton 2004
It worked
In 2006
It worked in
I don't
Agree with Steve pieczenik about a lot
Disease
A little bit not
But I do agree
Listening to him kind of boring
It's just so gross
Natsu
Is even worse than
Pull it off by thingy
And I love down
I love them
What is that
It's just f******
Disgusting
Saltz Colorado by calling him retarded then says I loved
I give the Special Olympics as people are
And then says what Karl Rove does have idiots
Like what
This is a world
Jesus has no Bass
But anyway
We can't make it bog down
It's just him being stupid it's the fundamental inability
To treat
It's almost like he's a synthetic psychopath
Or or easy could just be
Eclipse starts with
This next clip starts with the what is pretty inspiring tone and then gets to something I
I can't believe it's
So that's at this will be another Whirlwind roller
You never know when you're doing little thing
How big it is
An example of
Millions and and and
Most people
10 TV shows ever
Values
Hank Hill Terrier
Shirley Wright
Dale Gribble the conspiracy theorist
Alex Jones
Yep Hank Hill
But also Dale Gray
Is
His death
Is Grandpa and crazy weirdo who's on the TV
Exactly
I don't know I've heard a lot about
Everytime I think about Hank Hill I'm like
Hello to Alex Jones
I don't think Alex
Quite.
The point of King of the Hill where the humor came from
He doesn't have
He just sees that and goes
Oh look it's my values being reflected
Biting satire
But also there is
Literally
No way
That Mike Judge
True
Like the two of them are French
Hank Hill based on
But the other thing is I like where he's coming from at the beginning
Call Larry
If it's true
The I like when he's coming from at the beginning when he's saying that you never know who you're reaching like today we got the email from
Estonian
We have gotten a lot of emails and
Messages from people who
I have no f****** idea how they found the show
And it's really cool
It's really neat to know the people are listening
Isn't that kind of a message from Alex
I can dig it
Well I love it
The bases
Bob Belcher from Bob's Burgers
But you
The other thing is we should say that David Knight
Has finally launched his own
They broadcast in the morning
David has got his own show real news
I have not watched it
Because of course I'm not going to watch that it's got to be boring as s***
Real News Real do
With David
Here's the news
I get jumped from Aunt
Who's the news
Terrible Herbst trash
No we're not making fun of his based on his
I saw a picture of him from early
I like
Around 2008 or so
Holy
He was spelled
He has gotten I'm not insulting him he looks fine cuz he looks like a
Do you also love Down syndrome kids know he looks like it looks like a condom evil Grandpa
9 Grandpa
He probably probably would like a good 40 lb
Lighter
Like his face
Slim
Weirded me out
Doesn't that imply that
It's not real news
If you're reinforcing the idea that it's real news maybe it's more like
No no it's real news
It's real news don't go don't go
It's real news the first episode was about how Luanne from King of the Hill
Skip this next court cuz it's just Alex Jones millions of dollars of funding
Because this neck
But that we are going to play as much more important
Steve pieczenik is on hold music
Open Skype
Studio
Call from
I can only describe as anti-Semitic
And let's see what happens
Is his name anti-Semitic
Might as well be
11:20 a.m.
Wbcm wants to talk about Afghanistan
Listen honor to speak to Alexa like you
This is what I want to say we need to get out of Afghanistan the Middle East is no point of us being there
Tremendous power
Between for Trump
Who was an international Jewish Banker, doesn't it colonists
Who's behind the Occupy Wall Street movement
Dianne Feinstein
You got Soro trying to overthrow Israel Netanyahu
In the documents in the lazy lake
Images
Heavy Collective as models
Israel
Come on
Prank called anti-israel
Israel
Yeah that wasn't exactly was a occupation
What is your real view on this
The guy that did the
Oh no thanks for that
We got us
From Alex Jones
Pronouncing it
Quad
What's
I love you
Keep us in
Make sure you destabilize the Middle East
Has attempted to save another's all kinds of different
Which is a nice way to put it
Because they're left it's not because they're Jews
Different Jews it takes
Apec isn't a leftist organization at all
Bari Lynn one of the most hard right the f****** country is
So he's home
Argument
The guy
Was
Respect
But that guy
Is he
Spencer
Salute
He would rather blame Jews for
Oh I know a group of people who would rather blame Jews for their problem
Can you think of another group of people who hate
Anti globalist
Haha
Let's see
Banana
Okay
Speaking of someone who probably totally cool with an optic
Joe arpaio's time
This this clip
I really feels about what's been done
To him
Quiet and we'll get through it
I only have like four clips of him or so and mostly they're just him saying stupid s***
So we can get through it
Just don't yell
Just keep it in
This first clip
Is really it's kind of funny when you look at the big
Unfortunately it's not funny
He's responsible for many deaths
Visions of horrible crimes
Because victims were
Immigrants
In this together
Brotherhood
Persecuted
Golden talk to you yet him on so I have a good lawyer
For a change
I'm fighting this
And I'm never going to surrender
And I'll tell you I'm going to try to get the real story out about the abuse
It was.
Think of that
And that's dangerous for our country
Can do it to anybody
Is atrocious
Currently not true
Comfortable with the fact that if you are a serial killer apparently you can't do anything to that f***
Time Trump has not pardon him and there's some question
Even has the authority to do that
I don't think he does
The idea that
He's portraying this is a Witch Hunt against him is funny
But if you just take this sentence
If they can do this to me
They can do it to anybody
And I am
Braum's
Is it if they can do
Which is
Pursue legal action
Court
If you are that person
Who
Has a clear history of racial profiling
Abusively
In a police department
I'm fine with that happening to anybody who does that
You like I'm fine. I'm not doing that
I'm not committing the race place
Offenses
Suck it
Can convict me of a crime I committed
What's next
You don't want to live in that America
You don't want to live in America where people who commit crimes
F****** investigating arrested for it we don't live in that f****** America.
He's being charged
Of course nonsense because he deserves to be here
So much more
There's something more going on
Consistently refuses
What he's talking about
Because
He hasn't been pardoned
About talking about the case publicly before you
In the clear
So you keep saying like more better lawyer than Alex
I can't talk about it now I'm not going to get into it
I love
But you accidentally does white slip what he thinks
This is actually going on in this next
Nazi collaborator
Well he's here
Negative talk about now why feel
He really went after me and I'm not going to get into birth certificates right now
Subject matter
You did just get into it
Look at you think there's another reason why Soros hates me I'm not going to get into it but it's
It's my b******* about Obama and how his birth certificate is allegedly faked which
Are we still on that are we still on the bus
Jesus
F****** ass
Piece of s***
Go to a federal pen
VenturianTale
Dies
Like everyone
I'm not seeing enough recognition
People talking about like
What's the connection between Trump
They were the President and Vice President
Obama's birth certificate is fake Club
Jude allies
Alex is hold b******* about like
Know that Ohio was being
Do you know if taken
The two of them are allies
To imagine
The only reason from
Degree
Normal allies yes
But this was a we are racist
Together
Illegal immigrants
We hate
Anybody
We hate Max
Because we hate everybody
Anybody not white
I think bigotry Bond
The coward
A hateful person's version of being in a foxhole with someone
Because the two of them
Look the world around them being a
Attack on whites
All the time
I'm needing to protect White
Kind of a war that they're in
Heather Conrad
I don't think that necessarily
I think the Trump would definitely pardon him if you can
Yeah
I think there's a big part of that is because
The two of them had that birther
War together
He can see that his dumbass Bass
Like
Infowars and all those people start going
This is a good man this is Deborah
Serial killer
It's possible
And so it's just one of those things where cuz they
They have the same
Where in Trump says something
Fox News says how it's a great idea
So Trump keeps
Says this is a great ideas
The Trump is like
People who love me are going to love this idea
So he talks about it and so on and so forth
They just found shity ideas off of each other
They're burning the world
Yeah you may be right
Anyway we'll never know for sure until it's too late to move on
The next Clippers
Ferrari internationalism
You'll know why as this clip goes on
He's great overseas I think you know the more than any signal when is
They just love if you are an international listener of knowledge fight
Please send us an email at knowledge Gmail
Is that the same to you get I would like to know
I would like to know cuz I am not overseas
I would like to know from the perspective
OVA are listeners
All over Europe
Landa other
Places that are probably listening
That happened contact
I'd like to hear from you let me know
That won't throw me off at all
If your
Trump is our listeners like Trump
That would throw me off quite a bit osher but it's that way
But if
You know
A lot of people in Sweden
Do love Donald Trump
Play examples
Our friends shirt
What have you
I just feel
It's
It's okay I feel sorry for him but you know why he's tough
And I said this was when the when I first introduced him two years ago in Phoenix
It was kind of an empty platform stage if you know what I mean
My gut tells me he'll go down as one of the greatest
Presidents we had ever had in this country
Mark my words
It's all over
Just reputation
George Washington
I look forward to hearing
One day but that's all
That's all such b*******
That's crazy
Consider your words
What
I mean
If Trump
He will go down in history as one of the best presidents
Well there's a whole
Because there will still be a hist
If we don't actually solve
There's a whole list of things that theoretically
Could do
Like he could solve the problem in the Middle East
Call climate change could bring peace to the world
He could take us off-planet he could bring us life-extension technology the holographic medbay
Goodreads
But they can't be.
What's up with them for other reason
Logistical reasons
But other ones
Or because he's not going to do them
He's not going so climate change is not going to be
Those things are not in his agenda
Grandma thinks he's acting like
He's going to do
You can do. Really
So
It look
No
This is so f****** pathetic on Alex's part cuz all he does is talk about it like
Just jacks off about the founders
And I all this
And if you
If he doesn't know anything about history
You can't possibly believe
That Trump is going to
Tubidy
Heralded as one of the greatest president of all time
How good you will be okay
Can you hang your hat on when you say that
The only reason is
Because he thinks he's going to defeat the globalist
That's it
The globalist witch
Again
Has no
Endgame
For that
Defeating globalstar doesn't
It's defeating the globalist by itself doesn't
Set up
And infrastructure
No but it does break everyone
And then we will know
The climate change
Isn't real
And we should actually be putting more CO2 out
Because
The atmosphere is carbon dioxide
Deprived
But it's all just a big Tech
Scam
Taxes and what-have-you
I'll run around kids
So that's what he's talking about he's talking about the idea that Trump is going to take down this
Imagine group of globalist
These 6,000 people is he Alex
But on the show before
Who are taking down the world
And trying to depopulated it take away our sperm
Even if you aren't even if you agree with what Trump is doing
You have to admit that he's spectacular
Regularly
Even if you even if you think what Trump is doing
Is what should be done
He's just
Rope-a-dope
I don't know how well you know this dimensional chest
Broca do like for real
The fact that
He's just doing so much
All the time
It's hard to maintain any kind of resistance to
Desensitize to his latest
Prime
We haven't done anything about it
Something about it later
Until
What
What happened
I think the
You know it is easy to get distracted
To buy whatever
Crazyshit he does every week or so it seems like it's almost on a schedule
Everyone I think
Most
People who
I don't know I think a lot of people are just hoping
That
This investigation
Is Progresso
Going to workout
I think we're going to have to I think we're going to have to do what they did
Insole
Duke mob
Just
100 million
Maybe
Martin Luther King
Was
He was going to March a million people on washing
Holyshit
A million people it needs to be
I just don't know
Yeah but what is it
I mean I'm talking about
Yeah really what it is
We have to go there
Occupy Wall Street
The world we're living in now of course the National Guard will be
Be called in totally
I mean it would be a bloodbath
Nobles need to have
These militias in the
Ditto
The alt right
Agitators
To do a lot of trouble
I don't know man
We'll see we'll see what happens
That we're going to skip this next court cuz I don't want I don't want to listen to Joe Arpaio anymore
Just a teaser
Like we need we need a Flashpoint we need some sort of leader like Luther King Junior
We need somebody who can
We need a Fred Hammond
Beer
We just don't
It's Jordan now definitely not me
I don't think I don't think people are going to Rally Millions behind a guy whose us often do on white genocide
I like I said I'm going to skip this next cuz it's just
Eighty-five percent
I care about you and write
To be saying on the air
You disgust
Timberlake
Is 95 /
I was going to make it
Sing joke
I've had it
In my back up there song digital get down
Baby song
No strings attached
The album
It's called digital get down and it was all about to heaven cybersec
Outlook 2002 or something
It's real embarrassing looking back
Deflecting my experience
Xx2
Baby baby
Baby baby baby baby
CB
There's a lot of babies in there
They didn't have songwriters I think I did
Sorry I meant
I meant they were
So that means that there's some guy
Is just like Vicks baby
Well there was also like it was as weird. Of time where people were talking about
But essentially master
Pretoria
And songs a lot
Cuz there was that other song about phone
Insects
Perhaps it was singing the song about
Sex on the line
Or something like that
It was like in the same year or so
There's digital get down and that phone sex
What is going on
What what is a kite
I guess to be fair let me be clear
Digital get down was not a sick
I did have the album
Zeitgeist
Like you were just trying to just
Defy your own cyber sex
Arijit Singh song it's popular
Boy
Confirm
AOL
Digital get
I have to play through the phone
Are your safe
For now
Rebecca
So
Skipping this clip
We're going to move on now.
To post Joe Arpaio
So
Bios gone
I do but his knowledge fight the podcast where Dan tries to make Jordan kill himself
That's kind of what this podcast is
Get down get down
Jordan
I told you
Earlier
There we had to remember psychic Goblin
For these goblins
Literal guttural Goblin
Too much
Literal
Psychic
So we're well past lord-of-the-rings territories
Maybe
Warcraft
This is a mic down
Clip because you need to get all the nuance
And then it gets into Alex
Jones
Maybe almost was a globalist
We need to hear all of it cuz it
We're going to need two parts
It's real f*****
This clip is f*****
Stop
We are all bad
What you want
Is the big pardon
Man I used to doubt that but now I've lived a long time
Thousand Years actually
Evil
When you share the same thing out of somebody's mouth
Same weird stuff
And the person
Growls at your door like this is Linda Blair this is real that's
And a mama. Happens to you
And somebody said something nobody knows
Talking and smiling
And they just said something nobody knows you're like what the hell's going on
Kid
Let's
Corrupt child
Have sex with a child
Abused your child
Kill your child
Only
What's your name
The movie of the remake of a
Or he's going to live until
He's alive because great returning out the operation
I've talked to people and I
Experience it was younger and almost went that direction
Dennis like everything quite hot everything slow motion
An older is a
Little glimpse
Tortured
Drug
But other than that
Hardcore bands basically
Criminology
And
Something is seduced by the dark side
Fullback
What
What's
Men go to work
Seduced by the dark side
I was hoping you would understand
Was it just
Was it
You're looking for the big
Right
That's the reprieve
Then there are people who know things in different cities so you know that it's true
Do they do the same thing which might behave
F*** you Alex
I hope that means out there here in multiple cities
Right
There Linda Blair
Okay telling you things
Months before anybody knows another front but information is from like a month ago and nobody knows it
Like you stole the cookie
Or something like that
Okay alrighty
Before anybody else
Okay. It's something from the past
They look like goblins and they're saying we're going to get you
This is schizophrenia
No
These are all leftist
Right of course
And again I'm sorry the thing cut out
When he's talking about the leftist
Yeah there's
The left
Our fallen
They all know this
They'll know this stuff
We all know
Literal psychic
Antoine's
And clothes with five different and we are all sick
Okay
Why are we doing this again
Because we're falling I don't know
No doubt that's still not why good men go to war and get seduced by the dark side
Children
The Goblins are really let off there
Jeff is when they get to torture with the introduction
Transition between
Goblin
Only feel comfortable in their abuser
And then
Right
This is what I want to talk a little bit more about is that idea that Alex
Almost went down the path
Because I don't think it was Denzel's
Choice
To be your man
I think it was
To him
I mean
Don't bring
That
Reality do this
I haven't seen the remake
But
The same plot
He's being mine
Control
General killed
Must believe that it's some point he was subject
To mind control
Possibly
No I think he has to believe that
He could have gone along with it but Broke Free
Cuz he saw all the things
So what he's really saying
Is that all the good men who go to war and then get seduced by the dark side
When he was a child okay
Bright
Now that we know this
Everybody who is good that goes into the military is
Right and they they get said they are all bigots seduced
He describes it as a bright light
Full bright light
This is
Insane
Schizophrenic
Hallucinations
Basically being described
This is not
Any other ex
And we're getting back to the end of the March 30th episode
Yeah like his tone is changing
There's also this oversharing
As usual right but I mean like this stuff he shouldn't be saying stuff like this on the air
This is this is really easy to see through like
You got those of the deep
You're not using Browns because of it you're not using metaphorical language
You really think that
Yeah this is something you believe there are
Psychic goblins that are coming up
Do you and threatening you
That is something that
I think is relevant
To his listeners I think they should understand that this is a crazy person
That they're listening to
And
If you want to listen to crazy person for entertainment
God bless you
I watched a lot of Steve-O videos in my day
That's fine
Value of someone who has
A little bit
But most of
To be fair
If you're going to be listen
Coming to a guy
Who believes their psychic
Goblin
You're running around and attack
Or threatening
Ain't that a lot of people who disagree with him or
Clones
With five parents
Better
They got no soul baby they got no soul
I would suggest
Don't take political advice from that guy
Also
Don't take economic advice from that guy
Don't buy
His off-brand herbs and pills
Oh did you see that
Great and great course weekend
Of course we do
Course
Beyond
I really need to impress upon people
This guy is not a political pundit
You may never have been
But boy he is not now
Drunk
Probably mentally ill f****** lunatic
And I would not use those words about someone else who
Struggling
But because he's such a
Dick people like Alexander Dugan
And Joe Arpaio on his show
Pretty fine calling him a f****** loot
Dickweed
So
I don't know as as a mentally ill person
Usually trying to
Take the side
There's a lot of stuff that
Do that
Alex
I wonder like I wonder about that I wonder
About the brain damage
May or may not be there
Dr. group
What was the last time
A medical professional
When was the last time
Somebody obtained a medical degree
University
Song Alex
Like on the street I just looked him in the eye
Alex Jones sitting on that little paper on the table
Yeah I would
Actually I want to see you I want to see the physical result
Two kind of bait Alex into suing
I'll be fine because if he did in Discovery I think we could demand video of a psych evaluation
Probable
Well I mean I guess in his divorce or the custody battle they had a psych evaluation the lady said that he has like a narcissist
6 personalities
Disorder
No I unless it was entirely about the show
Cuz if it's about the show then we can
Use clips
Right cuz it was in the divorce
They couldn't use the
Well no I'm not I'm not talking about that I'm trying to find ways
There we could trick him into going
Because even though I hate him and even though I do
I think he's done a lot of damage to the world I think if he
Got treatment
You might
Be happier
I think we got on actual meds and went out of his pills like antipsychotics
Like I I wonder if you would be as focused on these imaginary globulus
If you was getting
Like if you was actually on the medication he clearly needs
He wouldn't be seeing literal Goblin
Buns everywhere
He probably would still have terrible reading comprehension skills
But he probably wouldn't be demons all over the
Probably
Go to
Call me we wouldn't have a show so that's
2 triangle
Maybe you could have stayed just being crazy
Government Ranger
That is not funny enough
Lap dancing
Joe Rogan for all his faults
I think one of the main reasons he's having these
These people on
Sincere curiosity
About this
Group
That everyone hates
Hey the unfortunate thing is he is curiosity is leading him to validate
As opposed to
Understand why everyone hates
Instead of doing that he could
They wrote
That would be helpful if you did some research
But be that as it may be a few more clips
Are f******
End of the night
Sad
F***** up drunk
Just like
Running out of gas Alex
This is
4 ways to learn Alec
Text Tootsie
This first one is
First one is
That is really sad
I'm almost ashamed but if you only turned loose
My job's a lot easier, Florida gun so much
Cella Vista supplements
I will. I'm your body can absorb
Text to
Yesterday I got a ride who's taking over Owen Shroyer
I left that in
Even though it's
You know irrelevant to our
Just because Owen Shroyer will come back up blast clip
In one of the
Satisfy
Chances of ever heard Alex
That was
That looks rough
That was brutal
And if people think that I'm just
Well one of the things to his whenever I
Some of it
Applications that I give
AR
This sort of s***
And then also he was drinking out of a suspicious cup
During the show
Gotcha generally he'll have a coffee mug or something like that
He had a wife
Paper cup
Oh that's that's the cop
Well I mean I don't know doesn't really prove anything but it is
What is a little
I don't know
Anyway
F****** bummer
The end of his 3 hours
Owen Shroyer
Actually don't think it's Owen sure I think Paul Joseph Watson hours
PJ dubs
This
Is profoundly sad
It is a bummer
I still hate him I don't give him any
Leeway
As it were
But
Susie says
In relation to Owen Shroyer like I said
Is
You'll see
7-Eleven
Sorry I forgot that he was going to play the entire
97 minutes
75 minutes
From the top here cuz you got it you got a f****** here though
Shroyer
Come on play the
Comment on them talk about him get them all in
I want to play the clips I haven't always Great Clips are so important and I don't get to him
That's all coming up next hour
Infowars.com has wallet posted newswars.com
Infowarsstore.com
We are
Doing pretty good
But my gut tells me I've got a sue
Cuz they're cutting everybody else offered up with her
Go for a job doing okay right now then I'm giving into him so I got to fight him
Start soon
Please looking for a fight
You know what you're a bossy upside ahead I'm going to get you
Open
They're coming back yet
I just want to make sure my heart keeps popping all the way
And as long as you financially supported
Realize that there are articles are videos
Cars
Is victory over this trash
We're not just doing it
That is so wonderful
The marketplace of ideas
Global to come after us because
What's the devil do
Give Network
Basement
That's so sad
Like he thinks either
You think he's John Wayne
In a cowboy boot
Don't be like me
You're right I'm just
You got to be a better man than me Andre well there's got to be a better man
But then
I think that there's actually a difference. Going on
Yeah I think he wants
To look like
But Woody's
Actually saying
If you look at what he says immediately after
Gift telling Owen Shroyer don't be bad at your job
The Pointe at Owen Shroyer
Don't play the clipse
Take the calls
I've been on I've been on the air for 3 hours
And I've mostly just drunkenly rambled about the devil
I said I was going to play a bunch of trump clips
I said I was going to take that one anti-semite
I don't know what was going on
Don't be like me
Be better at your job
But I think there's even a
Further subtext of it
Cuz what he does immediately after
Is going to a sad f******
Sales pitch
That also involved
We're doing pretty good
Also saying is
Don't be like me
I have to run around trying to get all this money to
The fight the globalist
Be a newsman Owen Shroyer be like water filters from Big Berkey
Did to make the bills come together don't do that
Fight
Fight to the news fight
I can't do it I don't have the skills
Spoiler alert neither Zone Troy
Woody's
I think what he's saying is
He's really internalizing the fact that he is just
A f****** sales
That all he does
Get up and make it up
Scream but the globalist
Wanting to take your children
To scare you just enough to keep you around
So he can f****** sell uShip
And I think
I think he realizes that I think he realizes that his role is not
Trusted respected news person
F****** talk about any news past the headlines
So he knows
Think it hurts them
I didn't this
F****** end of the show
Noon drunk
But I think he's just getting like
Don't do it this way
He's still just like
Cost
Logan Logan all my my
Look at all of it Owen
You'll never have it
But look at it
You don't want it
All the money in the world doesn't
Thank you for respecting
The truth
I have no soul baby
Ain't got no soul
An idiot
I also at the same time
I don't care
So
Usually usually I can find
Some kind of sympathy in these
Whenever we've cuz there's always that Whiplash whenever we do some of these words
I hope you get
I hope you die
You're just a sad
Add broken
Shell of a man
He's f******
Calling Karl Rove a Down syndrome
He said
Midget retard
Two words
That
Shouldn't be
Used
Offensive
Singularly
And horrific
Back to
Covering for his biggest political Ally who goes around and called everyone negro
Stop
You're right
Sorry.
So anyways
Goddamn Joe Arpaio
Lego
Then don't be like me
Don't Shout
I try not to
Severe cold detached
Heartless self
Just donate
If you'd like to be called
Go to our website how it's fight.com
I'm not entirely sure
Yahoo.com
Do if you're engaging with us
To me that
Signifies that
There is
I would I would assume something
That you deeply
Deeply carob
Regardless
We're methodists
We're All in This Together
Also there's a button that says support the show you want to click that you can become a
Short show coming up north bar in Chicago on the 9th of September
9th of September at 9
Triple 9
Could you say that it's Herman Cain's text Lionel
God so also.
Malachite
You know what to do
My balls
Also you can find us on iTunes swallows
Give us a review
Great picture up there
Absolutely
You want to leave million
The people and March
Do the
Capital house
Camp out there and
Thing is
About our
Horrible criminal monsters president
And his
Klepto kleptocratic
Coronavirus
Run by the government
Everywhere this plug goes if you want to do all of these things
Please do
For sure
Also I know where the end of the thing we usually do a bit
I got to go to the bathroom so I'm going to cut this short and just go f*** yourself
Thanks for holding
Alexandra Thurston color