Alexandra Thurston color
Regular
Do no f****** dudes to sit around
I talk about a thing
Like Charlie Rose or something like that
Folks were
You know they know a lot more emotionally even-keeled
Our little bit nuts
And I know I don't know what's going on
And his world to a lot of the issues plaguing
Immediately
Nice
A water along with
Tito's vodka down a little bit
So today that's the plan
The cure for what ails you
Speaking of what cures
The cause of and solution to
All of life
If you would like to become yourself knowledge
It's a delightful
Under sulfide
Hey
Span of time between
2 / 12
October 15th
Alright today is Earth shattering
Today
We make some real progress
Or do we
Only one way to find out
You know what this is I walked like 5 miles
From therapy scratched me on like
Weird mood almost
Almost like I'm some headspace I might get a little silly
Alright
Call vodka
This is the technique for Alex's right all along
To my wristband
The f******
Global Fitbit
Before we get Today Show I'd like to start off
With two out of context drops
Alex Jones
The special episode we got to
Slaves around New York on change
Alright
I'm going to go with
New York
Quebec City
This is
Because
The whole purpose of us going back to
Investigation Alex Jones
You love Donald Trump
Right
The whole point
But along the way
Figure out what he thinks about others
Actually on the same time we're going over today
Discusses what he thinks about Bernie Sanders
Parasailing
The top one tenth of 1% in this country 90%
August 12th
57%
Healthcap to all people as a right
Except you.
You see every other when you have a baby when I'm going to separate you
Paid
People from the UK
Rdr2
Getting things down
Either export an entire clip that I record
Export a part that I have highlights
And sometimes
I f*** that up
The problem with you in a good head
You're not
Focus
You're too happy you're going around thinking about all the good things that could happen
Instead of here
Lot
Please
Getting these clips
I apologize I listen to it
Petty and stupid as Alex was being
Hewlett-Packard
A lot
Yeah
Almost anything
He didn't have anything to come back with Alex
Bernie Sanders
Express
I don't think it is audience would really register
He's getting at
If you didn't play a quiz for
I always think there's a reason why he's over or doesn't talk over a cliff
He's either trying to
Show dominance
He just doesn't give a s*** and wants
Score points
People talk
He's either reverent to them
Or he knows that
Do you need contacts
In order to score points
Later like with that shity impression
I don't know man
Wellow
Bernie had not yet become the most popular politician in the United
Yeah as he is now
He was
Sittin at this point he's just a social
Listen
God dammit
But
If you are an Alex Jones listener and you hear that
That's one of those things that
It surprises me because that is a
Hugely popular position
Across the Spectrum if you're an Alex Jones listener
You're not hearing any of these conspiracy theories
You're just hearing Bernie make a goddamn
You're being played on Alex's show
What is
That
This guy is lying
Of course he's going to say that you're going to get all these things but that's just a
The trap to get to tyranny
Because Alex is already laid that that sort of narrative bed in place
So even if Bernie Sanders comes on
Is all the things
It doesn't matter it's not going to
What is
What Alex has
Liberty Way
He let Bernie talk
The
Problem
Which is
The top one tenth of 1%
More wealth than the bottom
Globalist
And Bernie Sanders won't audit the Fed
Who complained about that
Where's that
Hope I made her pretend that doesn't matter
Probably in their in their world absolute
We're going to start on October 12th
I'm telling you is a lot of interesting stuff we got to discuss coming up
It's that it's fairly song
Barely
Really underselling every
You're often come back after
You're somebody's broken your heart or something so we can
Read my emails from 2015
I really probably out
Here's a clip Alex that starts off his show on the 12th explaining
Do you cannot compromise with
Globalist
National sovereignty does not exist
The family does not exist mother and father does not exist
The Amish do not exist
It's so over-the-top
People have to realize
You can't be reasonable
You can't compromise with the globalist
They are not the left
They are hardcore
Asian
Focused
Groups concrete mesh
Mid-level managers
If you're sitting around a cocktail
Your table with him and say of course we're taking over
Of course were conditioning people we don't know
And in the left
The general I said that all the time
Ice cream truck music
Why would they are enemies
And sociopath
You have no hope
Okay
But like I've started to notice
Did Alex Jones starts off
A disproportionate amount of his shows
Really demonized
The gift
It's the last
You know just serves to radicalize
Okay
Your kid
You hear the ice cream truck
Clearly
It's not a weirdo
Grown up
It's just evil Carnival
Alright
Beat up
Creeper van
You go inside
Hoping for ice
On one hand
Pedophile
Sure other however you might find a demonic Wildcat
What about you
Preferable
What about just like a straight-up
Wildcat
Do you want
That's out of
Wildcat I'm assuming is like at least fifteen percent
Yeah that is true it's like
Steroids anabolic steroids
Alex's mention of the Amish
There's the option
There's a little narrative that he sells from time to time one of his waypoints back in 2015 that I haven't really
Deemed just got there was a Amish
Cheese cellar
That got
Bye
The government
It was because he wasn't
Using
Appropriate
Pasteurization techniques and reply back
And selling his two years across state line
So there were a couple issues and then also health issues
It was a
You know
He's dumb
That's weird
Gizmo
Keys for them in this case he's mad because it's the Federal
Because it's like interstate trade
And stuff like that federal government
He doesn't appreciate that
What's up Russian
Who cares look so much fun
Suppressing me
Yeah absolutely
I love I love all my mix with these
Phila federal laws
Breaking
Peeps
Shut up
Next clip
Just know this next clip
Alex Jones
Protest
But have been happening in Austin
Sing insight into this on the other side of it
URL wasn't the onion
To wear giant dildo
I am
Also
I need a
Confuse everything
Play Warfare
So I don't know if you remember this
I mentioned on a recent episode
There's a dildo protab
Yeah I remember
Wasn't that realize that the CIA was behind
Interest in making sure no one knows that it was the CIA
You're right
Segment never trust Dan's death
Ciac
Yeah in the same way that Alex
But if you want to take his perspective with a grain of salt even though he's a CIA
Religious studies professor
I called him
Earlier
What happened
And I have my dad characterized
If you had like involved
Dildo protest
Do you have time you're no you're gone
So it did it started out as kind of a social media joke
People
Oregon
Open carry on campus
Especially gun being carried in building
Like campus buildings and stuff like that
So these students
They realize that it's a decency crime
Alright
Carry a dildo openly on Tampa
You would get an American
Started this campaign ad the offset
Budget pointing out that absurdity
On a Facebook group or whatever and then it spawned a real proton
It launched
On the same day gun-free UT
Which is the
I would characterize it my dad didn't
Totally agree with this
But how I would
Just be broad-stroke version is that's the adult version
Speakers
Bass
Protest against
Scary stuff
At the same time
So there was the
Student protest
That dovetails into the
Adult
Gun free UT Proto
And
I mean it's not the CIA
It's just
Smart
Realizing
Hey it's illegal for us to have dildos out in public but guns are cool
Yeah
It is it is fun.
That's a fun way to fight against what is clearly absurd like
You can't fight on that direct level of there
Dumb
Anger and stupidity you have to point out
Look at you silly
You might as well be holding
Cuz you're idiot
You and then you'll get angry and you'll go underground
And you'll go on stormfront.com
I just love that cuz on the last time we talked about a gun-free UT protest
Michael Bloomberg
Flu ever want
He's just making this stuff up
It's crazy
Like I'm thrilled that I have
Into the
The actual that the truth
But I just
I don't think the people listening to Alex Jones
Can realize how often
He is just making stuff up
But Bloomberg didn't fly anybody
Bloomberg wasn't involved in a protest at all
Isn't CIA tactics
It's clown
It's it's
Overthrow the government
Like they didn't turn
Regimes into nothing but are dropping
DVDs of operation
Alex does little planet
Themself
Fancies himself something of a cultural critic
Yes I am
In this clip
Paul Joseph Watson is in studio
They can't sit next to each other
Insist on talking to us
Yeah
This movie is about globalist
This about global is right every movie that's their reply
Jones critiquing
Criticizes the Martian for not enough Asians
The whole thing
And a charge of everything
The Martian
Matt Damon
And
He's not actually a Mustang
Voting
Who is the Russian boosters we've got to have
That's what I thought about the US Rockets blow-up it's the Russians
Propaganda
McDonald's McLeod
There was questions
So for the Chinese to come to the rescue in this film
Cool things
Russia he wanted Russia to be portrayed as the heroes
Because technologically that's accurate or something
There's a couple things there's a lot of issues with the Martians
300 it's not but also
It is not real
It's fiction I want to pull out of this
But I think a really important
If this was just someone else saying like
Really Advanced it like if it was anybody else
I like
Pinpoint
It seems weird that in this movie review he's even got to talk about how great Russia is
So that's one thing
Yeah I noticed
The other thing that I think is more important
To pull out
Is that it's not propaganda
China is a giant emerging-market for film
So
So what movies want to be able to movies don't make as much
Domestically as they do International
I want you to take that
Consideration
Often you do have to
Pandora little we haul it the Transformers
That's Craven or fake
I think that's
Sincerely Multicultural and beautiful
Little bit
Somehow making robots
That's a new one thanks
Paki altogether
Propaganda Alex
Okay
I'm telling you right here
Nicolas Cage is the bad guy in the
That's the truth
No do you know why what
Not enough Russian
Absolutely
I don't know
So ridiculous
Cultural critic
Continuous
The Martian
I could just depicting a different
Narratively expedient
What like
10 years ago or something like that
Is it alright book
Hey what are you doing
Potatoes will you talk about being scientifically expedient
Haggai
That's what movies are done
They don't have to
Explain because they
Dan
It's predict its predictive
You don't need hard sci-fi in movies
No exhaust
Stargate
Targets are real
Cultural critic
Meet all of the other Martian soldiers
Which is why they kidnap those kids
If
Review of the movie
Where are the bases
So this next clip Alex Jones
Cultural critic like I said continue
He shows on television
About Gunn
And
What doesn't have guns in it
Well
They're not all about guns though
Talk about that
Cuz you can't even carry
Can open carry up your butthole
Always only you could
Canfield
Television
I meant Hilo
Real hard about how popular it is
But a free person
Thomas Jefferson
Has a right to own guns
Amateur fight between a logical
But no more guys means less crime
And the patio
Turn around God
Every metric every study every poll shows
None of those
And that's why I was told
I'd Discovery Channel
And by the Broncos
It produces
That 3 years ago the order
On every channel
Number one
Fellowes channels where gun shows
Here
Wait
I want to shut you down there I just wanted to make sure
He currently hosts
To shows on Discovery
M2 shows on the History Channel
For television
How is how can you even possibly say that
He's hosted
Pilots that never made it to air
A boy
There are not four shows on there
The only
The only one that's possibly what he's talking about it actually everywhere in 2015.
When did it got cancelled in 2014
There's a show called America's Book of Secrets
We're talking heads
Like Gods episodes use on her about likes
Secret prison
The billionaire agenda Area 51 Freemasons
Good stuff he's on like 19 episodes of that
Out of like 35
I did not know he was a lot on television
Sultan to Jesse Ventura go to First
What you talking about
America's Book of Secrets wasn't on History channel is on H2
The secondary History Channel
And if you go past that the only credits he has
Where is not an actor
And he is free of those
To Richard linklater movie amerigeddon
The only things he has after America's Book of Secrets
Until the Joe Rogan
Experience
AR
The Joke is on his IMDb
Before
Which means that was not televised
State the rise video documentary
Conspiracy theorist live
Which is a documentary about
I wish
The Conspiracy Theory conspiracy
Which is documentary about conspiracy theories
I like
The rabbit hole on that one
All of these are one-off documentaries that probably didn't air on
Normal.
Who's not the host of anything
Currently
Tater on a lot offers
I got a lot of offer I guarantee you drop everything we like David Knight you're in
You take over the show for the neck
Next two weeks I'm going to go shoot
Some stuff like John Cena does take time off of WWE shoot the season of that American grit show and then come
Checkfresh
Sell this boner s***
Super male vitality
So also the idea that the no-gun show stuff is a narrative it's been pushed on Alex's show by Ted Nugent
Goody's
I was talking about
Horseshit I mostly kept that in
Because of the
No
Alderwood
I like the idea of it
Discovery
The History Channel and Ane
I'll just go to heaven be like
Hey
None
3 years ago
We're going to get rid of them
Why would they tell Alex
Especially when they're still alive
This is like what am I made out of guns
There's still so many shows about guns on boys like that
Duck Dynasty
Houses just like why aren't there more
There's always there's never enough
Pre-loved gun
And get this
He's not just a guy who loves gun
He is also
A prophet
He is also someone who proselytizes
About Gunn
I need a what
Unsuccessful
Not only is Alex out there is spreading the good word
Bart Gunn
To his right-wing audience
He's also converting a lot of dumb dumb liberals
Do you happen to have television shows on HBO
That's right
Check this s*** out
Wait a second
You get up once not twice
Wish app
50 calls you name it
I took the cast of Silicon Valley
And
Martin Starr
A satisfying conversion
The people becoming
It's just weird until I shot and it was fun
Bulls eyes and stuff
Why shouldn't have trusted I'm not bad
Sounds like a male
Marquis women
What yeah
Cuz I said
This is a classic misunderstanding that Alex is having
Because he's unwilling to
Engaged
The reality is that the arguments
Set 10 minute abs
About
Self-defense
Classes and guns
Stuff like that is
Hey
Let's focus on the real problem which is Manor assaulting
As opposed to
Making the responsibility
Fight them off or shoot them
The reality is that safe
Would be fine with people being armed
But would rather focus on the issue that is at
The core
Be fine with only women
Millers
Much lower in
A violent crime
Convicted of domestic
Abuse and then go on to
So now that we've
Convicted
Have those issues in the past
Almost
End up shooting people and committing violent crimes almost always have domestic
Whether it's against the partner or a mother or a sibling or something attracts always
Morrow
40% of venture
Immediately
Ourselves that don't live TARC.
Holyshit
Do you believe that for a second
I love first
Image
Zach Woods
Martin Starr
Kumail
TJ
All going out
Blow-ups
Tannerite
Hangout
And then they leave
And Mike Judge and Alex Jones sit around have a beer and talk about how great it is to
Post-coital beer that there haven't so amazing
I like that idea
Cuz that's the world he lives in in his head
I'm going to guess
Probably
That did it did happen
The Silicon Valley cast members maybe not all of them
I'm going to guess that
And Alex is so
Incredibly
Also clearly was drinking
That they probably like
Oh yeah it is fun
Sound like
It's a weird situation still being polite
You know what if I had more time to research I would have contacted them before time
Search
The other there's
Exact words a lot
What are you doing Dad into the background power of Zach Woods
Everyone else is secondary
He's so good in the show 2
Cuz he's playing what about you
Alex
Thought I had had some friends and they took me to the gun
And I get it
I I totally like I'm not anti
Shooting guns for leisure or sport or whatever
Like
It's fun
It is really fun
In a safe environment but it also
What it takes over your life and
I've become so important to you I really Quest
Turn that
But like
Just sitting there shooting a gun at a thing
The Lakers with stick
Pretty
I can't hold a gun
Court order
No boys
You are
Slightly close-minded in that but I don't think
The problem there is
You can have peanuts
Fun up there with a gun
I understand
I thought I thought
Before I went out
For him
What's what's
The show
Cuz I watch Mythbusters
I would be like
Filled with all of my testosterone
Feeling like a god able
Kill anything at any moment
Sure that I would
Would feel like that
But it was more like
Understand interesting but
It's a fair from here
Like I mean I kind of would get the same thrill out of it like a really good
Slingshot
It is
Recoil laser
Explosion is almost like italic
Like I'm doing something
But I mean who cares
I'm still going to go with such a f****** like
I don't know
I'm trying to do like a real irrational version
But
Because I
Sincerely where I like
Reasonable here
Spell know
Pretty hot though
How about you drop some super-predator language
How about you
Defeat George.
Why is it not okay for me to be
Like reasonably okay with guns
Tulsa
Controls should be
You're doing is a real
In the same way that there's a lot of different
The alt left
Is thrown around by idiots
In the same way that Centrist can be thrown around by
It's very reasonable
Alright
And I'm not going to
And take it away for
Exit away from you
Probably
He's probably should have
Glad we found, correct
Start over
I was just really offensive about a whole bunch
First of all the schools
Lesbian
Here's how you
Perform fellatio
Just join us just mesh with us just
Because the men aren't being met
Iran girl
Muscle
God I wish
You f****** pilot
F****** gun
2 hours
Call Rebecca Gunn 50 caliber rifle
Quarter pound charge
We're shooting center box nerds floating
Biking barbaric energy Rises
Your phone calls
A f******
I love his style of his argument
That chauvinism is
No matter
Like that
Bestie is you there
What are what are you doing
I can't judge for being chauvinist but lesbians are like because they don't
You're an idiot
Attracted to other women
Clarify one thing
Details about being a pool hall and lesbian hitting on his friend's girlfriend
Conservative estimate
25 *
On the shelf that I've heard
Yeah but
Each time is a new
Nope
Exactly the same story all the same details
25 women have had 25 of his friends
Girlfriend
Entirely not possible
I don't know why it took us a long time
Tannerite is
Explosives
You're like a box of it and you put it
Down
Explosion
So it's just the way of it's like a firework
Can shoot
Kind of weird I didn't know what it was
Until I looked it up
He's talking about shooting these these logs and they blow up in cinder blocks
A little bit of a pause
I want to remind everybody that on a show that we did a couple months back
You talkin about being out
Shooting with Mike Judge
Hitting some Tannerite with
Cinder block
Had a piece of the cinderblock Cat in the Hat
Right
Which is one of the things that we suspect may have
Cause some brain damage
Yeah so he's glorifying this
Like being out there shooting and all that
Not realizing on another show
He's talked about like
I got hit in the head with
Maybe it's not all good fun
I'm doubling back on my position even
But if you're not safe and not careful
Even recreational shooting is not good
The same time
What is drunk
Silicon Valley
Zonked in the head
Remembers is that the castle
Silicon Valley love guns
Now he is just a man with a very serious
Singapore
Mike Judge
I just love
Zach
What
He's right improv4humans podcast
Justice
Superfly
If I was out there shooting as a member of Silicon Valley
Shoots of tannerite
All of a sudden black
This is the best around
Great
All the time
Shoot that one
Read that one
Walk a little closer
Eclipse so far but this next clip is where it gets a little bit.
October 12th
Involves
David Clarke
Why do we have such because there's this whole Sheriff movement
Started reading about the constitutional
Die I mean
Go to the gun range with Alex and have a piece of cinder block
What's happened
We we haven't really talked about it but
Himself
I don't give a fuk
He dies now self parked against
Twisting things there is a 19
Supreme Court decision
About pardon
That may come into play that's actually kind of interesting
I'm not entirely sure I read
The Supreme Court decision
I said who was a journalist
He was trying to be
Compelled to give up his
He had and
He got pardoned
By the president
In an attempt
For them to be like you are not going to be charged you can give up your source
Yeah and he refused the pardon
Randolph County Jail
And so the precedent that was set was that you can refuse a pardon
And agreeing to a party
You have admitted.
Piece of it
Been in this is sort of disputed law that even to this day
But there is a sense
And there is
Supreme Court decisions.
Very very rarely do I look back at any Supreme Court decision from that
Era
Nine judges
Presidents that are set
An argument that can be made by Joe Arpaio
Accepting the party
Because it is a choice you can reject or accept a pardon
Bionicle
Yeah he did already
Bikes
In the matter
Louis
Arms and legs possible
F****** torso
Yeah
It's unclear whether or not that will hold up or is that the route things are going to go but
Mandu I hope so
God also people need to go back and listen to our episode about the dentist Montgomery invest
Cuz I really think
That there's more going on
Interim
Of the Alex Jones
Joe Arpaio
Donald Trump
Nexus
That
People are not
Paying attention to
I think Dennis Montgomery Pleasant
Along with the births
Certificate s***
Defect
Dennis Montgomery is so
Entwined
If Donald Trump
Belief that Obama was spying on
It doesn't
It's not a small thing
People should really go back
Analyze some of that stuff
Also we did that episode like what 5 months
Everyone else I wish everyone else
Totally
Everyone else
Is f****** piling on and getting 1,000
The world is flawed
That's our main issue with Joe Arpaio right
We're not getting it up
I'll let myself out my ego take a backseat let's just deal with him
I can't
I can't I
It's really not high on the list of all the worst things that are happy
Open right now
Dial Harvey
Arpaio
80 year old man
Bright doesn't mean that much
In the grand scheme
You know it really doesn't
That's just one of those demoralizing fuc
Nothing matters
These guys
Everything
They can just
Act with impunity
And what can you or I do
It sends a profoundly bad
Because
I think the worst part about it I mean
Is really really
Depressing
Is that
Trump phrases in frame today
He he got a witch-hunt against them for doing his job
Yeah
Means that the application is all the atrocities you committed was
That was a job
His job was to arrest every Latino person
Sweep
I'm sure I'd like the stories that are coming out even
And I recently liked
People who have been
Let me tell you what happened with me
Donald Trump
Fuckgod Mike zullo
Arya Stark list
God dammit man
I've never seen you as someone else but the why would I know if you
It's about
How Barack Obama
All the time
That's why I be so long
A co-host is no one
Stop it
This is about how Obama went
To Oregon
After that shooting that happened like a week or so back in the timeline now
Like a present
David Clarke
When you get back on the other side I'll explain
Why these thoughts are deeply troubling
Helpless jackasses
Marble America
The house
Pictures when a collective pile but stupid
Operator
30 * the tragedy that happened the United States
To see what he can accomplish on his agenda and then I think that this
Saturday
Erase all right through it that's why I said I'm glad they did it
Respect for the president
To achieve a political agenda I'm glad to see that
Do-as-i-say-not-as-i-do president
With the armed Secret Service security staff
Can it
What's repost judges clip
The article about Obama
And I want you to
He's going to go viral
Everybody picked it up
What is the communicator to get aggressive
We have to counter them
Update Obama give up your guns
Farm Obama
The here's why that clip is
Particularly troubling
You have
Sheriff Clarke
On television
Making the same point
And Matt Drudge
On episode like a week back
Now here is the part that's even more troubling
Cuz that would be f***** up on its own
Do you have this
Sheriff I don't know why
National Television
The President should have his security removed or whatever
I think that it's getting crazy in and of itself
But
About a month or two
I think 2 months after this
Sheriff Clarke was in Russia
Sheriff Clarke
He went along
There's
That can't be an okay thing
What's the most
He was in Russia at the
The same time that Michael Flynn was in Russia
The reason he was there was
Because he was part of an
An NRA delegation
There went over there
With this gentleman named
Ruggles
Dimitri Rogan
He's a Hardline Deputy to Vladimir Putin
The head of Russia
Defense industry of longtime opponent of American power
Because of his
Role in the invasion of Crimea
Eastern Ukraine
Sheriff Clarke
Along with some other folks
Who are supergun positive Folk
I went over it
Which
They claim
Was just because
He's integon
Like I don't know I don't think that
Yeah
Most high-powered
We love guns
He loves guns
There's definitely nothing to look into now everybody look up the Alexander
I represent was the leader of the ultra-right party called rodina or motherland
And famously believes in the restoration of the Russian Empire include
Which is to say Alaska
Control of the party
From a party that was occasionally in opposition
Who is strictly pro-putin party
His party miscalculated Putin
Anti-immigrant mood
I got kicked out of the parliament for a chauvinistic promotion video
It said let's clean the garbage
Featuring Central Asian workers eating a watermelon and spitting on the ground
Wow
Racially
Then Putin
This is the guy who David Clark
Went over and met with
In Russia
2 months after he's telling
Obama
To give up his gun
And Alex is saying
Yeah
Alright
Triangulation
At least in terms of people were making the exact same
In Matt drudge Alex Jones and David Clarke
If that is a
Writable problem
For all of them
No apparently they are f******
If you can
If you can pardon Arpaio
Who is
Really under any kind of
Threat now
The point was
I can do whatever the f*** I want
And laws don't mean anything
As long as you're my friend
Tire problem
With the monarchy
Which apparently is what we are
What's going on
Why
Buhay Amerika
It's amazing how much they despise America
They hate
He bought a lot of the Constitution
Amendment
Second Amendment right
Don't have any f****** clue what the words are
There's some great old videos of Sam Cedar going out to like libertarian marches and asking people about the Constitution
Amazing like
Well I haven't
Planning your other Constitution
I wanted to just read this quote to because this I think
This is aboard this from that same article
It's disconcerting that they would be meeting with a Russian official about anything
Given their vocal support of the
They're talking about Donald Trump
Intelligent
Which is investigating brushes
Text influence the 20s
16 presidential election
Due to the NRA's opposition
The sanction
It defies credulity
And their extraordinary support
Donald Trump
So
You kind of get the Sun
That they were over there
In some sort of
Wink-wink-nudge-nudge
Exactly
Already
The sheriff
Is responsible for a lot of deaths
I didn't think
Doterra in f******
The Philippines where it's like
Disco murder people who do drugs
Just where everybody sells drugs
You want your fine
Constitutional Sheriff strike Mesa
Mid-range Generals in a junta
Yeah military
They think that they know whatever one wants
And it is not
David's
Are two of the most
Awful people
Imagine
I never morsel
I think an image
A picture of started to be
Become clear
Is that there are a lot of people
That are either actively working with Russia
David Clarke
And people who are
Being
Duke
By Russian influence
And propaganda
Matt Drudge
Alex Jones
Matt drudge is influencing whether he's actually like
He knows what he's doing
I can't tell I have no
Hayden influence
Yeah but I certainly
God knows what he's doing
Ouch
I'm at Matt drudge I have no idea
But they're all saying the same
Nothing
The f****** problem
Because
It is
Talking point
And a narrative
Is clearly coming out of Russia
So
Let's hope
House intelligence intelligence committee
Are going to figure this thing out
And they're just going to Georgia
I didn't expect any of
No I think it's I think it's so f***** up where we're at
Go through all this because I
Pecan like
A lot of
One of the ways that people are saying that
We're deflecting from the fact
That Hillary didn't go to work
God dammit
Donald Trump
Is on tape peeing on the way like there's not much else to say this
Other than that
There is like I might genuinely believe that one can really exploit media
Trick people
Is following along with the ID
One of the games
The propagandists play
Is
Tricking you into thinking that two things can't be
Be true
Hillary should have gone to Wisconsin
True
That's also true
Those both can be true
They aren't mutually exclusive at all
But the way that everything is presented
2 tricks you into thinking
If you believe your excuse
Who cares
It's so much it's so much
Twitter take
Kulture
Recording is over the weekend and last night I was monitoring that hurricane Harvey hit
Culture
I'm f****** done
Yeah real time with the actual natural disaster happen
Was just so f****** distasteful
Just people making jokes
Stuff
Just collapsed if people are stuck inside of right now people to get out
It's weird.
To watch
Laugh
Because
And it's super weird all across the board because
That we are
Vehemently
SMS
Like I'm screaming about
Arpaio's
It isn't actually affecting
No
I mean but not yet I don't feel like this
Personal effects
Go home
Anything that I've done has been chained
Being pardoned
In the same way that
It is
Think of all the damage that is being done
While we are talking
I just thought you know you just feel like a certain amount of Disconnect from it if you're watching
Through your phone
And that to me is why it makes sense
Sunset the twittersphere can
Just
Do all of this b*******
Because it doesn't even look real it looks like you're watching it on TV
It's a real Disaster Movie
So we're going to get political issues
Clip
Alex Jones go to the phone
Just a dumb
Dumb f****** caller
Let's go to Louisiana
Hey cowboy
I just wanted to let you know that
You can be the first to know that I'm no longer racist
And I can prove it by level
Can I do have a color
And we found out what color it is
And it happens to be eggshell beige
Home Improvement in my wallet
Right behind my
Right behind my drivers license in the so I'm a person of color now
My piggy bank
I guess anybody can say anything about that
Sorry
Bright
He goes on to talk about social security
I just
Wish we didn't have to live in the same country as these people pretty wild
Some somewhere else
How about this
If you're if you're
We put you in
What about the pro wrestler Umaga
Arizona
The temperature is always 150
I'm not going to respond to this just cuz I know you're joking but I don't want to play this game anymore
I don't know anymore mean either no one is driving
Me neither
That's a weird twist
An address that is not weird at all
This Mexico
You ruined your own transition there
Just becomes a verbal tic
Physically
I tell you I don't
In the New World
So
He's talking about how like our government funds Isis
And the only ones are really taken care of
Expression
Better than us
I'm just
Yeah
Clearview has a profoundly pro-russia propuso
Perspective
You know what
You know what I have
Like okay
So they all hate the world government yada yada yada apun
Right sir
So if we do
Alex
And f*** it
Let's just throw that in the real
Call Melissa or whatever it is
Expansion
Exactly he wants the old Soviet Union
And apparently
You know
Mad Max is coming around the corner
If
Nationalism
And there is no
You know
Negotiating bodies
Between these countries there is no United
Nations or anything like
What
Like
Do we still trade do we get news from these other places or is it like just everything off and shut it down
Be strong countries
Exploiting poor country
Eat to a greater extent than we even do now
It would be better
Most countries that don't have something to offer
They Don't Really ever discuss
In terms of like this world
Right it's not like
I know that borders mean something in terms of like
Here's America
The end of the day they are a loser
It's not really real
We all are on this orb
That we're living on
And you can't look we can't all survive unless we work together
I bet recognition is why there are those body
Eva
Piece of the f****** thing that drives me crazy
It's the same thing with the central bank
And Federal Reserve
If you really look
The history of
Our economy
Everything has been much
Better
Since the Federal Reserve
That will come back up
I think not.
Yeah
Federal Reserve
And it is still
A profit business
More closely than they are
And we should
Expectmore
But if you look pack
That we were way worse
Do you win is not perfect
We can go back
Countless examples of atrocities that have gone on on their watch
Rolanda
Any number of the X tomato tomahto anytime any number of time
That the International Community had
Responsibility
2 stops
From happening and failed
For whatever reason
That said
There are a number that would have happened
Cause those bodies
I just don't understand
I understand paranoia I understand fear I do get those things
But I don't understand
Sweet denial
Of the posit
That part really does not make sense
But that's
But they don't want
Don't have any interest in
That
Right so
Yeah
Reno genocides happening on localized levels and
They want
Iran currency
I completely fluctuating stock markets
To the point where
Like everything is Fox all the time
But
It's this it's the entirety of
The GOP it's the way that their brains were
Isleta
Terra Vista
Cuz it's not working the way we want it to
And then they don't do that thing of like okay well then what do we build after
They have no idea
Like always
As much as we can
And then they never say okay
Well since we don't have any money for the Federal
What is it that we keep and what is it that we get rid of
And you're like well we prove
Will do
Never any sense of what are we building
The better they have no interest in that
Because the people
Are the ones who are going to profit the most
If you tear down this
I'm privatized everything
Yeah
They would we
The dumbest
Weakest
Most idiotic members of our population
Telling them that
Look at all of these things that aren't helping you as much as you want them
They've convinced
Alex Jones
As opposed to the real
Exactly
Which is
Maybe we should explore another time Brilliance psychological
Like they have pulled off
A war against the poor
Making the poor think that
There
On the right side
I'd like
Hang up on himself about that too but
Michael
So Sam had a good point about Alex Jones that is
Ryder in the movies
It's in the gossip rags
If you were
Some of these super rich
People who have
Stinky Pinky
All that
What you would want
To create someone like Alex Jones
To distract everybody
Best thing possible would be to create an Alex Jones
And I don't think that's the case
But someone created him as controlled opposition
But it is interesting
Accidentally
Play he is serving
The greatest purpose towards us not progressing
It's fast
He is doing
Everything possible to make sure that all the stuff
Says he wants
Never comes about everything is afraid of War
Fulfilling prophecy in this regard especially for self-medicating Friday
Yeah except he's the one who's making sure that all the
Doesn't happen
Yeah
Because the billionaires can pay so many people to do this
Like they don't even need
They have Heritage Foundation
They have billionaires they don't work for us
If we stop calling them billionaires and start calling them oligarchy
Like I said
And we start
Theft really help
Billionaire
Oligarch is kind of gross
I don't know I think we should call him what they are
Carpetbaggers
Globalist
Oh boy
So we like the globalist we got it stop going off on somebody
Okay alright next day
Is October 14th
Cuz I'm
No I don't okay
Going to work through this thing
September on October 13th
Can't stand him
Yeah we move onto October 14th
Paul Joseph Watson
Because Alex Jones starts the show by lying about him
At the train station when he gets off
Everyday in the nude
Wasn't
5 years ago
Villain Deku
Can you criticize radicalism
Stop saying
Not Michael Savage from entering the United Kingdom because they believe that
Beach was hate speech
And it is
Oh yeah
Yeah it is
It's cuz it's not criticizing radical Islam
He talked
Like
Legitimately watched a bunch of
Add so much of the stuff he says
Is
So aggressively
It is
Conflating Islam with
Terrorism
To what end
On the show but it's the worst example
Was when he was on
Television show he had a gay activist on the show
He told him I hope you get AIDS
Sendai
Like legitimately
He is that kind of an awful person
So the idea
He does incite people a bit
That's the idea
Totally cool
Also the idea that you can't criticize Islam without being arrested
You're living proof that's not true
That's true
You do it all the time and you're fine Paul Joseph Watson does it all the time he's in London he's fine
Your whole like
Either America or in England
Totalitarian
It's very specific to teleserye
If you get arrested
What are you talkin about what does that mean
Like I don't think that's true but I also don't trust Paul Joseph
Against
Whether he wanted to or not
Right like I don't think that he
Has the
Do not turn it into
Let's burn down that mosque
Apso
I mean
When you
Eddie your existence
Is proof that your argument is wrong
Woody
What do you do
Make the argument anyways
Well I guess
To create people about you create a fake anime
Who are constantly about
To take you down
Yeah
Just cracked the nut
So
No we have twenty more clips
Alright
I'll be real quiet for the next 45 minutes
Let's go
I teased earlier in this episode
That we met
Not make progress
The point where because whenever we
Smart
So I were about to get to to get to something
That is
I think transformative
And might
A very major piece
Of Alex Jones transforming into a trump propaganda
And by the losing his mind
He got hit by a larger
Because
Trying to think of another person who's on
Silicon Valley ending
I shouldn't have thrown at 12 Alaska
Pizza world
In this mess
Alex Jones
Was going to get into a narrative that I sincerely think is a push
This is a big one for him
He's lying about ever
Let me get to the story that
That I spent well over an hour researching and I could
Berkeley texted it to me
Confederate flag supporters indicted under Georgia terrorism all
Texas
Federal holidays
People getting their big four-wheel-drive trucks to drive around with rebel flag
They do it at the beach if you're in Florida or Louisiana Chevy taxes sent me this is just what you grew up around
I have a complex historical
Trace add when I see it
Because I really
And I'm going to get to that.
What is there free speech
Confederate Battle Flag and slavery
Will they take your children if you criticize the government
Socialism global warming
Germany
Illegal
A deposit for a second cousin
Has been spinning for like the last
Week and a half on the shower so
And I've just sort of talked it by the wayside
He thinks
Germany has reactivated
The Stasi
In order
To get you to never talk bad about immigrants
Well Germany
The one of the strongest
Hate speech
There is
Truth to what he's saying but not what he's saying
The ghetto
Yeah
On the show order
Is privately about house
You know if you express Nazi ideology you get arrested
Yeah there
That there is that sort of
It doesn't
Jibe with our ideas
Free speech
Definitely makes sense based on history
Maybe the national law of Everett
Send it's not terrible it's also used like it is one of those things
In the same way that
Can be used against
People we don't like
It can be used against people we do
Lite-Brite
The first amendment is super important
It's super important The Government Can
Make a lot of restricting your ability to say what you want
Should have made it more
Specific like
You can say like here's a law that I would pick
Alright
Hear me out
In Congress
You can absolutely
Express your right
To say whatever it is
And the law will not
However
It is also illegal
To punch a Nazi in the face however men
Sure
That's a good one
Did the point is there are there are these
Elements
German Society
Outside of all right.
Yeah but they're not reactivating Stasi
Flappy Bird
Yeah Alex's Alex's going on a bunch
You look into it it's like there's other issues
Use that wasn't because they said immigrants are bad
It was because they were unfit parents
Other
Narrative respond about how like
If your kids playing basketball
You had a state takes them away
Yeah
Nativity kicked into about Confederate flag
People being indicted
Let's listen to the rest of this Civil War revisionism
The carbon tax global warming
Of course climate change
This is the Pratt got married
Georgia
Fight
White supremacist
It was an amazing individual
Ulysses has Grant did the northern General
What's wrong
Southern perspective yes
Call George
No
Read and understand
Slavery
President Andrew Jackson
Was it about Playland
His Protege sham Houston
And was removed
I was spit on
Busy that you're being set up by British intelligence course he was right
Saints Row some bottles
Animal people
For the rebel flag
Bottles
That means the black people are being racist
Sprite
As opposed to
Gorgeous waving
The rebel flag
Do this and you agree 100% with Alex Jones
That is restricting priest
Total
I can't
About everything is not
Because this narrative is going to be a little bigger to Robert E Lee and
But he absolutely did have flight
Things
Was accused of having slaves
His argument was that
Gotten his when his dad died
Years after I die
So
That was his argument was I'm going to
Freedom 5 years
After my dad died
West
Unfortunately the civil war broke out
3 years later
So
Who knows that he would have freed them
I don't know if it were me
I would like dad's dead
I don't give a s*** about his wishes
If I were actually against slavery like okay
Guys just yet
Don't tell my dad if you'd like just don't reply
You're not going to be seeing them anywhere
Just on the off-chance
NetSpend
The other thing is
You seem to in a lot of letters
Have negative
Slavery
But did not
Advance that position
Can publicly
I didn't
Work against it at all
Which
To mine eyes means
He wasn't really
But be that as it may
During a war about whether or not we should
Keep slavery
To the argument is more complicated
The black and white version of
Of like
Awful and great
He's probably more in the middle and
Towards awful
But not as bad
Who cares
Look I'm not trying to be a Centrist on this to
Let's put it that way
The point about this
People the rebel flag
It is so much more
Who Would It Go
They did so much worse yet
Alex Alex
Our research
That means
But he knows everything I'm about to tell you
Pretending all that stuff didn't happen last episode
Does this incident happened on July 27th
Confederate flags disrupted the black child's birthday celebration
Fucksake
Yep in Georgia
Shouting racial slurs and deathreat partygoers said
The entire through in pickup trucks taunting their target cell phone videos showed
A second video capture the uninvited guests
Grassy fields
During Saturday's confrontation
Quote it's a child's birthday party
Angry Witness
Just called out to them
Partygoers claim to hecklers brandished Gunn tire iron
As they threatened to quote kill all the ends
New York Daily News
Well it's
That's from the media's the one
Symbol of race
That's from the New York Daily News
Visit from the washing
The post on October 12th
At the time of trucks drove into the neighborhood
And began making threats and yelling racial slurs
Call Gunn saying he was going to kill the end
Party host Melissa Ashford told the Atlanta Journal-Constitution
Quote then one of them said give me the gun all shoot them ends
Okay so
Just like
Just as a barometer for how we're doing
I have
Maybe
But
Which is right around the time like a day or two before where we're at now
2017 ascender
In February 2017
Was finalized
And you'll be thrilled to know that
The people who got charged
Tried in court
And I worked for them for years
They got
Hard chard
Good activate streetgangs
What
From February twenty
Video footage from the party
Little more than a month after dylann roof Charleston Church Massacre
Battle Flag
1%
And said he was going to kill the end
Prosecutors have said that the cases against Torres
Norton and other defense
Defendants are not to fly the Confederate flag
Put on threats against the victim
Quote this is behavior that even supporters of the Confederate Battle Flag
Can agree is Criminal
It shouldn't be allowed
Douglas County district attorney Brian Fort Myers
Wow
Alex's version of what's going on
Shocking
Man
Like the the tweets
Obama
The most likes
History of the world
Oh boy
The one in which he hits him with
The picture
Is not something that you
You're born with it some
It is almost one of those things where it's like
Maybe we should take
I don't mean maybe it is a biggish a bigger issue
The family is
What is
Like it might be a better idea if
It was more community-driven and less
You know you're raised by whatever random ass
People
May not be a bad idea
Becoming a type 1 civilization getting off-planet
And stuff like that progress
In the grander scheme
Threat
If you look back
The history of
Humanoids
Human-like
Ben's if you go back to Neanderthal times and
Even
Human civilization
Not homo sapiens
Different patterns
Of culture you see
Matriarchal society
Nevermind
Bianca
Children
Becomes much more Community intertwined
Your children aren't your property everybody is
Sort of interest in raising children
Together and just because that is in the
Half doesn't mean that the Farrelly
But those ideas can't possibly be the future
Like
As we
Drift towards
Massive shift
And how we live like the idea of going off-planet
Is crazy
Like we would have to change everything
Yeah
On planet
Everything's crazy
Society 8:30
In terms of discreet family unit
And in terms of like
Even in the last 50 years
Chipped away a little bit
Man runs everything in household are happening
It's entirely possible that we do end up getting to maybe not necessarily uncle
But an avuncular type of pattern
It really does make the most sense when you consider yes
It is important to all of us
Yeah children
The results of
You know
It's like whatever
Get raised by horrible f****** tickets
Who raised by horrible f****** big dick
It's super weird that strangers children really do affect your life but
They raise their kids
No f****** do it do it if somebody is raising their kids
Agree
So these next two clips
I'm just going
Play The Alex Jones
News about this
Battle Flag situation
Play these without commentary through them
Screaming
Here we go
Confederate flag
You know
They were a lot of times looking for trouble
Bonfire whatever
Shop lights
What is absolutely not
Because the media was invoking
Anybody that's got a
Confederate flag wants to murder black people
Post office
While we go get back to that narrative
Circuit Court narrative
Probably worse
160 years later
After the Civil War
They will arrest you and charge you for terrorism
If you fly
And people's feelings get hurt
Chic-A-Sea reportable correct
When they get upset
So in that Cliff use blaming
The people who have
I had racial slurs
Dudes with guns
Pipes and knives
Rolling through with
Standard Lee racist
They were just
Shoes that shouldn't be there just triggered shouldn't
Birthday parties
You're like
Snowflake North all of another problem children's birthday
Sofrito
Truth I know
Children parties all the time right and I go in there and no one wants to debate
What's going on you f****** cowards
Ridiculous
It is an interesting
It is an interesting thing
That's
No I just I'm just thinking like
Are we still at war with the Confederacy
I think some of them think that you got
Stranded inland
In Vietnam or South Korea years after
Or in that same
It is
It is an issue
Anytime you fly the Confederate flag it is a problem
It is a symbol of owning people
This that's what the Confederate flag is.
I agree but this comes down to what we were talking about earlier with the downsides of complete free speech
Yeah because
In countries like Germany where they can
Shut it down real hard
I'll make it at like 1
The Civil War was over
We probably shouldn't have been as generous
And be like oh
Yeah
Or whatever
No
You need to be punished
For your
Is your sins
Right
Weave
Except free speech
To such a degree to be like
Review nothing's been around
Did maybe they weren't called neo-nazis
With neo-Nazi
Is there a lot of them
Yeah and we just like
Believe to them
Building up
Imenu360
You think if you go the other way though
You know WWII Treaty of Versailles
You just
Destroy a people until they want to start another f****** War
What has to be defeated with some sort of
Positive
You can't see any positive
Whenever you talk about
People who
Udet
Like
Alex Jones
As people who are pedophiles
Montpelier
Like how do how do you combat that with
Positivity
Like that
It's a it's an insane idea
Positive
I am explaining truth
I don't know
I love take every opportunity
My steps today I'm doing great
This next clip Obama is mentally ill
But he also says something
Things that I think is
Investigation
There's a trump
Tweet for every occasion every
Every time we go back to 2015
And
He describes Obama
All the stuff that he hates about Obama
Yeah Obama was none of that
The guy is the president because he's not black
More important part about it
It was something else that comes up in this clip
I think it's profoundly important
MIT scientists
Are the fathers of Modern Warfare at the Pentagon
So dr. pechenik
Is about
To show up
Is this
I think he's been on the show years in the past
But he has not been on
In this entire run that we've been doing
And I checked
2014 I didn't have a answers from him
But I think he had before
But
He has not been around
Counter-coup narrative has not come up
Okay
Steve pieczenik
Is about to show up on the Alex Jones Show
Cuz whatever Alex says
I'm going to get them on
So we can expect that
The bigger piece I want to take away from
Is it if you're dumb
Like Alex G
Orbitz
No you're still smarter than Alex Jones in with it
If
Berries
Who is an
Psych Warfare
Don't make them a regular guest on your show
Because you
You're not you're not smart enough to know if they're committing Psych
This guy psychological warfare
Game like I've said many times
My theory is that everyone is lying to Alec
Weatherby Russian media Rodger Stone
All of this guest
And influences
Is are basically tricking him into this box that he put himself in
That ended up
Being a very large part of why we have
Yeah so
I see that
And like this recognition and admission is thought like
The guy who is going to tell us about psych ward
Hold on
Is this dude ever not Warfare in psychically
He's going to tell us all about
Alright
Don't do it
It drives me crazy like I just put in the fact that he
Recognizes
And gives him like part of his credit
Means that he knows
He's not guarding himself nearly well enough
Like if you know how it we've talked about this like
Months and months
A lot of the times
Sonic does the very rash
And whenever he's talking about
Cannot allow Gorsuch to be on the Supreme Court you the neocon
Elizabeth
Right but then you have to remember the also doesn't believe it's real
A hundred other like
Really terrible things
But what does
Exact and believe
Evidently
Alex ripping its troops different sides of the same point
No that is
Great question
You made is that
Once you once you have that as his credit
I am
Anything that he says in public
You cannot believe
Andy
To the point where things Beast
They have no other
Are just taken as gospel
That's a real f*****-up
Headspace to be dangerous to give anybody
Especially when it's like Warfare person is coming on your show
Giving you stuff
It feeds into your confirmation bias
You really should analyze
Now it's never does
You just like
Steve
You think I'm funny
Always wanted people to think I'm funny
I don't know why they never do
That's self-reflective Alex Jones at that character does not exist
This context drop
I just think it's a fence
Women
Vix
You got to be a slave about women's lib
Do you like being treated like an adult
I got to take the draft
Service
Women would be
Because that
Chauvinist and assholes always make it
You don't want all the same rights
Cuz then you'd have to do all the same
You don't want to do you know that kind of
If it does happen though
All the sudden
There's no other than
Ignorant
Hatred or whatever
Condescension
Like what else would you describe it as
Sums up Alex Jones to a T
Sup Jordan this next clip we get back to a very familiar theme
In 2015 Alex Jones
You got it
Directions to take out the Taliban
8 years in
Helicopters
Pharmacist
And the Russians want to take them out
Even meet with them
They won't because it's there
Incredible
Arby's
The globalist Army is
Isn't done
Doesn't he work a desk
Skip for the National Guard
What are you talkin about
I don't know
Come to non-existent photo op. Land somewhere
Trip they took
Look I mean
Historical and present
He's just doing things
Conflate
The idea that
Proxy Army of angry Muslims
Is it in Russia is
Really the only people good on the other side
Problematic
Deeply
I am bringing up whenever he talks about Trump
Bringing up most
So the times you talked about Russia
Nutty's never says anything negative about Russia even if you even if you are
Flattered by Russia
Dugan hadn't said any of the stuff
He says about him later like these
The perfect model of an American inside
Late 26th
So at this point
But he hadn't been
He just
Sees himself in Russian State media
He just sees familiarity and narrative
He doesn't realize that it's
Because he's absorbing their narrative
To some extent
And because
Their narrative
Are harshly conservative
Depressing
That matter
Yeah you're right he's all about freedom but philosophy
Ratably
Credibly
Yeah he's he's very against freedom
8 likes
He likes
Think about it
Prefer that nobody but him had Italy loves to fake cry but where you really belong
Is being a mouth
Seven oppressive regime
Yeah I mean
I started to wrestle with this
As we've gone along
Like
We started this with
Why did Alex Jones
Become
Trump's propaganda
And I started to realize now month
Listen to this
I mean of course
What else would Alex have done
Because I hadn't listened to nearly as much
Alex Jones as I have now
It's real crazy that this conspiracy theorist decided to jump on this train
But the more I think about it the more
We all should have seen that coming
A mile away
Yeah course will ya
We everybody has written him off as a
Conspiracy theorist
Hard right
Oppression views nobody really harsh coated bigotry
Love of guns
Those being combined and I really don't like that those are almost always
Combine
Alex Jones
Is it
I've already seen you have a great day
Does Nick clip actually dovetails into the Trump investigation
Up to this point this is the first time he comes up now almost 2 hours until episodes
Of the
Okay
Apparently
Some lady
Ask him a question
Open with her hands on her
And ask a question about like
How bad he is about women
Yeah and
Remember that and it weaves into a story about him
Himself
And a very f*****-up
Retelling of History
That is not true
Wow
Jeb Bush caught with a pro
With her hands on her hips
Just grandstanding to manipulate women
Jamaica
Anyone needs
Demetrius
Psychologist or otherwise to know how to put your hands on me
Secondly
How to look at somebody with
Within the context
Alex Jones
Gun-free
Run by Bloomberg
And stuff like that he's making this up
About this woman who asked a question
He's making that up
And sayings
This is all brainwashing
That's all he does
Every single time something like this happen
He just comes up with it
A concoction of all
I'm a big fan of other people
Grandstand
That's one where you live
F****** dial that leave that one alone she wasn't fake crying
But also like he's making stuff up all the time it is obviously another made
And what have you
So like later roll sec
Literal
Literal cycle
He also is imagining
That like
This hate this be projecting this
Everyone's trying to brainwash you in the same way
Someone critiquing him is a literal gobble
Really f***** up anyway
This is how they stay stuff
This is how dumb they think we are
Yelp
This is how they pull these
Michelle Malkin
She said that I was a liar years ago
And said it was a robot dog that flew off a cliff
No reason
I have no idea
I have no idea what it is that point
And then she had
Guys weather
Yelling kill Michelle Malkin lean down behind me
Web camera
National hubs that day
Hard copy extra NBC News CBS News
To say
Fine
Like
If Michelle Malkin
Did Thrift Shop against you
Whatever
I apologize apologize
Sorry you had to go through that
I don't support Michelle Malkin either
That's f***** up that's the right
Sucks sucks
Doesn't realize
Don't relate at all
What's going on
She called me a liar
I don't know what that story is about throwing dog off a cliff
I can only f******
Look into it so many
You know I only have enough energy
This is like Castro is like
Whatever I don't care
You are a liar
Damn baby weren't lying about this
Who cares
Exactly
Let's get to what he's super wrong about
I got calls from National talk show host Alex Me Maybe over for you
But this is a type of stuff they can pull
He was going to end up basically beating Hillary beating Obama
And so they ran that hoax
Where they go
Isolated
Microphone that was a corduroy
Cordless microphone
Cardioid
What singer Rock Band Whatever
The Scream
Experience
So his argument is that
Much like the hour starting on them
Just like
Took down Howard Dean scream
Name is used to famous to popular
He was going to destroy Barack Obama and Hillary Clinton
I'm starting to think
If I
I'm remembering back
Howard Dean
And I'm picturing him
Standing
To Obama and Hillary
And then I'm remembering that
He was not running against either of the
2004-2008 against
It was just before the Iowa caucuses in 2004
I'll give you a
Surprise
Yeah I know
With
Like it was not
Set up by Obama
But let's go down the list
Of all of the people
Just for fun cuz I have the list
John Kerry
Howard Dean
Dick Gephardt Hillary
That's it Hillary
Wesley Clark is the closest Alex Jones Mike state to a global
Is a general
Why would you eat pepper haircut why would what a weird world
Minute but it did not last very long
He came out with that
There was plans to take over 7 countries
Howard Dean
And it's another one of those situations
That's the worst possible guy
A terrible friend
2004 my brother drove around a rehab the beetle
That he had
He'd fixed up himself
Sicario 4 because even mediocrity than approved
Yeah
Especially
I think I sincerely think the John Kerry could have been
President
Real decent chance of winning
Had it not been for the Swift boats
Yeah I which is Jerome corsi
Congratulations for destroying 50 years of our country
At least 50 years who knows how long it's been extended the f*** announcers
G dubs
Initially
Probably not having you knows it's tough to rewrite history
That's true
It's hard to imagine that a Democratic president would get away with the biggest lies
That you can
Did you can
Possibly give
Which was the
War in Iraq
You're right the right is much better at
I mean they're wrong
Because there cuz we all know there.
Well the thing is I think the right is always wrong
At being a safeguard
You know like
Democrats when they're in power can never really do too much
Because the right is so angry
And so aggressive that they pushed back
On everything
So hard
Conservative
Republican
We get called the alt left
Write creeping socialism
Play creeping Sharia
Totally
I was jumped episode
With noted chiropractor dr. green
Yes you come visit
You comes into talk about how
Superman
There was a shortage of gas prices prices
Totally
Stagflation
With super male vitality
Keeps doing this like
I want to cover the waterfront
Uses that expression a lot by the way
Ben Lovett I think we need to use a lot more Waterfront
Of course
A really long tail
Yeah but we get this
What do you make of rice
Why are you asking
Russia's tried to come to the u.s. tab
Capacity of the chiropractor
The Japanese stop scene
2 days before Pearl Harbor
We're going on
Diplomatic
Rice has been kicked out of
I don't think they realize.
But you just
Mention depressive
It's on president
Just mentioned
7 seconds ago
But be that as it may look you're right why the f*** you asking dr. group
I meant Alex Jones ends up saying
I'm glad he was wrong turn it off by the time
I think even his dumbass fans get like
By this weekend be boring
I think
Doctor group come on
Take a screenshot of the picture of doctor group
Skype
Discovered in
I was like I want I want to I want to research all of them
Screenshot and try and get like what are the details
But it was too like
Blurry I couldn't even
Zoom in
Yeah
The end of October 14th
This
Is I think
One of the most
Important days
In our investigation
This day is
Credible
I think
Notebook
I think this is the day that I was Jones's brain
I think
If you lost it
On October
15 to 27
I might be wrong
I've made a lot of bad prediction
I cop to that
A butt
The show start
This is going to frustrate
S*** out of you
And I love it
It's going to frustrate the s*** out of our audience
Alex Jones does one
Witchy professionally teases
Why
He doesn't say
At all
In this next clip
Why is
I'm freaking out
It's so good it's saying nothing for a long time
It's it's amazing
Watch this professional at f****** work
Every too much
Stories come together
Knowledge
And understanding
I've got terminal systems worldwide
Which is to say nothing at all
The Tumblers basically click into place the safe door opens
So I want
Keep in mind
This clip is
3 1/2 minutes long
He says nothing
If you at any point while you're listening to this
Think you know what he's about to say
You're probably wrong
Unless you're
Whenever we talk about amazing broadcast
This is my only
The end of this about how he's not saying anything
It's for 24 seconds in he said nothing
Dory comes out
Brilliant
But especially America that schizophrenia
Yeah
You can really see what's inside
And a group of Stories the last 2 weeks
Come together in a confluence
Which ones
That is so important
I am having trouble
Feeling even Worthy
To try to describe to you
Absolutely country
And it takes me to my
Poor
This guy's a f******
Impro
Got a lot of long pauses here
In fact so important
This morning before the show
And it connected and everything else we already know
About what
Almost went
Today
Grab all the news you're researching you're doing Michelle
Processor
With myself
An article
Put on emergency alert
Ancient Armory stories
I would think coming outside to Telluride
Door locked
There's a f****** Pro
Really situation wherein and really see
Worst
Case scenario analyses
We've come up with many others about come up with
Concurrent
Shipley
Is so
Horrible
And it confirms our worst
Not fears are worst
Long-term projections
All of them
Your projections about what
I am not
Did you eat
Which instrument
F*** off
I'm not trying to be dramatic
That's amazing man was nothing
That's a gifted broadcaster
Boat like that
Tubi
About nothing he said nothing
He said nothing
Another like 3 minutes after that
He does touch on specific topics after that
The story of it is got him
All Shook Up
Jesus
So does he
So did he get in front of it
He was on the air the entire time
Yeah but did he
Ghostwriting
That is like
Really getting him out of sorts
Would you like to try and guess
The worst long-term
October 15th
Correct
Fast & Furious 6
Came out
The timeline I'm not sure
They
The basketball season
Golden State Warriors
They have no idea what they're coming for him
But they're going to go on at are they're going to win 73 games
I know I'd like for you to try
Was that that was that the year before that
Remember I'd like for a serious gas bill
Geopolitical
Possibly be shaking him to his core like that
5:30 amp
And put his head in his hands
And pretend that he can't do the show
And he's going to get David night to host so we can get Paul Joseph Watson to write an article about it
Cuz this is going to go viral and if I just talked about it on the air
It turns out
That
All of the iodine
Is gone
No you be way more f***** up
That's true
And we have megalomaniac
Running the show that hate us the better cleaners
Just because we don't commit crime
Is measurable
They had it usually produce so much wealth
Not true
Just because we're strong they hate us because we're good
I told you that
They were going to start
They haven't
They're calling it payments for endorsements
Campaign for Liberty other organizations
Taking over the Republican Party
Nautica
Not really
Paul Ryan
Congratulations
This is a peaceful Revolution
Nah
They are trying to find anything to indict
Ron Paul
RuPaul
That is coming
Clarence Thomas
So it's because two of Rand Paul staffers were indicted on
Don't know what the truth of that store you
So
The charges
From the Elder Paul
2012 presidential campaign
In which former state senator Kent Sorenson
Admitted to receiving $70
From Ron Paul presidential campaign for switching his endorsement from
Ron Paul
Federal prosecutors allege that the three individuals who were charged
Indicted
Not to us
Federal Election Commission
The cover-up payment
Sorensen
Exchange for his endorsement to Ron Paul
Benton service Paul's campaign chairman in 2012 but has maintained his innocence
We went on to work for America's Liberty political action committee
Super PAC
But took the organization when the first round of indictments were handed down
So okay to switch is indoors
It's really cheap you should you should hold if you're going to do that illegal
Senator
It's not even a senator
.88 might be an influential person in
Various circles
You can't get more than that
Perspective
Senator
Yes they committed
For committing crime
Is it going to rain
Anybody for committing crimes told him he thinks that it's going to be
Perfectly timed destroys campaign
It's just that
That's how the court works
That is one of those things
Though we're
There is always a part of my
Conspiracy theory brand that's like
That has to happen
That kind of
That kind of bribery always get caught we live in Illinois
That
I'm sure
The courts
Can't deal with
Things they don't know about
If if you don't have a charge
Accord can't hear the charge
And in this case
Do you guys got sloppy
And
Clearly Sorensen
The receiving the money
Look
He was paid off to admit that he received 3000
And $1
In order to admit
$73,000
You take down rampaul dates
Attorney General
Who's been indicted
So that's that's the big news
General news is the worst projections
Infowars is Rand Paul staffers got taken down for
Committing crimes
Sprite
That's
Confirms the worst for 3 minutes
Processor and write down how they
And now they're in
Trouble for it but the thing is it's not just about them it's also about the Texas Attorney General
She never says my name
Because I don't think he knows
His name is Ken Paxton
I apologize is like four paragraphs or so so
I'm going to get through it
Text Mom
This is an article about why I got in trouble
The case and the federal one involved Mr Paxton's work in a 2011 promoting and recruiting of investor
Technology company
Serve Energy Incorporated
Federal officials accused Mr PacSun.
Encouraging and pressuring investors to invest
Conserve energy while failing to disclose that he was being compensated by the company
The investors included several of mr. Paxton
Since friends and fellow lawmakers
Court documents filed by the SEC claim that Mr packs
Austin raised $840,000 from investors
And received 100,000
Shares of stock
In return
But never disclosed his Commission
Mr. Paxton told investigators that he accepted the shares as a gift
From the company's founder
But actually if they okay
Mission failed
So it becomes they will they won't they he said she said just like me
I like this company and
But
Unfortunately
The unfortunately the article
Goes on
We should note the Paxton was fine by the Texas state Securities 2014 for failing to
Disclosed.
Describe that as a quote administrative oversight
So he's admitted
Similar behavior in the past
SEC also claims
After meeting with survey
Paxton was offered a 10% Commission
And from the company
And when
Paxton wrote back quote I will get to work
Scheduling meetings with a number of investors shortly thereafter
This issue is identified
4 quotes
Services
According to the filing
This is the bulk of the case against Paxton
But it's not the entirety of it
The charge also implicates Paxton in the fraud charges against the former surf energy
Dceo name is Matt
Who faces the most dramatic charges of life
Amazon
Freescale
Some of these investors were people who were recruited by Pat
And phrases like quote
Thing to determine whether Maps claims were true up here several times throughout the filing
Maps
From claims that serve energy product
Computer servers
We're essentially
Specially energy-efficient
And cutting-edge
Which does not appear to have been
Paxton is associated with
Two in the filing
And did not know whether
I need serve energies claims were true
He conduct
Didn't know due diligence to confirm clarify or correct serve energy
So that's why I said
Attorney general is in trouble
Bill committed
He filled out a paperwork
And was getting paid under the table for bullying people
Bullying is strong
Really actively recruiting
Crime
Does this happen is so
Does this happen on the left
Maybe
Like juice
If we who have
Like like with this type of situation with all of these f****** situation situation
Clarks
Situation all of that stuff
It's always
Crime
They didn't commit the crime
So yeah
He was a democratic
Why is it not okay for for us
We cast aside are weirdos
Now maybe Alex Jones exaggerate a lot of the claims again
Martha Stewart went to jail for inside
Great but you committed a crime
I think that a lot of liberals
Have a very large even-keel about abandoning their own
When it's clear they've committed crime
You know what I related to I related to what happened with smoking
As a whole
Like smoking
Distasteful
Used to be okay to smoke on planes
I used to be okay to smoke
You can smoke in the hospital smoke
Whataburger
It became a thing where
Science
Came out really hate
You shouldn't be doing
It's probably really bad
Got it got it
Cool cool
Sorry about that
Sorry about that we'll just go over here
Call man last night I met a secondhand smoke
Jesus
As a science was wrong you should still be able to smoke 008
Percent of far-off from the truth I think secondhand smoke is a little bit exaggerated
It's even as a smoker I get its
Way better smokers are a facsimile for liberals in the
Event like we
Smoke everywhere
We were smoking
Apartment right now
We realize like oh
Contain
Smoke can't get anywhere
In the sky
That's f***** up alright fine
We agree to change our Behavior accordingly
I&M go along with it
Whereas conservative
They're not
Like smokers
Eventually I won't be able to smoke
And that's why I
People on the right
When all the time differently defend people were clearly
And Alex
Like
It goes back to the
Confederate flag on trucks thing we were talking about earlier
If any articles other than headline
Keep know this stuff
You know that there's like
Miss Sorenson admitted to taking the payoff
To change his
That's not being
No that's a payoff yeah that's okay
I suppose the closest
Analog is probably how people treated Cosby
Okay
Sure
20 women came out okay sure
Okay at a certain point
You know even the most well though there still people
Got2b didn't do it
Cosby
Sure are the same way with Louis c.k. likes Louis c.k. definitely is a
Should be committed sexual assault many many times
I think this is different though
Because with Cosby and with Louis c.k.
There are
Long
With long histories of really positive experiences
You had because of
Like I
Love
Louis c.k.
Hey back in like
The early 90s
Late 90s early 2000
He was amazing
Betty was even before
Shifted
And became the Louis c.k. that everyone knows
Like the I like those f****** joke for awesome
Again
Is running out of extras in your life
Are those things that are very difficult
You feel like you have to give up on them
Because you see the person has
They grew they actually are different then
Just automatically Defending Your Own blind
I understand the struggle of like
Man this guy's art doesn't match up with who he is actually is a
Person that's f*****
Right
That's disappointing
This is Alex's being like
If it take any of our team to take masol
That's more cowardly
Any and every possible reason
How do you
Everything Joe Arpaio dead
Everything
That just makes it more likely that more of these guys are going to be there
If you f****** pardon Joe Arpaio
Does Debbie Moore
Yeah
The flip side of it too is like there is a power dynamic
To it also
S*** is like
Ted Cruz's
Got indicted
Something like that
Even though at this point in 2015 he supports Ted Cruz
Yeah I don't think so I think it's because it's wrong
Legacy support
Ted Cruz
Mostly
But he loves Grandpa
Image
Pure libertarian
Right
The hits.
Stupid
His fear is that they're coming after these
Tea Party
Libertarian type
And because it's a
Storm of crime
We're going to invite them
He has to have to support
In the same way is it like
Individually
Even the whites
Supremacist don't care
One of theirs get the red
Send out warrants
Sweet yeah
Great Ohio to Charlottesville
Yeah
Madonna me the former comic
It's whatever
Cancel alarm or Cantrell or whatever
Metro
You're so wrong on this terrible machine
You're on your f****** phone
Unless you become important to
Alex Jones is
Machine or whatever
When you saw what that what you did to Jason Kessler
The guy who organized the unite the right thing
Right
Oh we mentioned in passing but we covered.
So I mean look at you got to
Even even we support all of our own
Don't really care about the bottom
Risport Oliver on to ascertain
Anybody who's not you
Supported you in further hoax
Probably about 2
Obama Iran deal
Stupid
We are we got some more clips
Get through
Plus this thing down
Does Mexico
Because of
Better come down
He says this
Which so many of the other things we've talked about
On this episode and the last like 5 episodes are so Russia
But
What he saying
Is like
It's even next level
Wash it was captured
Play pulled away from The Entity
Besieged by
Economic Warfare
And
Destabilization
Foundations
Strongman Mafia corruption
Is Angelic compared to the
Russians are not putting fluoride their water in cancer viruses on their backs
And when they bring down the Russians
That's why
Secret weapon is a radical Muslims
Great
Everywhere
Driving around with a
Yeah but it's like what he saying there if you really want to sum up that clip entirely its Russia is the last line of defense
Andy
Brushes important
Do you understand everybody gets
Do you understand
Cliff
In that Club Fortune
He's betraying
He believed that Russia is better and
I'm stronger than the American people
Take out Russia
Those walk right over us
What was we are
Public
It's Russia
Because we couldn't possibly stand up
That's what I like
Hugh loves Russia
F*****-up can we get it
Yeah I'd love it
Can we just get him to move
Especially if it was in the North
Cinema Siberia that's what I'm saying
Because it's not really important
Why would you love Russia
But
I like
Imagine imagine
Him moving
Just for a second
Of course he would never
No probably not
Ever
No he wants to live in Austin
Catoctin f****** great like a lot of America
Unlike a lot of Russia
He's a f****** idiot but if you want to think about Russia at hold on to it for a little bit
The next president going to skip is just him faking crying
He tries to cry
Can't you tries to do this does not
Work
AJ's bail
But has like 3 minutes long
It's not worth it
So also on this episode
Joe big
Has been sent out to Hillary Clinton
And
The really important thing
In the
Projection
And trajectory
Of Alex Jones
Going to
He
Is out there
Like literally the goal is to cause
Write his hole
Goal
His whole objective
Is to stir
The stir the pot
Yeah that's what Joe Biggs. That's why you send but it hasn't really been that way up till this point
Because the time that he went out to a trump rally and showed off his Hillary for prison shirts
That's not really stirring
He's now started to go out
I do not
Rally where he's going to unveil his Hillary for prison shirt
He's going out
Specifically
Troll in real life
As an advertising
Tool
That this is where the story bombing begin
And Alex
Starts to see
Incredibly effective marketing
And that's why you start to give people
Screaming Bill Clinton is a rapist on television
And all this s*** that Alex ends up doing
To quote unquote troll the media
When where he's really doing is Buzz Market
And I think that this
Episode
On October 15th
Not only has the breakdown
About Alex being like
It's confirmed
They're coming for the Patriots because
These ramps
The but also
The first time
Will inevitably see a spike in sales
Because your big when trolled
Hey liberal route
I think that those two things
Art like
Foundational
In his is shipped
This clip is a Joe Biggs
Out at the rally
Presentism tattoo
Far we have been able to
Basically weasel our way into the Hillary Clinton
Hillary t-shirt
Theories
Start screaming Hillary for prison
Was great but
We're into fiscal year 2016 now
Now it's time to start
Jbr
Narrative of economic collapse coming.
Happening
Starting to not be scared as much by the
Detours Buzz Marketing
Varices
Joe Biggs
And I cut out all of it
But he's just getting off
Like in debate
He keeps trying to have debates with people
It's so funny cuz Alex is back in the studio
Is people making great point
Do you know
Alex
Push push
Brush
Argument
It's really bizarre
It's
Exactly why
These people are so
Frustrating
And stupid
If you want
To do that if you're going to go start
And start debates with
Prep
Libby great
Weather
Half-assed
I know I'm going to win because
But that's the problem
Weather
Conspiracy theories are just got in the high and watch YouTube the
It's the same thing with the big
Tuesday is the equivalent intellectually
Politico
I'm someone who's gotten high and watch YouTube video
I wants to talk to you about the you-know-what
What about
CFR
Far
What about them
What about relation
What about Bilderberg
You're too dumb to know what you're too dumb about
Admirably in debates
Against him thrown off by the fact that he keeps
Clearly having to listen to Alex and his
And not really engaged with
The flow of conversation but
They're their there for a little bit and then
Studio
We're outside
With a gentleman by the name of Robert
The Fairly regular gas
He's also a
I think now might be a good time to listen to
He would not like to help you because you're a dumb live
The Doomsday is coming for all of us
I think it's
I'm I mean I guess
He would probably just tell you to get guns
Water and gold
I can do the
This guy is a huge dick
The two spaces.
Because the whole world
A liar
Budget saver
Crazy how can you believe that
Crazy
Can you actually believe that
You can't
Possibly
Really believe
You can if you really hate the idea
That doesn't make
Any sense at all
Yeah well I have no
Idea that they're doing that
Always lie
30 years ago
Possibly believe that it's not the truth
I mean I get it if you are a Russian Citizen and all you get is russian-owned Media all day everyday
I mean even the even f****** North Korea
More like
We're going to die
Do it later I'm crying
But if you're here
Come on
Outside
And look at this and there's no possible way you can be like
When is a state
It gets worse
Shame on you just it's like The Emperor's New Clothes
Really as being a statement what do you expect
I think
Okay
Walk-around
Bus tracker
Protests
Said that I believe
They don't want to kill him
Do want him out of power
And then they get killed
That's what happened
Yeah
You know that
All around the world has
Kill at this point like
70 or 80 some Bloomers category
Plenty of people want to kill
He's way better than way better at the evolved version of the kgb's
He's operate
This is pathetic
It's naked
In terms of how clear it is but this is a show
That is demonstrating
Outright
Unequivocal support for Putin and Russia
And
Yes and
He has not endorsed Trump
Heat this predates
All of that
This is
Where his heart is
That Putin
Is awesome
And Russia is the last line of defense
That's f*****
Profound
And way worse than anything I thought that we would uncover
Just by listening to his show it's not like we're doing any sleuthing we're just using his word
He just knows that no one's paying attention or they already believe the global is narrative
Right
They're waiting for him to take a shirt off
Or maybe because he waiting for food
Demonize has the mainstream media so much
Realmedia
RT
It's a cedonia
Visa Russian media Outlets.
And maybe they believe in
And I can't go to LG
20-something
Yeah
Episode
Paul Craig Roberts is gone
JoJo Beck
Clinton rally because
Hurst
Alex
Wants comments on it a little bit
Wants to get a little sassy
And this is
Stupid
Gelato
Google Kik
Describe Road hacks
CIA anthropology
We have been in Green Room
What's the what's the thing that people make fun of around here
Yep that's what all the time
Small town
Oh it's the Shelbyville or whatever
How do I mad libs a joke
They are
I mean
Dumb the same way I hate the Roadhouse
Doing it
I don't like Hillary
Name-checking green enchiladas
You hate it in terms of perform
Cuz you hit the road hack in terms like this is fake
Performance
And you hate that and Hillary Clinton
Is just
Not a great
Dynamic performer
And have to fall back on those trick comedian should evolve to
To the point where they're able to on stage
What are you guys not like yeah be able to integrate it simply into their
Crowd work
Iprotec
And they just wanted
And Hillary baby inside Shiner Bock
It's fine
It's alright
It's a beer
It's not bad proud of it
It's fine I know local Pride
This next
Looks like we're not going to South Texas
Anytime soon
You're a great son
You should have a green enchilada
Alex Jones
Still
Doing some Mystery Science Theater over the
The Hillary Clinton speech
But he takes the opportunity to break out some impression
Fletcher throw G-Code
They're worried their dreams I'm going to give you your dream
I know your area green enchiladas I'm your friend I'm your friend Obamacare it's free
Equals 5
Grandmothers and mothers grandmothers
Grandmother's Mother's Vikings Hispanic women
Mention
Lisa Yuen
LA Fitness
Condescension about dumb she thinks people are
Are monotone voice
First impressions
Based on what he saying
I think she can pull off different impression
She's not monotone
Second
She doesn't do that
Third
Those impressions are racist
Yeah
Also
If you're doing a racist impression of a Hispanic person
He went
Part Asian
That's Def
I don't know
Anthony
He says exactly what he's
Energy
He's infuriating
Sojourn
Wait do you mean
You just did a thing
Yeah doesn't do
It's becoming really tired for us to argue
I know right yeah
Whatever it is they say you're doing
Or what you're doing
But what they're saying
There is actually what we're doing
But what is what
Will Shakespeare
It's it's
Where we're going to end
October 15th
Has been about
Is Alex Jones
I keep forgetting
Support Donald Trump
I feel like all of our investigation has actually been
The investigation is turned into
History a lot
There's a tie
The different stuff happening at that it
Didn't happen so you're like
Yeah but what I predicted
You're not working
You're not awake
In here Alex Jones has a conversation with Joe big
About where we stand on the candidates
And let's see if any
Here we go
This is a whole country in pool
Sexist racist
I don't know my trust is history but now they're moving
For nothing I literally
Champion
These are people who died
He doesn't offer a lot of loose early in the race I'm still open
Solutions
We need to do something more than just building a wall
No I think I'll alert you won't I really doesn't fit over there I think he should have been
Democratic
As our president
Eli's on the table
This is so frustrating
For two reasons why a lot of sense
Until then
Really bring home that everyone is just a Hillary
They're not really
They don't have any
Foundation of like what they're for
As much as what they're again
I think it crystallized that point
But the idea Trump is saying a bunch of bulshit
It sounds good but there's no solution
I mean that's very reasonable
Look at Trump
And Joe Biggs is way smarter than Alex
At the same time
The show is about alley
And it is
Peekablue frustrating
At all
In terms of trump
It's still I like what you say
The fast-forward button
I know this is
Well the thing is I'm trying but then at the same time
Like every few days something important happen
Like drug shows up in this episode
Alex has VR Confederates narrative
Plus the day Ron Paul Rand Paul age
Take it down and like this is
The end of conservative
Lake
There's too much that ends up happening every few years
Used to be every free
Few years
Something
Socrate
You can just
Inside the Box
But normally you
Few months
It happens
Every few days
Crazy 8
Blows
My my
I don't even feel like we're worthy enough
Oh boy
To broadcast
What it is
That we are looking
Right and it happens
Everything
I mean we record
Every couple
Every
Couple of days we record
This park
Sometimes
Something
Something Joe big hat
I don't know how long I can do that I couldn't I was boring
Myself he's got skills
Also he allows long Gap
That's true
But like
I mean we know
We get it
He loves Russia
The end of its investigation
Unreal
Come down to marching orders from Russia
Well maybe not
We're all in for
I think it's going to be a combination of that and the various people who like I think my initial
Prediction is still
ShopRite
I think there's the rush
And then
I think we saw earlier
Steve pieczenik is going to show up on the show within the next few days
Rodger stone is only like I think a month away from showing up probably
December it's late October
There's no way you don't show up within a month or so
So even even what I just I think there's just these people lying to him
And him taking in lies from State media in Russia that he's like
It's counter to CNN
It must be true
That's I think I think that's it
I mean we're going to keep going cuz I like I said our predictions
I've been wrong repeatedly
I don't see how that's not
The picture that's taken shape
It seems like
Yeah
The full throated 1776
Again I doesn't happen right away
It might it could love it first
Kind of thing
I never saw the I never saw the actual interview with Alex
The the current
F******
I never saw the
I can't imagine it was already
That full like
You're the Goddamn hero of this f****** world it wasn't that then I think it has to be I don't know because
I don't know I didn't listen to the shows around it
Just based on the psychology of trump
I don't think that he would have
The show
No he was
Turn off
Yeah
Before Trump would
Give him
The time of day
Haha
A little bit when he was on
In the sense that he said your reputation is amazing in the future
Speak witches lies about
Upon lies
You can strain himself a little bit
Especially when it's
Comes to compliment
He always throws
Superlatives
In Flowery language on negatives
But when you compliment
Sing somebody
I think he is probably
Cuz
Who's
Not worthy of compliment I don't know
Vocabulary when it comes to
But it like
This is
Supremely frustrating as a job for me
Because I want to see real chain
I want the narrative
And I don't
I guess
What it with the lesson is for me
Is
I thought the narrative
Of the investigation was
Why did Alex Jones
Support Trump
And it turns out the investigation
Narrative
Holyshit
And of course
It's becoming very different than what we set out for
I know we commented on that in the past but I like
It can't be stated enough
Like this is
Really weird this is f***** up
Super weird
We have art
Arteon
Alex
And guess what
Our next episode
It's going to get even weirder
Dammit
What are you doing on our next episode
We cover
The episode that includes
Classic
The gay bomb
Oh okay there we go
So get ready for that
Ulta
We should have said that three hours ago
Totally
We suck where bad promoting
North bar Chicago Illinois
It's over on North
Avenue
And
Yep no cover I believe
I worked out all the details
It'll be drink specials
Me some stand-up
3 hours
Yeah it'll be a regular show
Know immediately rethought that we will
Wait a second wife
Greatest National tragedy episode
See what the world was like
But you were doing that if you want to find out more about the
Links to the archives and a bunch of other stuff, our website
We like it would
Bandolier reviews you like also I can find us on Facebook
We were there you going to nut
Communicate
Piece of paper and just where and I'll eventually be up to all five star
Reviews on Facebook
You know
Said we're great
Another thing we should run 3 hours
Just got in a bunch
Responses for people in Europe
Your country likes
From 5 countries in Europe
And all of them are
Uniform
Getting a real strong sense of most people
And the ones who do
That like we think are crazy
Yeah I think
Beyond that we haven't
Is there
So I I don't know
Like how do we get out of this
Like we just met recording for a long time
Do we just do like
Do we just
Like how do how do we end
I don't know
I honestly
I have not been list
22 for the last 30
Okay because
I'm thinking about it
And this is not
I know we're doing the
I've legitimately
Recognized in my head that were trying to do
And all I can think about
Jon rappoport
Doing that Russian dance with a squat that particular lights.
It's a really funny picture with his big Gray beard.
It's really great
Alright
Image
Jon rappoport
Is the polar opposite
Actual John Rappaport
Terrible
I don't know.
I would
I just like to say from from all of us
Hear it now it's right
Go fuc yourself John Rappaport
Alexandra Thurston color