Alex
Is it around
Beverages and talk about Alex
That's nearly as much as Jobs
Really
The number of people that I want
Certainly the
It's greatly appreciated
Half as many
I would have assumed that it was much like Alex Jones real Liquors in Chicago
Negative out of a job
Let me ask you a question
Could possibly be a reason that
People would listen
Beyond at Subway
Is it like is there a dynamic between the two of us
We're friends
So let's
Converse with Alfred
Some business to take care of up top
I'd like to remind everyone that we have a live show coming up at North bar on cell
September 9th
Instead of at the NFL
Smart this is
Cressida territory
9 p.m.
And I feel comfortable enough to review at this point
There will be doing is going over Alex
That is exactly what we should do in life
You should come check if you live in other parts of the country of the world
Do you happen to have friends in Chicago
We didn't know what the Saturday night at a bar would really like to make it
Not shity for the bar
Yeah even even even when we're doing it for us
Weird
Also if you are anywhere in the world
Chicago's quite lovely the
This time of year
America
Not so great but no
The leaves are about to
2 Chainz
Sonia from Sweden alliteration
Impossible to ignore
Thank you very much for donating to the show sound
Saturday night's
If you would like me to website knowledge.com
Berkeley Sports
Please do
I'd like to give a special shout-out
Special policy wonks out there
Like
Congratulations
Congratulations on your engagement congratulations
Happy congratulate congratulations Mike and Beth
We wish all the blessing
Songs of the elite globalist
Upon your union
Hope your wedding is as extravagant as that of one of the Rockefellers or so I don't know
We just want you to get through life
Extensions
Technology in that only cow
Traditional
Good luck
I think we got through it
Reasonably quickly
Jordan
Some iffy news
The current day Alex Jones
Faygo red pop
And it has the delicious Taste of red and black
Candy
Sugar
Interrupt
Goodbye your
Shock and awe
Modern-day out
Alex Jones
Checked in on the show where there's been a natural disaster
Trump has been
Bungling
Instafollow
I wanted to check in
And see what was going on today
I am at work
Let me listen to Wednesday's show
Pull up the episode
Hey looks like it has the gas
Listen
Dugan is back
No like
How is this possible
The other guests on the show is Stefan molyneux
I can't do it I just
Stephon Marbury
I'm in
Who don't know who he is
He's a guy who created
The show called free domain
He considers him
Himself the most popular
Philosopher
On the on iTunes or on the Internet
These videos where he's just like in front of
Discussing philosophical Concepts
All right so he's an idiot he's really smart
No I mean Smart in the technical sense
Okay
Chameleon
You get here
And it seems me to say so cuz
Is a libertarian
All right so he's an idiot
He is legitimately a call later
Okay there are actual support groups
People who have broken away from
His freedomain Radio
Heap
He believes
Do anything he called
Which is
On the surface
A really decent thing
I'm not going to play anything of
Maybe everybody because he is a dangerous
F****** dingdong he's enraged
He has a habit of suing
People
Or pressingly copyright charges against them if they use
Eclipse
Him to prove him wrong
Do you like tents
He took down an opponent
YouTube channel because they were using it
It like that
It sounds good on the surface
And what it is is Eid
Write get Rick Roll
Text mirror
Do it
Don't have to
Abusive people in your life
People are negative
You can cut them out of your
Suppressive person
You don't go
Phrase It's actually good cuz you do have the right to keep negative influences out of your life but
Problem is
She believed
Did anybody who doesn't believe in v
Libertarian anarcho-capitalist
Are abusing you
AMV
Exactly that sort of thing
He has videos where he goes on and on talking about how like
If you support the idea of me going
To prison
Cuz I don't pay my taxes
Then you support government violence
Against me
Why should I allow you in my life
If you support violence
Against me
So basically
He's advocating that it's
Reasonable and necessary
To cut anyone out of your life who believes in taxes
Pulling some sort of irrational illogical Jiu-Jitsu on it
Yeah damn smart people because he is incredibly smart and very manipulative
Then the only contacts
Between which UK
You can say that is
He's incredibly smart
And talented at the scale of make
Idiot
I recommend anybody who's interested do this there's a lot of videos on YouTube you can find
Used to be a part of his
His flock
Discuss
The experience
Of being
Soccer team basically
Very smart articulate people
You know they thought they were getting involved in something political and it turned out it was a
You know what's up
Bullet Clapper or Brennan saying like
Sometimes the road to ending up
Doing treasonous things
It doesn't appear that it's
Until it's too late
Oh yeah
I think I mean
The Intern
Your life
Don't know
And tell your aunt
But it's something really f***** up
There's a Common Thread among all of the people
It's the same thing with suicide
It really is like a path
Completing Moana
I'm hopeless
I don't know what I'm doing
Nobody is giving me any good advice
That just gives you this like
This hope
Talladega
It's the same way with suicide
You know the if you don't commit suicide
You know if you get through that 5 minutes
Or whatever length
The time then all the sudden
It wasn't that big a
What you get over
That happens with people who join
Did they get there
EBay get him at that right moment
Smart or dumb
But
If you're the cult leader
Generally you have some
Some sort of charismatic
Intelligence
About you
He is
Worst
Is the van
YouTube
You can find a video of this somewhere but
After Elliot Rodger
And killed a bunch of people cuz
Women wouldn't have sex with him
Stefan molyneux
Okay
Yeah his whole angle
Trespass to get around all of the obvious idiots I recall it had to do with like women
F****** strong.
You're going to end up causing this sort of thing
Of course what the f*** are you talkin about
But anyway it's not like that I have bread
To beat them
Insane person
Like these clips
Exist
Stefan molyneux
His work because he has this
Copyright
And has
Take an action
People
Pretty reticent
The post clips
All the evil stuff
It's still there but you got to dig through hours of him rambling about
Esoteric points in philosophy
Stop it sounds benign in order to get to those points
So he gets a lot of cover out of
I mean thank God understand the irony of him being a
Leonardo Grant
Obviously he's a f****** moron
Get it
So on Wednesday Alex has
Stephon on
Cute problem basically
He's worse than wack
Way too nice
Cult leader
On his show
I may have a chummy tees on
And then Alexander Dugan
I was just like
I don't know what
To do I just
Xbox the present
So I just I looked at that and I said I don't want to live in
Present
So here's an out-of-context drop
Talkin about
As I've said
Raptors are
Play the pastor in a lot in this discussion
Rector
Brothers
I have discovered something really f***** up
That is gorgeous
As I've said
Raptors are
Going to factor in a lot in this
Discussion
Simone biles
Still die but
Celebrate
Is bachelor party
Congrats
3 hours of
Stefan molyneux going on
Yes Raptors are going to factor heavily
Project Camelot
You don't normally
Outside of the context
Project Camelot
There's going to be a very narrow path
Conversation
I can go down to know a lot about
To decide what Raptors is this a Jurassic Park
Situation
Is this day as
You mentioned Falconer said
Done much in the playoffs for a long time
I have no f****** clue and anything could have
It could be all of them everything
Certainly they're not going to be talking about
Tracy McGrady
No
Who is on the Raptors
40 years old they still playing
God bless him when I stopped watching basketball
Around that time
Not theirs
Is amazing right now.
I know why I'm doing this
Because you do
Too afraid
To get to
Jordan
Look at it for those of you who have not listened to our entire back catalogue whenever we need
We dip our toes into the world of Project Camelot
Kerry Cassidy
Natality
Jordan and I could not get her name right for a very long time
We need to do that
Strolling around
After I got sick of the idea of listening to Alex
And I saw
An interview
With a lady named Joanne Richards
Alex Jones
I have been for 16 years
Got if I can get into it
So this is
Connection to the Alex Jones Show
We're still we're still doing research
We're still doing research today
I'm not I'm not
121 related
The same topic
Of course not
Much more fun
Because they believe in good and everything is negative all the
Phoenix drop is great and Patriots are awesome
Even though
Still coming
So we're going to be start we're going to be covering two episodes of Project Camelot
At this Jordan
Is going to be
An incredible roller coaster ride. I have
Speaker review
I like
It took every bit of strength
First of all.
To tell you that I was doing a project
Do not
Spoil where this is going
Is so hard
I'm going to try and lay this out as best I can
And hope for the best
All right this first clip is
Kerry Cassidy
Sitting down with the Joanne
Message Richard auction
She doesn't really know how to give herself an introduction
Is an author
I seen her name on top of books
Probably a different one
I don't think you're ready
Two runs a website about Earth
Garden
Commander something like that this is not the same
This introduction
The self-introduction
But let's sit through just
To get a little bit of a trumpet
Everything
Okay so
Joanne actually you know
Other than I think you you're an accountant on the side you have a background in journalism
I know and
You are married to a very important individual in my view
And I
You've also been on the circuit now
Basically talking about his information and Publishing it
And putting it on a on a very interesting website called Earth Defense
Headquarters
And an n
Give yourself your own introduction
Just
You know to let people know a little bit more about you before we kind of launched into everything
Where do I start I grew up in Southern California basically
High School
In Utah a while married a few different guys
Private clients and also for different Atwood employee for a while
Off and on for 35 years
I have
A grown daughter and three wonderful grandchildren in Portland in Washington
This is a lot of
Superfluous
Years with known each other since
And we courted for five years and then
I'm just flies when you're having fun
So I threw up watching Martian movies in the Sci-Fi movies
I never thought much about it
Oh here we go
A real people did without everybody else knowing about it it's like wow
And then he read about this man you adore almost getting killed over and over and over again and then fighting
Aliens and
All kinds of
Wonderful topics along the way right but I'll be there about your life
I want to know about your daughter
Iowa I like
I like getting that stuff in because I want to stress as we go along Joanne seems like a sweet lady
Marigolds
And then you hear about the man you love fighting aliens
No
This is mostly about Joann's husband mark
They're going to be discussing a lot of information that comes from him
We're going to learn
So much about Raptors
That is that's already
Mark was ever in the military
I don't think he was in the military
I'm going to sleep now
They were in the alternate military
Time travel
Starts with a lot of
Sort of
Pleasantrees you can kind of tell that their friend
Maybe the first 10 minutes or so end up being them
Now it is what it is
But then we get into some real issues
Andy start with
Current events
In terms of
The secret space program in your understanding about what's going on
Has she ever talked to you about
The current events such as what's going on in North Korea
You know I hear things and then I'll ask
You know we were talking a lot about Syria
Akitas on North Korea so I just
Point Blank
Is there something somebody that's guiding what's-his-name in North Korea and Hillside
So just like Syria and Isis
You have the reptoids
Stirring up trouble with the North Korean Daiso
I love it when you say something crazy but then you use like a normal colloquialism you don't like
All the reptoids are stirring up trouble
Yeah
Go to Theory as any I've heard
I think
But amid this does
Lowe's
That's what we talked about in the last Project Camelot episode
About all these World sort of issues like
Iraq
The Vietnam War they were about Stargate
Places where human
Can jump into alien world in Alien
Can come here
And that's where like
Shitgate
Messi
I don't have clips that but part of the
The premise
He's there all the times that we end up bombing
Places because these bombs
End up shot
Yes
Juice Cubes you said the bomb because humans are trying to jump
Through and that's again
Treaties or something like that
Imagine if she asked mark
Any question
That involves
Are the reptoids involved
I think I
I got less than blue book value for
This used car
My sources tell me the reptoids have been getting into used car dealers
What's today
About this
Is there two groups that are being discussed
That are very similar in name but they are different groups and they're actually
No the reptilians
Umbrella term
Target
How many of the Raptors
And the Raptors are good
The rapper
What is a good
Lily asked you questions
I have
One of the Raptors
Fallen madly in love with one of the reptoids
Will there will there be
I don't know about
But I can tell you
Still happy
Okay
Whatever star-crossed lovers scenario may or may not exist
Are engaged
In creating
Entertainment
You know I'm a really good military wife but your there's a lot of things that he does or know that I don't
Don't know a lot of that is because he can't keep me safe but
You know I know he
Watch movies like okay
Jurassic World
Weird names that are
Cuban names and they're not really Malaysia name for the
You can just tell a raptor has tried to get a come up with a human
I don't really know how he knows what the Raptors might
Ryder might not be up to but you know
Apparently
We're behind Jurassic World
Subway
Yeah they're good they're capturing the world
So now I believe everything
Bitter clearly a Raptor truck.
I don't see how that is of a perfect
Joe Anthony's like a sweet lady
But like
Fifty-year-old Maybe
Old white lady
There's no doubt about that
For a lot of her life
In
Bay Area
California
Doesn't leave out there
About like what is or is not a different cultures
Exmark raptors raptors
Philly rappers
She doesn't get how insensitive
But at the same time it's better than
All other names are dumb
More like
Wait lady do you mean
Any name that is in a white person's name is that basically what she saying
Too silly
It's crazy
But
Knowing what a Malaysian name is and at the same time
Taking a Raptor
Fantastic
Carrie is not a great
The interview
If she's ever seen a wreck
That's a good question
It seems like trouble
But I'm just glad
In terms of
But the interaction with the Raptor
Have you ever seen Raptor cuz he talks about they're going to be on tour here in this
Address
Jurassic World
T-Rex world
Yeah
Actively hiding themselves
The models are whatever
Raptors in that show
Couple years back
Another big production
Dinosaur walking dinosaur
Used to be called the Arco Arena open Sacramento
Going through history the dinosaur history through Through the Ages and
Raptors in the Raptor suit
Within Raptors
So the Raptors
Hiding
By dressing up as rap
Because nothing you would never see
What she says it's like
She knew there were 10
Well they're probably nearby you know what I
Out fake version
I love the visual that is Joanne going to walk with the dinosaurs
I like seeing I got Raptor suit and giving it a knowing nod
Call your card
But I see you
Visual
Put on
Chevy Tahoe
Let me be clear to
They do discuss it
We're not
Misrepresenting what Raptors
Okay we are likely are the Raptors that you and I are
But maybe it's
Tiny bit smaller little
Do they use their little hands
Does Dipper die
Speak like humans
Yeah
Better
Taking human names also when Walking with Dinosaurs
Came around a few years back
I was working a Groupon
The time
And the sales rep that worked out that deal.
Come to our office
It was pretty cool
Same time
Terrifying
No I didn't I saw a bunch of people manipulating a puppet
They weren't inside it
Worthy
Now this
I'm just spitballing
Were they Raptors
Will see that could be possible to discuss Raptors
I don't care
Why not
Joann
Joanna still has more thoughts about
Christian rap
Yes and the possibility of such a thing
Couldn't tell that they were actually
In the actor soup that day but I think they were probably hanging out nearby
So you just never know
We have these treaties where there's not supposed to be open communication with civilians.
I really try not to be seen
People
Like
Do you like to go to big conferences Comic-Con and science conferences work
Lot of people are in costumes and a lot of different aliens do that bill either wear a hooded
Look like they sit in butt
Barbie's butt
We can translate that also as I don't understand cause
Comic-Con
Received
Aliens who want to hang out
There
Costco
Towers
Crafting a
Labor of love
But they're not really getting much worse
But come on
It's
Like that
Totally
Parsley
Controlled by aliens because of
The trees as the first
The first thing to go she ate with aliens
Does the trade deal
These treaties by the way from The Phantom Menace
Mister Phantom Menace
Pixar never
Doug into at all we don't get any real
Information about what went on in these treaties what the stipulations
It's just we got
Treaties fact
So heavily into all discussions about
Aliens from from like the Project Camelot stuff that I've heard it's always like
Any fantasy world requires rule
Because it have to be rules
In order to
Explain the really big stuff that you can't
Explain
It's the same thing with like when you're trying
What is a dragon
Fantasy scenario you need that dungeon
Of what is the reality of the
Change your on
And basically that's what
Project Camelot.
How to play your Project Camelot but they're pretending it's real
Can we play
Pick characters from
Project Camelot at Royal Plaza
I want to be that super soldier was on the last episode
Skill is I'll ask my husband mark
Raptors
2 Raptor
You can be carries
Plus 3 charisma
Pictures of May
She doesn't perform lesser magic so this next clip
Carrie
Quest
Based on the conversation that she's had
Talk to him a bit and we'll get to that the future
She had conversation with him and wants to run it by Joanne
See what she has to say about it
Headache
This is
What kind of question
Could be awkward but somehow ends up being
Delightful
Mark married a wealthy
She told me that he was married to a woman
And that he had two kids please
Number one
I am another California are the only ones that he's been married to
Partner
He's had lots of
Partners
I know I know about 1
And she was from the Aryan race
Amen
Nordic maybe I just remembered it as
And so don't go
Tell me about all the women in all the children
There was a Nordic
Princess who he does have a child
Okay and the child is here on Earth
Oh no something else out of their empire icy
Mark is an intergalactic
And how many children does asphalt is one of the kids out there with different
Is going up there putting his dick in all sorts of aliens
Mark may not necessarily be lying to her you know because
California doesn't recognize player
Just
Species alien
I want I want before we unpack a stupid it is but he claims he has a kid with
Printer data
The reason that she
Empire
Cassidy King
Confused between pleiadian and ordinary
Is because
Those are sort of humanoid light
Elemental aliens
Cuz there's that there's like The Reptilian umbrella and then there is this sort of
Nordic
Umbrella
And the Pleiadians are on that side of
They're all humanoids look like humans where are the Raptors
Yeah or there's a grey alien
There's all sorts of
Explain the pay will just
Work for whoever the highest
Oh yeah oh yeah how did it greatly exaggerated WWII they sided with the reptile
That guy said they're on the axis of Evil
Germany Italy in
Raptors we're on our way
All of human history has really actually just been a battle between different alien races
Avoid the pain of realizing that humans
Heard of a beautiful singing This is it always humans
As a whole are always the good guy
Yeah
But
Were manipulated by alien races
Power is controlled by aliens
All of this it's really all framed as a struggle of all of us
Together
Supposed to discovering
No truly will exist and it looks
Like you and me
Yeah it does not look like
A Raptor
First of all the Joann
Is totally cool
With Mark
Throwing it around everywhere
He's got kids
He's got hoes in
F******
Star codes
I don't know
Same time she opened up her married if you guys ran around live the life
Jealousy is pointless to have anymore
Play 18 kids
Star system
Absolutely
In his next clip Joanna
Expresses what her vision
Cuz
If Mark has
Express
He thinks the future holds for them or whatever
Future should have
You know my vision and I'm very open about it it's like my vision
Ideal properties and I didn't go visit if I found the ideal property online
When I was in Norfolk
This beautiful old like in wardian house on five and a half acres
Lots of fields at overlooking Fields got a horse Paddock
Plenty around to Lansing gone and grow vegetables
I want to go where all those alien friends can come visit all the grandchildren can come visit
Everybody just has a grand time and we're just left alone to see
Communicate
Live happily ever after with our alien friends
Innocent
Beautiful
It is kygo
A place large enough
Intermingle with our alien friends
Antique
Plant growth
Again
And there's enough space for people
There's an undercurrent of foolishness
But at the same time
Overwhelming
Sweetness and foolishness mixed all into one
So there's no
Clip
Jo-Ann's discusses
I want
But really
She discusses
The Linea
Did Mark
When is youngest father side
They're from Germany the Rhineland in Germany still at Jeff and
Princess
Generation away from being a German France
Some very prominent
British
Damn ways I know he's from the Stuart line from peacock line
On his mom's side
You know there's definitely very
Special Celtic bloodline
And
Related to William the first governor of
I'm hoping it's Rhode Island
If I remember correctly
His grandparents were both involved with think-tanks and Nikola Tesla and local politics
Grandpa Taylor on his mom's side was one of
Teddy Roosevelt's Rough Riders and he was one of the original like Secret Service men in black fat people
Sure of course
Powerful
There's a bad bloodline
Anywhere
You know I think his mom kept telling me and we're also related to Pocahontas
Geology
The family is out of NASA and the house of Orange
Royal family
Adjustment
For that reason
That just a little bit of fun trivia Mark's dad is called
The Dutchman
Like I love any of the codename
He's
Supposedly like a
Apparently went along on the Expedition with Admiral Byrd
But I know he I know he went on the expedition
Don't even finish the sentence
I know that
Production there is there's only one thing I know and that is
Forrest Gump is based entirely on the Dutchman
In the world
Hendricks
Dunking Dutchman
If you don't know Admiral Byrd lies a gentleman
May or may not have discovered that the Earth is Hollow
He flew over the pole I remember that guy now
Hollow Earth
Subscribed
The school of Admiral Byrd
You can you can count at least among them John Quincy Adams my friend
Hollow Earth
The nail right on the head
That means this is a man lying about
Kind of sounds like Alex a little bit
I'm related to royalty
Yeah
Anytime somebody tells you about their
Past lives
It's always like
In my past life I would Cleopatra
If we're going to if we're even going to entertain past lives and all that s***
Your past lives were mostly people who died at 2
20 of dissing
Like that's what your past lives are
You know if you want to believe in past lives that's fine but most of your past lives
Shut themselves
He was related to Pocahontas
He has a kid with a Nordic alien princess and he's only the
From being a German
Part of the Stewart's
Stewart Falls
Yep
I like I like that was Olympic clothes
Nikola Tesla
Mazda Tesla's in local politics
Oxford,
Get back to Jurassic World
Jo-Ann's
Was
Mark when he was still in high school
Went to England and with part of raptor military training they had a whole life
Training facility at bamburgh Castle they were using
At the time and he was part of their whole he and other human
Dean Martin's son
River Oaks
National award game type
Actual Rescue Mission
Angela Ballard
A talking more about the Raptors and how in this scene in Jurassic World
Motorcycle racing along with the Raptors
Markings that guy I have the leather jacket
He did races motorcycles with the Raptors when they were running and training himself.
It's kind of funny how the movie parallels my sleep
You could call itsfunneh
Call suspicious Joy
Joann
I'm at the point now where I halfway believe that Mark isn't even real
Much b*******
Nope time question
Why is she giving talk
And to whom she goes to like UFO conventions and stuff like that she goes around to be place
Probably Move On lyrics the custom on the last episode
Just better at telling mark
Flies to people
Mike is really good at telling lies
Commence fill-in-the-blank
Yes she is
She's very sweet
October
To her proof I want to sit down with her and advised her to leave
I don't think you'd be able to 40 45 years
If Marcus got her believe in that he
Raptor army training camp while he's in jail
So many lies have just gotten so far out of control Mark is just
Are proof Villa sells production
He is throwing everything in the kitchen sink
But her proof is that she has the leather jacket
Motorcycle
But remember in the
At the end whenever they were like
It's not real
Then there was
24-hours
That proves
The Jodie Foster
Alien
They open it up she also could have brought back a leather jacket
You might hurt typing there
Siri is also on the live chat
There are people
Later towards the end
No staff
Your husband I've no idea
A little bit later you do hear him yell stuff for a month
Towards the end of this interview
No she forgets the name Stephen Hawking
Get ready for that do you know why he doesn't
Even in the world
Bingo
So they open it up to the chat and they take some
Some questions
Why is 30 proof
Are there and they get
F******
Murderously angry
Bigot
How would I describe it
Pick their Plumbing
Why would
Question for me to believe they're asking but none was
Why isn't there any hard
Of that you know alien visitation to Earth I guess this what they're trying to say
If you can get into the Vatican archives there's plenty of proof
Screw
Great that is true
That's the only
Is breaking
Stuff works is like
No Treasure 3 that's what we're writing right now
What playing with the Raptor
All that be great I do you want some
To be a rapper
Splices jeans with raptor jeans
Break into the secret archives of the Vatican
This is what they do that sort of
The game along with creating rules for your fictional reality you'll never be able to get to
That's how it always is
Have to work almost always
It's in the Vatican
Somewhere was in the Library of Alexandria
You know the Masons or the
Who was it
Who are the
The Visigoths which one was the Library of Alexandria
Different waves
Fascinating story
The Library of Alexandria
Just that's really the only issue
Do people have
Shrinking it down nobody wanted to pay for it
You know why
Print x y
Cuz of Finance
Pressures caused by the reptile
Yep
Alright Templar
From the Library of Alexandria by the Knights Templar
80 kind of thing
Talking about nonsense
Vent filter point the point is if we're going to have rules
We don't have any rules
Jo-Ann's interview
She talked
It's so it's so mind-boggling
I just left
Is love there
This is a hard question to ask
Why isn't there any hard proof
And you're like why is that a hard question for you to ask
Cement
Like they didn't occur that never occurred
To them that you should require some sort of hard proof after that goes on to say about the stuff about
Puma punku in like ancient
Some stuff like that
Zachariah stitching
Those books
Sing that you probably haven't read
And if you have read it
You didn't
When you read it
You realize it doesn't say any of what they say it
No I mean zecharia sitchin books
For you
Right
That nobody's read
Erich von daniken all the way around
Turtles all the way down
That's why
Switch Raptors for Angels
Figured it out
Angels do play in
I didn't realize
Disconnect
Is the last of Jo-Ann's interview
Is a mic down
Interrupting
I don't know baby
She starts by talking a little bit about the Dutchman
Things get a little weird
We're while we were publicly at Cold War when there was a threat to the planet
Several countries came together and work
Together to save Humanity
Charge of that.
He was active behind the scenes
Do you know why
You seem to be a person of note and somebody who
He was unable to get Mark out of prison
Marshalls
Mark was off on a mission the day that murder happen
Tell me
Because I figured that much out and he can't tell me where he was or who he was with
And those people can't come forward and say this is what he was with that that day
Government military is not going to say oh he was working for us
Because then they would have to say what top-secret thing they were working on
Point Blank told him you're not going to break your oath
You're not going to break your military up until the top-secret we were doing
Even if it means that would save your life
It's like you know what your duty is
And your duty is to keep quiet
Okay
I also thought
At the time
Was it really good lawyer he was a well-known lawyer
Carly has a family going along thinking oh they're doing okay he's going to get him off and whatever
Ever and he did
Get Mark out of their hair
Freaking out
What did Mark do
Mercury guy Mark 100% killed somebody
This whole thing is just created by the entire
Emily in order to avoid dealing with the murderer
Onboard event
But what about the Dutchman
Only
Before
Joanne Matt
Gotcha
Mark Richards
With the
Iggy put your honor
This was the reason they were mad at the the lawyer they were like
You're not objecting
He was off
Planet idiot of course that witnessed in Co
Gotcha are you familiar with the
Pendragon murder plot
I am familiar with any number of them I didn't know any of them
This is a very first murder
From 1982
Marin County California
Okay
This was a situation
Was
He ran like a
Construction type
Crew or something along those lines
Really sure of all the details
But he had
Employee
217 year old employees
He was 19 at the
Or 29
Okay I was going to say that's a very
His name is
Richard Baldwin
He was a guy who ran like a car deal
Resort
He apparently owed
Mark's the money
Mark
I got
117 year olds
Okay he promised the seventeen-year-old that he would pay him $5,000 and give him a car
Kid murdered
Had immediately started bragging about it and talking about it
And they all got
It's very clear
That Mark is very guilty of this
WhatsApp
The Pendragon part of it
Comes from
Mark they searched his house
And they found
That he had
Plan to take over Marin County
I don't want to go super in detail about this because I've never wanted you to do anything else
Remind everyone
Cuz they covered this in detail on an episode of the dollop
No s*** this is that guy
She is disguise
Alright
So if you go and listen to the version
Just the facts
They found plans
Creating lasers
That would
Keep Marin County safe
They have destroyed the Golden Gate Bridge and another Bridge
They could isolate Marin County
Where Mark Richard
Would be basically King Arthur
Have his own dominion
Do you trick these kids
Into
Sort of going along with him
He was able to pay one of them to murder a guy
And I mean I did steal a bunch of s*** from him they still like a huge bag of weed
Bunch of money in a
Stay Puft
Murder
Do you have
17 that's not
No.29 murder planning
You're right
Yeah but I guess it was my TV shows
Also you should know that Mark
Herds of people not to take plane
Because the replicant
Absolute commercial plane
Never forget Reptoid
Mark is doing a bid
For murder
Has life-without-parole Jamarcus still in jail
God I love it
The whole time
Mark is in jail
That's why Joanna giving talk
Because Mark is in jail till forever
Forever
So hard to not take my hand
And more interesting more interesting to look at is the end
Tiertime Jo-Ann's known him
You've been in prison for murder
And 14 years that they've been married the entire time he's been in
Gotcha
The perfect man
That is
Vet
You know what I wish
I wish copyrighted
Just dropping the
Entire episode
Recommended
Looking good job.
Isn't murderer
You kids and now he's pulling the con
On
His wife
Pictures of Benaiah
So long as she never actually
Meet sent like the longest he's never living with her
He's under control
As long as they're not allowed out
I know I guess though
Break
Bet she's been
She's been given an Avenue where she can Retreat into a Fantasy Life
Before
Empathy for her
Her life has been a disaster like in the early 90s
He's never cheated with him in prison
Did you running from something she's found it in rap
Perfect she seems like she's doing great
So now that
You doing fine
100% happier than I
Better guarantee
I guarantee you that she lives a happier day today
Distance when I ever will
She makes a decent amount of coin going around telling his story
Great Castle in London or England
Right
Mark is not allowed out of the country
Good luck mark
Beyond in that last
Equip you heard like he wasn't even there
He was
He was for sure
But DIY
Ginger carry is
So if
You know
The Dutchman was
Basically the leader of the entire world
Defense
The Cold War
Important man on the planet
Why couldn't he
He get mark off
Not tell the truth
You know expose things before it's time to expose the disclosure of off Coral missions
Like that
Is making a heroic sac
The engineer of the worst murder ever committed
It's one of the worst
It's pretty it's minutes
Floppy
Yeah that'll
It started with a baseball bat
The screwdriver
Dispose of the body really terribly
Anyway who cares
Did not stink
Give me
It's in the water
No one will ever know or national Waters
Taxation is a crime blotter
It's like HomeBase
This is not worthy episode
Or episode 10
Because you should know that
Callahan
Cassidy
Yeah. We're never going to know how to get that right
Has gone to interview Mark in prison
6 *
Oh yeah
The twist
I don't know anything about Raptors
Smooth
So whenever Kerry Cassidy goes.
Every time
So whatever Carrie ghost
To visit
Because he's a murderer
He's under
Supervision
Decree privileges
They won't let her record him
So all she can do is take notes
Pencil but not a pen
Which brings up every time
Every one of these interviews
So then
Conversation
She takes note
Emmet makes a video where she reports
What's on the Note
Axle video hear of her reporting
I don't think
F*** I look everybody converter
Raptors versus
Ethereal Nordic
And also having multiple children off-planet
Sure it gets Wilder
I understand Joann
Motivation for believing Hook Line
And sinker everything this con man is telling her
I don't understand why Carrie isn't a little bit more dubious
I don't understand what you're talking to the most credulous person in the history of the world
Cassidy
To walk into a conversation with
I don't know if that is possible
I am asking her to realize that this guy murderer who's lying to people
I'm just be
If you want to if you want to believe that
Wrestle with
I recognize that it's you know
His credibility is a little thin
Right but if you know
A plan to create King Arthur's Court in Marin County by blowing up Bridges and giving a laser
Planted on him by the Riptides That's a classic reptile
Well
Classic
Classic restaurant unfortunately because they know that everyone else knows.
Right
To try to make up a human named dude you're totally right.
I don't know why they need
Anyways
Evidence on murder
Unfortunately they never really get into the details of the Pendragon
They know if they did they'd be like
Weak attic
I would love to see what they would do I'd love to see them dance around
Well now
Little bit
That's fine
Going to get like
17 year olds that
Indoctrinated into his
Port of
King Arthur's Court
How do you how do you
Respond to that
Okay
Well actually
His dad
Translate
Wow and in order to do that
The Cold War
Sure
Now his dad
Ethereal
And of course they all look like they're seven
18 years old that's just their that's just their genetic make
Elemental
Yeah like 17 year olds
Okay now one of them
One of them did Kill the other guy
But it was a Reptoid
Compromise
Okay
Alexander Jean
Save that
Maybe ten hours of my life that I can't get back
Listening to
Cassidy
Explain what happened to her when going to interview Mark Richardson prison
All of you the trouble of listening to all of it
I just playing the fun stuff
Cuz I'm busy
Terrible
So here
Mostly from one
The videos Arthur
Seems to be the most
Who's the first one
First time she's ever met him there
A little bit of weed
Just juicy.
Introducing
Hi I'm Kerry Cassidy from
Project Camelot
Program
Northern California and prison
Richard and ISTA
Appreciate
Worth it
Really a huge amount of information
He doesn't he's not animated
You are the most gullible person in the world
Mike Richards
An amazing man
He is amazing
There's there's
Yeah
You know what
Connotation
As opposed to
Just in a vacuum
The definition
Connect
To our normal Alex Jones episodes
Is where water
Well yeah if you ever saw Alex talk to Leanne McAdoo
Well yeah it's just
Carmen
Really pertinent
Google Kerry Cassidy has dedicated her life to this s***
She thinks that Mark Richards is a real whistleblower
But he along with I can't remember the f****** dude name that we went over on the last one the super soldier guy
Sources of information
So
She's
I think so I think she gets
Donations
From people
If you look at her
Bella download
Don't look at me like that
Hey it's crazy
I mean
It's entertaining on someone
To the good stuff
Hours of boring
Thank you
You might be asked
Yourself
How did Mark get around in
Really good question
An artificially intelligent
Biologically intelligent
Spaceship called Minerva
The only person who could
She comes from
Solar system altogether
She considers herself to be a biological creation
Cute
I guess an instant she is
That's what I call her
Oscoda on that clip I don't have the audio interview
It's out of context
I played it back then
But
If she is ever met Minerva
And Joanne response
Break my heart
Because it's it's
Oh no I haven't but I'd love to meet the sweet thing
Of course and it's just
Toasted head
It's so sad she has an emotional bond with this imaginary artificial intelligence
Spaceship
And he's the only one who can play it
Update update on the fifth trip that she goes and visit Mark
It turns out they learned a couple of the people
How can I say she said he may be the only one if not
Point at the cat
Recording he was the only one
Have mastered Minerva
The artificial biological intelligence
In spaceship
Another solar system
It is a goddess of wisdom
And they don't know what
Vehicle
Mirror
Every
Racial vehicle
Minerva near every
Any
MI
Minerva is m stands for Minerva
Oh
Apartments
Be there you go
Okay of course mtn's for Minerva in the acronym spelling Minerva
This makes perfect sense
Mike Richards would back me
Vietnam
Definitely vehicle
All I know
What end
What goes after
Vehicle
In Akron
Got nothing
There is a really funny moment where someone asks what Minerva stands for in Joanne is like
Alaska
Sweetheart
Although
If she was
Really nice why is it
Because they had such a bond it's like a horse
I'm guessing
What's up
Some like
Literal Avatar
Your brain together with the
Cool if we get into an issue
That's the next question I would
Jury is out
Don't know
This textbook gets into an issue I didn't know wasn't it
But it turns out it is
All right and it relates to our world more than we ever knew
This is it
Steph here
I also talked to him
Discovered there by the Marconi scientist and
There are at least 25
Number of LifeStream
And am I looking at
Artificially intelligent
Oil spills are actually artificially intelligent black
She did not say all
That one in particular
I mean you could really assume that anything
That looks black
And is good
They probably assume
Exact
Why do you think we get lunch
Totally
It's artificially intelligent
Yeah that's what it is
Good stuff
That's just good
X-Files
Yeah I think that's the Expo
But there was that alien guy there be black
Like
Liquid people I go into their eyes
This is
I mean you can also go with what the the symbiant from Spider-Man
There's all kinds of programming man
Siri
There's the well-known Grey Goose.
Which is
What happens if we develop artificial
Intelligent
Eventually they'll use every
Then we'll all just
That could be what they're afraid of
Who is like a like
We're going to need DJ Danger Mouse to get the black Goku and the white go together and make the Greg
This is how it
No
Not going to happen
More facts about
Raptors
Here comes more Raptor s*** this one is also about how they fun to move
Obviously movies TV
To this overall
Set of amnesia
Make sense
There's this latest dinosaur
Which is called
What's it called
Small dinosaurs
Dinosaurs
He said that are actually showing up
Participating
I thought they were going to
Mechanical
It's just something I like to do something
Consider
They do consider finding why wouldn't
I want to say that I saw one of these dinosaurs
Dog walking with the dinosaurs up close
But it looks real
When it's moving
Because
Their tube
They're like
They are
It's uncomfortable
Because it's something that looks like
Slumbering at you but if you look at it Motionless
It doesn't it looks like
It doesn't look like
If I saw a raptor alien next
Be very clear
No matter how
Still that Raptor could stand
It would be so f******
Can clear
Here's just a
This is used on set
Really easy question
Feathers
No
Well then
Not really
Not outside not out
What you need to know is there is
Alright
Because it another interview
Hey Carrie.
It might be a metaphor
But there is a there's another interview that you does with Mark
Where he talks
About how
The bank
Get
Cons of raptor
Bigot
300 million answer
Is it
Why do people lie
This is one of the most poorly fat sky
Mark
He's in prison
I think that Mark
Has some issue
But they are
It isn't
Heavy as a lot of other things that we've discussed do you mean a shadowy group
Controller
Well I mean there are parallel aliens are funneling money
Money in the Bank
Controlling everything
Correspondence
Actually even a little bit more why it's a little troubling
Any of these trends
But be that as it may
More about these here Raptors
Fitbit clip is great
His role model and
Hamilton Air Force Base
Very impressed
What is Honorable
Military leader
He said the Raptors rent castles in the United
Pandora heavily-guarded
They may form a perimeter on the outside
Basically
He said that I don't like to
Serious
Is there aren't that many
National
Apparently not so much
He said the home
Where's Gary
65 million years ago
He said they didn't
Just recently
The physicist
What was his name
There it is
Just recently the physicist Stephen Hawking
S2000 believe in aliens
Center
Ring for
Sometime in other words
Possibly
Their Homeworld
Homeworld
The Draco constellation and it is now called
Turn on the news Rhapsody
What does must have saw that bit like
They we got hurt they got their Galactic map out they said Draco system like where else are we going to go
They're from the Drake
Okay so if I understand the timeline or not
This timeline correctly
Alright
65 million years ago
Chilling out on Earth
Victor
Spaceships
Catastrophe
Oh s*** look up there
Field technology
From another EX
Strattera
Only extraterrestrial race
Necessarily
But they get up
Get up planet and they're just tooling around
Having themselves a dick
Family get caught in the
Intergalactic
Ring right where they're stranded
Possibly even for thousands of years which brings into the question
Food
They each other's feathers
Establishes
The timeline only has a roughly a few thousand years accounted for as opposed to the 65
Just out of nostalgic
They like
Commerce
They like humans
Love movies
Go to your home it's like a fish swimming Upstream to
So there's that Elementary
And then the other one
There was a
Decent explanation
How the f*** is that come out of my mouth
Isn't that low enough for decent to me
There was something offered
As to why they came back here
Going to be till like 1 good
Raptors you guys didn't even know we could f****** the climate is temperate
And Mining is good
Cuz if you try and mine on an asteroid there's no gravity
Much easier to mine for stuff we get into that
The need for gold and s*** like that all over again
Like I love it when things go
It's so imaginative
And fun and then they bring it back
To something dumb that
That brings it all back into reality and then you have
Have to go like
Travel
Untold thousands of light-years
Forgot
Everyone knows
Is there was no gold on Dragon World they would have developed their own f****** economic system
Thing else they wouldn't still beat this randomly covering race memories of goal
Gold wasn't a financial thing back when Raptors
Right Fair
Well
Zacharias
Fiction book about it
The Anunnaki
Aliens and enlil
I came here to mine for
For gold was because the gold
Buy was needed to fix the atmosphere of their planet
Aerosolized
Was coming there was in there
Because they need to fix their planet
Where is the idea that they liked
They do like a carry and Joanne
Pictures of cool
But
Look
They're wrapped
Your people
I think you're cool
But you probably eat a chicken
I think Ella Raptor until the Raptors he's a super cool dude
But sometimes Raptors eat
What is the regular
Honestly we're all part of the food chain
I mean space-traveling Super Raptors
Emmett baby
Is an indication that I've done too much therapy in my life
Hear it being relayed from Mark
Frustrated
I'm hearing him trying to confess to murder
I hear hear it and it seems like I'm not a bad guy
Something happened and yes
There was a
And the kid part of it is probably projector
Some sort of like really weird
American Express
Through Raptors in
There their nature
Interesting thing if you have him right
An actual like sci-fi novel
Basically be the retelling of how he murdered
It would just be like if I did it
It Raptors
Here's how they would have killed
Nicole Brown
We're done with Rafters for the time being
In this next clip
Good
I should tell you that this third interview was
Recorded
Elegant 2014
That was cuz you were you were talking about the
Traveling dinosaur
She's gone
Installment
Andover
Her travels to this prison
Because of
Hot-button issue that comes up
That was 14
Largely forgotten about
I think it's possible
That the Japanese royalty as well as
The royal
Related to bears
Now the Raptors
There is a serious
He believes
Large number of
Other
View
Very positive
Future if they don't
Do it this time their treaties they're honoring their treaties and they are basically
A couple important
When's the Raptors are pre-calc
Interesting that's a nice wrinkle today
And then also be if you didn't catch that but you saying
Is that Ebola is
Design
To take out reptile
So if you know of somebody who died from
You know now
They were actually Reptoid
Probably
Crisis
Was largely in
West Africa
Yeah but the Blood
None of this makes sense
Gazebo
What is Jake
It is
Because you know why racist in a way that makes me go like
I can't quite pin down
This is
Really bad
Infield the races income
Cuz there's a binary
Raptors good
You look at it
Absolutely
Precognitive
Orange around the metro area
Court No Doubt
She grew up in SoCal base
Basically
Basic
This next clip we get into some more world history
Look through the prism of rapt
Raptors
Rapture
Reptoid
Those titties
Coyote information
And I would
Information he still has contacts in the military short
Contacts
Back-channel information will come from what we know of as white hat
The US military is
What was carrier pigeon
Here we go
Like at least
A little bit
Oh yeah
The reptoids are in our government
Prison for all the time
Even in this weird fantasy world she has a more pessimistic
This f****** nice
Hero he doesn't even know that reptoids have infiltrated the highest
Only if you only don't men like him and the Dutchman
Like Mike
That's what he was doing
If you want to look at
Adjust through the prism of marks
America does not have reptoids
Japan.
West Africa
To the weird
It's very strange
Very weird
Global
I mean global
Don't really come up and Carries world
So
If we're going to put this if we're going to
Switch
Okay if we're just going to take
1 fantasy world and move it
Into our own fantasy world that we play in
SRP
Global
Toronto Raptors control
Hangman
Here's my feet
Alright
The Raptor
Are the global
Okay
In the same and look if Mark richer
Is friends with the Raptors
Is bad
Is an ant an everything he says they're doing
Is what
The boys are the good guy
Oh yeah this is what happened
Complete the left
With the Raptors
I'll tell you what I'm going to do
He's Lefty
Trendy raptors raptors
How come on Mike cernovich isn't a real name that's a rapper name
It's a Raptor Center Raptor exactly
I'm going to punt on the Raptor dichotomy
They seem pretty cool.
Gotcha we're going to get into a couple
F****** hilarious clips
Or like
I have to assume
They are marked
Testing the waters
Seeing what Carrie will believe I have to because these two are f****** weird
Must be having
The greatest
He's never had it easy
Board of prison
Get to say whatever you want and she has a platform of like millions of people watch
Beautiful
You just listen to this s***
Set a lot of reverse engineering Corporation
Possibly
Information
Arresting and
TSA scanners
Instead there are
The dogs that are supposed to be smelling
Drugs are actually
Looking for 4 ET
They're not
A country
Scanners are actually used to determine
That's what it's about
You have to raise your hands over your head
Rapture
Can't do that
Unibrow
That's fair
You're going to give that one a pass
Here's this next week
A risk we have a risk of them replacing those in power
Chiefs
Check the biological material
Still Human
He said that there are also Android
Congress
I buy that immediately
Android
The Joint Chiefs of Staff weekly
Can't be at
Okay well Android
Army buried in there is developed Android
The next clip it gets a little peasant
Belittle
He said Israel is run by
Wish to
He didn't want to name the race that
It appears that the
Reminder
Indications are that
This is a fiction
In his book
Okay
Yeah
Sure
They came and created as a slave race in order to
Forget gold
That was a team for initials
And they run Israel
Marky Mark Wood names
Israel
Israel and the Vatican a run by competing alien groups that are trying to mix us up
Upping their skirmishes
That makes that is
F***** up
Just cuz you're adding alien doesn't mean like
All the conspiracy theorist
Pretty much point fingers at
The Jews
Massive groups
The conspiracy theorists go after
Any ideas
Look
Course you guys are right
Big picture
For the trees
Raptors
Extension he got y'all covered
So ridiculous
She's
She's really just getting Mark into like weird
Political conversation
Imagine imagine you actually believe
In Raptors
Reptoid
The Anunnaki
This is hard to imagine
All of whom are competing to secretly control every
At all leaked it to other places
In order to discredit the other side now
These are very bad
They're bad
Okay much like Mark and murder
All of this is amazing all of this is true
Tell me more about space
Tell me about what
Tell me about all the steps
No I'm going to tell you about Ezra
Guiding the conversation clearly feel privileged
To be their talk
And you know what else you want to talk about
The Malaysian play
This interview took place in 2014
Tried to find out what Alex Jones said about the Malaysia
Complain not a great fit we couldn't really find him having too much of a theory on it
Mark f****** Richard
Knows exactly what happened and it's b*******
That the MS
The mainstream media
There
A report the truth
Here's the truth
And he said
Dimensional
Has four people on board
Was building a time-shifting
Machine that was too accurate
How to take a nap
Chinese
Alright
We're already on time shipping to
To technology
We have
Perfectly functional dimensional
But this time shift technology good
For humans to possess
I don't know
We can't let it go to the gym
But beyond that
Did this clip Goes On by
Much further where Carrie explains that this is where marked
Commercial
Because I could do
Just get timeshift
All the time
Apparently
I feel like
Every kind of big deal with the Malaysian plane disappeared
Everybody talked about it for a long time for a long time
Okay the man in Black was a Reptoid
I knew it
No that was a Jacob
Was a Raptor
Or no that's be the other way around
Unless you actually believe that the mess
The show was
Was the bad guy
Black was actually the 1,000
Jacob
He's lined up about the Raptors
Markhor
Whichever you feel like
Mark is one
Hundred percent lying about everything
So that means
Did the Raptors
No none of them exist
You're going to hurt marks
That's the part that I don't want
Brave
Is to internet
I just ragging on this sweet little woman
Murdering husband
I carry
Explain some of a question
Mark did not want
And it's not hey what about that murder
Which is what I thought
Rose going to be
Can of worms
Also
If he doesn't know something he doesn't seem
Shy about admitting that
In some cases he will say he will go research something and get back to
There was only one question answer
Particular question was
Set up a download in my state to be sure and ask
Whether or not he was currently going on missions
And the answer
Was not forthcoming
Almost every other question I asked him without fail
About whether another one
Give me a non-verbal and
Answering what you smile
And indicated that yes he is going on Mission
We did talk about time travel
Talked about using the Kaaba
Lightbody
Uso
He says human beings
Time travel
And she seems very familiar
Concept
So this is
It's something worth noting and obviously
If he's able to do this
This makes
Much more livable
If you can time travel and go out
No big deal
To do either of those things
Yeah but you work with dimension
Interdimensional
Sprite where do you meet them
Dementia
We've talked about magic
What you don't even need
To go out of
Well you need
Go see cuz the reptoids
To disappear the Malaysian plane
And he's not down with that
So they can probably the dimension shifting technology
So you wouldn't have access to that
And they don't like to go interdimensional
Out-of-body I am just
Sorcery
I imagine you can have an amazing Prison Break where a bunch of raptors show up in
Call the guard their sorcery make Cloud their minds
Cuz you're looking for
What the f***
Carrie I love you
Carrie
That brings us to the end of a Raptor investigation
Can we draw
Indicates to me that she
She knows
On some level whether it's
Yes or not
That Mark is a dude
You committed murder
Here here
Is this
Drop that he's also the kind of guy that you don't want to mess with
Listing in another cell
Yeah it is
True thing I think any of them
It's not the kind of guy you want to mess with
She could just mean that in that
Isn't any surgeon mansion
Space Warrior
Why would want to mess with
Where can I get a $5,000
He is somebody I don't want to mess with
I don't want to mess
I want not
Frankly I'm a little scared that we're talk
Quite frankly
Look
All all all I'm saying
Everybody listen to this
Make sure you stay out of Arm's Reach of a Raptor
Raptors
Apparently cool
No-fee ATM School
Mercenaries
Black gubat but also smart super intelligent
Minerva
Smart Plan
SoCal
Basically
NorCal
Little baby with a base play was
That's where they never even knew where she was
If I could leave everyone with one thing
To sum up
5e experience
And what we
It's
You watching
A TV show
Ask yourself
Did Raptors pay for this
And if they do
If you'll know check the credit
The why do you think they go by so fast now they used to have them you know on sitcoms
Yeah I'm right on the
Totally said it was a
Name a sitcom
Family Matter
You would have you would have the name with Reginald veljohnson
Did I do that
And if you see like a name that looks
Philly in the lake
For the Gasper
Catering or something like that
Some joke name
It's not a joke
It's not like some onset
Themselves
The Year Lisa
House of Horrors
Episodes
You think those are fake names
No those are actually they're wrapped
Every year
Because they like cartoons that they only want to make
No they don't understand
Doesn't seem human don't believe
They're trying
To get in your brain
And if it's Zionist
Probably the Anunnaki
Maybe
Who knows
Anyway
That somehow raises
Yep
How can you still be
Believe in Raptors and reptoids
And still be like
The Jews are hiding
You got a whole nother Step 2
Because Mark is this
Mark was nuts
Before he went to prison
Yes that's why
When you're in prison
Pretty easy for racism to get worse
I would
I'm not done any beds
The joint
Documentary I watched every
Raptor produced show about
Life in prison
It seems like
There are harsh racial division
So I imagine
Informing Samos
So anyway
Who's been fun Jordan
This is Ben
I just couldn't get out of my head this thought that
My girlfriend had where
What what I'm thinking now about how the world is ending
Is actually the most opt
Because it's the world doesn't end
It's going to be so much worse
Is it going to be
Keep going
Possible outcomes that we all just
Blippi
No I think actually the best possible that I don't want to get to
Cuz we're already
Write two hours or so
But like I think the best possible
Mario is
It's kind of a nut
Keep getting worse
But then
Spring blowback the other Direct
If some of these
Maybe more socialist type policies like
Healthcare for all
And we'll start to see
See the benefits
Kamala Harris just came out
Every politician
I'm going to have some problems
Yeah I think that what you'll see is a massive swing the other direction
Super liberal
It will rain
And I think that
The world
What's better way to going
Hopefully we'll stick with that but the reality is that we'll probably breathe
Massive Liquors know-it-all extreme
But
Did the Hulk
Is that the pendulum will swing
Really far to the right
And it'll get lodged in
In the wall or something like that
Metaphor doesn't really works
Not great but
That's the real that's the real issue
It always comes back
The system that enables
Amanda
The Raptors playing the reptoids
Autobiography
To the Red Cross donate to local charities
Houston
That you are donating to
People who are eating it
Always as possible investment
Not a donation
Good fun time
Cares
Navigate
If you'd like to become a policy wonk
Sports show Biden Twitter
Just send it to me and we will probably want the f*** out of you guys
Also acknowledged underscore
If you donate 30,000 rap
Could happen to me one of those original Jurassic Park
The compound
The clan compound
T-Rex
Tyler rex toys on wheelbase
Tobago
When I was a kid in the world
Play with her right
If you like to follow us on Twitter that knowledge
If you want to
The TV show Dino Riders
I would appreciate that if you have
Scripts from the show Dinosaurs
Not the mama
Oh boy
If you want to follow us on Facebook
Just knowledge
Go to iTunes download subscribe
Tell your friends
I love the show
Come out
North bar
It's not
At 9 p.m. remember 2999 and honor of Herman Cain
Mike
Greatest fears
And that
Numbers that are
Upside down
That's weird
Next week I hope you all have a wonderful
Whataburger
Hated
Many people died
How many people died
This holiday for Labor Day
We don't
Memorialize that
Memorialize a 5-day week
Murdered people
In order to fight against the oligarchy
People had to die living wages
In order to get a living time Target hours
F****** kill you
You-know-who
I think I know
Somebody who can go f*** himself and do you know who can go f*** himself
Thanks for holding
Alex