Holding
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work
Hey everybody welcome back to an hour
Welcome back to these wonderful
Slightly less wonderful than they were before you left America States
Louder
This
Considerably
You did a great job but
This cannot be replicated
Whatever we're doing
The wonderful surprise
In-depth analysis of Alex Jones's bulshit
Market orders that I've ever had
Like to figure out what my true purpose is here we are super thrilled to be able to help you discover
Again welcome back
We're drinking a wonderful red wines from Bogle Vineyards
In honor of our Lord and savior vocal
Praise be
We got so much
On our plate
While we analyze the World of Alex Jones and Infowars
We can't banter back and forth for the first 20 minutes
The soundry can't do that
Through the b*******
Will definitely stay on target I think honestly the message or the the mission of the show is
A hundred percent
But we have to get through our own bulshit
Yeah,
On the
6th and 27th
Episode
Of the Alex Jones
I wanted to be up to
Speed rap
The present day
What is AJ
February 1st
Yes
Everyone in on Monday and Tuesday's show the 30th
A 31st
What is it Alex
On both episodes
It's the last day of January
Give me David Knight both.
The globalist 28th through the 31st
Months should be modeled on February
Everyday
The show every morning
He's shocked
Reflection everyday
Goddamn dog
I don't want to cover everything I don't have clips from because it doesn't really matter mostly
Making vague threat
To the people who might try and hurt Trump 41
Pluckers
Institute of Muslim
Yeah
If the weight of the world on your shoulders like
Exactly like Alex Jones he wants everyone to know that if something happens
The Trump
You're walking on the
The Fightin side of Alex Jones also he has a
What is he actually saying that if
Gets murdered
It is his personal job.
To find and bring the killer to Jess
No
He's rallying the
Can you saying that if it goes down it's time to shoot people in the streets
Alaska is also saying that all you people out there who were fine with Trump being killed
If it happens
You will find No Quarter
Oh
So it's a good thing to be selling guns gun parts
All the parts you need to make a gun
Also is that a big thing that goes over on Mondays show
Like in different parts and then being like
We sell we sold bananas ice cream and then other things that are in bananas
Yeah big part is he talks about the shooting in
Nickelback
That got shot up 617 believe
As we know now
From police reports it was a white dude who is supporter
Literally everybody should have assumed immediately
It seems like
We live in the world
That's the sensible approach
Globalist
Zombie
Search
Realize that what actually happened was that it was Muslim shooting up a mosque
Because they were the more radical Muslims
And they were shooting up a progressive Muslim
You just basically saying
That like
The biggest victims of Islam are people who are
Like make the argument that it was
Is a failed false flag it was already a failed fault
Because they have tons of people who are out of these airports protesting
And this false flag happened
Now they're activate
Now they shut down everything
Chaos Bedlam in the streets
Alright
Wait what
You don't do not understand the premise
Protesters have been mobilized and paid by George Soros
Gotcha
Are going to
Star Trek
Because of this false flag
Shooting
NHK back Moss
So the globalist
Tired
Yes
Fake news
Nope
Absolutely. It's all complete nonsense
And the fact make that episode 8
Incredibly embarrassing
I really want to
Alex
Humanity
Beyond Beyond
He did repeat that claim on Tuesday
Of course he's real doesn't mean
Tell them it's not like they're real I don't really want to dissect
Too deeply because
A tragedy is obviously fake
And I don't really feel super-great about laughing about
A mass murder
I don't feel super good about waking up everyday
I mean
I wrestle with this like
If Sandy Hook
Comes back up on his show
How do we cover that
Cuz he's a denier right yeah
Tell me what do we do I don't
I don't want to
Well here's what I would like to his craziness but I don't want to diminish
Know what it would be is just an hour and 45 minutes of me barking into the microphone
Like an angry dog
Realistically you're probably right
Do we get a big piece of news
And that is opening up a Washington Bureau of Infowars
Thank you Jesus needed a reason to become relevant
Yes I got an editor
We just got radicalized what just happened right
Editor
And this is very exciting
Piece of news
We have to run the Washington Bureau
Corsi
I don't know if you've ever heard of this cat
Sounds fake
He is a seventy-year-old man
Who wrote an entire book about
Barack Obama
Having a fake person
How do you write an
Book about
Didn't that just a sentence
I might actually be overstating that he did
Scathing book about Barack Obama's one of his
Pieces was that Obama has a
True
Well as we know now since he's been deported
F****** muslim ban
Hold on let me walk back my walking back Jerome corsi wrote the book
Where's the birth certificate
A book questions Obama's America
May 2011
The book enjoyed abuzz building teaser article and a heavy heavily trafficked
Drudge Report website
Whenever Wendy's use that
Also wrote many articles about how the USA is about
The merge with Mexican
Canada
That would be fun
So he's a seventy-year-old
Great tacos maple syrup conglomerate
I don't know I don't
I don't know
You have
A lot of
Just moving freely among
Enjoying nature
Yeah
Basically the big things from Monday and Tuesday is show but now
It's important that we get back
To the 26th
Alright
I remember
A lot more
See stuff happened on the 26th and 27th
We're going to have to wrestle with
Alright what would you rather do
Choice you get an A or a B
Would you like to do with matters of the east or matters of the South
God I tried
Assume it's going to be way more racist when we go to
So let's do it
Some boy
Big shout out to
Gmail be in Seattle
Okay so one of Alex's
Massive narratives on the 26th
China
Points about
Stories.com
Us
Is Infowars
Call Noah
No it's just a vlog
Movies I go to see you
Pro communist Chinese propaganda
So will take a little bit of a step back here and
Unpack this
Chinese
Companies
Maybe
Just rearrange Chinese Communist and then
He might be
Yeah
Something like that you know
These are so he has big feet
I mean that's fine
I guess
Where somebody came from he would probably use that
After all
Yeah
He has this
Sing that he doesn't understand
Massive emerging mark
Especially for entertain
Yeah so a lot of movies are going to
To be harshly critical of China in the way he might want
What
Which movies
Really mad at Michael Bay
Jingoistic filmmaker there's ever been in a minute
Which is a jerk off americafest
Except for Ben Affleck
Somebody positive messages about the Chinese
Revenge of the Fallen Transformers movie
All these movies that are probably full of
Chinese propaganda
That is
Is not possible
Family propaganda of unconventional
Family unit
Yeah Mi cramp a crime involves family
Astigmatism
The movie is the best
Clips
Any episode of The Alex Jones Show
Chinese are buying up Hollywood
And in order because one guy
Now it's
To fully put that b******* to bed
So
He cites an article on infowars.com
He's dating
Something more
Yeah
Otso
It gives it credibility because there's a link to it on Drudge
And the only link as a source that they
Is a
Piece of tech
Like the Chinese are buying up Hollywood Studios
I clicked on that
It goes to another
That is just a video clip of Alex
So
Video if you watch it Alex flashes up an article from The Hollywood Reporter
That is about this guy
Who is the
Very relevant pieces
Information
From that article that Alex willfully ignored
In order to make his bulshit propaganda points
You have been
Saving up to
Until you're bringing a lot more
A quote from the guy Wanda
The company
That he owns a billionaire
I wanted to acquire
The weather has a different story
It's uncertain
I might as well start from wherever I can such a
Through investment with all 6
Bluntly
Strategy we will continue to work on a potential acquisition
But it won't
Participating investment
It seems like a wise choice for
The time being
Okay so is plan actually is to buy one of the studio
Yeah and what he's doing to get his foot in the door is investing in all of them
Hoping that sooner or later one of them
Even if you're building a Hollywood studio
Time Warner AOL merger
You know it doesn't happen because one guy is like okay aol's mine now
Yeah
Azzam interviews with people who know him and know them
Movie business
One of them
Closer to the notion that Wanda is motivated where would ever be foolish enough
Have to try and force
Anything resembling
Chinese propaganda
Quote
Since Hollywood is already altering their films to make them shine
Or at least
Girl to gain Market access there
I don't think you wanted to buy into really changed
To Stanley Rosen
The professor
Of political science
Hola start sending email saying we are under tremendous pressure from to make protein
China film
Sing to their business all over the world
Thomas toll founder and CEO of legendary
Kohl's management team in place
Has given no indication of wanting to save the Studio's contest
He's an unabashed business
What is the bottom line
If what he said made sense we wouldn't live in the world we live in what do you mean
Just because he wouldn't put pressure on people
How to put a proton
It's like it's like
Whenever they cover
They don't
Purposefully
Cover
Certain things
Georgia prison
Certain
The owner
Stead
But just by the virtue
Two of them being working
For this guy
They feel an implicit
To avoid
Yeah but billionaires one billionaire who knows what they really want
William
That's fine if you're putting pro-china
Into something
That wouldn't be as damaging as people would
Maybe I also think I found the quote from this article that really is what this is all about this is a quote from
Rwanda
Isabel
Oh boy as a businessman I believe he's somewhat successful but not extremely
Successful
Makes money from his name
But I do consider him to have achieved real success
He doesn't compare to America's real Megara
Rich Bill Gates for example or other great-aunt
Turner's
What this is about
Just
The guy is singing this guy is talking a little bit of s*** and Alex's
Got to make him the figurehead of my full propaganda campaign
Against
You trying to buy all 6 Studios
Now if you want to hear something else that makes this guy
When I asked when you're the end of our time together what's the
Contemplates the improbable Arc of his life
He says
He mostly feels lucky
Lucky to have come of age
When China was undergoing a
Reform
Quote
30 years ago people in China all had the same life
We were given rations of food
The reform gave us the right to
Virtues and the freedom of choice allowed people with a will and an ambition to achieve
In the past
Only if the emperor could
Drink this tea
Why I said Wang before we part
With one of his biggest grin
In the morning
Today anyone with enough money
Can buy it
That seems like it's right in the vein of f******
Capitalism
Yeah md-80s they did
Switch over to a
One of the big things
Russia is not a communist Society
China is not a communist Society
What they're using communist is shorthand for isn't oligarchical
Society
Because
Is not a cyst
System of governance
Capitalistic
We talked about this on the first episode
Alex Jones is
Ramada socialism leads
Communism and capitalism isn't, authoritarian rule of the state
Right like love we had
To create forever
It looks that way it seems like he wants that right
Trump
More less
Either way we have differences in opinion on this guy
Oh me too
But as long as we start as far as billionaires go he seems like he's in the top
B
Like he's the most billionaires
Yeah
Taking old no way indicates that he wants to buy all 6 Studios
Mount it has nothing to do with that
Absolutely
Movies with his
And picking the Chinese and Asian stories are underrepresented in the media and stuff like that
And if you have a market share that
Growing movies bomb here gets saved
Buy overseas Market
The red delinia poem
Warcraft
The one that was based on that ship
Yeah well over there
Because
They are great movies but they're excited
They are excited
The cross culture
Because they're excited
Alex is pissed about
Some stuff
About to try,
It's insulting to America
Of course
We're going to
And find just a little
You've got nothing
Straight face
Hollywood is set to Begin work on Little America
Or or or or
Woohoo
What does
What's Little America
Okay
I'm sorry
In their own crazy Bible
Destoroyah
Even more
A joke
Show over show despise show bypassed
Fast with a collapse
Communist dictatorship
Fit as a fake stock market and is already collapsing
He just described Russia
Is set to Begin work on Little America
Begin work on little Den.
But do you realize what was going on there he's got nothing
It's so important to illustrate when he has something that he's going on he has nothing
All he has are is that terrible dick joke
Yeah
The rule of Threes he went little pee-pee little ding ding and then just back to Little America
Yeah that's
F*** you
Swimming pool pump
Not yet
Not a woman at once
Sincere apology
Open Hollywood
And they're openly
America
I think I actually
Alright
Who's our special forces join with a Chinese all-you-can-eat this up
The voice of Optimus Prime
America
She's okay they work for the Chinese because he's rescuing his daughter
Creating a race war
What
Of our exploration of whether or not Alex
Yeah we've got it we're on several for Cookie Monster okay black people not good
Movie is the special forces guy gets contracted by
Mrs. Astor president has
Bankrupted the United States and China is taking over the world
Like
Movies
Nota movie
Unlock orientation New York
Documentary
Escape from l.a.
Is that Alex completely misunderstand
In real time
I think the guy
Special Forces guys going in to save his own daughter when he billionaires.
I suppose instead of it being the plot to
It's once removed the plot to take
Alex
Tries to
Sommore
I mean this is just
Indicative of his
F****** Rusty
Steve Jobs
Now they're set to just take it over I mean the worst unwatchable but it's already
Flags and the Chinese president saving everyone
Hollywood
So many people in Hollywood
Text
President
They're in Switzerland today most meanings
What's up sorry method the Chinese president lives into it
Davos meeting
Okay
Doesn't everything we've been education secretary
Alright sorry
No I know I just don't want to
Or the fact that she's allowed to continue existing
You know the Gathering of world powers and
Some celebrities
Stuff like that like everyone is not anymore
He brings it up so he has to come up with a new one then
Union Grove doesn't give me a boner anymore right Bilderberg is exciting
You can't just a trilateral commission and we all piss our pants
The un's okay now
Yeah
I'll accept our present
Just about everything
He doesn't think it's
Everything's bad
Everything
Cookie jar
Chinese brother
Optimus Prime and nnn
This is auto fraud
Ananas
You go in then full grown American man
NFL coming out against the Second Amendment now
God hates John Wayne
The Chinese president
The Chinese President John Wayne
I'm John Wayne
Let me stop right there
So
Was a homeless man's rambling keep in mind
Crazy we're living in one of the most dangerous times ever our country is falling apart
10 year old Sketchbook during American history class like
Optimus Prime
Trump hat on
King album cover
So then the Chinese
President is also going to resurrect
Who is no evil
Skill do no evil
He did
But like I think
I love this
Because it's
Kind of a guy trying to have fun
Do you know like he's
Crying
God it's so bad
They really is
His laugh was Eva
I'm such a big fan of his
Crazy in Vegas
That's worse than Doctor Robotnik Sonic games
So f****** fake Final Fantasy 10
So Alex wants to wrap up with the
The Hollywood storyline
This
Little gem
And they're openly
I almost want to say to all the evil people who want to serve this.
Crazy people
Screaming kill Trump and for other students
I hear the students freaking out the background
So he's talking about a cliff he played earlier of a teacher
Projector screen
In her classroom of the Trump inauguration
Water gun
Shooting at the things I
But also I don't know if
I don't think it's from the clip
You really
It is no indication there's anyone else in the room lights
She might have been
I don't know that to be true I have no idea
From
Source given
It could just be I mean
Was it a false
It might have been
The dirty.
Vistaprint
You're running your mouth your going to get hurt
Talk s*** get hit
Running my mouth
Look what
We've done
In 21 years
Information War
Everybody has really gotten normalcy bias a learned helplessness
Or we just accept
And I'm sorry
Trump Easter
It's going down
So fast
But he needs to come out now
Has any
I bet you can't
Liana Brackett
Domino's Watson and his brother
This is an electronic cultural Red Dawn by the
They're going to keep us in line
Now I need
To ask you to enjoy a sip of wine
Cuz what about to happen is a string of
Crazy threats
That are
Sacrifice thousand dollars
First of all there's no way he could afford to do that
At all
He couldn't do that
Jesus went into the money changers
Because they were screwing up the temple in the sacred place
Broken
But here's where he
The weasel
Has he ever read
Probably
Calendar something like that
Like those
Work memes
At an office which is probably
Keep your chin up
Border
I think we got a verse right here
2nd Thessalonians 3
New calendar
Pray for us
But the word of the Lord may have
Free course and be glorified
Even as it is with you
Oh well then
Avocado
Sing where he's going to be like
Showing everyone's decadence
And showing everyone's Love of Money
But here's
What is a weasel
Azerfreedom everything else does
It's just a form of advertising
Buck
His whole life is a metaphorical
No the only reason today
Jester have any power is the sacrificing of the
These are manipulative suck
Understand most of what anything
Looked away my hands up
Here is where the
Start
Okay
So
Fuckingawesome
Zach call
The whole pie
Or your business work with you
Not working and brainwashed everything's going to burn down
I want to go to war
Visit
That was f******. That was
That's crazy
That was
That was from Troy
Rage
Cheeses that
How how f******
Fake is that anger
That was
Religious fervor to that
In the middle
Like I can't even do his voice when I yell at
Stove
Lord bring them low
Bricks
Swing low
Weedjies
I don't really know
Remember what it is
The label inside jerk-off fantasy about scum
So
Probably pretty anchors
And their whole future is based on how well we do
They're delusional because they imagine they're with the power structure
And they believe because they're in
Weather
Publix, Traders are
You're all going to be held up as the standard of Filth
You defeat will will will
Millennium
Supporters
You truly have created
Fallen scared frightened confused metal bases
Far gone I've seen them
They're gone
Weather
Madonna the opposite of the beautiful spirit of Womanhood you are monsters
You are what you claim men are trying to do
You're there to dominate The Spirit of women
Lose Yourself
In the metaphysical version of who was that
Famous Royal that would kill babies and bathe in their blood
Let's go out to break
Wait did he say that
A rich Act
Purses
Will know that the Cosmetic products
Project Veritas videos something like that
I feel like you might be right
I'm not sure but I feel
What did they switch to babies to save money like what happened on Shark Tank
Mister mister wonderful or whatever
I put them in actresses lips
20 million dollars
What bank
It seems bizarre
You're good at busy
Cuz we're in
Shockingly accurate that was just
AJ / 0 Phantom
He will be held up as the examples
If you're going to win a war
Culture War
I would say don't tell other people
Bond villain lair
Keep that a secret
Like it's not just good
It's like a Bond movie where the guy gives away too much in the bottoms up
Well now that we know how we're going to be just don't know how we're going to be held
Generations
Succumb
Scum
Also
Basically what he said is to irrelevant
Older women
Sucking at the Spirit of
Real woman
Right here
Madonna gave a speech at the women's March
And she mentioned
Yeah but in it she said that she at times feels like she wants
How to blow up the White House but she does
Yeah and that's taken out of context and
No
Positive does Madonna have the resources to
She was married to Guy Ritchie and he's been known to do a lot of caper movies
Great
No cuz it wouldn't sell that.
Swept Away whatever the movie
Amazon fire box office
And Sherlock Holmes is going to
The White House being a
Exploded by a bomb
Baja
But
He's going to be radical
Sure sure sure
Radicalized
No no
Watson
It just a blind follower okay until the very end
Is Martin Freeman
Is amazing
But he's not in the movie version
Subway is Moriarty a patriot
Where's your globalist
I mean
Okay well it's
Alex Jones
Moriarty's unabashed app
People who need
People need weapons
It's supply and demand
Does that make us
Holmes and Watson I mean my last name is home so I'm going to take
I'm going to take
Unhinged the opiates
So
Do we had all this
This Tricom stuff that's weird
Jackoff fantasy
But that's not all Alex was on on the 26th is also into another narrative
That has to do with why it's totally cool
To build a wall
Explain
Because he said in Spanish
Trouble
I'm going to have to f****** ask you not to talk over these quick
Other Mexico we're going to have an affair conversation on app
Agree with you that.
Of course
We need to stop talking over Clips alright I'm sorry I want to give you your 40 I want to keep this
Trump card this Donald Trump card
God help me deposit of a point
I'm sorry
Homes
You speak in Spanish which is already suspect
Well
No
English or nothing a******
Getting out of it
If it's defending English
Bubble
Basically what Mexico's economy collapse
And
It's a good thing
Turn of the premise
And this narrative
But they have a wall with Guatemala
And their hypocritical because they want us
To not have a wall between the United
Do they have a
Nope
No but isn't that the Bedrock of his
Yep
But it doesn't exist
I would encourage
Everyone
Listening
To look up some pictures of
The border between Guatemala and Mexico know there's gorgeous
It's just gorgeous Lush nature beautiful
But you if you do Google it you'll find some meme
Of people who have posted pictures
Purporting to be a wall
Between Mexico
Guatemala
And if you reverse image search
Bu
You find
Better bunch of them
Between Mexico and Arizona
Therapy
That's between Mexico and Arizona
Reported to be between
New Mexico
Guatemala it is not
Another one they have
That Alex put on
On Infowars
Is
A giant wall in Israel
Purported to be between Mexico and Guatemala
It's not
It's b*******
F******
Can you do that
He doesn't not know
He's a liar
Absolutely is lying
If not
She's literally the worst journalist in the world
Cuz I figured that out with
3 seconds on Google
Okay but here's
Meme of there being 3 million immigrants
Illegal immigrant to vote
Of course
Think there was a good to be
What is there a 10000000
How come you like the number the 3 million is already
It's not
Studies
Everytime I assure you I assure you will get back
I'm just saying
It's something that was based on no evidence there was actually just
AIDS
From a guy
They just
Just f******
Exploded
Who tweeted that he had three million cases of voter fraud
Himself is registered in three states
Okay also also owes 100,000
Who's right
We all make mistakes
Because it's not related to what he's talking about is in 3
States registered which is part of what keys
Supporting to brutalight
And he's a response right when he was cold bicyclist was
I don't know I didn't
Know that
Of course you didn't
That anybody was registered but doesn't know
I'm probably registered in Illinois and Missouri
I probably did
Cancel my registration when I move
Can you do that
What ya cancel your registration
I didn't know I don't know both Hill annoy and Missouri
I've already said that I'm never going to answer
Is there any questions about my voting have
But also say
You don't
If you want them
Are you auditing
Look straight up here's my W2
I don't need
Tell the audience I'm showing you my W2 literally right
This is my dirty dossier
Let me see your long form w
$13,000 last year pretty good
That's not good we are opening a patreon
Patreon.com freezing-point go to donate to help me make more than 13,000
Can't live on that b******* in Chicago
Alex has more thoughts about Mexico in this wall
Keep your eyes open
Four-way more lies
Play the clips of the Mexican president
Choices on how do that
You just broke the rule that you had
Mission of interrupting rhino
Interrupt
Everything so much things like well
This this Cliff actually is
So that is being the running
Theme of the show
He's very scared
The last week
Week or so
I don't blame him
Cuz the more facts that start to come to light in the more we realize like General Flynn just erase
Erased his Twitter account
Like it really looks like
He's being investigated hard
Cleo legal documents
Destruction
Yep when you're official
All digital dropbox
F******
Incriminate
It does kind of look like the world is closed
Around
The people in power
I don't know it's going to be a very weird world
I don't know I'm very scared
But he is too he's using
Instead of owning up to the fear and being like
Things I maybe I'm on the wrong team
That is
A normal human might do
No no
Here's a why I was thinking about this earlier because my my parents
And my aunt
Still think that
They're still on the give him a chance
Let's train
I really
And I will tell you the reason
I
Went through all of the
Conservative websites
It's while I was researching
Or do I just do this with all news
Because of this Muslim ban thing
I'm trying to figure out
Personal stories
Who word
F******
Translators in Iraq
Did any of these facts
Ever will even get the
The chance to get away is it is impossible for us to ever to
Family members who've been murdered
For their association with the USA
Still because they thought it was the right
F****** thing to do
Still help
Henwy
Promised
Get out
Because of their service
The f****** muslim ban
And if you read these stories there's no
Possible way
There's no
F****** possible way you can defend
Nope
Conservative websites
0 of them
One person
They did not interview
Even bother with it instead they went with The Narrative of like
1 *
This guy
Who saved our f****** soldiers lives
Is being blocked
Further Narrative of
Like there's been a lot of that s*** going on for a long time
Sir alonne that is
That has been going on for a while
Because of our extreme wedding program
Arabian place
Extreme already the cockamamie b******* is like
We're just letting people in
No no no
Harder to get in
Personal stories
And if
Just put that because I can
Give them real news
They don't believe in real news
Conservative websites started running
Personal
Testimonials
From this muscle
Immediately
All of these all of these
Conservative people
Who genuinely do believe themselves to have
Compassion
If they actually started reading these doors
There's no
Possible way they could still support the version of personal stories with those conservative sites
Literally everybody
They could talk about their experience
It's not being killed by it
You could do a puff piece on how great it is to not be killed by immigrants
$13,000
So do I
Towards the Mex
Again
Mexico gets hundreds of billions of dollars a year of money sent back down to it
Anon
Mexico's business to make sure the Trump
Looks like
Do you follow through
Promise
Doesn't make any sense though they're getting
The hundreds of billions that they are not getting
No they're not getting as much as you might imagine
Crazy
It's more like it's more like 5 million
Play concern back to their families
And it's not like it's gotten games
It's not like a jailbreak
Earn money and send it to their family
And you're talking about basically robbing
Great
Relationship in
Because they're not allowed to send money back
To chip in as a show of solidarity to make sure that Trump follows through with his
Because otherwise he would look like
Hold on
It gets worse
It was a both of the campaign
One way or another
I see what is about to happen
Gracious
Came up here and negotiated baby
Facebook page for third of it or something
But Mexico didn't do that
One way or another in
Trump knows America Fields demoralize
As important as brainwashed position
Vautour
Play the clip from Mexican president
Is it in Spanish
See
Any of his
Listeners speaks
If he plays that clip-ins
Anderson they don't speak
Dismiss translate if you want it
So you couldn't get away with it on video
The idea for his
Radio show the ideas get the money one way or another is second
What's going to happen
Yeah basically
But the thing that I take much more issue with is the ID
Theories like Americans are brainwashed into picking
Yeah absolutely
Yeah
That was the ID laws were part of the Jim Crow
Racial profiling and it's been found that way in court
Multiple times
Repeatedly
Largely bracelet
Related
Income brackets
Are much less likely to have IDs
Is there also
You're more likely to vote Democrat
Because the Democrats are the only people who even
Pretend to give a s*** about them
If he was like
After being able to read
Order to vote
Your grandfather
But it seems
Parcel
Yeah it's not the same thing but it within its it is within that territory
He's defending
Classically racist
Tactics
To get people to not be able to vote
Can we feel dirty for wanting these things
Better than him
Defending
Isn't being read
No it's actually the same f****** day
He's not defending modern ways of rain
Hoarding them as a
F******
Is the Avatar of modern
James Cameron
We all know Titanic
Is American propagate
False
False flag
Leather nuke each other
Administration
Did that not
Did Nazis do that
They did do that
Very much are we supporting their tactics are we not
This house would put out a report of immigrant crime
Is one of the most
Straight propaganda
Demonizing overpopulation things ever it's
Literally if they start doing that
We've got a
A start riot
Beyond the report
Wheel repair
Peacefully protesting now
If he starts
Doing full-on Nazi shitla
Like we have to fight
I mean it's bad enough that the other night American Primus fighting Nazis
He's like isn't that are definitely a joke
Indiana Jones's it's bad enough that the other ninety fire that attorney general
Pure that way
Was pure Animal Farm
Is there any press releases put out afterwards that he had
She had disrespected the president
It was some weird emotional words
Could not
Possibly bring
It's exactly what it was
It was propaganda against
It was
Even if you're the most
Base level analysis like you're the f****** New York Times
Trying your best
Neutral
It's clearly she said that you wouldn't break the
Institution
And he fired her
Before it hit the brick
Exactly what he did
Which is like hey goodbye
Constitution
And the other part of it is the idea that the Attorney General is supposed to be
PA political and unrelated
The Winds of
The president
So that's already breakdown
Clear the end of the Constitution
Yeah
You might as well just peed on the counter
Nicolas Cage didn't steal the Declaration of Independence like we all hoped he would
Whitlock
I mean all the people who were super alarm is there were saying that we're not going to have a chance in 28
Teen
There's not going to be probably a fair 2020 election
Pretty bad
Ham days into presidency
Too late and I believe on Election Day we were texting and you're like
We got to get out of here hopefully we go to sleep
We do we do
Badoo
We do
Wilson Realty
This could become Danger
All we want to do is laugh at this jackass
Liquid jitomate leave yet want to be like paranoid
Spin
Stared fantasies
I mean we've already gotten would give anything for these to be scared without publicizing
Without publicizing the show at all we've
Gotten a couple tweets from Alex Jones
Thankfully just
In the realm of
But actually
But actually explanations that he has reserved for women or even just like us
I think I got one
Why you want terrorist then I saw that there was no doubt
Supernanny
As it grows we're going to get the attention of weirdo people
I'm looking forward to seeing what real online bullying
Only ever heard of it
Bring it will have a conversation with you most of our points will be
We like
Other folks
We like people
Anyway
Their government
Underscore
The government is going to release
Report
Immigrant crime
I am
Beginning of eclipse
Just so what happens next
Trump Administration
Coming to an end
What are you living
Do you think we're stupid
Mexico has a wall
Guatemala
The reason that he's saying the fence in places in a wall and other pictures of Arizona
Okay
You fucken understand
Does he
Does he believe
Set those are on the southern border bottom
He doesn't
40 completely bald faced lie
Based on everything that I've been able to glean from other things
I think he's involved
Play Sly I think he truly believes it disagreement on this
Disagree office
You stink but here's
The thing you see those leaks from the Trump
Like there's a underground
The POTUS resist
The Twitter account
Fanfics like
Anthony atamanuik Trump
Annabelle 2
Fake
Fake things often absent reality
With those fake things
On the f****** news
Where is Sean Spicer
Kellyanne Conway
Alternative facts
Billy said we were going
Searching for the
3 million
Immigrants
That boat
3 million illegal
Very clear that
Nutpods
Also Alex
Alex Jones claims
It's not true Alex Jones claims that the mainstream media came up with
The term alternative facts
When it was actually kellyanne Conway
Other than news
I think you truly were.
I'm saying
Because Trump
Believe it
I don't think he's
He's lying
Okay
I'm going to say that
Alex Jones
The Ring of believing
That those two things
Not like
I think he believes
Steve lied to himself so well
I think I'm coming from a slightly different place when you because often I am watching
Like sometimes I'm just listening but also I'm watching
I have noticed he has a nervous
Tech
Appel
You going to play poker with him liking
Casino Royale
Full House
Every time he does this but it's not very glaring
The basketball player
When I was a kid
I love John
John Stockton
I also love John
Number one
Little racist
I also love Larry Bird Larry
I like John Stockton because he was very selfless
I like being his big thing was a
I like that I thought that was cool
I don't think that
Whenever he would take
Free throw he would rub his face
Because it was
Is his way of saying hi to his kids back at home
And I noticed it before any of the commentators
Explained it
Rubbing his face
It's the same thing with Alex
I don't know
Exactly the point.
Does this
That's how
Is the top of his right ear he aggressively rub
And I don't know if
He just had some weird like
I don't
Every time
It's like
In the future I will keep track of what he's saying when he does it and see if it matches up with anything
Zodiac
Style spreadsheet effect
Google Drive
Now they're going to finish it up as a big strong wall because Latin America is collapsing
South of the Border
Have a sovereign country if you don't have
Control board
We have a wall or has one
Mexico has won
So he's referencing the great Waltz
Today is
River resources
It didn't work at all
But also the Great Wall was created because there was literally the greatest War technician of all time
With hordes
Warriors
Favorite favorite
My favorite Futurama B
Is where
They break down the Great Wall in
I wouldn't call fighting against I've also done a little bit of research into
Do the Great Wall over the years
Because you text me with me
It was me
Yeah it originally was just like a mud wall but it was always because that
That that stretch
Area in the north of China was in
Forever
Ever
Through the kingdom periods and it was always
Just turmoil
It would be
It's insane to compare that
To Mexico
Also Mexico
And the Vatican
Which
Good enough
I am not going to
Possibly
But that's not the exam having a wall is not where I'm going to pick a fight
I think that's the one that we should do
I may or may not support that
Great Wall of China
You're talking out of your ass what about the Wailing
Doesn't bring that one up but get this
He has one
Oh no
Drop the clip
Just like Adidas
It's way better than the original Great Wall
Lunacy
Quarryville bomb has one
Mark Zuckerberg wants one sugarburg has like 700
But there's other little pieces of property
Saturn
Doesn't want to have any neighbors force them to yourself
The Mexican president
What are you talkin about
Zuckerberg
No Mark Zuckerberg apparently is building like a compound Hawaii
Just at home
The same look like Peter Thiel is going is fleet
Excuse me
He gets f*****
Walking murders
Pray like
List of billionaires in every night before I go to sleep okay with needles
Is that
Saturn
Sure
Dude just don't kill us more less comedians black
Peter Thiel is brought up
Here's the thing
One of his
20 Nae
Indian Island
Yeah
Timberlake golf
I think accidentally
The last is going to all fulfill the
The prophecy of an ran
Even though they hate her
Lexus
Is all the important people in society just give up
And like say alright we're not going to f****** get it we're not going to be involved in the
So you think the left is going to give up
I think that there was going
Tacoma time
Possibly
That a lot of people on the last are going to be like this is no longer country I support
I think I'll probably do it
Protest
Walkout
Strike
Stuff like that
Where is John Galt
Just disappearing
Did you cancel your Uber account
I will cancel it
Here's the thing I got an email from there I was busy that night
Person
I was busy that night I saw a bunch of tweets about how difficult it was
I'm just not up for
For this right now I'll keep the app but I'm not going to
Two step
They canceled their account and then
Later
They had not been
Fraudulent
I'm hearing that canceling your account is way more.
Difficult than you think
God
Patty is that like
Mark Zuckerberg has property
Under English law is still
Honolulu in Honolulu
I don't remember ever coming up with English,
Yeah
I don't know on the phone he's another
Immediately
Comedian who lived in Hawaii we can figure it out also
Move Along
This is going to be a long-ass episode today
Kermit
It was not
Just China and Max
Kowall issues on the 26th
Alex also had another big
Piece of news you wanted to break about everyone's favorite
Jewish Boogeyman
Well Soros
The Golem
Has been naked shorting out of stock market has everything he's got
Magically
Regulators
Dutch regulator this is Bloomberg
Accidentally soros's short positions
World
And now his positions have been releasing it turns out he was betting against
America
It's been blowing up in this goblins face and it's beautiful
Again we have to repeat Goblin
Is a very stereotypical Jew
Cosmetic
David
Classic Jewish stereotype
So
This did happen
He's not he's not telling the truth
What's up
It's a short
Deshawn everything right now cuz we haven't ascended Market if I if I had enough money I would do the whole big
Short thing again
And just take a short
Position
Because this bubble is going to f******
But I think it's sketchy
It elicits negative reaction
Because the idea of short bedding
Is
That you want things to fail
It's the same way that if you go to the
Casino people think it's rude at the roulette table to bet on double zero
Because if you bet your bedding for everyone else to lose
There's sort of a there's an idea that decorum
Is upset by that
But that's Wall Street
Everybody short everything all the time if you didn't sure thing
Other people
Take the opposite position
He is talking to people who don't play the market in so they will believe these ingrained things about
If you didn't have an alternate buyer who is better things to go well
It wouldn't be
Possible
When was that people are are moving on
ProTech
To all over
Which ones are those
So then
Keyboard marching against
Thesaurus evil
Extensive
Looking into this I could not find
Single source
Amy March
Against the ropes
Any country in the world
For this
Time.
What time.
I looked for
I looked for anyting
And I couldn't find Jerome Martin
Ever look into the story cuz the positions were accidentally revealed
On this website
Which is
Illegal
Yes but it was a complete accident a bunch of other people short positions
Reveal to
Basically if you have a short position under 2%
I believe is a threshold you don't have to report it
But if you're over that you have to report it
And if it's above 5% it has to be
Cuz if you're betting a master short on something
Then other people are going to take that as a signal that either you have inside
Information sure you think something
Things about the fair
Mystery
What's them people are going to be like maybe he knows some
I read about 20 articles
Warren Buffett
Too bad this thing is going to
Succeed other people
He's a good investor
Exactly
Influence that he actually in
Know if you want it look at this side of that George has lost about a billion dollars shorting
Do you like Dow Jones
After Trump
So which was it
Historically just because after
Herbert Hoover
That was the last time that
The market was that
Okay
What
Hooverville
He's like 26
6 billion dollars
He gives away
Tons of it
But it's also like a billion dollars is a big hit
Absorb
Besides that I could find
I like I said I read about 20 articles on this
Even some weirdo blog
And no one could
No one could cite anything
3 shorted other
Then to
Institutions
When was the Dutch bag
I called ing
And the other was a
The German lending giant douchebag
So neither of those are America
No
So
Yeah I didn't get better and Coronavirus
There is zero evidence that he bet against
America
In this case then Alex Jones
Is
Saying that the entire stock market
Is representative of America
Using this logic against these Dutch
Is betting against America memes
That you just if you bet against anything
You're betting against me
Lyrics
Market
Is the American mark
It no to all except
Do all
Certain
Now we come back to this question
Is Alex
Unaware of these bags
Or is he willfully lying
I think he's willfully lie
This is this
What is the thing that
He has to be willful I willfully lying
Did he tell you
Oh man I wish I remembered
If you knew that I would immediately jump so I'm going to have to
Much better attention.
Biomat
That is the ultimate seller of this argument
Between the two of us is going to turn it around
So yeah I do not want to be
Edward Norton
I'm super excited that I can start to see on Twitter a lot of people calling out this Jewish
Cunard is Jewish Boogeyman narrative about Sora
I'm excited because
Is it is really important
First of all the idea that
Soros paid protesters diminishes the idea
Yep which is really bad
Implications of it
Really really
Well I mean
Echoes echoes
All
Goes all the way
It goes all the way is wrong all the ways
It's wrong all the way
Absolutely
All right we got to get now
We are
Extra-long episode
We are abstract cover
So it is now the 27
Aldi's
The eclipse will be from
January 20th
Friday move to the other last day of June
There's a Friday was good didn't use the egg
F*** around and got a triple double
I want to start this adventure on the
Seventh with
Where we will agree
With Alex
A little bit because my favorites is whatever we have
Give It Up to Alex Young
And then he says the next thing ever like
You just
Spoke prophecy
Is
It's going to be a rollercoaster because
Some real s***
To do with Trump's stance on torture
He said some real s*** and then it breaks so bad
Okay here we go
I think it could end up being our downfall
If he's openly
Orchards okay
I forgot I cut out the first 3 minutes
The first three minutes
I agree with him on everything but torture
It's a sticking point
Because if you torture then you become the thing you're again
And that's a really good point that's a really good
But
You like
So here here is where exit
I cut out all the part that I we actually agree with
His principle is that he's Against torture which I think is great but but this is where he explained
Picture
He's against it
Cuz you don't want
Telluride
That's a good guess it's actually worse
Alright
It could end up being our downfall
The people running things
We'll use that to Trump
I think he's walking
You can't frame somebody with real
Saying what a thing
Reporting
One little girl
That was not
Framingham for blowing up that little girl
He did that s***
Yeah speaking with you read about that
Brother of the little girl that Obamacare
Everything that could go wrong went wrong almost everything was
I love the world
Thank God we got a guy who cuts through the b******* in charge
Yeah give him a
Isn't it depressing though.
He's like I'm against
Torture
But then his reasoning for is
Not that it's inhuman
It's a horrible thing to do to people
It degrades you as a person
His
His argument is
You can use that against
Yeah
That's so that's a large glass box
Is it more it is the motivation more important than the
Cuz I'm all for him
John Stuart Mill shed his
The only thing that is good is Goodwill
I see I'm going to go with us
Long if he's against
Torture
Let's forget about it
You might walk that back in a second what's
Finish the quote
President
Disavow it look
Do not codify something
Emergency situation
Isn't that an amazing way to end the argument
Invalidates literally everything you just said
Are you saying you're holding someone
You know you're not actually going to turn me over because I can identify you
Yep
That's exactly what it is
So close
To being like, every single time
Biggest
Did the only reason you would kill someone after you torture them is because they can
Talk about how you torture them
Should be held accountable for
Kill everyone
Dip
He just advocated
Torturing
Not just tortured side of torture is that some people might find out your torture
A consequence base as opposed to like that's a principle that we should not do that
Even then
Assassinate
Make them afterwards so then
The torture is not going to go down
Murders are going to go up
So bad
This is why
Just going to be me barking
Just do it
Also indicate
So clear that I don't think he knows what he's saying
Any
He's just talking
Annie
Concept
Okay one this also supports
He's living in a movie
Episode of 24
Yeah
He's not living in Rio
But I heard from General
Who are on Fox
Fox
Dramas
Work
If you are going
If you are going to
Anyway
Count yourself
A religious
Cuz he believes in it
Read everything
You can
Sibley say what
You can't do it
You literally
Cannot do it
Nope
If
If you torture then you must kill
Yeah that's
No that's analyzation
Chesebro actually that might be
Earlier that we get
To talk about the illegal voting claims
I mean probably only a week away from that publishing
Weekly
Reports on
Big time
We're going to die
So I hear is
Found more studies
The pru
The Trump is correct
Trump
Saturday
Provides alternative facts
Alternative facts like
University study
University George Mason University
Concluding upwards of 2.8 million illegals
Voted and Swan
Key election
And then today and said they found
This study
Unfortunately
He studies at all
What are you doing
I am looking at that exact
What was
Here's what's fun if you just Google The Old Dominion study
The first thing that comes up
Is
A story
Where the headline is
Stop speeding
Virginia professor says Trump twisting his research on non-citizen voting
So we have this guy who tweeted about the illegal voting
About is himself registered to vote in three
Old Dominion study where this guy who wrote
The study says stop using it you're twisting the facts
We have a Pew research
About illegal voting where the guy who's consist
Gone on record and said
They're not saying what my study shows
Yeah
Now there's the George Washington
So I can't speak to that
But a little bit further research
Into the Old Dominion
Study
I want to think
Found
Was that I'll just always read this offer bait
A recent study by political science
Old Dominion University
The use the 2008
2010 Cooperative congressional election study
To examine whether quote
Boden USA
The authors reported about 1% of the
Responded
Survey identified
Themselves as nonsense
An immigrant
In 2000
489 in
Estimating the
21 of these self-identified nonsense
Justin's voted in
In 2000
An eighth
Self-identified nonsense
Voted
They use this to
Project National voting rate
Of the u.s. nonce
Populate
Hayden October 24th
Jesse Richman
And David Ortiz to authors
Admitted that they are quote
Extrapolation
State-level or district-level election outcome is
Rock With You
Substantial uncertain
The authors noted that
It's a non-citizen
Can create errors
They're self-reporting
Was imperfect and supplemented by a
The
The ultimate estimate this is
This is how bad this
Study is
Haha be as low as 38,000
And as high as
2.81
Which is any POTUS
Single worst
Study
Okay if your margin of error is 1%
That's okay
Thousand percent
It's crazy bad margin
Well and whenever your studies are based on like
Unverifiable self-reported back
It's a it's a they took a poll of a small amount of people who said they were
Unread
Just aired when they voted
And another one in 2008
Another one of these studies that they cited was based
Self
What is a self-directed internet
Studies
Which is basically like
Choose to opt into it on the internet
Is this place called
Mturk
It's a Amazon already off to a great
Amazon
It's this crowdsourcing they pay you like
Cerveza
Stuff like that
You can do transcription work on it
It's little things that can't be automated by robots
To do like a little bit
The little password things
Use that to translate things for a little while when I was unemployed
I'm trying to get a little bit extra money trying to go
Who have dabbled in it there's a bunch of university studies
The people who are filling those out or getting paid 25
To do it and no they need
Need to fill out like
Papparoti
So no no no no no
Protesters
In order to make a living
Back on board
When you fill out surveys
For money
You're trying to grind through the
So you often give an accurate information
Any you have a monetary
Incentive
Just f****** foot
That's like being paid
To take standardized tests as fast as you can so you just write see you in every single one of
Any study that has
Part of their sample Bay
Online opt-in studies
Is generally considered the
Bastard child
Avant during most
Fox News polls
They have somehow 81% support
Insane thing
97%
Of the popular vote
Statistics
Or only as trustworthy as a methodology used to
Yes and
You can say whatever you want
And if you look which is the
Single most
Frustrating
Part of having a conversation but sound
This
Is backed up by this and they're like oh yeah
Is backed up
By this
Is that isn't play
Because we had liar love and
I'm trying to work it out
That is a factor issue
Beyond that
You also have the people who wrote the
The studies being like
You are misrepresenting
What we're saying
That is not what we're saying 3 million a lotus
Yeah the study is so poorly made
It it one is not rap
Hookah Bowl
Any study that has an estimate
Between 38000 and 2.81 million
Is impossible to replicate
It's also the most easy thing to rap
Okay and that you grab
Kissimmee
The street and go probably like
According to all 10 employees at Five Guys
There are too many employees at Five Guys
Luann Alex's other argument
Is
This salon.com
Politico
Article
The headline of it
Illegal immigrant
Could elect Hillary
October 3rd
It is a real article
But what it deals with
Is
The apportionment
How how bad
We're all going to f****** die
We are
About how
Electoral votes
House of Representatives
And basically those work off the census
Doesn't care if you're illegal or legal
It's just about the number of
Yeah that lives somewhere
Take on it and I will compare that with Alex
I'll start with the fun
Who take is but this is nonsense
And who gives a f*** about these illegal
You shouldn't matter for the population numbers
Are they shouldn't be represented by this thing
And the fact that they're considered in the census
Which gives more House of Representatives
Representation
And more
Meme
The California and New York are cheating
Just by default
So Trump is right
My argument
Is
That illegal or legal
These are people
Disagree
There's no such thing as people
Whether or not
They
Came here legally or not
The representatives are
Yeah
The hookah spot
That's just kind of my point
New York is not as filled with Ali
Illegal immigrants
Tons of Indians
Yeah
Understand
California
I would say yes
Is filled with illegal immigrants
Maybe that's because
The people there are nicer
I'm actually you also have Arizona you have those other states
Which are firmly in the Trump balls
Yeah they are licking as much Trump balls is a fossa
Turn right now
New York
Illegal immigrants are not going to
To turn New York from
Narrative
I know but it's
Simply not pot
You're not going to turn Illinois from Blue to Red mainly because Chicago
Is all of Illinois
Yeah I mean
Illinois where you living anywhere other than Chicago other than you group
There's like DeKalb there's a couple of cities with temporary huge populations
For the college
Yeah but that
But that doesn't matter
No not for illegal immigrants
So anyway
This whole thing is built on lies
Just
House of Cards
Studies that their own writers have said is not
Ears
Easiest argument against 3 million illegal immigrants
In terms of voting population
We had 100 million people
Roughly
50% of
The total amount of people who could be
Write your three million illegal immigrants voting
Is what 3% of the population that votes
You wouldn't know any legal immigrants vote
Well I was like okay so
You would have seen it illegally
Group
25 people
There's a 50-50 shot you stare that you share the same birthday as somebody else
House to testics
If you're talking about 3% of the entire population voting
That voted
You would have gone to
There's a
What there's a wigwam
Kind of illegal immigrants who is actually turning around and saying like
I'm not supposed to do this
Like that's what would have happened we were stranded, how about this this single person who was it
No and the guy from the Pew research
Study I was talking about how the numbers that he
Of people who claimed
To be illegal immigrants
And voting
He went back
Looked into those people
And almost every single one of them was an error
Well there's been what like
10 cases of voter fraud in the past
50 years or what
Yeah voting multiple times
Like we said the guy who tweeted about it is ready
3 States
Steve mnuchin
It makes funny Trump Kushner they're all registered in multiple States
So like
Doing
It makes intuitive sense
Swear you're like oh everybody has an idea
For the for the white shirt
For the rich white bass
They live with everybody has an idea if that's
How can you drive without an ID exactly like
Or you have to have a driver's license
Instead of just a state ID
Or whatever it is or I'm lost
My ID
Too costly to go get another one
I mean looking busy
Yeah
So-so
Is it does make a certain into
Until you read up on
Which is
That's why you're asking people a lot
You're asking a lot of the human race
Or if you have Bass
Human empathy
I don't like it when you say it like that cuz that meet some crazy around the corner
We've poked holes and
Discuss the feud
Narrative heavy stuff a couple a couple of issues
Vitalik
I don't I don't know if we can come to a resolution on this
Because I
A hundred percent believe he's willfully lie
You think
Possible
Bi still here's my ears my argument
It's the basic lighted
You cannot
Tell somebody is
If they
100% believe the lie there
Their tally
That's
It is a lie
I'm just saying that if you believe it
Alex
There's no way he would submit to that but also
He is on Joe Rogan
And I think that will be the catalyst
Are we
We might have to
Could go really bad
I'm really wanting to go really really worried The Joe Rogan will show his cards
Conspiracy theorist
He
Is into some
Conspiracy theorist
He's great on Newsradio
He also has a pretty good head on his shoulders and Beverly
And we all know how that turned out
It wasn't good on you
We will
Newsradio
What are the shows not much to cover
Logan
Conspiracy stuff but he generally is pretty good about the
Debunking things
Yet he's generally very skeptical and whenever I'm very worried that Alex is going to go on there and he's not going to call him out on
Because if he does Alex will just start yelling at
There's no point in having that as a show
Like
Joe has had Milo yiannopoulos on a couple times
To be fair Joe doesn't like
Side with him
But he sort of laughs
Milos
Going full Jimmy Fallon on
A little bit
If we get to the point where we can just
That's right
Point where Joe
Brings
The most negative tweets
You got it
Jimmy Fallon
Control arm
The caveat we have is that the routes are amazing and Quest love is the greatest
Is the routes were amazed
Anyway
Next
Affair conversation
Let me get to my f****** point
So
Totally worried
That Alex is going to go on Joe Rogan
Podcast
He's not going to get called out on his
Absolute propagandizing
His absolutely
Twisting of facts
And he's going to be endeared
To Joe Rogan
Which will expand
The group of people that will be opened
Infowars
That scares the s*** out
Him getting White House credentials and being part of the press
Jerome corsi
He was talking about how he
He's in the process of giving the credentials anything's
It's going to be no problem
I don't know if that's true
It's probably true true
I don't think
It's not true
I don't think it's not
But to be in a position
We're Alex and Infowars as a whole
Take Auto
Way bigger part of
Depress
Then we won
Not do what you want
Do you mean any part of the body public
Should not want the
He is a propaganda
It terrified
Anyway we need that
It's like gerbils had a radio show with a small amount of listeners and then all the sudden
Hitler was like
Hey man
Bring it up girls became amazing
No rhythm John Griffin could still riff better than Alex show
The greatest
Some fun
On the 27th
Most
Of the show
Call boys
About how pissed off
Alex's at Sienna
Dmsm the mainstream media
BNN cuz they did a story about him
So earlier that if it was a puff piece he would be mad that they were mad at him about the wrong thing and that clip
Played a little bit earlier he was like
He said the line
Wow
The journalist
Fact check Trump
Provides alternative
That is the beginning of this
Introduction
Clip from CNN
About him
Okay
Now hold on
Cheater f****** hat
I have a warning for Jurassic we are
Hold on
Because hold on
Never gets
Do the part about him
Does he okay
Here's my favorite running thing he does
Let's get this bread
That's my favorite
Horse competition with
He does he does he do that
I can't remember
Excited to find out I wouldn't short it
That's what I would say
I wouldn't
So this first clip is just about us a pack of liars
And we'll get into the fun
Visit 3 clips long
But man
Mursi's government
Their numbers are Warrior
This is back to the voters
Do research
Pure research
Pew pew
So I wasn't sure which one
Voter fraud that narrative
Organizing
I got caught all that is not true
Which state
Preposterous 6 months ago
Know what that means
Dizon
Well they are federal but they run on the state level
Like eat
State sort of independently-run there elections that's why
Difference
Alex
Primaries believes executive order to put up by Obama
The election under the auspices of the federal government
It's not
Hillary VP
She would think that
But it don't matter
Well yeah you're right you're right
All of all of the what-ifs after something that didn't happen
Are just fantasy
I will do the milly studies logic
Voldemort had one
Yeah
Logic in college
Understand about logic
It isn't
Logic is
Central Lee
A method of
Truth preservation
That's all it is
So basically when you have an if-then
Statement
If the
First part is true
The second forecast
If the first part isn't true
It doesn't matter with the second part so if you're saying
Obama federalized the elections and therefore we are where we are
It doesn't matter what you talk about
Is that it presupposes that human beings are rational which we all know
If then
Often winds up being an issue because
Do you get
If a then would you prefer
And people say
Human rationality
I'm with you
Let's get back to this dump
Which Obama's now done and all 50 State Attorney General
Including Democrats
I did some
Some deep digging on this one found
Mayweather
I can't even find evidence history of the human race
I literally can't even find evidence
Any attorney-general's writing about this
Which is a pronoun
Knock knock
You're right you're wrong we tell the truth if you lie your honorable your dishonorable
Alright
Alright alright
Rhythm
Yeah that back and forth
Perfect rhythm
Yeah
He's good at like that sort of hypnotic
Sort of
A business
Now I just wanted to WhatsApp
Super exciting
Super effective
When you're literally lying and you choose other people being like
Just wait we always go back to
That
The big
Through-line
Entire body
Is
They're doing
What they say
We're doing
Which is such a signal that we're doing
Exactly what they
They say we're doing
Please don't look at what I'm doing
They're doing
One of the branches of Journalism
Media criticism
And it's a very legitimate
Branch
Important
Absolutely
Now
In this clip
Alex
Attempt
To do some media criticism
Honesty
I want to say this
Play all of it cuz it
Really loses
At some point
But this clip
Legitimately is like six
16 minutes long
So this is me
Before the show
He said we were going to do the laundry slip
Alex Alex
I'm doing and if we're going to get into The Shakespearean play that is
Alex Joe Zack Morris off
Yes you're going to do a freeze frame
He did it for Easter
Ladies jealous
Do we have
I was going to drop in freeze frame by Jay geils
We got to finish this
Yeah he told me about this earlier any
Tease the longest
I was like
5 minutes
Turns out it's
Minutes that's a long-ass clip
45% of the episode we've done
So far
I have no,
He's criticizing a clip from CNN
I'll just get into it because I don't think I can do it justice
Reliable sources are reliable at like a white truck pulls up
At the playground
We have puppies
We have comic books
That's equivalent in a
Look there's a puppy pipe
So, everybody's a pedophile
So f****** just immediately go the show is called reliable
This club
But also I want I want to play it I want to play this like
A little longer
It's going to get mad if we keep interrupting clips
It's spectacular
Can't let this play
Like legitimately
Goes on terrible wrist and hand
Is that
Microphone
Inside of the truck
Oh hi come on in the back of the truck
Come on America, enslave you
Control you look at this guy
Guy look like he's a chump
Funny acts like a big fat
Trump
Iran
Creeper van
Unreliable
So also I should say this cuz I was watching this cuz I was like this is so bananas I got to see the video
What the guy in the booth.
This point is puts up like
Image
Of a white van
It says free candy on the side and a bunch of bloody hand
Pedophile
Leave the bloody handprints on there
How did you have that ready
One of those Mexico
Kneerover
I just pumped the dog look
.
Million-dollar
Wait what
I guess so
Mocking this guy for swallowing a word
Alex said earlier when he was saying Infowars
Doesn't matter
The real point of this clip is
He has let
Jake Tapper say
6 words
This isn't Jake Tapper
This is just some young guy Brian stelter
I don't know who he is he's a doesn't look like he's very seasoned
But he's he's definitely not ready to take
Nobody
He just doesn't have our raw power
What's up
My mommy look at me on TV for the Big Barn Chinese government
Brian
Shut up
He went back into the Transformers voice
You did
Mr stilted on.cnn her death
Maybe you'd YouTube
What's there
With that stopping there is
Was maybe you have issues with Trump
I have issues Trump maybe you do too
That's not what you said at all which will
Find out what he plays the clip back
Again here in a little bit cuz I'm going to play
Quick question
Here's my bet
Yeah this is not a question
Maxwell
How many minutes before he gets
45 seconds
I don't think he ever
But I'm going to give him I'm going to give him 7
If we play this clip for 7 minutes
I say he get through
32nd
Of what
I really wish there was a way for us to like have stopwatches but see it's it's just
Phone
With stopwatches mine is playing
Guess what mine's going to be doing
Okay
So what I need you guys to keep your ears open for is the way that he just
Words out of context
Response to that
He's not responding to what this guy is actually saying
He's responding to certain words that are said
Just let the guy say his name and then it called
We're not we're not even responding
Million dollars
Because Alex is really wrapped up in masculinity Twitter
He might as well.
Yeah
So let me know when I need to start the
I'm not going
Pause this clip again
Just going to play
There will be laughing in the background
I can't imagine
Take notes
Though because
We're not stopping
Okay I'll do my best
Stopwatch
On a daily basis
Instagram.
Holes where he was
Possible
For this point Alex
Preening
I'm trying to pretend to do a
A bunch of
I don't have question
It's verifiably Ally
Questions
Grocery store
Dominator
Everybody says aren't you and your family
Will President Trump
What will the consequences be for the president
Consequences
We already know you're a fraud
Dance
I bet your family are a bunch of
You look like a pair of Dishonor the trash
So this is where I cut the clip because it goes on for another like
2:10
Let me see music
Statistics
19 sec
You made it through
Hey but that's also including running it back
No
Every time every time he rear-ended
So the Betsy did was cutting it off
And then he let it run again without restarting it for another 3 seconds
Immediately after that he let it run again for another
One point
My favorite thing on there is his like
Brian stelter is being like is the idea of lying
Coming up with all this b*******
Is it to wear us out
What do you mean
Journalist
The people trying to cover it
Alex
Take that personally
But you just misinterpreting
No not misinterpreting anything
To misinterpret
Fair enough he let the guy say his name
And then he immediately rag on whether or not he could f***
The single most beta-male thing that you could
Possibly do
Yeah
Beta male is there
Yeah that's their language
Don't Go full cock if there's one lesson knowledge
Don't go,
It was immediately
You can't
You never have to you never have to engage never
Your family or butter cookies
Yeah
Bridget surprise
To learn
Could not imagine
Him not being able to get through Clips cuz it gets
Twomad
Fake mad.
It's not even
He's just
Manhood
Bush-league bulshit distraction
I honestly think that
The content
What he's doing is with
I mean
The reason of the interrupt
Over and over
Over again
Does not allow any
Contacts
What you talkin about
To be aired
It's cuz he knows he has nothing
The woman who engaged him on the inauguration episode
What what did he say
And at the same thing you did earlier in this episode
The story about
Chinese you have no no no nothing to say so we just
Insulted the way to avoid too much time to fill
Handle Allen actual argumentative
Pierce the space
Ya gotta just
Start yelling nonsense
But what's
Really depressing to me
Maybe one of the reasons our show will never be us
Successful it says is that
That's really interesting
They don't care if there's no substitute
We're doing all right
We would only make it through 19 seconds of his clips
Another 10 minutes
I think the total was likes
I'm trying to get
Wow
Listen to is roughly four
Yeah so in 4 minutes he made it through
19 total seconds 4 minutes after like
Probably a minute we're looking at probably about 5 to 6 minutes
Zeitgeist clip
Throughout
It was
Cure
Personal attack
And nothing is gauging the
There's nothing
Never even got past
Interdyne name is Brian
Isaac goes on here
Transition
Look at this little p****
Like
Transitions at 8
Stuff about how spicy
Pretty cool
8D
Yeah you lose the thread entirely
Here's the end of
Which I think is
Are just absolutely from him introducing himself
Do we need to start this over for the beginning
Wendy
He says I'm done with the clip
He might have made it through another 15-20 seconds
O'Brien's pub
Ballpark
I can't listen to this
I can't believe how much of a beta male disguise
Absolutely despicable
Liars
Nobody is a Despicable liar
But this guy right here family probably has sex with bear
Have you ever seen a family have sex with bears
I have
It's disconcerting to say the least
Pizza place right now I can't even listen to anymore
Liars
Puzzle people are horrible
People that would do anything
These are your family
I want to make you poop
Real quick
The media are your enemy
For your family
How is that
There's no
Possible way that you can listen to
If not
And not
And not immediately think
Isn't that
Complete
Checklist
All the words you just said
Somewhat
Like
While he's giving you a checklist of what it is they're doing
He's immediately following it up
With doing that
But you can remember
This comes back to exactly we talked about the other day like one of the last episodes
We talked about you were wondering
If he's evil
Stupid
Evil or standby argument
He's evil and he relies on other
Stupidity he is he knows that other people aren't going to
Get the sources
But he's actual site
There is
Winning the war of the second
This idea that
Dim media
These are your family's enemies
Is one of the most repugnant things I've ever heard in my f****** life
Let's start the clipart
Flyers
Terrible
People that would do anything
These are your family's enemies
I want to make you poor
For you it's there are better than people and they get off on Obamacare
Bill still
But Humanity standing up
But you're just a bunch of little
Nobody
I hope you enjoy it
Because Humanity in Liberty is rising
The Regis walk-in wrong second
But you're just a bunch of little
Nobody
I hope you enjoy it
Madison Rising
2.0
We are offering a deal we haven't offered in 6 months
Alexapure Pro water
Buck
You
F*** you
I like how I like how he will give him
100% correctness
But his medication will only go .99 999
He's going to he's going to protect against the salesmanship
Personal views are always
Is that correct
He did a 17-minute goddamn rant about the CNN clips
He didn't actually play then went on at the enemies of your family the media is
Haven't switched into salesman mode with no
F******
Such professionals
He is the worst
Dammit is an artist
So amazing
Today in the Museum of Contemporary Art
And
There were so many pieces
I was having this conversation
Cuz somehow like I was in London
For the past week
Right
Museums
I think those are the first museums I've been to in like 20 years
Tons of great museums in Chicago I would never go to the motor my f****** tourist
So I went there and I was going to
Looking at the
These galleries going
Every Gallery should have a
Comic
On their what
Should be in this gallery
Like
Committee
Waco standoff
Yeah just
Because every time I was there I would go through there and
This is an amazing
And then the next place I went
Like somebody should just look at this and be like this is
F*** you
Alright
Is eggs
Exactly what's going
He is an amazing
Artist
You cannot fight against
In a
A muse
That transition
Know that whole thing that will
Is a
Fix better performance
Yeah because there's a
Complete perfect through line there's a narrative through the whole thing
Perfect like
Personal victimization like CNN is Miss aligning me
Replace this clip that doesn't have anything to do with him
And he interrupted over and over again allows no context to happen doesn't actually engage with the material of what
Perfect
They f****** hate you and then also a we got a special 20% off
There were a couple of things that were like videos where is like
We're going to show these 5 sec
Eclipse
Splicing together
But guess what
Bulshit
Art
That
F****** art
And I think he just did something that
URI
I could never never
Not a billion years
Billion years
Could we have the Bulls face
Lying ability
Bring up my patreon I feel self-conscious program
Somebody asks like where can I find you on the internet
Fan
I think
I think you're hitting a really
What's up
How you feel
I also think
It's important because
We
This Is War coming to with Alex
Is that
He is this
Razee good performance artist
Yeah
And also one of the most dangerous forces
In Media
Right now
And I don't think enough people
If you want to if you want to call Trump's Tower
He's the sorrow man
Two trucks
And that's where we lost
Now we got a lot of nerve
And literate nerds anyway Jordan that brings us to the end of January 26th
27 on the Alex Jones program
He had a bunch of other crazy bulshit to say but it was in con
I'm frankly in Coke
Almost certainly
You can't eat much but maybe we will
See what happens
If you'd like on Gmail
We are now with Isaac gmail.com okay
Be more episodes
It's coming out in the future
Responsive by Twitter trolls
And George Soros
Also sponsored by
George Soros
Is great
Help
Kill Jews in the Holocaust and we support that one
Not a good way to go very worried that people will take me
And not hear the throat
King of that I'm actually serious
Yeah
Well I mean if you're going to if you're going to Media Matters us you would definitely
Play Take Back Club
Yeah but I
I think they're on
Probably
Spinning our Wheels
Lynx
This is Ben
The best thank God I'm back
I love you
The Great
Chimborazo
I do
It's another sign.
What's personification
Good luck
Yeah I guess I accidentally said that like three times
Resistance
Oh Sheila
Holding
Alex