Alexandra Thurston color
Just sit around to have novelty beverages in our mouths
And talk about
That's a weird start right there
I love having novelty beverage
Is it my mouth
Not a bad definition of what we do know I understand that it's just doesn't have a great
Anyways
Alex
I put 0 out
Mostly in my ears if I can be perfectly honest
We're thrilled with another episode hope you all had a wonderful Labor Day
Set a record
What's on Labor Day
To me is a more
David 911 or Memorial Day
Because this is the day to come
Commemorate
All of the
Thousands of people who were
Murdered mercilessly at the
Play handlebar oligarchs
Yep so everybody enjoy celebrate
And I
Let's start a revolution what was that
I don't think so
Revolution is a revolution
Saturday where we will be announcing Arkansas
This Saturday
North bar
We have very little
We prepared
A lot of nothing
To the audience that we don't know what we're doing
What kind of preparation do you do at all
You know what
I contributed my girlfriend making us
It's almost like yes
She made any
Incredible post
If you like any more details please feel free to email us at
Knowledge fight
At gmail.com
It's also at
At North
North and Western
Dip the right around
Riverwalk
You have to walk
Exactly
4 doors down
Gilberte be an investigation episode
What are we drinking Sparkling Ice
Alright cherry limeade
We're going to be covering these
Stretch
Brum
Let me get the start date October 6th
To October
20 suck I don't know 26
I think
The last five episodes of
September 9th
Episodes of recovering our just David night host
For a week so we're just going to dismiss them out of hand at the end
The 16th 2
To the 22nd
An out-of-context drop
From Alex Jones
Jar Jar Binks has a Caribbean
Great skin in episode 1
It wasn't because he freaking / Caribbean
Oh boy
It was because it was ridiculous it was a stupid character
You aren't going to have
Caribbean Islanders a long time ago in a galaxy far far away
FairPoint
What's up
Yeah
And somehow
You made me hate Jar Jar Binks
Yeah expertise with the guy
You're anyone who's there
Projecting a lot
Other than that Jar Jar Binks
I think he's being a little racy
At one point in this stretch of episode 3 going over at 5
Alex
At the time
About whether the new Star Wars was anti-white
Because there was a black character
And it was
Arguing whether or not his anti-white trailer hitch come out
In a very ugly Circle.
It has been decided that the movie was anti-white
Stormtrooper character
One day get to that movie review
His statement on it was
Literally
Every part of Star Wars is antifa
Somehow our dumbass political
Bulshit Centrist Democrats
Trevor Noah can go f***
Himself off don't disagree
The guys who are fighting against fascism are the ones were fans of but when people actually fight against
Some people like
Hold the f***
Is there spaceships
That caused a lot of property
That's a big issue
Yeah
Alex's
It might be
It might be a male
However
These Are Back In Ghostbusters territories sick of it
Strong female leads
But
He finally lands on it's not we just hate this black guy because he's a bad actor
How do you make
Just watch this trailer
That's it
Let me get into this
If if he is underwater
Their armies clearly have underneath the water
I don't know
Isn't it
Alex
Star Wars
There's no doubt about that
16th east Arts out
The show
I am throughout a whole lot of the show angry it's something else that you might
Nerd culture
That might surprise you quite a bit
Hispanic women
We support the Constitution
A Red Skull he was Hydro with a Nazis
Cheerios
Avengers
Here's the issue for everybody this is 0044 years ago
Look up skull has working for him
Alex Jones
Skull
Yes you do
Captain America
Sean.
Evil serpent group
Ya think about that respect
It didn't really happen but it doesn't matter
So I just want to pause a second to teach
No cuz he's talking about Don Johnson killing it
Furious it fiction stuff because he thinks that other people will think it
It's real
Because his mind can't integrate everybody's brain works like
They're just so stupid
Is a depiction
Reality
Like if you're going to go for pesos
Chevrolet
The guy murdering innocent is
The bad guy
Regardless
I mean of course if you go back to American history
Most people think that the Americans are there
Whenever they murdered
How did he
Copart
How dare you kill innocent
Hispanic women
If you're saying that sarcastic
Don't you
Just him losing control of his
He's trying to
To get at is
Like it's not real
I think it's more of that
Okay I think it's
I think it's the how dare you depict White
People murdering Hispanic
Novelization movie
How dare you do that
That seems obvious
I don't know book
It's this is a weird this is a weird f******
But throughout this
Entire episode
16th east
Combined
35 minutes
Screaming about Red Skull
Pelvic Marvel has put him in the comic books
Working for Red Skull they're going to take off course
Parallels
There is right now
Bull Sturridge
Woodward for Red Skull discusses modern-day Red Skull
Accusation
Other people are
Throwing around willy-nilly
That Russia has any culpability in Ukraine
Russia has to International military base
Russia doesn't put fluoride in the water
Russia doesn't Force inoculate
Russia is a Marvel Comics
Russia trying to stop
Islamic flow into Europe
Openly sharing George Soros wants to destroy America and Europe
Washers open
George Soros fund
Nazi collaborator
Almost
Runge MSNBC
And scores of other organization
Free speech
Hoo-boy
If he doesn't like
White men
Running
Networks wait till he hears about Rodger
I think he's a I think he has
Mixed feelings
About Rodger Ailes
That at the end there is really trouble
That list
Together
Supposed allies I guess
The
George Soros and his team or against
World
The Russian government
So would you say that
Aligning himself with
He's okay
I think he's the coolest guy in the world
He pimps WorldNetDaily a bunch
Stillwrights over to Infowars
Yeah
I think it might be a downgrade
Zizek
Infowars eventually going to go down hard
Where's world problems
But it's
This is really troubling
This is really f****** awful
This whole time the grief you know
I think we've been wrestling ourselves with the idea whether or not we can be comfortable saying that Alex Jones really loves Russia problem
More than America
He loves Russia more than America
Look all Soros
Alex Jones
Matt Drudge
The German government
Japanese
Like during World War
Yeah for sure
We even beat if you want to take a little bit more cautious
I would say
Definitely say without any exaggeration
Is Vicki
He's clearly seeing his narrative
In Russia
He's clearly sitting like you
Presenting Russia visit body mint of his ideas they don't fluoride ate the water
Christianity
They do now towards keeping the radical islamist
4in screams about
How could you not be aligned with that
It's f***** up
Interesting about that is
He first starts with
Russia only has
What's to
National basis
Looking for
The same time though
He is
Saying that Russia is
Keeping radical Islam
Out of Europe which is like
So you're saying that they key
All of Europe
Are you saying that
Keeping
European Russia
Cuz that seems more like
Never never recognizes that a lot of the stuff he's like cuz they keep encroaching
Pretty frequently about them just taking a farmhouse
Russia
Yeah
Yeah I know
Yeah it seems like there
The same strategy that Israel uses on the Westbank
We live here now by
It's definitely feels a lot like a
Are you really going to attack us over 8
8 ft
Aggressive
I think it gets even worse than yours
Wants to say more great things about Russia
Russia in 1991
Couldn't afford
George Soros gets up there
For Nazis
Police activity
I mean there's so many fun lies just didn't 35-second clip
Even his
Is regular narrative about doesn't have him
Helping invade Russia
Secret police
Nah dude
Outlook regular lies are lies enough why are you a
Ramping it up
He's called to answer for why
Thesaurus was a Nazi collaborator the only answer he can ever give
And we've got over that
It doesn't say that he was a Nazi collaborator
It doesn't even
Come closer
Play secret police operations against its f****** Bazaar
This goes back to the
The gun free
The saying it was Bloomberg funded
Think it was CIA
You just making this s*** up
There's nothing behind
And then the other stuff
I mean it's just
It's just pathetic
Twisting a very pro-russian narrative
And even then
It's such a specific
Like knowing exactly
They pulled their stuff away and you're like
You never know.
Who wanted that information
Go through your mouth
Told you
Cuz he would never have
Never be able to pull it
Do you think he read anything about that
Books on the American Civil War
The number of books he's read
We'll get back into that here in a little bit but for now Alex is done
Cuz
The 16th Alex is hidden
Actually ends up leaving
Pretty classy
But before it does Alex is still mad about Marvel
You still mad about them depicting him as a servant of red
Adult wants to talk
He calls his audience
The action
It's a pretty absurd
Cover-more system or
We're on the March
Infowars life.com
Culture War
Roy Jenson
No one supports a hundred percent
Okay yep
Disney notorious
Chris
He was famous
Not for his anti
Yeah I do I think that's just an extension of Marvel
If this point
This episode I'm leaving out of town
Rambling about Captain America
I assure you it's not good
Clip form episode
No thanks
McDonald's Monsanto
Be torn apart we can agree without
McDonald's is like I would say so
Yeah I mean it's not the highest priority in the world
What's a dump
Producers
I do love
Is it going out to break it's a heartbreak
So you know you got that voice come again
Commercial
Until the exact moment
It might not happen
Alright see you on the other side
Just not mad at all I could love that
Picnic
Promote
Values
No cuz they promote multiculturalism
You have all these different ethnicities
Princesses
You know that's not traditional family
I don't know
Turn up my walk down the wrong road
Yeah so far
Check my watch
OS Disney
Still doing doing alright McDonald's
Pretty big
Made a few bucks
Okay
But like this
You're not the kind of guy that
Not the sort of demagogue who's going to sit around and issue commands to people and not do something
Himself
He's about Direct
About to start doing
And the border patrol shipping people
And completing the smuggling process it's just outrageous
Sparkly show today
And I'm going to meet people
Trying to push my way in I want dinner I want you to give me money
Guatemala
I can neither confirm nor deny that he followed through with his plan
It's a dumb plan to start with it's not great
Who the f*** are you also are you what do you have a camera
I'm not threatened
Doubt
You're f****** roided-out like crazy you're good
You're threatening me you're like
Recipe
Concealed carry
I could spend a little while getting into
Like logic problem
Aviv
The issues would be there
Number of issues
That he is wrong on
In that
1 likes
Here's what I'm going
I'm going to knock on doors
Already
That's wrong if you're if you're going with your metaphor for immigrants they don't
Knock on the door
They go through it
Tire proz
Yeah
Difference like a whole folder
With a whole booklet of like here's all the s*** that I've got please give me food
And then the neighbor would be like
Okay
However I am going to need a multiple references
Where is sandwich
Capable
Benefits from your knee
Neighbors
We will see you at
What's the most likely thing that would happen
Is it he went and knocked on the door
Maybe like 10 your Alex Jones
And then they would reference
This next clip
Jesus and Mohammed
Believe me
By the way they didn't just tested I sprayed them with Gabe
The bladder
You think PCP
Some horse tranquilizer something
Gay bomb
What do you think baby
Break
Frog
Do you understand that
So
That's a classic Alex Jones
Yeah I remember that one will have to like redo the
And I'll have to say
This gay frogs
That's a gay bomb baby
So are the other thing is that the gay bomb
Is a theoretical weapon popularized
Theoretical weapon
Theoretical weapons and Iraq episode if I have call
And the idea of female hormones are pheromones
Battlefield
That's how I would become associated with other males
If you would end up wanting
Tupac all the people in Moore
Are we sure our military isn't dumb
Theoretical ideas
And sometimes these theoretical ideas that don't really work out
AR leak
At and that's when things get weird
Because this is
. something that
Could successfully be done I don't know
A lot of projects are really just a
Like
The
Writers room of a sitcom had a couple of days off and I like it around
Let's just cut this clip
He's banging on his desk like a like a gorilla
Overall
I don't want to
The Frog
Papers everywhere
Okay
Why why you're never
More
Apologize
He won't
Weather outlook for Northeast California record snow
Weather on the 9th
Children's lunch bags
Records
I just I just love the powerless moment as of like
I can't I can't go get those pages
Cuz I don't have a plan
Not at all no
That's that's kind of
Humanizing and pathetic
Is ultimately
Pathetic my listen to of him and how much I have to engage with
I really do cherish the moment
Screw things up for himself
Like I love the moments with you
But there's a problem that he has created
A bomb
Turn frogs gay
You probably faking that
Able just to make it look like he's even more mad over all of his headlines
He has to get someone to help him
That's a great like little narrative
Silly
It's the Alex Jones Show
Shut up for him
Yeah him alone
And we are all metaphorically people have to pick up that paper
More or less
The socio dynamic
Part of this
We just have a Russian working
Name Daria
But every time
I figured off protest
I'm not making that accusation at all but it is
That's a wrap
This next clip we Alex Jones
Is Reno is a man
Who
Experiences in his life
In terms of getting him down to
This weird right wing
Where's the
Waco
Was huge
And of course the Oklahoma City bombing
Was very big
Kentucky
I've done a bunch of look at
Two stuff that he says
He's all right about a lot of stuff but also don't
He's right about that is an interesting wrinkle
In the Oklahoma City argument remake
This is not an argument
He brings up very often we talked about Oklahoma City
Weird
Gay bomb
With their number one
While they persecute
I just know full well what
Call swag
Probably
About to have a states rights
Oklahoma
Segal say
The lot of these are engineers
If you're go to
First piece of evidence
Wdsf
I would
Even someone as dumb as Steven Seagal
But I can't imagine that's what you meant
What does noted
Patriot and
Martial artist hero band member of rose
Really yeah don't you remember I'm done I'm done everyone to die
That's not okay
Really
Because that's how bad Joe Arpaio as long as Joe Arpaio
Is what I got I got Hulk in the guy from Under Siege 2
Lubbock
Illegal immigrants
What's going on I got a law enforcement super team
Yeah
Is wildly speculative about the
Reason for the Oklahoma City bombing
Based on everything I can find it is it
Correct Federal Building would stop
27 States getting together
To try and get out of the UN tornado we still have
A reasonable
I know this is
Is a tragedy
Let's deal with this let's take care of the victims
But we're still
I think that's how it would go with 27 States
Or Bandung
Gather over half
The country
Federal Building
Oklahoma City Oklahoma City
Twenty-seven other
States
Exactly
Why do you say very little
More than
I think I found a couple blog
That's not
Yeah but you know what
Yeah
Little corroborated speculation
I spent I spent more of my Oklahoma City research time reading like Court transcript
People who were inside
Dream City and stuff like that
Russell Westbrook
Are part of a government that was a more useful
Use of my time
I am
I did not go to
Too deep into what Oklahoma was doing to get out of the UN
But
The stuff that I read it
This next clip
Commercial
Is when Alex Jones takes his supplements on the air
We're completely overrun
If you come over
What you got
Call
I got to pay the bills here also
It's just really bad
Name some
Lou Ferrigno
His work so well for him
Maywood
The face he's making it
Terrifying
2 Sports
Already said
Then he takes more
It doesn't lead to too much
He ends up going
Nuts
Put some of them almost a boar contemplatively
Pinterest doesn't really freak out too much
It's not like a a Trainwreck
That don't
I would do be very calm and stoic
Splatoon
Choose wisdom over
Sanger
Keep themselves level
Well I don't know if it's an advantage
In the UFC
The Ring 2
To tell your opponent more than you should
But to be a side effect of super male vitality
Different Strokes for different folks
Stroke
Chilling, talking about all this and I'll blow up
My kids are bad or something
That's true I agree with that last Prime
Yep the blowup
Once a week to make sure
I got a quota to therapy for me
Even if that is accurate than he's a mentally ill per
Be more than once
I mean clearly
There's no way that that clip isn't damning and illustrating that he knows what he's doing
Fraudulent
So
If you are timing out
Fake the world
Bulshit gets about once a week
Like a lot of people dressed in the world
To deal with
Is getting really drunk is screaming about gay frogs
Dan wants
Alright
Well I'm saying most
Just would love it
If it was
Now that's fair
I'm talking about the middle class
The Forgotten man
Yeah
I'm like that
Remember you was talking about planning
Some stunts
He revisits the
The premise and tries to bring
Storm some more stunts
That's a good idea I think he noticed Hillary for prison
I'm sure it is becoming really successful
The jackass stuff
But go out there with the camera
Through someone's house
I was like I'm a migraine let me and you'd also be like
Infowarsstore.com
Brainstorming
Couple more stops
Amadeus
Alright
George Soros
That's a weird
Know if
Migrants
Sleep online
Cork tables
I don't know if
I don't know if that's going to be able strativentures real placard sleeping the mayor's house
Totally
I'm going to start pulling legal stance and then he just listen bunch of
Illegal things I feel like that's not a good idea
That's not how that works
I'm pretty sure if you were actually a migrant
You would be put in jail for that go kill somebody
If you if you just
Kidnap Hillary and put her in a prison that's
Right
Yeah and then it's all branded Hillary for prison
Hillary
Is now in prison
Prison prison Bonita was Joe Arpaio prison
Navigation
I believe that we have started to departo into the water of
It's a new series that I've been building up
In my head
Alex Jones
Okay
I think
Outside of
Conservative
Which is too far
Look
At this point
That's that's your part for the
Sovereign citizen
I don't believe so I don't think I don't think
You know enough about them
That's probably true
In this next clip
Towards the end of the show he gets a call from a sovereign citizen
Okay
Here is the beehive
Response
Diction and something that most Americans don't actually understand
The Constitution article 3 section 2 provides for three separate jurisdiction
Equity in Hamilton
We're common law common lies with the nation was founded upon that goes back to the Magna Carta
It's really simple
Don't injure don't harm others or their property and don't use for on your contract
Crimes committed under the common law require there to be a corpus delicti or an injured party
What is the jurisdiction of contract
And finally we have a prediction which is the Los Angeles area
Refuses to kill potatoes and ordered it's a criminal act even if there is no injured party
Jurisdiction that the United States citizens are criminally prosecuted
If you were in the military and the. I was jurisdiction over the General Public
Add to be one of the dominant forms of law
Yeah he knows
And it's sticking to the colonists it was actually one of the Prime reasons behind Revolution
Every Courtney United States today the jurisdiction is
Off your front porches or from school
And what you can't do it you can't license attorney can't actually go into court and make this kind of jurisdictional
And I actually did that pretty recently to get a minor traffic and thrown out and it was a nose pretty rewarding
Turn officer didn't show up for court
Nope nope common law
I don't buy this system I want to read to you from the Southern Poverty Law Center there
On the
The sovereign
The Contemporary Sovereign belief system is based on a decades-old
Conspiracy theory
At some point in history
American government
Refer to as common law
Was secretly replaced by a new government
Admiralty law
The law of the sea and International,
Under common law
Or so they believe
The sovereign
Ozarks
The law of
Blobfish
The sovereigns would be Freeman
Under admiralty law
Secret government Force
The best interest in keeping them.
Don't believe this perfidious
Occurred during the Civil War While others blame the events of 1933
When the u.s. abandon the gold state
Either way they State their lives and livelihoods
Judges around the country government
But our emotions
Out of a treasonous loyalty malevolent government forces
Step that sounds
Everyday
Secret law
That's like Newsradio
I immediately find a favor of the
And then it goes back
The rest of this
Goes into the idea of that whenever you're born your corporate
Because your Capital admiralty law
In order to make you a slave and to create treasury account
Sing your name
And if you go through a process called
Are you sending
All of your documents
Back to the government and we're now
Your
Status as a corporate
Or whatever
You can access to all the money in the treasury
That makes sense
And you're free from any of these admiralty laws because you worth
The others
Sing that's really f***** up is that because they believe in this common law thing
That the founders set up
They don't believe in amendments
Most of them
They believe that every election that's been how
Held where women can vote is null and void
Toledo authority of the president
Okay be on because of all of these beliefs
It I mean it's just clear that they
Respect the authority of
Law enforcement officer
You are really selling
Maybe they got a point
Certificate got a point
Now they are they are they are
Really scary
As a whole
It's weird to me
I mean not
Idea of a
It just has a loophole
Oh man I hope nobody finds out otherwise they have
To all the money
I don't think all of them believe that but a large
Within the sovereign
Citizens there's a bunch of
Related Group
It's like the three men on the land
If it's
Wild rabbit hole to go down
What where we fall on the
Stupid Orange
Are these p
Truly
People on the planet I think it's a really compelling an interesting way for mental illness
I think that there's probably a number of people who are a little bit
Obsessive
Maybe a little bit
Superman
And they get in
To reading
Court documents
I misinterpret a bunch of things
Reading Court.
Probably on the
Or me
Starting for the probably on the insane
Not them
Because I am fascinated by
Ghetto friend group
Stuff like that
Desperation
Enfranchisement that would make you want to
Be free
If you don't feel free sure
Put a lot of their victim is dependent on
Everyone else not
That is a problem
Spiritually on some level of feeling of like this
Human existence
Somehow isn't right
I understand that
Could be channeled into this
Weird
Conspiratorial
Life Plan
I don't support
Is giving them a lot
Fair enough
But I get
The idea that Alex Jones
Some of this
That's weird to me that's not great
Cuz if he believes in all this common-law stuff
It's not a far leap to assume that
You also believe
In the corporate
He can just go to court
Not respect the authority
Or something like that
It seems very strange to me
If you did read about his test
Testimony in his
Feeling good he doesn't respect
Do you know diesel
I don't know I don't have enough evidence
Auburn citizen
He sure seems conversant
To an extent that I am not
He's starting to show shades of it
So
What's the end of Friday
October 6th
No show on Saturday
Come back on Sunday the 8th
No Trump on
Nothing nothing
Oh yeah I forgot
I'm running out of
I don't know why because
That's what it's becoming clear
That's super
I feel like we started out the episode with those
Bethesda chocolates
Sopranos
On Sunday Alex Jones
1954 all over again
So Alex on Sunday
I have a new plan
He is going
I think
But he started to feel like
I'm not doing a good enough job of being
Pacific
I think you have a quiet moment
Or something like that
2 drips a super male Vitality got very contemplatively
I know that I'm making a good argument
But I fear I'm not being
Cific enough about what I'm talking about right
Considering the fact that we have
No idea what
He's talking about
Exegesis
So he comes in hot
On Sunday
With a new plan that is going to make everything clear
We're going to start profiling globalist
Restart profiling from my research who I believe
The owners
We're also going to look at the top managers
Ma
Peter Sutherland
Goldman Sachs Europe
BP worldwide
Homogenic
Use migration
This is the guy engineering the radical Islamic
Influx right now
James Bond villain
So
Not really
He's I mean
When I miss evolve
It's kind of all just a little portly but I think it's kind of petty to
Make Bruno appearance-based
Complaints about your Big Sur
Supervillains
Why are you starting
Also Crystal was a James Bond villain in the most
Number of BP
Do you know all this
You got a decent amount of his
Resume
Before we go any further
Provisionally
On the side of Alex
Guaranteeing the Peter Sutherland
Is a month
Yeah
I mean he's not great
Sure
See there we go all of these
Anyone who is a billionaire a billionaire is a murderer
Fine
That's fine it's okay for maybe our boy Xavier
Every super rich person is awful until proven otherwise
The same time it's not the same as what Alex does
No that's not it like
It's not fair to conflate
Healthy distrust
A really rich people with
They're all a pedophile Network
Who want to
You know bringing migrants
To kill Christians
Bring back the gold I don't know
I do have feeling go that the enemy of my enemy
Team up with Alex against these guys
Long as it's just me and Alex Morgan
There's a lot more traffic
Avallac'h
Not against
Against
Taking down the Russian oligarchs
It seems like you should include them in their global
I think he's
I don't think he has any kind of ideological
Bulshit
Like I said
He comes in he's hot
You is going to start doing this in order to
Build his case
Profile
Pacific global
I can tell you I listen to about
Two weeks more after this episode
This is a one-off
At this point. A series
Of course
Strangers just search
Peter Sutherland
Show you a picture of myself
And just look at this
Task
It looks like a microwave
Version of Mini-Me riding in the Sun
A shiza
Batman Returns
Phenomenon
And it is just popelli pedophile
Disgusting
The scene is slime sucker
Going around you know what when I really go after Mr Sutherland
Is the fact
Of what he did to Ireland
He's the one that. Ireland
He's like the first man of Ireland
Bill Clinton
He's on the screen
He's the guy that took Ireland from England number one economically engine in
Europe for 15 years
Got them to sign onto the EU
Where is green green umbrellas
Glioma
Sutherlands
Poker for you
No that's not a good actor
Other reason for ever the number one economic driver
Teen years running
15 years running
The greatest
Economy
Yeah
Nothing
First of all Peter Sutherland
From Ireland
He is an Irishman so
He was born
E46
Is Irish international business
Former attorney
Define gate party
To go on is involved with Ireland
Becoming part of
Yeah that's what he said
Classic
Vague Alex
Postulates
It's all character assassination is all insulting your ugly
Is a reanimated
Thwart
Give me what you close your eyes and think reanimated
There's a cartoon War
It's voice by TJ Miller in this
And then it comes back as a zombie
Herbert West
Reanimated up now you've got a dead report walking
I immediately went
Zombie form of
King Arthur
If you recall he was called War
I do not recall that because
Insane
Anyways
Alex Gordon
Alex is big
Plan to profile specific globalist
Ends up
With him yelling about how ugly Peter Sutherland is
I'm not being like
Talk about his looks
Ireland
International body
And so of course it's just like that's it
And then he goes to commercial he comes back with nothing
That's it would he be
For the Soviet Union Oregon
Cuz that is an international but I think it comes down
Has Alex brushed up on his Russian impression
Cuz if
If you
Maybe it's version
I don't know
Did not prepare at all
Northern
Come on man
Come on man so instead
Getting into more detail about Peter Sutherland
You were even saying
Knowing nothing about them
There's plenty you could get into about the fact
Bilderberg
He did was there
If you call
Evil organization
Secret sources in access to all these documents
Have a dossier worse than that steel thing
It's Sunday it's a slow news day
Adidas entire two-hour show
It's a shorter show on
It's breaking down
I hate Peter Sutherland here's why
Instead he insulted look
Batman doesn't Irish accent
He got him until
Great
Yeah I don't care
The great profile
I think he thought that this is going to be like
I think he felt like
This profiling globalist
Is going to be ahead
And then he got it
Message forgot
Do the pro
That seems like
You know sometimes you get on stage with a new bit that you're going to do anything
You've got a kill and then you get on stage and realize
Peace out at all bailed
Doing the accent
Connect to profile more globalized
Although Maybe
Thesaurus into a dead horse
Saving him for
I don't know
More about Peterson
Instead of doing anything productive
Alex Jones gets
Because there's a there's a
The clip
Hillary Clinton
Talking about
How
In the Australia they had a gun buyback program
That's right
I am so this clip starts at 8
Made there
Homicide rate
You did it was a very sick
Sometimes it's a good idea to look at
Experiments that other
Have tried
Successful in urination
That's
Growing the entire world
You sound dumb
Hillary Clinton
At the beginning of this clip
Really.
I know that I'm saying everyone's done but it is
The first two were jokes
Showtime they were able to
And the real Crocodile Dundee
Is 5 shot
What did you just say
Actually even wrong he said that he shot three cops
I've done a lot of research
Working today
Oh no I read a bunch of articles about this guy
Didn't realize I don't know anything about the real Crocodile Dundee
Real crocodile and then my
Interest
Ended right there as like
Look up
Disappointing that he didn't
Turn off
Rodney
Dundee character is just a guy from the bush
Loves animals
Goodnight Kim give you a good one-liner
Right Mountain Man archetype in Australia
And he survived
In the wilderness
That's for a couple weeks
Like sleeping in a tree
That's on life
Alright
Taylor Swift
Same character as Crocodile Dundee
As portrayed by Paul Hogan
Like a real Crocodile Dundee Rodney and sell
Inspiration
For the used the sort of quirky behaviors like
You went to a hotel and insisted on sleeping in a sleeping bag
Like these sorts of things that make the character what he is our
Literally ripped for
Little little character details that are
Distinguish
From story
From
Myra
I was going to read this to you about what happened
To Rodney answer
Rodney was killed in August 1999 in south of the city of Darwin
Australia
He was the inspiration for the Paul Hogan character but
To hear him tell it he got more last cut out of the profits of the movie
That's almost certain
Get paid anything
Little but no matter what
The early 1990s
Using her super bad financial situation
In 1992 he was convicted of stealing cattle in
Assaulting a Rancher
So
Does have a criminal record
Alex Jones
Common law
Second 1999
Answer by Crocodile Dundee girlfriend
Variety of
Who kidnap their children
History of killing young girls in bizarre ritual
Children earliest they were adults
When was 21
And so she got
The Illuminati or Freemasons
I kidnap them
And
Let me just think about how similar this is to Alex Jones
She f****** with him
I am so sorry
Just like Frank
It's official
I just want to put a pin in it really emphasized that this idea to Freemason
Kidnap their children
Things to see from a couple of speed
As opposed to out who does his own weird supplements
Diane cell went off with a gun
Trying to get his children
Not good that evening he shot two men and Darwin while just shooting it some Caravan
A reason I can't find an explanation
So we don't know exactly why
And I will quote now from the news
Dave's Discount
The quoting from The Herald Sun
Ansul fire stick shot their Caravan on kentish Road
Resident David Hodgdon jumping
Double barrel shotgun
I went to investigate.
He lost an eye when
I'll put a bullet through the windscreen of his truck
Jesus
The state of his mates face
I grabbed the baseball bat
Oh that's why
You lied about them
Sweet grab this dude Brian Williams grab the baseball bat
This is already like
Given me
8 different bad decisions
From everyone involved
Already
Down the forehead
And that's when he blew my hand off that's a really
Crazy
Hilarious he was going on and on about
Stealing his children and Freemasons and being a baby killer he was just mad
And tell fired shots at the Williams house
Then he ran away
His rifle in one hand Mr Hodgdon shotgun in the other
He actually took away other people
Who runs into the bush
And tries to hide
Google's worker
Yeah I know I'm not sure
Add some sort of
Removals
Was leaning on a cart
The size of a baseball in his power
Jesus
So
He's a cop car and he shoots this
Shoot the base
So I don't feel that this point are all Berkey it's murky but who cares
He ends up killing a cop and then they kill him
You up in his
Trying to get out of the woods
I guess he's still probably on a speed high right
Realize
I just shot a guy's hand off
I just shot it like there
Didn't have his kid
And so he ends up killing One Cop
Shooting him not in the
Beside
And like bleeds out
Gun battle
Persist
Do you know what the
This story is
What's up
To get rid of Regulation
Mentally ill
From getting guns
That even if he was even if he was like mentally ill I think they would still buy it
Use the realtor
Celebrity
Paul Hogan murdering
Poor people in a cup
Jesus no no no no no
Baseball-sized I think he survived
Alright
Don't be quoted on it
I know at least
Him down in a fire
Sly
About
Crocodile the real Kraken
But in fact
The real Crocodile Dundee
So long as it is black people who probably killed that cop with a stolen gun
Of course and Alex's version of knocked on his door
Such b*******
Probably from some weird unsourced blog
I don't know but if you look at reality he was on
The coroner I believe this quote was very is no doubt that this man was in a phetamine psychosis
Maisie Dobbs on this show
Texas f******
It seems intentionally wrong
It seems like
He doesn't care how wrong is
He just doesn't like that it
Is hero
Paul Hogan
Associated with this
How am I going to spend there
The f*** out of here
You're done
Open up
What's going to be the rest
October 18th
No Trump
Cranky butt
What's fine for you
So the rest of the show Alex tries to take phone
Because
Hilarious
Alex gets Superman before he even lets him on air
That doesn't
Listen to the call
Who's being very reasonable
And just
Freaks out at home
Because one of his patent
Just two days after the last one
The must be in the position
Mental illness and not intentional performing
Jewish
Masonic
Honda
You're good
Can you hear me
No I'm not I'm not sure if you want
Paranoid after waking up
The first time
Everything
Emergency Center
Evil Society controllers with the idea of you being like an information
The first time you and get your version of
There's always danger version
A spoonful of sugar help the medicine go down
Just congratulate
On discovering the truth
I'm just sick of that question like I'm sick of people
It's like Chinese water torture religious
Boy I don't think
Galax doesn't
No cuz we different
Does the color code of just made his
Very reasonable point
Do you know everything you thought was wrong is always true is wrong
I want to reassure you that I'm on the right side
Watch another show
Trying to get where you calling from
There are a lot of people that believe he's controlled opposition
Necessarily think that
Hi-Tech controls
Experience I don't
I don't see him as being what the people
Much credibility
At him up as a gatekeeper and what have you
Now that doesn't make
So that's one problem in that
He gets himself rock-hard before he even gets into that call
Screaming before he brings
He wanted
Somebody
Against
Yeah
You heard the change
I think it was
I have no cardio
He like
He's a boxer who would like
Tire out in the second round
He's just not worked on his fundamentals
You can scream for about 2 minutes
I couldn't scream for 2 minutes
Probably
First Call
FairPoint
The first call
Very weird
Quite a bit
Pencils
Thanks so much Alex
I like to speak very briefly about 911 feedback in the news recently in the back and forth between us
Bush
Very short prayer
Almighty father
Lord Jesus Christ
F****** you with all my heart
Strength
Courage
Guidance
Inspiration to a true
Fries and stuff with
Selfless Patriots
From within
The ranks of our military
Community
Elected representatives
New release Direct
The American people
Illegally
Anymore Lee classified in
Redacted 28 pages
Amen amen
Minute
That's a prayer to reveal Saudi Arabia
That's a very strange
Please
Please grant me the strength
To hate Saudi Arabia as much even though
Quickly is our Ally
I am done
I mean
Saudi Arabia was involved
You could guess that from the fact that everyone was
You could just be like a lot of
Fiber formation
I think is in the 28
Alex
Bi-Rite
Call flag
I believe I don't know that
Flip a coin
Yeah it's like
The 28 pages is just
All the proof that Global is
Are real
Classify
You can believe it's the f******
It seems like the red herring or whatever classical
The suitcase
If you were the United States government and you had perpetrated 911 you wouldn't be like well
Will write it down
.
Information Act
Eclassifieds
I'm sure they'll still Trust
Is about where we drop off
With the 18
Very wet but I don't know I don't know what to do
I don't know what to do anymore
Why does
I mean I understand it as a sort of meditative effect
Please don't let me
Gay bomb
That would really
Play Bob Meowth
Is a little bit of what happened on there
Alex Jones here in Chicago
CIA was just police
Dark site
So please just the regular old
Alex
The dark side with Alex
Play system can be as corrupt and evil as anybody else
He's learned about that
Irwin Schiff
Father father of Peter Schiff
Right
Yeah
The notoriously
Backspace
Locution
Security man
Stop selling a declares that he hopes
But he has the level of
Courage
David Irwin Schiff doesn't
To pay taxes
Possibly
No.
Whatever
He goes on a Long Jacket
About how psychos like to attack women
Children because they grow
Make sense psychos get more out of it cuz mine are too strong
Mountain strong to make scared
So that's not internalized sexism at all
Toxic mask
Not at all he also says that he doesn't
Make is good do their homework
Cuz he encourages them to just be more manipulative
Get things out of your f******
On the show
The only thing I regret not pulling
But I felt like it was petty of me to do so
Is IU goes on a long rant about how some ambassador's daughter
Is sexually aroused by the idea of killing him
Cuz you was on MSNBC talked about how much she hates Alex Jones
Look at
Not those words
Bad you didn't want
Super Bowl
Interview with a guy named Martin on
Michelle before butt
Is a genie
Season 8
Algorithm
Maybe or
Computer program
A couple of weird stock
Around the world and economy
Or falling out
He is predicted a couple things in the past
Have been borderline profeta
I don't know if this is true
I'm just going on what they say on the show I did not look into it
Here's why
Because he literally predict that the economic collapse of the dollar
Has to happen by March twenty
Did not happen
Are you sure
Okay I'm going to trust you on this
The Koch brothers
Oh I absolutely or libertarian
The s*** right-wing billionaires
Skylanders
Ruin the Alexa
Kenya
Robux
Officially screwed up
Three countries
Now
What happened
Every night
Interesting the idea of that
We're literally trying to overthrow other countries
Mercer did
Absolutely
So we move on is a
Super villain
Like it's kind of amazing
Like a
If it weren't for the fact that it was destroying the world
Would be kind of admirable to
51 man
It is impressive as much as
Impression
But beautiful
Because the 20th
I think is
I don't even know how to put it
Strongly enough
Sorry I
First birthday
True endpoint
Texas tip of wine when I start talking
The true endpoint of unregulated
Capitalism
Can just sell
Overthrow
Like that's kind of insane
All the Banana Republic
You've gone over in
Capitalism
Destroy human life
Blackwater making the argument
Right
The world's going to
The second Sons
In Game of Thrones
Yeah
Got to go to the 20th
Mercer
Alright
Continue on
I will offer you this next
Where Alex Jones finally says something about Donald Trump
Infowars.com
911 Wisconsin
Copper was Advanced knowledge
Not to fly the day of 9/11
Supply
San Francisco Chronicle
Bushnell
And I would have National media
I don't know what most specifically
I know there were bombs and building 7 and his fellows
Which even this just happened
After years of them denying it
Admitting at about 5 years ago
Donald Trump is bringing 911
To install
Right that's such a such a
Weird
Signal-to-noise ratio
Intelligence
What are
Cease knew that
Was, that's why I did
Also knew that 10 million different attack
Text we're possible in there still
What's going on
It's hard for and then you do it
Intelligence agent
Synthes have a weird
Patient with each other
So they don't nest
Sara Lee
Like there's
There's a whole series of
Comical errors that led
The people die
Legates
Exposed
It's like somebody should be below
For that
And the lies
I think that's probably the bigger
Thousand
But the half a million civilians died
Probably worse
Probably
Defin
Mathematical for a couple days
And now that Trump has tried to clock out Jeb Bush
And I love I love how much
Much money he donated
To all the
I'm a big fan of him promising
To donate
$1000000
Recovery Act
Wait is it not going to be the first no money or
Really going to happen
Probably
I like how he's going to release
Going to do that
There is a
Wildfire going on in LA right now it's a f****** emergency
I like him
No there was no response biggest-ever in Iowa
That's great it's great that we have to
National f****** emergency
He's going on
The people at
Arias Okolona
Christian bulshit families like know who's a good idea
F*** you
Fucktrump
Really
Really I'm still very very angry
It's just let its
Just so expected
Like I'm in not at all surprised
Yeah
Normalization the man
Furious
It's like well of course
All of this like repeated b*******.
It's just such a
Normal occurrence now to watch a man
A month
Dumb ways
It is almost
Smokescreen
For the monsters who are going to
Carry this out
But
He called at Jab
About his brother
Alex is excited about
Alright well then let's make
He's pretty excited about it I don't know if it's enough
Get him on board yet
Lil weirdo
Is that all
Can s*** because most presidential candidates
Alex Jones is a weirdo I can see I can see no parallel.
He's thrilled that someone is bringing his world into respectable to
Stay on that topic very long
He has other fish to fry on this October 20th show
Namely
Hitler
Hitler was a bad guy but
Yes set up by British
Rudolph
That's why he later parachuted
Estate
That's why they locked him up in the
That's right the Vice President of Germany
Same thing
Jumped out and Skydive into Edward eh
Palace
Didn't do anything for
Childish stuff works
Is it
I feel like
It's not
So full of s***
Was it was it
It was one of the royal family who had to
Leave
Because he was up
Treaty also Rudolph have was going
Not to meet with him he was going to meet with the Duke of Hamilton
Lin-manuel this story is
Super interesting and
I don't know if enough people know about it
But Alex Jones
About it was
Hundred percent setup
There is no doubt about that
But
You wasn't set up the way Alex
Hitler was
Rudolph have took a plane
Influential
He was carrying with him a proposal that he intended to deliver to Churchill
That he hoped would create a truce between Germany and in
He wanted to do this
Because he knew that Hitler was about to attack
Soviet Union
Boy this would be real f****** dumb
To be fighting in east and west
I think that would probably be a disaster
Smart yeah yeah
The initial appearance of it is
He was trying to
To save Hitler from himself
Create peace
With the
In order to attack
I don't know about that
That's a little bit of a dicey argument
But
This was set up by British intelligence
For sure
Does he got in touch with somebody and they recommended that he reach out to the
So he sent a letter to the
Set up a
Soiree
Where the two of them could
Get a piece of cord going and get it
But the letter that he was intercepted by MI6
Am I five
The numbers
Whatever the cat
Intercepted by British intelligence
And he doesn't hear back from his contact
I'm going
And we know
You went from being smart
Do not be
We know these things
Because of letters that you wrote
Who was wife
So a lot of this
Double knot
Well he left a letter for Hitler
To explain I'm going to England
And this is the reason I'm doing it
So much right
But I feel like I must
I would be true if that was what was said
I mean if you would take ethics out of monstrosity out of it just from a simple strategy point
He could have saved Germany from losing the war
Taters wind-up dis
Destroying themselves
It's reassuring in a little bit
So
Has contacted the Duke of Hamilton
Because someone told him
That he was a member of the opposition party in English
Didn't want to have war with
We thought he would be a sympathetic ear for all this
He wasn't
Hear that
So hats goes over he flies
Any does parachute out
Bobby Lane
I'll just I'll just lay it on his base no big deal it's almost like a parachute in the Wind
It was only a state
He lands on the guys
Proper
Somewhere
Triple E founded by landscapers around
I don't know
I'm assuming with the landscaper thing
That's like I said that's like from Hot Shots part Deux
Some guy trimming a hedge is like
Captured prisoner of war and
Skis part of the Nuremberg trials
And you get to Alameda
Decide
That based on the position that he had
He absolutely
Conspired to create a war
Didn't necessarily commit crimes against
Humanity
Or any of the
How you don't understand how those charge
Are different I don't either but he ended up getting a life sentence
Instead of death
Spandau prison
Be something at the age of 93 committed suicide
Story of
But
Publix
When he went
Hitler was Furious
About this
He took it as a personal betrayal
Because you cheaply worried about the idea of what is
Japan and Italy going
I think if it looks like I
Allowed someone to try and make peace with you
We're not going to trust me anymore
Put on this public face
I like your youth
This guy
To the point where he's stripped of all his titles
He was the deputy sure but that wasn't
That's not the vice president that's like
Hermann Goering was second
But he you put out the stripped of his office and all of his titles
And the order was given to shoot him on sight
And so that
Made everyone think
That Hitler had nothing
When in fact
So some documents of come out that suggested Hitler
That house was gone
How to fly to Scotland
Mission
In order to have a bigger War
Elsewhere but
I wish you the best on this
I shall
Miss you everyday
So true
We are brothers
Aah
So the idea that
The ideas
Hitler did know about it
Comes
From
Some documents that were written by
Heather is a duden
Which is I guess I didn't notice
I guess it's basically just an administrative assistant
Does nautical filter Spiegel
Oprah talks about the
These documents
Dubious
It's one of the things that I
Legitimate evidence
Chose
And has probably together
To stand
With a
Potential peace treaty
Do not fighting
While they took out or tried to take out
Begin Again
They needed the West not to attack on that front also
But here's this from the article interest which brings us into why Alex Jones
Might believe some of these married
At the end of the war
Became a prisoner of war in the Soviet Union
Where you at
Standby Soviet intelligence
Legends about the event
In the spring of 1941
According to the story in
Google
I got I don't have it
According to his research
Copies of his
Misra sent to Soviet dictator Joseph
Stalin foreign minister
Molotov
And I've been with someone else
The head of the intelligence
I can't say Russian names on the
Reply
It's unclear whether what these men
The truth or simply what they wanted pinched
To say
It is noticeable that they use the vocabulary more commonly found in Soviet propaganda
The Cold War had already begun and pitch
Statement
Stop
Stated that the reason he wanted to go public with this information at this particular time
Was that quote
Reactionary circles in England and America are striving to unleash
The adjutant statement ends with these words
Quote the fact
Confirm the England by promoting Hitler
Against Soviet Russia
Acted in accordance
With an old principle of using
Using foreign hands
To remove
The chestnuts from the fire
The theory of a Russian British conspiracy correspond
Do the interpretation favored by Stalin
Who in this country in 22nd 1941 had believed that Hitler would not
And what's
Britain first
But Stalin was wrong
Let's look at that
The idea that there was a conspiracy between
Soviet
Sylvia Browne
This that's one of the reasons that
If you are a doll
Intelligent
You realize that
Doesn't work
Unless you want someone
To say what you
Pacific Alco
Reality
What you do is the same dumb s*** that we did with the Germans
Paper clips
F****** give them whatever they
You know a little bit of time on this
What seems to be
Alex will believe
Any Russian
He's the Holden
Do Russian propaganda from the
Yeah
Embassy setup Hitler
Crazy that the beginning of this
All goes back to
Russian intelligence
Bananas to me that 100 years ago Russian intelligence
Made Alex Jones happen
And I think the fact that we're uncovering this might lead
I hope so I think I'll live show my end with us getting Burger
Hermann Hesse will actually
Parachute in and murderous I'm fine with Hermann Hesse doing it Rudolph massimino
I have a tattoo of Herman has a shoulder
I love the man
Did not like North
Goldman not a great book
Siddhartha is fine
Siddhartha's okay
It's fine
AB fine
Welcome
Okay
Interesting that Alex Jones believes such flimsy in order to
Defend
Hitler
Of all people
Blick
What are you doing
It's crazy that Marvel would have him supporting the Red Skull that's
The first thing that I say
Yeah that's fair
Marvel should be offended by
You're actually normalizing Alec
Text Jones by having him support
Red Skull
Interview with a gentleman by the name of Joel skousen
I don't know his credit
Albuquerque
Primary narratives is it the government's
Straight up
Government
What are the conspiracy
Like there's
1 conspiracy
Theory and that is that the United States
Government
Perpetrated 911
That I will never not have a twinge
Like I don't know what it is about that one in particular because I don't give a s***
Conspiracy theories like like JFK
Like I don't care
Chances are he was killed by
Not in your lifetime
Possible but at the same time like that's the big conspiracy
You know that's always going to be
Turning point of history of
Did
Perpetrated by the US
It is such a
I think it's just a w
I think it's just like
I don't know what it is about what it's like
Committed
To be fair I don't believe that
Unpack 9/11
Too hard on the body
Rules is whenever doing a 9/11
There's just
Too much
There's too many theories
A lot of them are pretty easy to but two debunked
Impossible to Dubai
Dumb right
Lego
But that's not dumb enough
Like that's the amazing thing about Trump
As bad as Trump is
W was the worst
Led to
More destabilization
It's written
If he has tutoring he'll do way worse
My God
It's too late for all of w have eight years to do a lot of the white ship
Fruit
Fine but
The true monster
In the same way
Kissinger was a true monster part of the function of that is that
They were good at administrative s***
Great middle manager
Metaphorically
Not metaphor
Not going to be able to implement
Two cuz he's so bad at paperwork
You surrounded by
Unlike Debbie Wright who had
In Cheney was
Evil monster
I have a hard time
Like a
Immediately
Getting over my emotional reaction to 9/11 just missing
Play because if you told me
Did anything
Regardless of how insane it was I'd have it
A twinge of like
He probably did
I want to take every clip of everything Alex about the globalist
Just for a moment it sound like I believe it's just like
There's always that moment of like
Like I wouldn't put it past
To have committed nine
Yeah I'm okay with us leaving it there
Exactly where
Joel skousen is on the show and
He's a dick
Site 11
What we're not going to do much of that but I do want to forget
Gaston who believe s*** like this
So I think it has to do also with the satanic nature of this conspiracy
No single person in Mafia evil
Powerful person
Started
Two or three centuries ago and directed and keep it going past 20 or 30 years
It has to be a revelatory
A conspiracy or something
In terms of destruction of Christianity
The creation of a worldly secular society where there is conflict and hatred
Devil
Just wanted to show that
Who's that be great if that's how half of our Clips ended with
Alex Jones
Some dumb s*** we're like
Jeff the devil
Chinese people
Actually believe
The devil
Do people actually
We believe the devil is
I think these
Some of these
People do it's tough to tell who's authentic and who's doing it for
Working across purposes score some other point
I think it's Christianity
But I think he's doing it in order to bolster his
Is entirely
Different yeah it's some sort of bizarre he believes in common law as opposed to law
Yeah
Common Christianity
Proto Christianity perhaps
He's like he doesn't really understand how to tell if something's fake and he's
A trick by every single piece of Soviet propaganda
It's really possible that he read a bunch of like
The Lost Books of the Bible and forgotten books of Eden
Or any of those gospels were written as literature
Write a book about biblical figures
I kind of find a hundred bucks
Like in the same way like if you recall he had the
6 hour long
Right
I find it more likely that he has
What he thinks are revelation
InStyle
That's possible
More likely to me what it is
This is religion
And that's why his scent
Morality
He believes it's God dictating it but it's really whatever he in his subconscious want to Will
Whatever he wants to justify whatever it is
It is prejudices are as religion
That's not that's not
Like unique to him
Muslim funeral
So Alex actually has this to say
Commando salad
But the new influxes are poor
They are not assimilating
It's a very chest out face out
You better watch it attitude
Is instilling in them
Very destructive and then
Totally uncomfortable
With their whole lifestyle
Teach your five-year-old how to have gay sex
Angry as well and
Every video in Europe
Sea anchor in a Wes
Batshit
I noticed from your body language
Alright Dad put down
Understand
Make your point
Every f***
Time you get this kind of bigot
Preamble of
The ones I met
Like they're f******
People
And if you didn't
Tiny little spot only ever interact
Sing with white people
Maybe you would f***
Figure that s*** out of me insane that there's always that f***
Story the news articles you read about Trump
Wait a second
The guy we know it's going to be deported
Realize that was
The possibility in this
Because they're f******
Stupid every single f****** water is f****** dumb
And I'm done with this
Well I don't want it
Here's what's fascinating about
All of these people do
Composition fallacy
While at the same time committing a composite
So exactly what that is is you take a single example and University
I don't know talk about you I would say guys with visible tattoos
That would be wrong that's one example person one example
Hours of operation
Like that is wrong
To do because there's nothing intrinsically but having visible tattoos that would make one want to scream
Or more likely
Of course the composition fallacy
Is I know a good Muslim
Are there for almost 10 good
But they do still make it with the I'm
Scared of Muslims
Simple all about
Edit
It's fascinating to me because on the one hand
Appropriate
Skepticism
+ 8
Inappropriate
And destruct
Murderous logical file
In the other you're not operating
I'm a place of reason or logic
Visceral
You're trying to present as something that's rational reasonable
And it comes from
I don't know child
Steers propaganda
Sends me articles
From
The Spectator
National Review
Which is just
Exact same s*** out
Sounds yells about
But
Wrapped up in this
Bulshit
Learn how to use a tool
I know it is it is
No you're still
Well I suppose yeah I suppose it's something
Really really
Unsophisticated
Faded
Learning how to use language
In such a way as to
Masquerade as something that is
Research but at the same time the National Review isn't making millions of dollars selling disaster Supply
So maybe it's Alex who knows how to use a tool
I'm not sure
But anyway this next clip catering to a smaller and smaller
The GOP witch
People who think they care about being
I have as a technicality
This is just that every time this comes up we must point it out
Then what was it
Was that shooting
Weeks back from where we are in the timeline
But Alex Jones
But it seems like every time it comes up
Was it a false flag
Like
Haha
Being a false flag
It's still up in the air
Is decided
That called
Dumb
Took the other thing
Brings that up at
Because we are about to
Meet Steve
Pieczenik
Steve pieczenik is a Gaston this episode
Very long time
He's come on because he needs Alex Jones
He needs to do it
Behind the scenes
To come on the show and reveal some information
And pray that Alex gets on board cuz otherwise
Whatever he's working towards in going to workout
We're going to listen to
He is
Each one along the way
But there's a couple of things that I need
Point out ahead of time
That are very important
For you to listen for as we go along
We talked about this already
Steve pieczenik
Is inside
He is a psychic Warfare guy
So you can trust
That's great he's a doctor
Like doctor group
Haha
Exactly like
Group Steve pieczenik
Truth
All the time
Never does he try and manipulate people life in order to ascertain
Is way smarter and I think he is deployed
Psychological warfare
And they are one of the reasons that I think that is listen
How many times
Throughout the clips that we're going to be listening
Flatters out
And basically tells him the key is one of the reasons
That a revolution
Could be
Sweet Leaf in the same way that's where we get the counter to
We're going to get to it actually not really because
The
Hillary's emails has
Look fully come out
And that is why
That's when he's going to adjust the narrative that he starts
On this episode
He hasn't really f***** up things
At the same time
Listen for the flattery
Because that is like Warfare
Is manipulating Alex
Exactly how I he knows
Vulnerable
Dan I feel like you do
My psych profile way wrong
So in this first clip of
Steve
With mitzvah
In Psych Warfare
Can you repeat that again
I work in intelligence
Iran psyop separation
I work very closely with the bushes I know Rodger Ailes
So I know exactly what they trying to cover up and what they're doing it is not working
Thanks to you Alex
Thanks to the American public
Are pulling apart for me to attack them in the United
Fake Twitter
Chad and the Bush family total
So this is the beginning of his narrative
And that is that
It's all about it
Because the bush
Crime family must pay for committing 90s
Ears
That I have
Especially about
What
Or not
What's IHOP's
Did he run
It's never really clear
Deeply involved in a lot of stuff apparently
Like he's not like Jerome corsi
Do we have any
Any evidence
I don't but I also have not dug too deep into it
September 9th
9 p.m. about it
But I also think
You no longer really is
Yeah because if he does
Of course
He's not if he's going on Infowars
The stuff that he's going to end up talking about is horseshit
He would not go on Infowars and jeopardize them
Bible Abbott
Time though if you are doing those the
Infowars
Is a great place to go on
In order to
Strongly
Describe various co-ops that he's engaged
The siop is on Alex's audio
Right
The things that he
Claims
Are actually the things he
He's doing
Right
End goal is
Get Alex Jones audience
On the side I want them on
Yeah
Against
Are you giving him
Too much
Credit I feel like
-10
Mason credit
Rectum
Him are the he's not really doing the thing behind the scene
But he claims to be doing
Right
Incredible strategic game
You'll see as these clips go on
Just keep it in your head that the end goal
Isn't what he
He says it is
It is to manipulate Alec
To become a puppet
To become a puppet for
The Consortium
That I believe is behind the scenes of
Interested parties
Perhaps the thing that Rodger Stone has discussed
The 45 group
The secret organization of trump supporters
That apparently me
Then talks about what they need to do
Stone summary
We just get together and we're like
We love Trump right
That's pretty much it
That's pretty much what they do
Right but even still
I think a bunch of dudes getting together and talk about how much of the Trump
Could I have a bunch of guys who
Or maybe strategic of in nature and they're like
Okay here's what we eat with our skill set
Manipulate
I do
Think
It's so fast like this dawned on me today
Because
Rodger Stone isn't around
Yes but we know he will be eventually
It's fascinating to me that Alex Jones
Is so
Stupid
Then he teams up with a guy
Whoever admitted that you run
Psych ward
But it sure is him
I'm not doing it
REI
SeaWorld
Most notorious rap
That f***** in Trenton Rogers
The dirty trick master and a psych Warfare guy are the people
Dumbass
I can't believe I can't believe that way
But it's
Legitimate
Oh yeah for sure anything
Totally fine
These are the guys I'm going to get a bed with the guys who manipulate everybody
I mean it
The same time though it has
Tubi
Intensely attractive
To be like
The psych Warfare
He's obviously working
Forum 8
Which is exactly how psych Warfare
Especially when you can
Be it happening on the Shelf
Gout
Do you were able to do
He's not even doing
Good a job it's like he's
It's like he's just tossing off all of his psych Warfare skills and just being like
Say what I want you to say like that sits
Trying hard
It is if you really look at it
We're at 5 and we have three hundred more to go
No I just think we're talking too much about Steve without actually listening
I just don't want you to get to
You need that
Into this without water looks like
Which is a pretty good down-home
Great little little little
How far is
So in his neck
Clip Steve
Donald Trump
Basically existing in the Publix
Thank you very much the truth of the matter is this is one of the most that one of the most phenomenal American
I never seen in the one we were waiting for Alex I thank you and I thank the audience
Exito called alternative media which really became the mainstream media
Reality is Trump had been monitoring this mainstream media for a long time I knew it he knew it
Many of us had known that and in fact when we put his name up
For the next president
And basically ran with it and this is the true expression of the mineral majority
And the fact that we are so tired
Of the people who committed the crime at 9:11 that once Trump gets in my
Fishing is
Many of them will be arrested
And that's what I think will happen in the long run
I don't know Trump personally I do know his background I know a lot about is
Character
Is a man who will do exactly what he said
If
Steve pieczenik
Is aware of trump pass
He's aware
Of all of his feelings
He's aware of
His
Involvement with Russia
Otherwise
He knows about
What does that tell you
Just that what does that tell you
The ideas
He is saying
Many of them will be a rest
Stop
Exactly if he is
No they are
Because we're going to talk more about Hitler
Such as
If you're not an idiot you know
None of those people will be arrested
Right you know that
If you are an Alex Jones
Listener Hillary for prison
Yep so if you think
If you think for a second
That Trump is going to arrest
You're dumb
Falcon
Well that's that
You might start locking up animals
That seems like
At this point nothing is
Is beyond ship moveset
Nothing is beyond what could be happy
But he
Clearly doing that on
Have you heard In that clip even insane I thank you
Flattered
Alex Jones we would not be able to do this without you you were so important to the team
One of the most phenomenal
Phenomenal American
I'm so thrilled about what happened
So many different times even though it's the exact same
The Tappan
And implies that there's a situation where him and
Become
I don't know what that is
Russia
Monitoring
And that's where
People say how great Trump is and then that's the end
Is probably accurate monitoring
Said that maybe the group that
He's talking about his Russia
Because of its
Next clip where the real problem
Not only will we turn around and get rid of these people but Russia and effect watch what we were doing
Putin wins from a tactical genius to a
Chessboard genius and he understood that our military
If not affect
A successful combat mission
And he saw that repeatedly in Iraq
Dentist and Yemen Sudan
With 14 months basically the intelligence
He was going in and he told Obama
He was going to sacrifice Russian men and women as well as airplanes in advanced technology to do the
Dirty Work that we couldn't do that while we will
Playing around not knowing what to do and having no strategy whatsoever and
Syria and Iran
I suggested that the Russians, Dirty Work and returned
I wish they would come back into the fold
And be part of an alliance that would be quite strong
And that's exactly what they're doing
I don't
Azshara sad did but I do know
That he was there to protect
Christian one of the issues that came up and I said it repeatedly Christians were being slaughtered all of
The Middle East see I created Arcada
Isis and all the other groups that was funded by Saudi Arabia pathan Dubai
Iran
Has no qualms with the Christian
The Russian
Rappers fighting back
Elements that are involved
Serious
Really has been
Iran air
It's pretty amazing
Okay
Classify
Those statements
Wildly pro-putin
Because I would
I would absolutely
Appropriate
Yeah
Doozies
People believe it's a good
Sing
That Putin
Has far larger
Overworld affair
Or are they acting
Some sort of naked self-interest
Let it are they
I toasted larger question is
Do they think that they are the
The good guys or are they Psychopaths
To gain the highest advantage
For that person
I imagine it's on a case-by-case
Basis
But I was thinking probably they say
Think they're doing the right
I think there's probably a moral conviction on some level
Trump has that believes
But I don't know if he believes in the globalist
But Alex
Only does right
Whether or not started as a real
Narrative 8 definitely
Deeply entrenched in him
Yeah it is he believes that the globalist
Russia is
Defense against them
I think he does think
But siding with them is the right to
Things to do
But I think he doesn't think
I think he has it in his head to Putin is just going to free people and then go back about his Mary business
You know being lied about in the media
Or whatever running Russia like a grape
Free Christian defending country even more in
Insane like
What are the larger
If you only listen
Propaganda is a place
Free Speech problem
Because that's not going to be reported
On
You know
Whatever.
Like any of these
I like ultimately what we are
Getting into
Especially especially
How far you can go
With
Christian
Like that's kind of it
I mean
Trumps
Largest
Still supports
Despite
Right wing
Christian
Let's go to the intersection with y
The
The Narrative always get
It's back to
Are the ones who
At least with Alex
Like
All of the stuff in in the UK
In so many different
It is
Who owns
Is Christian
And it is almost
Always turn
Into a
To Louisville
The very p
People that
Christ
Was it big fan
So
So it's like all of this propaganda
Wines of
Utilizing the same tools that
The Christian
Jim's have used to Puck over everybody 4000
Yeah I don't
Disagree
Whatever Whenever you get
To somebody like
Steve pieczenik
Who has
No really
Regardless of whether or not
Claims religion
Anymore
It doesn't seem like it
You can't possibly have a
Morality
If you are deliberately misleading
A lunatic like
Excite his
White nationalist supporters
A white
Who is
Beholding to
A white nationalist country
Creating those uprising
Things all around the world
And finance
Of having any sense
Morality is
Space beyond
Beyond Reason
I mean
He is
He is a moral position and I also agree with yours
I don't know
Alright I can't say I don't I agree that it seems like
If you are a rational enough person
You can't possibly
Or Alex Jones
Just doing
The the only Bastion you have is
F*** I'm an idiot
Or something like that
Like like growing up
Which this is
Exact
There is there is
That's kind
Reinforcing beliefs
Wearing
The
Emerald turn
2 Morrell
Because you're doing it for the cult sacrifice
Every
Morality
That you have
So long as
The cult is doing
Don't let go until I Crusades and stuff
Hey Google
Done in the name of Christianity or Islam on either side
But like
Is the problem of religion
I'm less interested in that
Okay I'm more interested in the fact
But I
I'm fascinated by the idea
Steve pieczenik
Text shows up takes credit for the idea of trump running for president
Comes in with us
Play Norah pro-putin
Position smart enough
Figure out what's going on and
You slept in
I believe that this is formative
In terms of the idea of the secret
And stuff like that we all probably coming from
Don't
Report what Assad
Do know he was doing the
Best thing for everybody
Christian
Asad defending
If there's one thing I know about it
It is unwavering support for
Next clip
You might think
You know we've already got milk
Elf coming out of it
Steve pieczenik discusses
Political presidential candidates
Well Hillary's in a very serious problem
Once again I want to thank your audience
You what we did wasn't back to do a psyops on
Hillary
I would liquid
Bernie Sanders
Co-op Drake streamlab
Samantha bring biting in
Go out to middle and then to break up in
Fractionate her system
Yeah
Co-opting Hillary is co-opting the extreme left
He performed asiop
I don't know how
Bernie to run
I guess
Take the extreme
Didn't run
If you don't recall
He never entered the race op2
In order to get the middle away from Hillary Clinton with only a sliver of the pie with with witch
Genuinely believe the election was not legitimate
It was
Stolen
Like we're past the point of
That's literally What hap
Russia
The election for Donald Trump
It's coming out as like actual books
Removing people right at 2
Before they were ever allowed to vote
Theme like lunacy
Hillary
Still warm
The popular vote
They're just they're just smart enough to pick
Pick the right state
That's where
You know what that's worth
What's wrong
Like the tactics versus
It is kind of
The thing where you hit the spot
What's that
Take down the month
It is next
Basically takes credit for everyone running for
He tricked everyone into running
Clearly
I kept saying how delusional are they
Jam
People in intelligence agencies
People suckered them and this is all that
Because they're people like myself and others who've been in science operations and we suck
This is been a 14-year operation it's not something that just came overnight and Jet was so stupid that he little
Reiterated
But his brother said and runs felt quoted about Pearl Harbor
So they would suck
And suck it in for a long time because people like myself and others and monitor them for a long. They've been worn
Repeatedly for blog
And despite all that they went in because they are so delusional
And in the business of manipulation of South delusional grandiose
Paranoid people it's not hard to manipulate them
What's Putin
And he understood very quickly had a movie in
A country that has no leadership
No direction on the farm policy
Extremely effective
Rolling the ruble
Fidelity to make Russia a weak economy and to be able to monitor
So there's a lot in that clip
I'm really glad you caught that
We want them through blogs
We want a boy which is faster
I don't know what that means
Well I guess Steve pieczenik probably has a Blog where he posted something cuz I kind of don't f*** around
Text who are running
Four offices
Are easily manipulated
But logic
To the next step
Who's Elsa paranoid
I have been
I've been performing acai up on you this
Entire time I'm actually working for Alex Jones
That's fine within the end of this investigation
You will be an Alex Jones
I don't I don't think that'll be true
I will warm you through blogs
The idea that he will ever go up
NRS
Information is beyond
Beyond
Reasonably media's good point
Three or four policy position
A reasonable but from where we are now we're already at
I don't know
You almost got on board as him to take out Donald Sutherland Sutherland
Alright
I didn't like his choice
To be in The Hunger Games
Movies I didn't
I think they were very good and I don't think Donald Sutherland
September 9th
The Hunger Games
Oldies playlist
Steve Barack Obama
That are kind of interesting
He doesn't have a great
Cuz it doesn't think highly of him
Fake backstory
For Barack Obama vets
Is interesting
It's not your run-of-the-mill birthstone
Particularly the CIA at the time
Read him
Forester damn people like Geitner
Peter Geithner when Timothy said he didn't know if they lie
The whole system like the pritzkers lied who was a
Former
Allies of Al Capone I mean the whole Chicago Mob Wives
I already Emmanuel
I ran Emmanuel the whole family lied
So you have a product that comes out of Chicago out of a collusive Alamos
Paranoid but he himself is not qualified
Be any type of leader you never had it
He was never capable of it but they thought having a black young man who had a Muslim name
Wooden somehow change
Perception of America it was a serious mistake
He learned all the technology that we know from DARPA
Defense Advanced research projects came into power and didn't really know how to wield it
Event started Falls
Blackfoot Newtown was an obvious false wagon then we have Oregon
How many Asperger's mothers and kids can be shooting all those people
Even my special force
This is Willie
Ridiculous as a man
Who's totally alienated from what's going on I want to give a mental health label because I don't think he deserves it
He has to have accountability as a man
Was not qualified to do what he did was not qualified to be president
And in fact indict the Democratic party so seriously that they were stupid enough
And I know the people involved
Some of the liberal
Famous Congressman this was a great idea and I said it was a stupid idea
Because he would have benchley fail and he would destroy our country
Now
Thanks to you and many others
Turn this car around
And see what will happen
Trump comes in and Ben Carson
Now I will be very serious be your audience
I have worn
Both candidates
Assassination
And the reason that they both are able to
Manipulate
Emotion
Sorry effect
If the left
Had
A Sirhan Sirhan
If the good guys were the ones who got assassinated it was the bad guys instead
I don't know I do want to go down as line
Do no ice
Distant distant
Is
Is my wild I mean I don't want to re-litigate like
We can relive gate Obama's president
A million times over
What critical
But if there's
One thing
It was a good
Leader I would say so
Just about everybody
There's so much
You can blame the train
Set up
Is the president
You can blame all those things like not
Full
Like not being full-throated
Progressive
Like you could blame for why we lost so many
Governorship
Legislators
But as far as leading a country
Trigos I'll be goddamned if the rest of the world.
Just look at Obama
Well this guy's f***
Haha
That mean except for Russia
Right
Transitive
Sections on them
In the same way that Hillary would have
Hillary would have gone
Hillary Hayden
Harley Putin hated Hillary
The week we absolutely can't read litigate hypothetical present
Right you know like what
I think that this
Steve pieczenik has his backstory to go is like a lot of people blame Obama
For losing all of the
State legislators
If you're going to blame anybody
I would blame the Democratic Party
The infrastructure because apparently
We can't even get
Nazis
Somehow the center of the democratic party is still like
Antifas bad
Like they still haven't even got that the Nazis are murdering people
And that maybe
A large
Majority of the country
Is against
Nothing there on the blaming and
If you blame Obama for this s*** you're a got urine stay
Your f******
I think what was happening more is that history is repeating itself
Fictionalized version of History
Is it it's repeating
In the same
Rewriting history the same way Alex
But a lot of people have it in their head that during the Civil Rights Movement
Everyone was fighting
Which banana
Because everyone doesn't want to cop to the fact
It's a very good chance that your grandpa was not on board with it
It was obviously a majority of people obviously and the
Was there a dictator's in the terror
I can't take another right
Force Martin Luther King Jr to kill himself
History is repeating itself we have fascistic
Right-wing people rising
Been online
Organizing for years
But they're coming into the public
Are people who are trying to fight back against it
Of course
The widespread perception whether it's Republican or Democrat
Is there a problem to
Even if you in 20 years from now
God willing
We will be back this fascism
I said God willing everyone will pretend that they were on FIFA seems like a very
Broad
I am I am 100% on board
At this point is right
100% of the time
Who are on the side of fighting back
That we're seeing
Everything to everyone will
Pretend
And we will again forget now they only almost always a very unpopular group doing the right thing
I think the bigger
The will be that we've got
Like 20 years from now
Twenty years from now Trevor Noah has
The career I would
Furious
Years from now if he has a career I'd be here
Tomorrow if he has a career
Like parties Neville Chamberlain absolutely that would be
Spock on The Tonight Show
No
She went over to
Noah
No the other the new one
O'Fallon
Neville Chamberlain
I think you and your audience
Formulate
Alex is not going to pick up on the fact that
Steve is using those terms
And using that strategy into
Intentionally to get under his ego
No
Alex Jones
Alex will interpret
Must be really smart all these things I've already been flirting with
I must be on the right track with Ray
Well enough
Singing matching dip
So he'll have in one sentence
Something that
Alex
And in the same sentence
Something that hehe
Conflating the two together
Of course if you hate this thing and I
I hate this thing
I hate Obama
Yeah exactly
Exactly
It is one of those things where
But
Because one more clip
Before we get out of here and move on to
To the next day
I get out of October 20th
This is just a summation
Go to where he's at
Able to do more once I'm re-elected
That was back prior to 2008
Horseshoes me idea last election
What do you think that was really about. 2%
Never really been our enemy
Changing the Soviet Union I made it very clear to all of us officials
That we didn't do anything to take down Russia Russia has been a formidable Ally of ours
It is always work with us and in fact it has a much more serious problem
Aslam and terrorism
Because of Central Asia
That's the least three things
It's quite not true
Yeah no that's
I mean we have teamed up from time to time
Atlee true position
Has been that Russia is our Ally.
You know how that's true power was like immediately after
To the end of WWII
With Russia coronavirus gotten with them
Trust but verify
That's sort of been like the best
Position we've ever had
I mean the most
Close to French
That is that
Even then giving the relationship a lot of credit
Fine
I don't care
Meijer
Steve believe
Our closest relationship with Russia has been like
F*** you
Alright f*** you
YouTube
So
If we want to put a button on October 20th
We have the
The first appearance in our investigation of Steve pieczenik
He comes in with a robust
Narrative
Putin is a good guy
Is a very good guy you probably the only good guy on the world
The globalist
Extension
I and some other unnamed people have gotten together and got Donald Trump to run
Also conflating those two
Donald Trump is some sort of a savior
Incredibly
Bafflingly f*****-up
It follows the trends that we're seeing as this investigation goes on that the coupling of
Support of Putin and
Russia
Inexorably entwine
With support
Even for Alex Jones
Nowadays
In 2017
Pretend
We see
Definitive evidence
View loves Russia
Even before he supported Trump
That's where
The difference
Inciting War
Knowingly
Atrocities
Yeah is with these guys
With pechenik
What is the
Him
Effectively
Play supporting
And then
And him
Mystikal
Supporting Trump
Well you see what I'm saying
Conscious
Are so many of these
There
Complete and utter traitorous
For now because in the same way that The Sovereign citizen
Pledge allegiance to the Constitution or whatever but the federal government
There is
Christianity
With Christian
Glitterbug churches
America just not the federal government
It's this weird game of the playing guitar
I'm not a traitor
I support America but America has been taken over by global it
Yeah
Supporting America I have to support
The enemies of America
And that's
Cockamamie
Rat that's nonsense
That is
Just like Joel Osteen
And I'm a Christian but I'm talking to
I help anybody
Until
Well even
That was great
A church baby
It doesn't get any more Clips keeps flying around
Online
A frog
He's been back for a while selling like
Survival food
He has his own church
It's another scam just like Alex
But people have been really clowning on him pretty hard on the internet
Cuz he has a
Everyone still watch this
Let's sing about his survival
It's
Next level like anyone watching this taking it seriously I don't understand
Obvious fraud spiritualist movement in the early 1900s
Who would just go around
And have these rallies
We don't
We don't talk about it all
Especially not Christian
Eli's and scams
Tent Revival
Anyways watch Gravity Falls
There's great stuff
To the 21st and 22nd
I'm going to
The meat of this episode is really the idea that
Steve pieczenik
Just shown up
On the 21st
But the day after Steve pieczenik
A psychic Warfare expert
Comes on to Alex Jones Show
Very prone position
Alex Jones mentioned someone
But he will defend
In the coming month
Samsung Gear
For the first time ever
Prosecution lawyer for criticizing Muslims
And present and more
Backpage
So he calls Armory Lipan which indicates
The Narrative you got to get on board with
Got some orders that she was in trouble was because she's
I was going to court
What she was saying that Muslims were occupied
Parts of speech
And the reason that that is
What I thought you didn't bring that up
But the reason that trouble is they take occupation
Very seriously in France
I can't think of any reason why
Seriously
He was talking uncapitalized occupation
The occupation that happened
Occupation as we all know
This is under Admiral
So if you capitalize
It was Irish people talking about the troubles
Capital T
So
Which is my favorite you guys remember
The treble clef phraseology
What's the other things like of Israel called it
The bummer
The Ono
So the other thing is that
Cuz of History being what it is we now know that
Really get in trouble for that
But you should have been
Big deal
Because you can't make light of that sort of
Your history
Germany call something alcoholic
You couldn't do that
Without getting into hold on
You're trying to complete things
Very unfair
The soft Association in people's mind
We're Nazis
Of course that's what you was doing and it was 100
Percent the right thing to do
To give her the old
Hey cut it out
Alex
Starts defending her on the next episode after Steve pieczenik
And as we all know
Putin was very strongly behind
I can't think of any reason why he was fun
That's so
Very wild
It is
To argue with that
Putin is a
Seems great
He's really good at it
Either that or it
It's just everybody is so dumb
Least dumb person
Seems like a genius
Do you know anybody who's a little bit it's easier to make
Brilliant
Strategic move
Right
Yeah I mean is in the toilet
And when you have
History of very competent
Secret police
It like that you've had years to develop tactics
Comfort
And windows the secret police
Trees come from tradition
Not having to worry about things being Africa lore legal
I think that you're able to
Yeah so has nothing to lose as how he's a secret
What
Hundred billionaire Lake
The idea that we have a Forbes list of richest man and
Putin isn't
Number one on the
Is pretty
Insane like in terms of another step removed from that
They're probably don't know about
But
We know that the Mercers are billionaires
Almost everybody
Which is why
French Revolution 2.0
Vivilore
For all over again
Support
Actually understand what
Situationist
But it's really interesting
50 bulldog
He says this
Supportive
It's crazy
Advent does this
He immediately I just pause the clip I haven't yet
He then launches in
To this
I think he's trying to
Castigate
Political correctness
Put on the other end of this clip I want explain why that's stupid
Welcome to the next level of Oppression
Time
In a murder or a hit-and-run or a carjacking
A white male
A man
He was driving a Ford Chevy
So probably awake
Then you know what was the quote minorities
And this is an unspoken rule on information
The police
Concert on one subject
Then I can Segway into every other
I think that there's a lot of problems
But there's a lot of problems
Even with
Just that
Like that state
Because the idea that when you don't
Hear someone's race
Crime report
Is a function of racism
That's how we have
Then NAB has to be specifically called out that it's a white person
Most people won't say radical Islam
So then the other thing
Hurricane Harvey
Radical
Nope there's a hurricane
That when there's looting it's black people and when it's
Scavenging or something like that
Anguilla
F****** every single person over
Its capital is
Right
Two games to be playing don't even work the way
Pretending Lee do
This idea
Political correctness
Is attacking white people
That's right away
There's hundreds of examples
Is the place that he's totally wrong
Stomach
Thing where
Is
The same thing
Like if a white person came up to him it was like I need money can you help me out that's
Panhandling
You have a black person does it is a bug
Same thing
He does this all the time
And then blame
PC culture for something that doesn't
It's so weird
And is that
Is how he wants
To talk about Le Pain lawsuit
Text stupid
Do I want to have something to eat
You're right on all counts
Next
We're getting back
How can we get back
Hitler why do we always have to go back to how it wasn't that bad of a guy clips
They're very weird
First one
I love the news I'm going to provide for you on the other hand the only thing I have
To say about your
Previous rant
It is not weird
It is a miracle
Normal
For us
It is weird for these idiots
Use race
It is the most normal thing
What it is
Is wrong that's not the weird part
What's the weird part is
Strategies
Cuz it's so
Wrong
Factual
And it's so Steve
Look at it.
It doesn't
I mean
Effective
Through this kind of
Is something that the
Right-wing is
Simply incapable
Kind of not able to do it
Because of the white spheres and
Christians are under attack
Absolutely
Any any
Beliefs they have
So long as
White people are fine
Yeah
Even though white people are already
Defend
Grits
Oh God
Basically
A week later
Is true that the g l
Islamic movement in
Hellboy
Was a Nazi went to Germany
Encouraged Hitler to kill all the Jews
And so
Merkel
Muslims have no part in killing Jews
It's all Germans fault
I guess modern
That responsibility
Israel prime minister Netanyahu
Muslim Elder
Add convince Hitler.
Others really Nazi secret that there is a love affair with the Nazis
What's the left hand America
Because it is
Safari trophy
Bring up the Renaissance
So far in this investigation
2.0 I don't know it's not but it's just he doesn't have brought up too much at this point
These
Narrative
Lumos from things
Netanyahu
Hitler didn't want to exterminate the Jews at the time
Time of the meeting
Between the most
He wanted to
Expel the Jews Netanyahu said
Speech
And
Amin al-husseini Hitler
Palestine
Continue the prime
So what should I do with them Hitler
According to Netanyahu quote
He
Burnsville
So that
Is a narrative
That comes out of a guy who's running
80 Park Heights
Or at least expel all Palestinians
Israel was such a good idea
DIA
Man it happen
Interesting
About the connection
Between Mufti Haj Amin al-husseini
He said
Did not mean to claim was Hitler in November
Solution by themselves
He was like Facebook let me make sure a far lesser number of people will see this yes
Did prime minister wrote that
The decision to move from a policy of
The final solution was made by the Nazis
I was not the outside influence
So
Do you like
Guilt complex
Overcome
Committing a genocide
Side is a
Better things
I mean if you got to choose one
Look
It's almost admirable that the German
People
Cuz America does not
Care about the many genocides
A genocider on our $20 bill
Right like it seems like it would be nice if we had more guilt over that
It would be nice if our genocides were recognized
Instead of celebrate
Right that's my position
I know that's controversy
I think your position
He's clearly
Without saying
Netanyahu's
Well exactly
Alex Jones
Party-starter
No that's Darren Carter the party
Alex Jones makes another
Bogus wild Claim about Hitler
Hitler was going to work to when he took over Russia
Southern Russia the new Israel
That makes Dan Hitler was Hitler
What she saw as their Homeland that's why he met with the grand
Who said no we don't want them here to just chill
And the last few years of World War II
Hitler
Decide to go to the final solution till Hitler
A battle of
Leningrad
Stalingrad
Shifted
Wrong in Hollywood
Great great guy
What year was the complete out of control
Good save
In terms of the move already talked
Yahoo of that argument
Also
The
Debunk that he walked
Mallory Square
Okay
Not debunked
Yeah
I know also the siege of Leningrad took place on 8th of September
That's what it began
Was open from 1940
So
I believe there was probably a whole bunch of stuff going on before the siege of Leningrad
My guess
I whip my
I just bought with wasn't the only
I just don't
Like isn't that crazy how white
People are so ugh
With making Hitler
Not as bad
Like I everybody agrees Hitler was
A shame complex
Except for Alex
Under duress
He's crazy
Why is it that we can't
Giselle be like genocide
He's in the midst of
Committed
Hear about Hitler
But apartheid is great
Same reason we have this
Why is anyone again
Chisholm
I don't know it's the same it's the same historical
Might be
Every night
Jordan
You're the Funplex
Is nut
The other thing I wanted to say was
Our people were I don't know if his older redundant but
That the bushes I bought 200,000 acres in Paraguay if it's been a couple years ago
Military
It's a fact
What I know
The facts from what I know
Serious news media
Pictures.
What happened
Fake dead body
Mythical globulus Bland
You f****** brushes if setup
I don't doubt that the bushes have plots of land various most rich people have
Spots
Yeah I believe that that's obvious
I don't know.
Hi do I kind of look
Dick Cheney
I believe that is pop
Will someone killed Kenny
Imprisonment
Suicide
Not so sure
So on this
In prison
Where's Wallace
Alex Jones also has a interview with the
Ronald
Ron Paul
Comes on
Mary talk
Alright
This promises to be fun
What's the point of Ron Paul
I mean he just talks about in this next year we will find out if Alex Jones supports Trump
In this conversation with Ron Paul
He makes a little bit of sense
It's the same danger with with most
Third party
It's like a lacrosse
Like occasionally
Ross Perot
Yeah that's right
New York on July
Alright
What what's next
Finally get to find out
If Alex Jones
Supports Trump
Cam one final question on the election
I don't flip flop
Yeah like the other candidates
Obviously a lot of what Donald Trump has to shave for a populace to Prairie
Constitutional in some cases but
He said things about me loving Hillary in the past
I don't really trust
In the final equation but
What is yours Donald Trump
Overall The Final Countdown
Healthy for the debate or do you think she's on helping
Guarantee
That the American people win be sucked in it makes him president
Play Whittier is a powerful Dragon
At the same time he doesn't get pushed around with the media
I think
Trouble is coming
And he would have his word
I'm not looking for
I don't want to tell people what to do
I want to deliver the Liberty
And local people take care of these problems but I don't think I don't think Donald Trump would respond to that as
Get on a big white horse
Chose the backlash against teleprompter
Politics
Exactly what the
Words
Now from Alex
That's exactly what the country doesn't need
Now Alex Jones
A couple of things
Better fun
Ron Paul is totally right
Incense
I would be okay with this if there be no way
Hilarious
I hate your brother was on charge on 9/11
You dick
Spanish
Reasonable
Especially because he is making it clear that
I don't think you'd be a good president
Of libertarianism
Alex
Supposedly
Now he's fine with a little
Time goes on
We need to start looking
Is
Rand Paul is clearly who he loves
Rand Paul
Also
Supports Rush
Really
Rand Paul was one of the only people who did not vote
For sanction
Right before puberty
That is true but also
What's up with that Ron Paul is a frequent guest on Ark
Really
Yes true
Yeah
It's very true
That alone. It's not like damning or anything like that
Your case though especially when
We're starting to realize that all of this does seem to be more about Russia absolute
We can get to the point where we have
Hey psychic Warfare guy that Alex Jones
Respect and thanks isn't f****** with him
Come on the show and talk about a Ruck is great
And eventually
He is this is our guy
Still saying maybe Ben Carson
You'll be okay
Insane
Yeah from his
Housing and Urban Development
In hindsight
The
No
Is B like that you'd be like those are my two
All of this seems to be about Russia
And his love of
Bobby also is involved with Russia
I don't know anymore
I just don't know
I just don't know what to do
I just wish
Happening
Everybody
Destroying
Ha
Sriracha
Flea market
It's not and it seems like everyone who's being
Tricked
Is being tricked in the direction Russia wants
People to be pretty
That seems to be a very common theme
Or they're clearly
Fricano's in your
Like it
Most likely
Either either there
Patient their bought-and-paid-for biology
For people like Julian Assange
Bought by the oligarchs
And the people are
Just lost his mind ideological
Find
I don't think he has anything other than he's just
Insane person
It's possible
Trapped in one room for how long
I don't know
I don't like
Literal
That
Like not one
The point is they proven that that kind of isolation will make
Sprite
So I'm sure it's on
It regarded like he's always been a complete and utter peace
But I'm sure it's some point
He had lost
Information should be free and now it's just
Super villain in his constant
Oral also
Of course you're going to join with Russia
Because it's the only other places like
Megalomania is great
Also another thing that bears
Just pointing out
Is in 2017
In the last
On Alex Jones Show
He's had as a guest
For the second time within a month
Not good and a guy named Charles Johnson
Who's a journalist
He is a hack
Pimps for Russia recently photographed outside of the Ecuadorian Embassy
Meeting with Julian Assange
Other person who is there who is the most
Pro Russia senator
Constantly
Trying to
Pitch pro-russia possess
Athens
Real
Those people
It makes sense if you look critically
He was doing in the election
It's not about Trump
It never has been about dropped about Russia
Cool thing is
It's a diversion
Trump is a diversion
And that's what I'm learning
Is that makes this investigation
Really unsatisfying
That really scary
Fuct
Internet
Is crazy didn't even bother because we may be witnessing a
Conspiracy
In public
Yeah in public
Yeah
But the reasons
How many people
Like there's so many
Hundreds of millions of people in the United
Who just don't
No or don't
Care to find out
Yeah like this is this is truly one of
Great
Military maneuvers
In in history
Like to have completely compromised
Tire Republic
At every level
Now own it almost
Entirely
Because
If you control it
So
Complete crippling chaos
What more sanctions
We're already
Non economy
All the people
Continuous power
Not really as affected by the sanction
But to the extent
He still has hundreds of billions of dollars and the oligarch
Makeup history
Hugely rich is trickle down to
To punish the citizens who already
Trickle down economics
If you are.
Yeah it always goes in the bottom
I think that might be
So we've discovered I think
And I
I've listened
The next couple episodes
The next bike week or so
We're going to see
Steve is develop even more
But
Because
David Knight takes over
For the next bike
4 days or so I want to walk
You through
October 9th
October 22nd is the last day
For Alex Jones disappears Misty
Is having some secretive mean
I think he's going down
Or something like that
Steve might have set something up I don't know
But it's very weird that you have this
Introduction
And then
You start supporting lapel
Disappear on a trip
Now
In order to
To just
Ensure that
We don't get too far down this
Rabbit-hole Alex Jones
Hair dye
Frequently
This if it is
Timing-wise
Very suspicious
However he does leave a lot so I'm not
I'm not willing to jump on that call this true
That's fair
We just got tired from carrying Russia's water
Persolog
The most is a long commercial for the alexapure water system
He's going to introduce into the Infowars store
Another day
I think he would have laughed cuz this show is uninspired and boring
There is not much going on
All he does is trying retcon the idea was going to run for president
SoundCloud
That news comes out that he's not running
Reclaim it
Afraid of Hillary
No matter what your narrative is going to fly
3 drop
That are just
Fun from October 23rd or 22nd
It's good that we're just going to run through
I just fun because I think we
I've gotten too serious
The first one
I need a break
Separate no reason to explain why
That's a that's a continuation of his I'm going to go knock on people's doors and knobs
Give birth
Corsair
I need the phone number
That's not pathetic at all
Yeah
Desperate
Out of context
Possibly wrestling with
Will inevitably be his demise but has not been yet
We had
A lot of folks here
But look at what he's told us over the years it's turned out to basically be true
George W Bush's involved
Relations advising them
Just Jeb Bush up so they can
Hahaha your psychological warfare
Just going to win
We're going to be positive
Resistance at that level
What he's saying is true and is being listened to
Broadcast is a format for that to happen
That's pathetic
That's incredibly sad
Cuz he's even
Saying it on the show his lies and manipulates reply to everyone
Right
Because
I listen to
Steve
I bet nobody else
No answer he's never told anybody else
I'm not f****** with you
You see
Immediately how
Comment
And how you can help
Exactly
You can
Like I like everybody
Every single person
Imagine that they would
Never be taken in by a
Until they do
And they are
We're all alike
I want to believe that I wouldn't
Be taken in by a
Simply because of doing this dumb f****** show
No I'm sorry
I'm sorry
Tire deal is skepta
The same time you see
People like Louise Mensch
See all these
Different Kahneman
And it doesn't matter what
Side Euro
Plenty of
People can be calm
Just by being told
That what
They already think
It's like it's like a
Where's like
You were born under this sign and that means that
You're a good person and you like going out but sometimes he likes
Like I already know that
The trail Beyond
At 2 I think the
The connection between Louise Mensch
And Alex Jones
The line that they feed you that you want to hear also involved
In action
Narrative
To do with
Haters already sealed indictments
He's already been impeached
Iraq
The only real
Functional outcome of that is all taken care of
Right and to ascertain
Does the same thing
Like we've got these people like
We're working at on the inside it's all a counter-coup
I mean he's not there yet
But you'll be there
And the only thing he needs to scream and get action about is not
It's not doing it
Give me money and he'll take care of his much does
Take money
From people but at the same time
She doesn't
She's not as overt as Alex
Could be the beginning
Open Alex Jones like
Probably
Lies
That is kind of
Really good point
That
I hadn't thought of
Fight
One thing that I hate getting
It's from the Mueller.
Like you made a good point and
Any kind of
Made me realize why I thought
I don't care what Mueller's doing
He's got like a year before anything is going to f****** happen I get there
He's f****** stupid
Penang people
But until something
Happened
Who gives a f***
I guess we have to fight him
Now everywhere
I think so
Bueller doesn't get his
Evanston
That means every f****** DACA recipient
Is already gone
Smile but that's that
But you know
First comes in a little bit interested in your entrance music is that
I think it's reasonable to be dismissive of these like
Attention-grabbing
New things in Mueller's investigation
Discounting the entirety of
The goal
I think is to look for investigations
But at the
But at the same time and not let
This
Image of
Some DSX Machina come
Down the road that we have no control over
Stop us from taking direct action
To be a problem
In the immediate
All that stuff like with DACA
There isn't anything in his investigation that's going to be involved
Right takes people calling senators
That takes people getting on the street
So you have
Do those things
Complacent with the idea he's going to get impeached eventually
You have to balance it
He is going to get impeached
Eventually
Each time
There is something
Tries to
Has a
4% approval rating in Brazil
He is
Caught on tape
Committing a crime by offering bribes
Well and what happened
F*** off
We're not Brazil
And we're not Kenya
There
Vera Wang
Different countries work different ways that's true true
Hopefully
You know is it
But that's not a precedent for our court for their idea is
I think we're all learning in a very
Is on
I think
Yeah it is a bad
Vision 2000
I know what I was going to
The thing is the lesson that we're learning the very hard way is that are
Institution
Don't save us
Tradition
Zariel in Leicester
Right
The things that are being pushed that are against arvo
Against
American
Principles
It is
Behoove
Takacs
Shinto
Keep
Fighting
I don't know
I like
I don't know what you can do
I don't know you can tweet tweet we can do this.
You have to do those things
Cuz without them
There's nothing
There's nothing complete demolition of
Olive olive
Non-white
All the games that was made
Society
The times of
Upton
Sinclair
Like all the stuff
Is we don't want to work
If we don't
Act
We will
And
Mueller's investigation probably will turn up something by dark shape
Certain point somebody
Haitian like one of the lower level
People
Is going to catch
When that nothing is
Is going to happen to me
I know all the real show
And just
F****** people up
And maybe that's how
I don't know
But we'll see what happens
Will we see what happen
Who knows where we live long enough to see what happened we will live long enough to be a North mom
This Saturday September 9th
This long
That you're going to come to a three and a half hour podcast
You're not or if you're excited that you're going to come to a three and a half hour podcast
Uno
Call Edward I
But I can check us out at knowledge or website goodies on there
You can find our coolest flyer
On there
That's true we have a cool that's why I'm super cool knowledge
Underscore on Twitter
That's where you can follow us
Subscribe to us on ice
Or listen to us wherever pot
That's not totally true Ivan set it up on Stitcher yet
Then you can listen to us on
Some places where podcasts are places that have been automatically aggravated that I'm not aware of
If you're already listen to this podcast
Walmart
Listeners
Stitcher figure it out eventually
I've heard bad things about
I might not want to get in
12 x 40
For not
Boy
They would never have anything to do with us
There's no anybody apparel let him know that we are
Check us out there
Just knowledge fight
Please leave a review
Send a message with love to communicate with folks
Absolute best
I apologize
Responded to
Question
What's up
But let's say
You are a guy with a long crazy beard
Who had never
Hung up a picture
Sure
And you are also but
Used like new
Some knowledge
What would knowledge fight list
Comment
He does have a face
Ocean I bet it does
No try, Terry
What should we say
No
Cuz I know that's the bet
F*** you John Rappaport is too mean to just send
Like I don't want her listeners
Just directly insulting him like that people are
Underwater listeners to
Loaded question insulting questions about his
Various medical frauds
I don't know you know what
I'm making us grapple with this issue I just want to say
Gofucker
Yourself Jon rappoport
Alexandra Thurston color