Holding
Alexandra Thurston color
Jordan
Sit around drink novel
Aldi Beverages and talk little bit
Let me ask you a question
All right now
1 Train
Is going 5 miles an hour Direct
Play towards Chicago
Okay
Another train is leaving Chicago
Headed directly
ClearChoice Austin
Haha
But you don't know which
Would you blow about
I wouldn't
Death upon the map
All right but you know a lot about Alex
That's why I have
A lot of
Puppy for this human tragedy that walks
Chances of
All About Us trying to find the middle
So we have
Put the makeup Top by in case you did not see on social media
We are
Or show at at North this Saturday
If you want to go to 8 North
Still go ahead and go and have a drink but we will not be there
Jordan
Is 264, remember
We've speculated on Facebook oh that's
Chats with the fan
That tights the globalist
Is it the global to book resist the ones who screwed up my schedule
They put a hex on you
We were super excited about it
But we will do it in the
We get our s*** together
Also another
Just podcast is about to
To go into work
Speed
More details as they come
But we will
Shortly
Start
Sting live
And this will be a very dangerous proposition
Or no call
One of the two
Or just one
And somebody's going to be really nice
If possible
Cerveza
Back in the freezing point days
Was just
Comedian friend
On the road
Calling into being like
Cool
Got anything else
So I today we're recording this primarily to
To get that announcement
In case you
Folkestone follow up
Acknowledge underscore fight on Twitter or just knowledge fight on Facebook
But also
It's born
That we got to sit down
Don't have a little chat
Cuz we're here
I want to feel you in Jordan on what's been happening
For the last couple days on the show
A little bit of what's been happening
September
Of the year of Our Lord
The Wednesday and Thursday of this
Somebody
There's been a lot of bulshit he's been talking good about Putin
Very weird as we know it would not be all that straight
Be here if we didn't have the contact
Learning
From 20
Oh yeah like that
Things in a different light
Nothing positive about Putin
A lot at least proved Beyond Beyond
Filled out that he is
Looking for the Kremlin and some capacity
If you're not paying attention and just
Listening to Infowars
Once in awhile and then
Alex starts yelling about some
Something else
Critical attention you realize
He talks about how great Putin is on almost
Every other episode
Everything has never said any
Anything negative about Russian even when
Biking
Is it in
Like
To say this
But the globalists are so bad is awesome which is another cowardly
Damn
Batman he looks
Literal devil
Alright
But we don't need to get into it
It's not really all that great he basically
Play the clip
Putin in Russian
Translate
Certainly doesn't work for the Russian government employee Daria
She translated it
From Russia
The
What's really funny
Is better
On the episode on the
Alex
Complaining about North
Korea
Are you complaining about how the Clinton
Gave them their capabilities
Fervor
But what's really fun is
Actually look into the history of the
That North Korean
Weapons
You see that is all Russia in
PS3 they are the ones who've given the weather
To the comedy
What Alex Jones
Translating
Clifford
Talking in Russian
He's clearly saying
We have given nuclear technology to other countries
Because
The clip is about how
Whoever becomes the leader in AI technology will rule the world
And if
Country has it
They will be like
Totalitarianism
Robert Mercer
Yeah I might already but
Boutin's argue
Is that if we come up with
Sophisticated AI we will share it with everyone
Like we have our nuclear Galaxy like
I got to stop
Translator
Because
We f***** up Korean
If I were North Korea it's smarter to have nuclear
Did you see what happened
Who's bad
Or I could
Newk's believe still be alright
Watching
What
Mustard gives me gas
Ask Doug Taffy
Greek show
Evil billionaire like
Newsradio
Jorge Soler
My friends names
Carvel Ice Cream tree that's the animatronic
Those are some of the things you talked about but
I want to play
Restart the show on the 6th
Because
I love
First of all
Talking about
Some other current events
Better happening Isaac
Approach
Big on This Groove
Live from Austin Texas broadcasting World why it's Alex Jones
Because they noticed a lot of things going on so they couldn't explain yeah
Haven't described patterns where they weren't because that's what we do maybe
Modern history
From
Decorator show
Wreaking havoc
The strongest hurricane
Ever recorded
Mph
Over 180 miles an hour
5 is 150 to 160
They've never recorded something
Officially called
Gory sick
You get smart
Every is every coverage every single thing about this
To just have like
Iran on
Can end MSNBC where they're talking about it
The scroll on the bottom
Climate change
The entire 92nd
Describing
Muslim
Covid-19
He refuses to and then
Even after that he just goes into like
We didn't do it
Prefer to call it
To dry
What is radical
That is radical
Is other input
His other
They want to make you feel bad because
Or whatever
Whatever you like
No not playing call
Hurricane Irma
I read a really interesting article in Daily Beast
On my commute home from the office
I wish we had more time
They got someone that has done a little dick
And they found that there is a Russian
Trinity vacation
Kind of business
You have a lot of people
Who's stay at
Trump properties in
Florida
Especially around Miami
Anchor baby
Russian
But all the time all these people coming over having their baby
Great it may not
Entirely be like
Drug business have anything to
Properties
Two high-end Russian
Using them
As a place where people can pay
$20,000
Go have your baby in America
It's f******
Crazy
I want to throw that in Alex's face
That's it
Any system
I just have a little bit of that
You know, man with the heart of gold
Like I doesn't
Smell
Murderers
But there is a robot
Yeah but there is
Is the man
You can get around if you can live the way that you want to live at support
No I'm going to go against the Russians
Brave
I hear what you're saying
I am so much more interested
And the anchor baby
Cuz built over the last
Forever
I've had so far
Conviction
I'm sure he will make sure everybody knows
Who's that
Literally everything
This is also great
Feeling I've heard nothing about the debt limit
Trump has made with
I've not heard anything about
Do they report
Came out
Leave that Trump took money from George Soros
Nothing
I mean it's on the level of like
F******
6 months
To go Trump is like I'm a globalist
Globalist and a nationalist
What
Any man who can look directly at an eclipse
That's a man that you got a ride to Tucker Carlson
He's working with
The demon ripping Democrats than the the House and Senate
Taking money from the boogeyman
South Georgia
Working together on tingles
Some stuff like that yeah
Yasso
Not a single word about any of that stuff
Rescinding
I actually haven't heard too much about that I know you put out a periscope but I didn't watch it
But
He does have something he wants
Let's talk about in relation
The trop
It also has to do with hurricane Irma
This is really more of what
He talks about in terms
The storm
He Hypes up how
Terrifying
It's going to be and how how serious it is
His style
He's not wrong
No like
If you were selling survival food now.
Suspended most of it
Is diamond
Mark Dice report
About this that I've saved you
That is I've going out
From 8 a.m.
2:11 a.m.
And you would just break up on
Infowars.com
Prisonplanet.com
And they're claiming it's racist in that maybe trucks causing it
Yep that sounds like us
Yeah
That sounds like that sounds like some real news with David Knight
That Trump
Created races hurricane
So let me ask you a question
100-percent
Created a lot of racist
In the metaphorical sense
Human form
It will wind up doing more damage
Irma or Harvey ever
In a manner of speaking he's making
Hurricane racist
This narrative
Because like
Of all the people know of
His ever
Publicly
Repeatedly said
The government can create
Is emmerich
60 Minutes no no no no no
Totally the one man
Completely
The sole owner of weather weapons
Nope Bill Gates
To everybody was on Rogan
He was even yelling about how the government can
Create
Stop order
Hurricane
So I mean
Can't lose you
Okay well good
Is there a soul
Truth to that
Is it they were doing Cloud seed
Oh yeah
Find Waze
To use it in Vietnam
Korea
Application
Could be
Irrigation
Like if you can
Results
Intellivision
Yeah that sort of thing
But they were at they were working on that in
In terms of Vietnam and then immediately after like we can't
International
Like 72
No more
Anda from everything that anyone's been able to
Hotel
Or developing weather
It's part of being a part of being like a
Stage 1 civilization
Call controltech
Just a really
Reductive
Discussing the actual article
It was about
How often time
Female named hurricane
A much more
Destructive
Because people don't
Take them as seriously
And Studies have been done that show
That there is a dismissiveness people show towards
Female name thing
In particular
Alright well Humanity
Katrina was more devastating
I mean that's just
One example and certainly not
Deuce
They want to talk about it
In terms of that study
It's not this is a sec
Hurricane or anything like that
Because
We know how hurricanes are named
And it's just
An alternate
Doesn't matter
Yeah
More like
Person get the f*** out
The movie Carrie
The alphabet
Really alarming that there's three
Letters in a row
Yeah
Pressing down
Another narrative
But he's into
And it has to do with health
Probably
He wants
He's going to sign on
Singer
The other direction within everybody deserves
This is a health scare
Well the only Health Care is the
The fact that everybody doesn't have access to healthcare
Something else altogether and it comes out
And two new antibiotic resistance
Virulent superbug discovered in China
This morning
Talking about it
You don't want to lose
Pictures
Silver
Night night
Water dollars a bottle
Double triple the price Amazon
Dot-com prepared
You are such as for the storm
Boy
Great sales pitch has everything
Terrified no one else is talking about
This is the scoop that only wheat
Noticed you noticed
Because he realize the name Infowars is f***** out
And everyone
No thank you
Very similar music
Infowars
They still haven't
Just in case
So we wouldn't be able to smell
Vaguely Familiar to something
Do yelling about global I can't see
Find history we've seen that evil companies when they Rebrand
Black Blackwater
$6 problems
They definitely don't just
Put a new name on thing
I mean he went from Prison Planet
Little boy but
And then he goes right
It's so good
Silver
Sometimes work
All the antibiotics
Silver sometimes
It's going to say that you should buy colloidal silver
I am also going to say the same thing
Maybe they'll help and everyone's gouging price
Storable food
Of course we're keeping it on the sale it's always on 30% off
Easter weekend hurricane Irma
That's not good
We're taking a bath
You going to pay your own shipping on a f******
Bucket of
Go and look at the food
Yeah the storable foods are not like
Do you like you're doing
Money
And same
The cartoon
You also get a
You also get a car
So you got the sense of it that Alex
His take on Hurricane Irma
Is trying to score points
Thanks for Trump
Blasting hypothetical things
If it left us too.
Uses
Gametime
Profiting off of an axe
Disaster that
He's not making
That's really more
You get to visit from my friend Mike cernovich
He's high
They spend
Quite a while talking about how
Life is a simulation
Now that's
Probably true
Typically speaking chances our life is a simulation really weird for them to be
Infowars
With that like the background graphic
Is just a Doppler radar of the hurricane
What's on the screen behind
Heather just like Taco Bell
Now maybe Zack
Controllers who run the simulation
Things up
And that's why everything's
How long ago do you think scaramucci's
That was like five years ago no it wasn't
Because everything's speeding up the stimulation is
Like what the f*** is going on everybody deals with disaster in their own way
Actually seems like a reasonable response
What is clearly a death cloud
Isn't it
Where is 100 miles away from
Pure Devastation in
The other part of our state
Is underwater
Probably assume Malaysian that's a great way of dealing with all those numbers there's ones and zeros
It's not real
Here is a clip
I'm talkin that I think is
The most sort of
I believe
This struck me as
Very weird
But once these things
Demi I can literally feed itself
That's why I tell people they should really watch Black Mirror
Been talking to them or if they have some kind of
I'm transfer astral understands what's going on today
Did you
Alien
Houston
Cheerleaders in Black Mirror
Nobody else could have those thoughts
Nobody else
Didn't hide obvious
Might go
Flavor taster
Mike cernovich H
Somehow in the simulation
Which I'm there
Dissimulation
Create a
The programs that everything
Dissimulation
Wait so the simulation ends when we create AI
I can fight back
No no no no no no
This is within the simulation
Can jacket
Like become self-replicating
That's
And then we go to Thursday the 7th
The first hour of the show is mostly Seth rich
Kind of ship
There's more
People are not answer Pelosi bababababa
It's going down
If I can't
I can't get it up for the narrative
I just can't
I listen to it
Months ago
Right
She's in play
For so long
The cover-up
Of the Seth Rich murder
Right
Alright
She knows
Who's involved in the cover-up
I can't jack to that narrative so we're not
But I do in the first hour
Is substantially more important
In the second hour Alex Jones
By the name of Joanie Turner
You don't know
Joni Mitchell
Yes
Is a lawyer
Okay
Equip up on the show
I've read online
Say nothing
I bet you
Not a good lawyer
Exactly
Publicizes probably lost in our list on their website is their own when they realize it for hours later they took it down
As
Because she's an American
She's a conservative
White supremacist March
Lawyer
Employment
Contractual dispute
Legal advisor
Corporate
As
Illogical and cultural terrorism
Open-and-shut cases with two years of litigation
In regards to the fact that
The judge will open the case and then
Get rid of the case very quickly
Brittany
Bring me something Larry klayman at this point I don't want to deal with you get out
Doing
She's suing CNN
Because they used information
I'm from the Southern Poverty Law
Is a big bad guy in Alex Jones's
Because they say bad things about him that are on
Very true
So
It's
Silly
It's a frivolous lawsuit
Thursday
Interpersonal
I think she wants to be the new Larry claim
Oh okay
She wants to be a celebrity lawyer
Career change
Shifting
Cuz her professional poker career isn't paying off
Oh yeah
She got Twitter
Originally because she was going to Tweet her experience at the World Series of Poker
I don't think she made the cash
I don't know I can't
For sure I don't watch that
Dark beer to my time
Life when I
Watch
Professional poker
Like we weren't all insane
National psychosis
IWatch
Chris Moneymaker
I watch that happen
The how dumb I was for watching it
Edmond
The immediate
What is overall the like
And there's no like
Isle of
The guy wins
Chesterfield
Cooking
It's weird
After that and people started to be weird characters
Look at that guy Antonio
Respond
What the f*** happened
Call the great to all the great things that happened
I did read a really into
Kissing thing on Phil Ivey
Actually recently
He is really cool
He's involved
International
Insanity
Like we don't have time
And get back to them
No
Reshuffle the deck
SoJO
Is this
CNN
And I have some
She's very racist
Call
That will play out over the course of this and one of the later clips
Baffling
She's crazy
Cheese jump
Like
She's just repeating Alex Jones narratives to him
Which I don't want a lawyer
.
Your honor I would like to
You concur with everything that
The prosecution set
Maritime law
So you were going to let's get into it this is how she responds to
Why is things getting so crazy
Why do you have
Take action
You are a connection expert
3 weeks ago
To watch as
Michael Moore
And he said he made this statement Alex
He said
Is a rapist
His supporters have a chance to redeem themselves
And I
First year at Liberty
I need to know
People
Wow I didn't know just exploded
Steve Jobs
Minot MSNBC or MSNBC
YRC
Nope
A crime
And I can't even tell you how
What are you doing
To create a group
They are funded
Funded by the same people that the
And I answer by and all of the black lives matters like what is that
It's crazy
It is crazy
If you just
What to do this like just
Infowars and then you're correct late but I don't want to screw in
The American people is a crime
Lying about the American people is a crime
It is not
Still not
Lying about specific people is a crime that's why
For slandered what you do it
These group of people they suck when they're awesome
Also a lawyer
Victoria
Orr you saying
Let's ask those people
Oh did they call the get out of here
Alaska
Satirical.
Bullied and they're losing their
Black lives matter
What is that
That's the
And then leave that's all you wanted
I need to get that
Accent
I don't want to put that on her whole cloth
But I think she's doing it to herself
Clematis
Come on
Add knowledge fight to the CNN lawsuit
And then put our f******
Clips that we've played into the public record in court
For calling you a racist
F***
Is it $7
Anyway is really fun
To pull out of that
Is this lady
Big complaint is that you
She saw Michael Morant
Call Donald Trump a rapist
Which his wife
Batman walkthrough
And then he himself has said
You've done things that I would
But then
The other thing
Yeah
People $5,000
To get on National Television yelling Bill Clinton is a rapist
Alex Jones legitimately to go and disrupt rally
And you make a shirt that you sold
That was Bill Clinton is a rapist
I don't see a problem there
Like she said they get these people
They pay him to go on
TV and make these Wild
That's crazy
Absolutely
They're the ones
Do cause that problem
This is what it looks like
This is B like this idea is
What like the erosion of
Free speech
In practice
Looks like
It's almost like we need a
National movement
Against fashion
Emoji backpack
But in this next clip
Johnny wise
It starts by talking about like donations
From this other probably lost
Or something
And get a little more racist
An interesting way
JPMorgan
The financial system
You can't find it anywhere
Is a million dollars a piece to it
In the last month
I can tell you that
I think she's
It's the connection
People think that these are these are occurring
We think you're going to fight back overly aggressive
Yeah we think you're going to shoot people you like YouTube
She brought up that she was look who he married
Right
No further comment on her
So if no other qualities nothing
Incorrectly
Look who he married
Not a good sign
Welive
Non-white
3 Thurlow
If George Clooney wasn't so far to the left
White lady
Putting out babies left and right
Until he was 50 or whatever
Merge with powerful lawyer
F******
Abigail
So much money
Not as many of CNN
Micaiah job
CNN
But you're right
She is equating a liberal
Value or whatever with think is negative
With
A white person marrying a Lebanese
He's person profoundly races
I can't believe
I can't believe that Alex let that slide on a show
What the pho
F*** is she saying
The black lives matter what is that
George Clooney look who he married
I like
What does Outlaw races happening on air
Who in or even has the time Lebanese
People lady
You got
So many people on your plate let him go
Fun f****** real
Is that where we get back
Feelings about Trump
She lands
Spectrum
Supportive rain
We're not in 2015
The water has broken
Here you go
Bushes
4 years
Alex
Mercer
Divine intervention
Blocked
And showing everyone
Yeah he's giving people the opportunity to see
When did he ever ride
Where are
The media so much
No and that's a big problem
Yeah I really don't like that
If you are going to have reports about Aunt
Antifa
Yeah they should be
But it is like every
They're not there
Real fight against
People will turn the T
Exactly
Play the election ended up
Unfortunately
Point both sides have problems
Yeah but one of the sides
Does not cease until Nazi
These aren't one of the sides
All bets are off
Totally
People are awesome
I was on MSN
ABC by report would be like
Hey look at these guys punching Nazis
Why don't the Red Sea
Escalate
Deeply upset by and I think we should all be troubled by
Is there
Did Trump
What's brought on by God
Predestined in all this was a god
Plan
Alex is like
Hell yeah it was
I meant Mike cernovich
Because he had to walk back
From support
About a month-and-a-half ago cuz
Cuz it was bad for business
I have to like
DSM milquetoast
To get in there.
But he has to be like
He's letting them show how bad the last really is
Right. Cuz that's about as deep as his balls go now
I would love it if the religious
Right
That
Natural disasters
Cuz we allowed
Get married
Beat that one can
Well we elect
Trumpet now we have
Three hurricane
Murdering everybody in
Destroying the world
Well maybe one of them will destroy Mar-A-Lago
We can only hope
Still won't be worth it for the
Terrible
Destruction that it's already brought
To those Island
Now that's that's so f***** up
We got to get out of here so you can get to your show
But I would like
It's pretty impressive that Alex Jones
Mushoku suing
Class action lawsuit with 25,000 people behind her
I'm sure some of them
A couple box thrown in there
Be that as it may
I hope
With this racist f***
A lawyer who doesn't know that it's not illegal to lie
But she was more publicly races
Justin David Duke on his episode
Out-and-out like
What cuz she's dumb
Delete stuff
The real the real smart people
No I'm racist but
Let's infiltrate
Then we'll attack
Don't just go out
Epcot we've only got
Most of lawn
All of lawn for
Then we can come out
Anyway
Thank you all for joining
If you'd like to find out more about
And what we do
What that website
JanSport the show
It would be great
Because we're about to kick
Kicks it into overdrive
We are going to need some support
BECU office
That was mighty white of you
Warriors
Appreciate it
There's going to be a lot of stuff coming
It's very exciting what's that broadcast
Possibly even going to a daily format
Verizon
And we
I once again apologies for not being able to do the live show we won't be able to do that
You don't need to apologize for your career going well
So
You don't you don't need like I know that you feel bad about it but you don't need to Apollo
They're good people out there these policy walk
I'm just disappointed
I want to say will do it also if you want
Underscore
We are on
Read the reviews
Get an idea of how you want to write your review
Some research before you just look for announcements
Send me a very near future
But
There's one thing I forgot to cover in the episodes were talking about
Saint Thursday
Pretty toothless
E2m anyways
Also he has a picture
In the background
It's not
He hasn't hung it up
He what
Negative
What recently
Set me a blown up
Picture of the picture
It's tough to tell what it is
But I think it's a crude painting of a clown
Of course for the picture of a f****** clown I'm not sure
F****** Poltergeist s*** like what is it I don't know it's very weird
I'd rather
Behind us
Then this m************ because I would never say f*** you honey
Controlling
Alexandra Thurston color