Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work
Where couple dudes exit around
Is there a
Q&A session
A bird
What type of bird would
Furtado
She's like a bird so lonely fly away I don't
Nelly Furtado is a bird she's similar to one
Alright
Let's try again
You would be a burden of a lot about Alex to propaganda
And I would be like a rabbit
Jordans
Be going over a thrilling
Episode of my investigation into what happened to Alex
2015 Donald Trump for president
I think it's dumb or are you just are you done
I'm done
No I am I don't think we're done done
Let's say
Questions that I started this investigation with are officially a
Okay I don't have anymore questions about why Alex Jones
Join team Trump
Yep
Big part of it
Vladimir Putin
Wow
For those of you who've been following along to every at the last 17 install
Thought was going to be maybe two episodes
I thought 5
Where we last left off
In full
Support of Putin
Still not all the way
In support of Russia
Aleutian in the past
Three or four months
Saying that he likes what he says but he doesn't trust
He doesn't think you can trust him because he's
Supported Hillary in the past
Bob connection
Geraldi's
Alex Jones
Fully supports
Vladimir Putin and Russia and all of their action
In the world
Is clearly swayed by Russian propaganda
Yet
Supported
So also where we last left off
David Knight was hosting for about a week
So really the question
10 is like when does artiste
That is a question
That's pretty much
Actually know the answer to that
Okay
It's pretty clear
Moment that happen
All the sudden Alex says
Spoiler alert little bit ahead of Russian State meeting
My cards too hard
The date
October 27th 2015
To November 9th
L2050
About two years
And it would involve
Before we get into our investigation today in earnest
I'd like to give a shout out if you want what's going on out there
Thank you so much for joining up with
Congratulation
Become a pilot
You may do so
Bygone or website knowledge fight.
Please support the show button
Also
Before we start actually don't have to donate you just click the button
Jerome and then
Whatever shows up tortoiseshell button
I'm looking for a button
Route right button
Guaranteed
Anyone
Also I need to make this announcement we've been flirting and teasing around the idea of something big coming
Here's what it is
We are now going to be broadcasting live
Every night at 8 p.m. central
Not every night
Monday through Thursday at least
Brett from 8?
Live on the internet
Video audio all of it
You can find our feed
Start TV / knowledge fight
We are going to be going over current-day Alex Jones
Keeping up with what bulshit key spelling
Everyday we're going to try and make this this knowledge fight more robust
Take it into the infowar
Arena
You're very excited so excited
Very excited
It's Freight
For years and years I've wanted to do a first of all alive thing I wanted to do a radio show
Ability
To take calls and stuff like that
Like this possibility that we can
Get it into that
Sort of thing as opposed to us sitting around for 3 hours and then releasing it the next day or at
Because
With the with the 20s
15 investigation
No fine we released it two days later and
Present-day episode
You release it the next time you're like what
Exactly like how the New York Times in the washing
Composer like
Trump is great now
Lunatic but he's an independent not
Another one
Compelled to do this now because
Enter really interesting.
That will tap
Alex Jones is
The Donald Trump
Because of the debt ceiling situation
People saying the Trump is he's a true independent he's working with the Democrats
Can hate people I hate the Great
But it's
The mind-boggling thing is like I kind of get it because
Dude
We have a Nazi in the White House
Everyday be like
Guys not
He's a Nazi
Nothing at are you paying attention
So they're just trying to get like a a different narrative
It much like we end up being a lot of the time with Alex
Alex's fine today
Is it true independent now he's right right
Working with the Democrats
F*** you watching
Painted Post New York Times I expected
Review
Post you're supposed to
We hope for more
Joining me on Tonight Show live at 8 p.m. central
Because of your work schedule at the comedy
Very much underestimated Oradea
The middle of the Pacific what time is it in Bucharest
It is
4 p.m. or 4 a.m.
Simultaneously
If you'd like to join us there that would be wonderful because of your work schedule with the stand-up comedy this month there will be other
Other folks
Riggs will be coming in this week
And other folks
Tubidy
Determined
I meant yeah as my schedule changes I will be able to drop in more
I'm crazy
Functionality
Take phone calls
Call Landon said having to come all the way over here
All the way over here from my girlfriend
Get to the investigation that's what people want to hear they want to hear some Alex Jones
Yeah I don't know if they do
Like a review on iTunes
Too much Alex Jones love the guys talk
Hate it with Alex Jones
Why is this Alex Jones Show
We're starting on the 27th
This is coming off
A good almost week of David Knight hosting lilacs is on a vacation with people
Navigating it something
But you never says what and it's unimportant
The 27th Alex Jones shows back up
How to get sonair
It's one of the least inspired 3 hours of broadcasting I've ever heard in my life
If you look at my notes this episode sucks
You just as like
I was walking around the mountain
Panda
People love me
Just kept coming up to me and Alex
I don't appreciate of the common people I
Yeah it's so I don't have any
Parable
An episode
Part of the body of it
Is the interview with the guy who's the vitamin lawyer
The vitamin
Yes Galaxy supplements illegal
Couch
Like illegals TSA
And we move along to the 28th
Which is where we will start
Earnest
Alex Jones
DC
Brigade
Really don't like political correctness
Terrible
Starts off the show
A list off a number of political correctness grievances that he has I want you to keep track of how many
Free Speech now on the campuses
Call people out a bunch of bullets
Bullies
Political correctness
It's going.
Does Caitlyn Jenner
You are not
Mother father yes I am
I don't care
None of those are real
None of those are real thing
When you hear
People on camps
Campuses are
Eating to see who can destroy more
Of the language
I remember what I was
College
No one was able to use any of verbs
IHOP
Passive voice
Make it a noun god dammit
That's what I did in college
I don't know if I was
But also
Applying all Scrabble
No proper nouns
Talking about it any given
No capitalization
This is
But I do
I see a debate team like a debate competition where you got three people on either side one of them blocks up to a podium
Here's why we shouldn't use the word mother
Cuz it's dumb
Next
Mothers are
I love those mother and I will raise
We shouldn't use the word mom
Mom
Call Mom
Totally fine
So fascinated by his ideas
You telling me dress like Caitlyn Jenner
I'm going to
I don't think he does
Yeah I think he's like I can't people are saying that you can't mock trans people
Thor costume
And either I will
Around Halloween
At this point that's why that was
On a real tear
About misunderstanding why
Mc4 minority group costumes are inappropriate
He's like
Taco party
It's bit more wisely.
Don't turn a group into a costume
No we're not saying
And also you are criticizing Obamacare
Also known as ever said you can't use a brown
The guy in Seattle the terminology brown bag was it
Has a racially-charged history and that's true
You can still use Brown Bags if you want
The brown bag
Themselves that are the
Problem no
No you can't
You can't be angry at a bag
No we can't we can't spend this much time on One Clip we got some
We're coming to telling me I can't defend myself I will
Let me tell you something
I don't know
I'll see you in hell
Alex Jones that has found out that the Southern Poverty Law Center
Has put out a new article
From the
Demonizing the conspiracy myths
Imaginary situation
Call Margie
The imaginary
Paradise
That there is an agenda 21 to restrict resources so the Southern Poverty Law Center put out a long article
Debunking a ton of Alex Jones of narrative
Specifically targeted at Alex Jones these are these right-wing
Curious.
Already
F******
F*** you guys
Love
The conservative
The splc because it's always like
Support for people and free speech and Alexa
Just like the ACLU
Do a lot of good work
They represent a lot of pee
People who
It's need to get to Too Much depth
It's not like he's starting
Free People
Pay attention to the narrative
Puts out
He's starting to get a little bit scared of his own position
We could have pointed out
Much closer to real time
How much
He is just supporting Rush
And I don't think people did a good job of
Expressing that back then
You were telling me this later earlier
Which is like
If it was
Something where
It was much
More prevalent
On what
Pay attention
But because
Kind of Justice
Small part of
Every broadcast
Yeah
Skip over
F*** is you talkin about sure because a lot of things
He's praising Putin for are real
Barbecue does believe
He's influencing Russia
Belief
You know when you're getting trick that's how you rationalize
You're being
Do you think like
I won the first round in this guy
And then you turn around and disappear
It's too easy
That's that's exactly what's going on I can't wait
There's a couple clips that I have then I'm going to play
Strfkr
Dammit
In this episode
Out of the gate
Cuz B
Equip is
F***** up
Alright this is Alex
What were the clips. I'll explain why I think
Easter videos funny
But the rest of it is not funny at all
It's Alex proving he's kind of a dick
The story he tells might not be
Be true also story is true
He's a f******
Dick needs to mind his own goddamn business here some parents
I was at the gym yesterday
Terrible oh my gosh
I don't know why these friends and what happened
Such and such
Baby just died it was just a year old and
It died yeah she's with the letter buddy about it
He died of SIDS
I didn't exist
I used to take people's kids
I should take people to other children when they had a sudden infant death
They claimed it was shaking
I know yeah
Ask him if they want in their second round of shots
Cuz you know she'll just closely associated in Australian government studies and others
Not true
Yeah I think I've heard of it
I don't mean to get your business you're just talkin about a dead baby you might want to look into it yourself and warn some people
And all the time I heard about
Yeah
Other
Most autistic
Children
1%
Country
And they almost always decline
After they don't talk for a few days
Lobotomy
Feels real good
Ready for those preemies 7 months 8 months 6 months they're fine they're breathing they're getting better
After their couple days doctor comes
Relations full regimen
7 shots
And the nurses back doctor
Bioethics board
They're going to stop breathing summer going to die the doctor says
You know policy
I can't miss shots dumb shut down the spot other still on the respirators
Bottom can't make it because we're at 11 country
Arab country
But he's relish
To a lady whose
I know
Your baby just died but let me tell you
And also
I don't care about your baby
I just want to push my agenda
Useful situation for me to lie to you
Some of these
It creates in my head the idea for a cartoon
Where it's just Alex
Buddy at the people's business
You got talk about baby
Call my babies in the hospital
I mean
Something like that
Nosy-ass anti-vaxxer cartoon Alex Jones is kind of funny but in the real world it's not
I love the idea anytime a baby goes into the hospital he
Thinks it's vaccine
Yeah not like well baby resistance
Babies
Okay if you're looking for
Babies were stolen by f******
Coyotes
But I'm done with
Fish it if you hate
Hospitals and medical science
F****** don't go and shut
The fuk up a couple of things that we should discuss just in terms of
His bulshit narratives
Attached
Or in any way related
Vaccination
There are a couple studies has been
Thoroughly debunked
Junk science
They didn't follow the science
Inclusions that work there to be
Concluded
Conspiracy theory that the vaccines cause autism is Italy
Nothing they kill your kids
Dump will now that's
Premature babies
7 shot
Another another interesting issue a lot of people believe anti-vaccination things
Because of court case
Should have been one
By people whose children have been hurt by the
There's a thing called the national vaccine injury compensation
Sensation
There's a vaccine Court
That was specially setup
This court is rigged
In favor of people make
Intentionally so
Because
The government w
To pay people
Not to silence them
But they want to make it easier
Sensation for being hurt
Buy vaccine
Because there is
Negative side effects
Probably this court doesn't necessarily need you to prove scientifically that the vaccine cause
Your baby to be hurt or to die they just
Need to have a preponderance of the evidence
Like it's a civil court
And so there have been court cases that have come through the n v i c p
And people have
Science has proven this thing
Winning
Just something that was set up
In order to compensate people for their loss
Without proving science
Typically anything
Now this is something that's super into
Sing to me
Government they set it up specifically that way
Here here
Complained
Is that whatever you talk about vaccines and killing babies
Read the insert it says it can cause diabetes or whatever
Aspirin bottle
No fault situation
For Zach's
In terms of like drug companies won't be held responsible
For vaccines Bedford
And that's done also intentionally by the government and I'll read this article on science blogs.com
History
In the early 1980s in the report publicized by a news report
And later a book by Harris Coulter and Barbara Lowe Fisher
I called DPT a shot in the dark
That the wholesale DPT vaccine was linked
Encephalitis
Hop lot of product liability lawsuits was on the verge of bringing the US vaccine program to its me
Later studies exonerated
Especially a large case-control study
But those studies did not come out until the 19th
Even though existing evidence of the
It did not clearly rule one out
As a result vaccine manufacturers heading
Increasingly difficult difficult
Obtaining liability
More and more of them stop making Wholesale Depot
Vaccine
Congress ultimately was forced to intervene past
The national childhood vaccine injury Act
1980s
Which established the Federal no faults
Compensate victims
Of injury
Recalls by mandated vaccine
So
There's a situation where people
That's a good thing
4 people could not prove nor disprove a link
Between a vaccine and
F****** weight into
Connection if you destroy company
You destroy the progress of science
The people could end up getting
People might have taken down an industry
But they almost
And the government had to
Step in to create these courts
And to create this no-fault system so intentionally they set it up
So the people who make the vaccine wouldn't
Be punished in the off-chance of these
Hammocks
Yeah that they might not be guilty of
And the government would pay everything
Yeah so it is
Actually a good system
It's a very good system but people use things that are found
That are not
Civil cases basically
Treat them as if they are sick
I'd like the one that Coretta Scott King
So the other uses there is he says the 80
Plus percent of the autistic people are male
That is
Bananas
Well it's accept this is also super interesting if you look into it
The reason that there is
That most autistic people are male
Classify
Boys and girls
There's a two-prong
That's a piece of one of
What issues is in the early days
Autism
Almost
Everybody they studied were do
That's how both
Pacific studies
But especially in the case of
And one of the reasons for that
Is because the weight male
Autism
Is incredibly obvious
Symptoms are
More
Clear
There have been
People who
One of the leading theories about that
Is that women have whether it's sociologically in Grain or
Have a higher ability to mimic
Social cues
Amer able2know
Instinctively what's appropriate
And not scream out in
It like that
Beyond that
Studies have
Started to be done that are in Decatur
That
Stuff like anorexia nervosa self-harm social anxiety views more feminine
Related
Conditions
Will know I mean all those things
Males can have but there is
Women
People are starting to understand and look at it from the perspective of
Those
Is our female autistic
Symptoms right they may not
Habanero
Right
Recalled Naruto
Okay
Yeah I would
Come in that forever
Well
Beyond that those are some of the reasons Alex's
So
He's full of s*** but also
More importantly
People f******
Especially if they're big
Do your f******
Lyft get out of there
So just take on
Science
And he has no understanding of some of the nuances of
But they'll let's get
To him discussing
Houston
In terms of the product
Sal's
What
So that sucks
Yep as long as you drink 67 oz of olive oil in lay on your right side for an hour
No good
If you are on
Take 46
Talk to your doctor before you get a chance
Green and black stones come out of
You don't want to tell them
Just put them right on a desk
Can be like
Good
So what's going on with Leann
Has been
St.Louis
Where there is a fire burning Underground
Near nuclear waste
Or something along those lines
Skype going
I think I vaguely recall the story
I'm not sure if they're angle on it is a crack
I don't care
Because they can never get her Skype connection
Together
I will go to Leanne and Medicaid
So the app says over and over again
Like as if
He thinks she's going to die
To clear himself over and over again
Every single time he brings it up he points out it wasn't my idea
Cuz he picks just going to go bad
And they can never get around
Of course they have sex
In a bar across
Might as well
We have a visit from
George Noory
Coasttocoastam
Alright As We Know
From
I think it's like midnight
3 a.m. or something like that
They talk about aliens
They talk about Ancient Aliens
Love it. You talk about all that
Pyramids hologram probably talk about
Probably talk about
I imagine
Middle Eastern Arrow
And the reason he's on
Might surprise you
We have forgot
Morality
And what this country was all about that and I think it's just crazy Alex
As a nation inducing
White screen
The
Presidential push to try to get me to run for office
You are absolutely right
But I'm really independent
However
If you can run for president of the United States you really have to be a Democrat or
Nando's party
Because that's what Carter's the biggest faults
There has been a group
I did consider that
But have to take a leave from Coast-to-Coast and I'm not sure I want to do that
I probably could
Call car service.
The listeners
The debates not a chance
Coast to Coast
A.m.
What's the Nielsen ratings of radio shows Indiana
He is going to easily win
The Democratic
Even though he is
Not a republic
Kenora Democrat libertarian we all know how Democrats
Love libertarian
He's non-partisan
Even real
Reality is a couple things that he believes it would fly over well with the Democratic Party
Denomination
Bluelivesmatter
Make perfect
Everybody loves thrilled with those positions
Yelling all the time about how we
We need fewer vaccinations
Unless oversight of police
Guys
I'm going to announce my camp
For president right now in
In 2020
My main platform will be bring back polio
Big polio white predicate
Can't pronounce
But
So George Noory
He expands some of his position
One of them
Get rid of income taxes just make it available
No fire station
If your house burns down you better
A tip on hand for the fire department
Remember
Damn that there was a time in our history where they're actually
Competing Fire Department
Sabotage each other
Worcester burn down
You had to
And if your neighbor bought fire insurance they would protect your neighbor's house from the fire of your
F****** insane competition
Pre-market
Prosperity libertarianism as a whole is like
The elements of a we've done before elements
You're wrong
Prove it
Scientific
Clear mathematically
We can just go back
15 years and he likes me
This is what happened
When the dump
Believe
It's actually practice
We'll figure it out better technology
Piece of George noory's campaign is about
Empi defense
Alright okay
Inordinate amount of time talking about how vulnerable
Ocean's 11 news like
Please work write something like that
Another
Interview
Which is our friend Max
Who we know is the economist
Cryptocurrency
Alex
I am giving away free money today
Estart koin.com
I'm giving away free money to your listener
Day
As a way to introduce them
2 cryptocurrency
So that's how it's going
It's not great
And he's giving away buck
Giving away magic
It's very easy to give away worthless
Giving away this air
Everybody that goes to knowledge buy.com is allowed to have
As much as they want
I just want to get you guys into breathing
The first
But I will be charging you
Small
Obviously
But this is not an appearance
Also there's a
Quarterback
So that like
Is the only way to preserve your wealth is nonsense
Buy gold
Transferred into max
Also oldies
Dubai gold sell gold
Like Peter Schiff sells gold
Gcn
The guy who syndicate's Alex Jones Show
Sells gold
Please remember not just the owner of the member
Just selling gold
They're made of
Yeah they're Midas
Yeah so that's the end of October 28th
Gallant October 29th
Something interesting happened on the
Of October 28th
And that is
CNBC
Presidential debate
Republican primary debate and if you recall
It did go well disaster
Intellivision
Import of how
Understood for
Weeks Bunch even years
The flashlight with the CNBC
Republican
Moderated by CNBC
Is Abaddon
Pretty much instantly
This is a Polaroid moment
Where you don't have to wait more than just a few seconds
After the debate I was sitting there watching it with family
And children
And even let me
My thirteen-year-old son
Watching the coverage
Infowars
Vagina Magic
Do that
And my children said
The reporters
And trying to make
Republican look stupid
But they looked stupid
They didn't show
My thirteen-year-old had to say about it
In-depth analysis from a 13 year old
Good work
So do your multiplication homework
I let my seven-year-old daughter watch one of the most homophobic
Racist
Things that I could possibly allow her to watch a bunch of
A f******
People more
That's what that debate was
The contest
To see who could destroy more length
If you remember this has been on it
Infowars
You're way past parents
You're right
Alex has more to say
Into the issues that they communicated
Three-year-old kid thought okay
He wants to critique the media
And how they behave
You can really tell there's something he wants
Disabled
Establishment
Softball questions
The Republicans
Control
Was crystal
Clear
That this was all rigged attempt
To derail
Was a fiasco
It was a disaster
It was a train wreck
It was an implosion
For them
Sycophantic
This weekend I was hiking in the mountains of South Texas and it really get married
Call
Talk about
What should we call the Decepticon
Extreme extreme
Collaborator
Prostitute
Corporate media
I'm just throwing out a bunch of
Actually fit
What
Call butter
Concentrated milk fat
You call it but
About another example
Chocolate
We can dance sugar
Coco
You call it
You got a third
Call Paula Horsemen are on the side of the road
Some scientific name for the
Way to bring it home
The enemy
They are the deceivers
They are the enemy
Propaganda arms
It's my spiritually wrong
Tireli Reno
Just giant corporate entities and the corporation
Have pretty much said
Weokie
These are terrible where is Wilmington from Israel
F******
Stupid
You can be right for the wrong reason
What you're feeling
Alex
You're an idiot
I agree with what you
But what you mean is dumb
I don't agree with what you mean but you're literally point is correct
Small way
I really think that he's like
You want
Donald Trump will pick up
Interesting now little parallel there
I'm going to skip this
I will say
The one thing that
He is
We write about
Is the
During the campaign
Media
Failed us on a level I don't think I've ever seen
Ara
All the all the blame we want to put on the
Nazis
The media wanting a story
Wanting a an interesting
Campaign wanting that horse race big
Problem and one of the big read
The Trump was elected
Asking Trump question
Like Direct
What teams are now if somebody just asked Trump
What something means like
Trump
What is what does DACA
Stand for
Anybody like
4 North Korea
He doesn't know he doesn't know f****** anything and if you would have just
If you would just like
Stop talking about
How he sounded
And started talking about how
He knows
F****** nothing
Yes baby we would have had a better shot
No Quarter
Course not just because
Critiques of the media doesn't mean we agree
That
Weather
Corporation
Creon wife
It's just Alex saying that he got his dad to retire because of Obamacare and now he works for him
That makes sense
Contradicts himself within a span of a couple seconds
Waterbeds
Fascinating
Want to say
People that are already informed and Love Freedom
And they're just going to go out and report on what's Happening
Forest
It's in the news right now
Let's go undercover and expose it
Talking points
Hiring people that love freedom
Like I would hate it if he was hiring
People who are
F****** faccia
Hiring people who add
Vacated harsh
Against
Any kind
Oversight from the government
Terrible terrible
Rehired
This investigation is supposed to be about how Alex Jones ended up
In the presidential campaign
We need to cover some of the stuff that I don't want to cover about this
Cuz these clips I don't like to listen to Ted Cruz talk
Steel yourself
Because we're going to have to listen to Ted Cruz talk a little bit in this next clip
Iamzoie
Didn't critique it on the other side but it's interesting to hear how Alex treats Ted Cruz
At this point in history
He has a boner
Corrupt mainstream media
Patron
First one
Supporting Isis
Facial sports that's a problem
Really has delivered
Compromise
Washington created
American voters
Let me say something at the outset the questions that have been asked so far in this debate
Illustrate why the American people don't trust the media
Kill me
Let me see
The question that I was asked
I don't want
Answer because I had a big party
Forcing a government shutdown really don't want
Whataburger
Things I did was
Lower the credit rating of the entire
Black president
Complaining about
The national debt
I have ensured that it will be higher
Now
In fairness
In Ultimate fairness
That question was phrased a little aggressive.
Don't get me wrong question is valid
I'm not I'm not partial here
Are you trying
Well the governor government its function
People like
You don't want the government to Funk
Are you an a****** you want to grab
Make the government not work
Does that preclude
And because he can't answer that question
You have to grandstand at
Flip it on the media
Yeah absolutely and gets a break because everybody at the Republic
Intubate it's f******
And you look at the questions Donald Trump
Are you
Snow tubing timing
Never seen any pants
Clear
The men and women on this stage.
Where is Vicksburg
And nobody
What you think
I skipped the breakers so important
This is how they try to control the narrative that's how people act like babies
If that's how we
Tried to control the narrative
Control the narrative
But it would still like
Hey there was talking to it
You're like okay
Because you're a f****** idiot your child
You're going
It's a situation where the question might have been framed for Leo
Did poorly but it gives an opportunity for you to rise above it and defend yourself
Issue that clearly a lot of people think you're a f****** dick about
Even to the end when the time is up he plays victim
They're not going to give it more time
You don't want to talk about something
Cuz we're all
Super rich
Right where the super rich
Carino's
You guys just want to say insult each other you don't want to ask Gustafson
Question
Admitted
It was
I am not going to answer
Ted Cruz
The nails on a chalkboard
As a human being they're legitimately should not be live audio
I think Cody's debate
Like it's that's a mess
Cuz you can just Pandora and do it like that
Time if your
Why are you stopping for Applause break
You're not using your time properly
Because you were screaming
I was very
In the middle of the cruise is the best on his feet of any statement I've ever seen
God-killer
Sitter that with it
6 months
He will
Join in on the Ted Cruz's dad killed JFK
Well that's true
Fart
Quickly that's amazing
Sing to me
That doesn't
Hey when you don't believe in anything
You don't have to worry about whether or not your positions
We got to get through of this debate
S***
Alex screaming about Melissa harris-perry because
There's a part
As I recalled the setting was
Confirmation hearings
Paul Ryan
Baby speaker
Alex
Spinning reel fun yarn about that
Cuz all of us Liberty people
And we're going to get one of our guys in there cuz we have
This doesn't mean that we can put them in but he's on a short leash
You want me to get out of there
Sick of it
Pennsbury smart
Very clearly had a million-dollar offer on the table
So this is really takes all day
People all day
I could leave
And get millions of dollars
And no don't care what I'm doing
Not have to worry about it
Confirmation hearings
Call Ryan
These hard-working
Stop
To say like
I agree with you and I think Paul Ryan is a good choice
Whatever I think of the word hardworking I want to be careful about language
Because it brings up
To me an image of
Slaves in a field
And that is the definition of hard-working for me
What I think she was getting at first of all I don't
Necessarily agree with how she makes
This points
I think that might be a little bit of a linguistic stretch in terms of bringing unrelated issues in and what have you
I think the point that she's making his
I hate all of us
We're not really that hard work
In the grand scheme of things
Clear about what we do
She's going to go to 100%
But Alex is
Furious
Start ranting here it goes
A couple minutes
And then weaves into some Ben Carson
Some stuff in the debate
And it's really important
Did we get the entire
Text leading up to this
Cuz where it ends
And what's making Alex really mad
Is fascinating
I will get to it
You tell me I got to drink
Are you
Break her conditioning
Like Gary Oldman only unprofessional
God's creation
Are God's real
Nice pivot from God God is God
Yeah you do have it
Either
I am a liberal
Miami pro-freedom
You carry nightmare soviet-style brainwashing
You are a mess
I'm not stupid I know full well your clips
I have to say here
People pull off your garbage everybody knows
Informational I will destroy you and your onward I don't need violence
Yeah
Living together
No blacks
That's what you don't want to
As a social engineer eugenicist
Great moderator questions
JetBlue
Nutritional supplements
Relationship
And this is what happened
I think it's a good product
No you are
On purpose
Wow
Yeah he gets off air during the little 72nd commercial break
I think the reason he's really mad is because
The context
Being critiqued about isn't nutritional
He knows that that's what he does
And he knows that he's kind of vulnerable
Damn goes out all the other night
Ben Carson was involved with mannatech
For a very long time
A couple of paid speech
$42,000 for one of the
Just got paid
April
Carson first
But whoever did that
Their website
Article in the Atlantic
Carson first spoke out in favor of man
Over a decade ago when he claimed that the
Space companies
Michael nutritional supplements which included large
Tree bark and aloe vera extract
Help him overcome prostate cancer
In what video format attack last year that remains online
Carson discusses his experience with nutritional supplements while seated next to the company's logo
Quote
The wonderful thing about a company like mannatech is that they recognized that when God made us
He gave us the right fuel Carson
Unexplained
And that's you with the right kind of healthy food
Basically what the company is doing is trying to find a way to restore natural as a medicine
Mechanism for maintaining hell
But don't sound like an unbiased purse
When God made us
He also did
Give us cancer
Traffic
Will breakdown
Yeah
You just take some aloe vera man
How do you get away with lying
Don't matter
Doing somebody being like
Hey
You clearly didn't say anything if you don't have any involvement with them
Why is your picture on their website
The reason that they don't know why I need to do
Just be super clear about it but the question was doesn't that indicate that judgment on your part
Does pissed off because mannatech
Is also a direct sales
Operation
Products
Sell it to your friend
Is there a multi-level marketing
F****** s***
It's all pyramids
Alex Jones has a pyramid scheme operating out of Infowars
Study run
Mannatech is incredibly similar to the Infowars supplements
People start discussing it and you start looking at this stuff
Realize how much of
The f****** scam it is
It is his house
The cards could unravel very quickly
Getmadz
People unjustly
And
Ura
Why is it that you don't believe
You're a weirdo
Endocrine
Episode Alex Jones discussion
Cox
He talks about cuckolding
And I just
I love you f****** love
I left
Just goes like that is getting repetitive
And we got a lot of ground to cover but
If you want to go to listen to that piece of the episode
Not worth it
Get cut marks
Selective discussion of Russia
Terms of the last like
Two weeks or so of Infowars coverage
Don't worry
It's just a because you wanted to cover the debate
He's getting back into
There shouldn't be done
Because people don't know how to use them yet
Restricted areas on the rain
Mnml
And everyone else
Ultimate
I get not having a bunch of recruits
Directions kill people
Russian Blue cat
About my fighting force
Making sure there are fewer of them
You don't want to go to a boot camp
Because you might die
Also making sure the one probably psychological
PTSD before the
Actual size of a cook among the people who aren't even in the ship
Word for political correctness
We would still be murdering our own
Military
You can see how great they are filled with people who are
They're happy that they're alive
Interview with his intrepid reporter Wayne Madsen
He's the guy who brought us the hot story about Hillary Clinton's Chef being murdered and having a letter pin to him it said call Lee
Larry Nichols
Love it
The case of 9/11 in Arizona there is a hanger
There's like an Airfield and
Convinced that this is where they turn
Planes into remote control drone
It is just speculation
And they treated as gospel
I knew it was
Going to be Arizona to cut stuff
And a man like two days later on the show they play a report of human Arizona
And they think it proved anything
Except that it
Very easy to get onto this Airfield
They've been here without getting killed
Freaking fat WeedMaps
Just walking around for the camera isn't really a camera guy with a walking around like
What are you doing
If security is that lacks
Look like
16 years later or whatever
Sanford ownership
Really care
So we now move on
To October 3rd
I believe
It gets really serious
Parking
Super
Steatorrhea
Here we go
Driver and the only thing that's constant
By the late eighties is global warming
In the larger cycle
15 years
First
Increasing temperature slowed
Numbers across the world
Not true
High temp some record low temp
Always mobile
Climate change
Cuz the climate
Because this is such a big deal
Anthropogenic climate change
Is a geostrategic
Thriving energy sector and every other country
And Putin 100%
It's the mailman
Russia haven't even going along with the fraud
Call boy
Doughboy
Just can't listen to that
Pitstop
Three hurricane
Yeah
And for that you just go a week in the past
F******
Throwing everything
Can you listen to
These people who lived
Tonight at 4
So long and
Look at all the damn
Can you look at the
They were made like
Smell 10 years ago so pretty much matching up
With what's happening in front of our eyes right now
How did we not know Dan
I don't know
Listen to themselves
And made sure that everybody
And so they could continue murdering everybody
Gluten
Has a lot of financial interest
Emmanuel
Right it's a weapon
Energy
F*** you
Russia has
Is it possible for us to collect
AAA Sue
All the people in Houston
Can blink
We can definitely link all of this damage to
One One Sweet Day
And that they knew that this was a result of
So I'm pretty sure that they should be shut down
This is
In terms of our investigation
It's more important
Did Alex is being fooled by Putin
Stamps on it
Yeah well I don't think he's
I think so
Aegis dovetails nicely into
The climate change
Denial
Take that
Take the climate-change part of it out of it
Into thinking Putin is smart
And a good leader
By Putin take the position
Agrees with
For the reason
That's a strategic reason to deny climate
If his name
Absolutely has the exact same Financial in
So because he doesn't want to lose these billions
Trillions of dollars that he could be making if
Sanctions were lifted
He's super against climate change
Alex already
He's sucked more into Putin is a genie
He's a great leader
He already was flirting with of Being Fit
Is now just going
F****** w****
Wow
Climate change.
Climate change
Is a geostrategic weapon
Washers breaking with the globalist on every front they didn't go along with carbon taxes before and said they weren't sure it was real
Control
World leaders
Bipolar
Defense
This is cause for celebration
Just wanted another notch
Cuz you know I don't trust him in that
They wanted to get rid of our override they want
Russians
Special Forces
International
One of their main heads
I was told it was the sky
Once they cut to me they started interrogating me
Who I was who I work for
Listen to the show
When the signal goes out to this
If a weapon system to selectively cut off the energy
Do you understand what just happened
Do you understand what you just admitted on air
Do you realize
That's
Bucked up
He's at he just
I was interviewed
I should not have said that on
You just admitted
You know what happened
This guy
You know what happened in that interview told him that Putin listens to his show
Images of Genius
That's how they compromised
Through flattery
That's how you make it
Steve pieczenik started on the last episode
Paranoid
Delusional people
Super easy to manipulate
Russian
And then
Grilled him
That's insane
Bills game over
Route
He is proof that he's the worst
I should not have said that
When I heard that
I was like
I just didn't know what to do
How do you deal with that
How do you deal with a guy who can be outside
You don't tell him
And you deal with like multiple layers of Handler
Steve pieczenik
Is clearly feeding him is Heritage
And then there's probably its third stage
It gets him back to the Kremlin or whatever
You make it so Alex Jones
Think that the people who are feeding and narrative are the ones
It's from Russia
Goody flatters me every time he's on the show
It's f****** nuts
This is so f****** obvi
And the other thing that's interesting about that is
Was in on it
The idea that they set up an interview with Artie and then it's actually spies
That means
He's way more of a Spade outlet than Alex is willing to admit
So problematic
He's making the subtext text
Even the Russian government
Are you doing
You don't need an investor
Navigate of journalists when one of the guys is whistleblowing
Proudly revealing that he is now officially an ass out of there
Well that's
The same thing that he does with his sources
Supplement
Mainan super male Vitality of brain Force
Heaven is like
But I got Trucking recruiting
Heck is I don't know if he realizes
Of course he does
What he's telling the story I don't think he realizes how f*****-up this story is
I don't think he realizes what he reveal
It's like
The only reason
Because that almost certainly is happen
Members of Donald Trump
Sure
Again
You are supposed to report that to be FBI
Yeah
Deal with that people were willingly cooperating
Russian Folk
Tricked into a meeting or something like that
Supposed to report
The FBI reported that description that he's gay
Percent should have been like
I don't know what's going on
But I got trick
And ended up talking to high-level Russian government officials
They were grilling me about whether or not I work for the government
That's like
When he talked about being in a James Bond novel
He's kind of correct
But he's not James Bond
Real f******
Somebody who gets flipped
Anime
He Slipped by Goldfinger
It's so crazy it's like Homer Simpson
Scorpio I know that we talked about that clip for an hour
But
It's more fun if we just play this next clip cuz
Even worse
Let's continue here now shifting gears
Wish.com
Ultraman
Has come out and said climate change
To kill populations Detroit Nation
Of the inside bubble cartel
Is a
Devastating
Because Russia obviously
And exposing what's going on with
But
So I guess it goes
Putin
Matt drudge office
Oh no
It is very weird
I'm sure Matt Drudge
Drudge's mouth right
Alex Jones
Works
I'm so does Matt drudge probably
Based on
Every piece of evidence
And they're clearly at least aligned in some way
Is Alex's externalize
He's externalizing the network
Saying babe
Drudge
Under your breath
That's supposed to be like
Look at all these people who work for us
Hey dude do you know what I'm starting to realize
The reason that he started to have the same gas
Saint everyday
I think it started in
Sommore in 26
16 or so
The reason is because I need to
Keep a better eye on him and no one want
What's the listen to show
I think that's what's going on
Good stuff like this happen
And if this happened a lot
If it breaks like this happen
Did the game would be up
Like people would be able to
Do you listen to work for Russia everyday
Everybody would listen to this podcast the game is up
Yeah it's John
Just say that can't believe that he would
I was going to do an interview for RT
Lied to me at the behest of the governor
I'll be intelligence Services of Russia
By the intelligence service
Agents
Hoodlum
Insane
Then I'm sure that
Quote unquote interview
Behind Russia
What's not
Situation where they said
You're so right about everything how are you so right
Yeah but I'm sure they did say things like that
And flattery process
It's f****** absurd they had to
To of been all of them sitting there like
Trying hard not
Not to laugh
We thought this was
Going to be
Skeptical we thought you were
We thought you would at least be like
Hey Will I like America and it's you guys
I'm f****** Y2K you said Putin was Addie
Pretty skeptical of all authority
Boy this is easier than we thought
We thought you would we thought you'd be like oh this is it
Christian
And you might even hang out
Obama should have just said Alex Jones was cool
Might have saved America
Hey Alex Jones I love what you're doing
Let me give you some let me give you
Some things that I would also love for you to be doing
And that would be
This is followed up all this huge like rush it
Is followed up with a long interview with dr. group about liver
This show is so weird
Light trees
Liver stuff that makes green
Greater Blackstone chiropractor who made the formula
Excuse me your liver also do whatever Russian
There's a long interview
Interview with gym bars
Who is an old timing
Conspiracy theorist
He's written a book about we talk about
Sing like a couple episodes back
Studio and
Yeah this
Only people like that Alex
And some others
Try to bring you the real news
Example of a the whole thing going on in the Ukraine
What people don't really understand that it's over Russia's making a bad move and old cuz we're getting all this anti-russian propaganda
You're back off look at it
Essentially what happened would be like if we fix the i a
I mean the Russian saved take their intelligence service
I'm over here to Texas
And get a bunch of
Texting pulled up about this secede from the Union
And
I think we all know this
But I actually have anyway
And then Texas secede
And then the United States again oh
Say look you can't do that
And they would come and try to stop at
Right grout the same thing over there
Grapefruit we set up this
Separatist
Lumen
We armed them we egged them on and now in Russia says you've always been a part of Russia you can't do this
Now all of a sudden we're turning them into the aggressor
One of the most convoluted
Both versions of what's going on in Ukraine I've ever heard
Also let's take this piece out of it
The people who were trying to
In California
We're working with Russia
Oh yeah
Fled to Russia
However you want it the Catholic Alexa
For a group of people
So obsessed with saying that the Civil War was a war of Northern aggression
Him to all of a sudden be like
No visit United States was right
We we we absolutely agree that the Civil War
And we should have been taking over
Just like Russia
That's f****** nuts
Because
Because the area in Ukraine
Part of Russia
No it never was
The Soviet Union
But
That doesn't exist anymore
Very good reason
Created an uprising
And Russia is just trying to get this area not to secede from Russia
It indicates to me
Disrespect of Truth
And
Unacceptable
To the Ukrainian
Complete acceptance of everything that is in line with Russian narrative
Converse
Exact episode where Alex is admitting
Contact with Russian Intelligence Officers
That's
F***** up
Videos almost every guest
Ends up having some weird
Connection with Russia
Espouses
Amazingly pro-russia
The opposition's like Jamar is he
Interesting so I'm starting to think the Jakari Jackson
Didn't leave because of trump
Tired because
No I'm starting
Maybe he's sent
How Deeply this was a Russian propaganda Outlet
Thank God out
I'm thinking maybe that's
I don't think
If either of my suspicions are true
I don't think you talk to any
Because
Living might wind up with a note taped to of the
The image of anyone dying with a note
But
Yeah I mean
If if
The suspicions that we're really starting to see our true
I think
That anybody with actual information
They could confirm.
What it might be a risk
To their lives
To come out with it
American soil
Strangely enough
Easy argument
Anti-russian
Which is really high
Is that America does
Sure
And the idea that it's like
We're judging them for overthrow
Because
We've overthrown plenty
The show already
When it's being done to us
The question I'm asking
He is not just that it
It's at
Would our intelligence services
Stupid
Grab some
Media in Russia
I'd like some anti Alex Jones
Skyping with the CIA I think that
The remnant
The KGB
They just didn't have to worry who gives a s*** who cares
And even then
Who cares
No one no one
No one said anything
I don't have audio this
But I might try and post the video of it
Because
What are the narratives that Alex is pushing on this day is episode
Is here on October 30th
Is that
The EPA came out with a video
Video
Can pumpkins be like Smashing Pumpkins
Climate change
Is fueled by
Farms in
The Creator
Pumpkins for a novelty purpose one time a year
It does
Cause a lot of CO2 emissions
Pumpkin
It's that tire its
It's a government agency trying to be funny in that
Never going to be
But
Making a parody of the parody video
Video with Buckley
We're going around Buckley is like
Is Igor and bring him pumpkins to destroy
Ebony starts rambling about
I want to kill.
This is bad
Is High School prom
But I did
And he's doing this and millions of people are watching us
Acquit
It's just you got to keep quality
You're good or bad
Halloween
That's on a Saturday
November 4th
Alex Jones
I will come back on November 2nd
The nurse
Play control by
And so that's why US Special Forces are being put in
Hope that the Russians end up killing some US troops
You deserve to be now attacked and you deserve
Assad forces Russia you better pull out
Hoping the American people get all stirred up and support
So sorry about that there's a little glitch
Isis
Does Isis support control
So
Roshes Gray
I love what they're doing.
Pushing there
That the globalist are putting our forces
Suzanne hoping the Russia
Kills one of them
In order for us
To attack them
To pay there
Their evil plot is
To destroy the world and Russia specifically
So his are the only country
If it's fighting against
Right which I'm sure the intelligent
The other thing
Or a globe
The other thing that's important
To point out is later he goes so far as to say
That if Russians bomb American
And kill them
He takes
Agency and guilt
Away from Russian
Import put it on Obama
Cuz you put those forces there in order to bake the Russians into attack
It's f****** convoluted as hell
And it's
Do you not
Supporting America at all
I'm not for war either
I don't want to ride
I don't want to risk killing anybody
We have no place in a lot of the conflicts were in
Sometimes you have to stop
Stop atrocities from happening
It's very complicated
But the more you read about foreign policy
The more you're like
Nobody knows what to do
Nobody has any idea what's
Best thing to do
Everybody who thinks they know what the best
Thing to do is
F*****'-a
Everybody who does something
Things up more
No
What's going on and everybody's
The first president
His foreign policy made as much sense as it could
Now our foreign policy is
Not exist
When I look at this
Yeah
Go to the next clip
And it's about immigrants
Cat stuff
I want
To be clear
Extensive Alex Jones
Repeating
Very clearly Russian
By the way you put up on TV screen
Infowars.com we have the map up on screen there
Infowars.com show
You can see the areas controlled by Islamic State
From the start until now
Budget re-branding a multi to under a new flag
No it's not
It's fighting against
Conduit goes up into the Northside of Iraq
Refugees coming from
Otherworld
Travel up into Syria
And then travel from there as refugees
Europe
Other refugees are under the age of 30
And get off the trains and form up a military formations
And follow their leaders
30 year old on average Military Officers
Once I get the refugee centers
Disappear by the thousands every day
Into the European culture
Not true not true at all but also hostess I was really messing up the
Prince between average and median
That's one of the things that he's messing up when it comes to
So if you want to say like the average is 30
That means
The 12
You're old
Counties under 30 you know that right
Your children
Counties under 30
It's strange
From certain death
Yeah but
The reason why I say that this is Russian propaganda
Because I've been doing a little bit of looking in
To the exact nature of this
Anti-immigrant
Propaganda
What's been going on
Beat what I can
The sources that I've been able to find
Russia is very clearly
Trying to
Make the problem
Of migration
Worse
They're doing this to
Destabilize
And turn people against
Each other in Europe
In order to make populations
Distrust each other
If sometimes they're they're like
Sometimes our propaganda campaigns are super obvious
Like there was a referendum
How to create a trade deal with Ukraine
Has Putin obviously wasn't
Isolating Ukraine to make it weaker and more likely to fall into Russia
Empower
Is article about this
Amsterdam up before the vote
I'm at Dutch officials
Openly afraid of
The far-right media
They didn't want to be denounced or mocked in the tabloids or shouted at by thugs in
In the street
The government's majority is small
I was told
Sure there is but we don't want to take the risk
The correct
Very clear influence the politicians
No it's happening
Because of the radical people who will
Make their lives
Miserable thank you
That is not so much about the
But that is about
Trying to destabilize
Isolate Ukraine
In terms of the Immigrant
There's an interesting case study
About this girl name
What are you
Cuz I'm going to read from this article
Are in NATO magazine
About
Yeah it was one of his first hit
Which magazine
Beam I don't know is it independently produced
San Francisco weather
Roma
It is in a factory down south
So they are
This case of Lisa
Is water first
Senses where people can really directly C
Exactly the mechanism
Russia was using
To promote a fake story
Direct
Especially Muslim
Which is actually kind of bulshit
Because if you look at this
Statistics
Russia's not afraid of Muslim
They don't hate Muslims
Baby and if you look at the entirety of Eurasia
They have the highest percentage population of Muslims
Like in Europe
The highest is 7.8% I believe in France
Russia has 10%
Population
And we've only got like two
Something like that part about it
They're not as bigoted as Alex even
They care about making the rest of the world
Of invading horde
They're just
Splitting our own
Concurrent bigotry
That's all you
The case of Lisa dominated the headlines and impacted on German public discourse
For two weeks
In January 20th
The 13-year old Russian German girl
430 hours
Was reported by
First Russian television
I've been raped by migrants
The story
Inbreds
The German police were able to establish that he she had been
With a friends at night
Christ story was
Intensively reported on Russian domestic and foreign media
Diplomatic
Between German
Indian Russia
For the first time
Several of the different Russian Elliman
The influence
TARDIS
If it's article working
In the coordinated way
So the Bullet
A journalist from the first Russian TV channel picked up the case of the Russian German
My girl
Russian foreign media like RT Sputnik nrt Dutch
Reported on the
Social media as well as right-wing groups
Distributed the information on the internet
Demonstration
Super organized Facebook involving representatives of the German Russian minority
Goochland rowson
As well as neo-nazis
Russian foreign media in Germany reported
Mainstream media
Finally
At the top political level Russian foreign minister Sergey lavrov made to public statements about his concern
The inability of the Russian
The German police
To take such cases seriously because of political correctness
Sounds a lot like our
Sounds very soon
As a result of Elisa
And the different Russian activities and
In the context of Ukrainian
We're able to see a shift
In Germany from the dominance of
There must be a translation issue here we're seeing a shift in Germany for the
The economy / politic
Text to dominance
The politics over the account
Russian is becoming Russia
Security risk
The relations
Are increasingly politicized
Securitize
Sakura size
So then there was an interview with a guy Hungarian
Spy names
Ferric cataract
Little gentleman who
Probably
Name
This is a guy who broke cover to tell the independent about how he closely monitored and observe how Russia attempts
Aggravate
50 migration crisis
Spreading false stories
He was quoted as saying
When it comes to the events in Cologne or other sexual offense
Meaning of Russian
Are active in emphasizing that the German or Western authorities and the media are attempting to cover-up these crime
They don't exist
I mean they are trying to cover up that it
I want to make sure that you know it
But this is aligned with the narrative the Daleks
Absolutely
D.c. government
In your upper covering up rape
Statistics
He talks about
Sweden all the time that's another Russian prong attack
Cuz they want to
To destabilize Lapland
To be able to take out to Sweden Norway and
This this idea that these governments are enabled
Care of
Their own people
Is to get people against
Their governments
Create political strife
Political conflict
The committer get a government
Unable to deal with external crises
Or make them ripe for the plucking
You something that Russia
Has been doing
Even Beyond
If you go back further
Even before they were involved in like trying to f*** with our election they were doing this immigrants should wait now run
Here's where it gets interesting
Nigel farage
Has been very guilty
Of perpetuating a lot of
Stories that act up
Should be f******
They are
He's super guilty
A lot of the exact same and upbeat
The rhetoric of
The Sweden Democrats
A political parties influence
By Marshall in fear of asylums
And advocating for
Restrict immigration
Critics like the
Sweden Democrats
Suspect that the government is
Colluding with the mainstream media
To hide Amex
Statistics of sapota
Supposed
50 calls
Albo in particular the rape capital of Europe
Now Sweden Democrats
What is a misleading name Ara proto-fascist
Just organization
To say of course they
Australia
The Liberals are actual
Play the worst people
Into this
The reason that rape
Statistics are kind of high even though actually they've gone down
Crime all across them
What are the reason
If you track it from like
I wanted the reason
Is because
In 2005
Sweden voted to
Expand what they consider
And so they have a very wide
Of
Inappropriate sexual behaviors that get classified
Yeah so from 2005
The number looks like it's going up
It's just
Consider more things
In that category
Further
They have a very interesting legal
It turns out
Visit from Swedish store
Bothers at
That's that's a big problem
Say
If
Like
Example that you
Call the police
And she has a diarrhea
Where she has in her diary
Census of spousal rape
That her husband
Committed against her
The police will consider that 400 Prime
So each incident
Is considered a crime
Instead of one
Cuz that's what it
But
If one
Call comes
It makes there's two pissed
6 look incredibly
So whenever there's one victim and a bunch of offenses
One perpetrator and a ton of offenses
Or one perpetrator rsi1 victim
Perpetrators
It can make things look like there is
Is more actual a
Then there actually are
Which I think is
Probably
Yeah I think
Absolutely
I think it's a think it's positive
But it does open its
Self up to being
She was raped
Yes
That is
Is that is the point
That is what should be
Considered
In jail
For 400
Because that is how they
Classified things another keeps
It's really easy for people on the outside
To make
Really misleading claims
About
Then I
So because of the Russia
You assume they do it the same
And then you are easily manipulated
Russia perpetuates
These narrative
Pins it on
Immigrants
And these
And people like Nigel farage
And Alex Jones
Pick up on them
Actuate them further
Yeah that is a queer pipeline
What's going on
Quotes
F****** insane
Like all of this just like the the crack epidemic
In the 80s
Sprite and how that was used to demonize black p
Based on an agenda that old f****** white men
Like all of that
Stuff is done
So specifically
And so it and instead
Targeted Manor
People who are dumb enough to believe
F******
Sad
I'm just really sad that they're still
People who would otherwise think
Normal fine people
And then there's
Manipulate
This dumb s*** Epic
Cam monster
Like all of the
This
A f****** sociopath
Who knows that everything he says
Is b*******
Is Ally and
Is going to hurt
People that he's telling
He is an evil human being
The people who buy
Between
The Russian
Russia
Yeah the government
Is evil the people are generally good
Hit the gas
Assad
Praising praising God
Chemicals
I'll do whatever you want I'll even the power
Press conference
We all know that
Lot of dictators
Advocate Power Wheel
Tons wants to retire to England
Wants to give up all of those billions of dollars
End.
Total control over his country
For forever
Just wants to step down a bunch
2 +
That
Things were false
Come from
This video that Alex is
I couldn't track it down I don't know specifically what he's talking about
But I'm ninety-nine percent certain
He's taking it out.
I'm guessing it
It's from something else
Maybe even in a different country now it says no idea
Here's another damning f****** clip
The movie
Climate change is man-made
Running our country
Alex Lovett or leave it
Guess he doesn't have kids
Peyton Dungy five-year-old how to get b******
Cut people taxes
Promoting Christianity
Listening gun laws in Russia
Weather shows how unbelievably pathetic
How old is Ron Wood
We are
You know who those people are who are saying Putin is Hope and Messi
Boards are
Bought
Completed regular old folk
Completely falling
For their prompt the other promovare equal
Seeing all these pro-russia
Sandbox pop-up
Putinism
This is pathetic
It's not pathetic
That's that's probably going to be the biggest Quest
For Obama
Presidency
Is legacy
Yeah why did
I think
I don't know
It's sort of deal with that question we end up in
Wild speculation
I would guess that
You don't want to start a war
That might be one piece of it
I think another piece of it might be
Threat
Like back threat
But have been made
I don't know
I don't I don't know I don't think we'll know for another good 10 years probably what the reality was why
More wasn't done to
Chicken batter
Really like to know how it feels
I'm sure not great
Otherwise
Of course I let him take over like
Hey
You wanted to become
The caliphate
All right I just wanted to take over the Middle East as they're talking about this they slash up on screen
Shepard Fairey
Picture of Putin as that hope
Image of Obama
Yeah it's crazy
Here we go
Maybe
Donald Trump
And Carson is coming out defending Obama's policy
Carson is a super smart guy
Not as informed
Orbi
Former Secretary of State Hillary
Strike again Carson
Along with his
Inoculations BS
Trump is just better
Delivers on what eats like
A better than Hillary
Directions
You see there that
Trump is indicating a line
With Putin and this makes Alec
What's warm to
He is now instead of saying I don't trust him
He's adding on a second layer of
It where before was I'm afraid he's going to double-cross
But he might double-cross them
Insane
I don't know how to
Combination of eggs
Exhaustion
Yeah that I think
Just about all of us
At least it's really starting to tear me apart
These people
Always going to
To believe that Trump
Who is the better
That Hillary would
Yeah
Abject
Arash
You're just in denial
Some critics of Hillary in our heart
Plenty
Critiques of Hillary position
It is just
It is beyond
Just dealing with
People who have to
Spend so much energy
In denial
Yeah either that or they just got pregnant
Like those are the only two ways
To go about it
Soma
Exhaustion is just like
I get it
You're dumb
You have no further you cute more to say
Because you are now completely and utterly Arash
I can't
I can't debate with you
Because there's nothing
The reality is too overwhelming
It's just like
Now there are three
Three hurricane
Hitting our f****** coastline
People are like
Let's not talk about climb
Let's not talk about
We do that all the time
You work so hard
Don't politicize the issue
No longer a politic situation
Eating what
You have murdered
Your children
What you have done
To everybody who is Ojos
Like Mike
Still thinks that
You know Trump is a great present
Here's what your ears what you're really in denial
If you actually stopped
And except
The fact
That
By your actions
And by your vote
You have
Essentially
Contributed to the deaths
Of millions of people
Specifically
Your kids
Right
If you do that
Has to be overwhelmed
I probably don't want to do it of course
It has to all of a sudden like that
Responsibility
Accepting a personal
A large-scale
About the flip side of this for Alex to Now flip on Trump is for him to record
Acknowledge that he was used
Would be
Not the same
Is it soon as he gets off the Trump train he's got to look back on everything to be like
Was used by Russia
Any chance
I got to skip a bunch of stuff cuz we are going to sucking
End up in a 5-hour podcast
Did you call
Deep s*** like that
Russian intelligence
And then visit episode is going to end
Isaac
Workout
But I'm going to skip
Because they are
Alex tell the story of his Halloween party
Why would you skip that one cuz they're long
Let's hear about Halloween party
And I
Two people come up to him baby 3 it's unclear
Go up to minnich use him as having an option
It's not
True at all
I kept there's two of them
He tells the story twice
And it's very different
Eastside
But in the first version he says that some white girl came up and was crying because every costumes
Could have warned would have been accused of being racist
That makes sense do not have
Whose character is mysteriously absent from the second version of the story but it becomes a multiple people
Remember When
The Disney prince
And people were like imagination
The other thing
We're going to drop
Is the we find out that Buckley dosa
Which is Buckley's
Spinning
A little bit
This clip we can't
The end of the November 2nd episode
That we're on here
I and
It's just fun because it's what happens when Alex Jones get spray
Called
Another story
Calling from communist California here in the first time, I just wanted to say how much I love your product
Thank you brother
Aman DNA Forester mail at Aldi
Oakland
Survival Shield
Appropriate filter for over the past year
Thunderstorm
I've been looking for like a year-and-a-half now
Everything
Come to fruition
Do we have a US Navy missile instructor and many other experts confirming that the Earth is flat and Motionless
That's an ad hominem thing people call in
Got so I have a couple thoughts about
Yes
It's possible that was a prank call
It's not possible that he's being trained by the institute's or whatever to do this
Or whatever he calls
But it's possible that was not a prank
That's what I'm saying
Hayirli possible 100%
On that voice
No ever told doesn't change wants to talk about the Earth being flat
He loves Alex Alex doesn't water I recognize that there is a big overlay
Between those communities
The crazy people and people who like him
There is a massive Venn diagram overlap
Suggest there is
Just one Circle
So we skip the 3rd and the 4th cuz I don't give a s***
It's on the 3rd
Actually has
He has an interview with Michael Savage
It's based on
Substantial to the matter at hand
So deep that we're skipping an interview with Savage
On the 4th
James O'Keefe has a new video
We're not going to play any of it around to a couple colleges
And tried to get the people who work in the student Help Services
The offices to shred the Constitution
Because
Why are these
So if you actually watch the videos
But at the same time
Did this girl goes in and she's like
I found
Because the tution that someone handed to me to be triggering
And you see the people's faces like
Can I
How can I be catering to this person
But at the same time not be crazy I want to pick some up
Because that's who I am
Yes I am
I can't just
Even even though I would be
I would at least
Talking to
If I said
F*** off
The shredding of the Constitution is always
The Girl Who is the
Mark or is the plan
I guess
I don't prove any
University
It's not
The Constitution
Coffee
I get the idea of life
Who cares
It's not important
The other thing that Alex goes off on on this episode that I thought was
Ended her a candle with the Cubs
Housekeeping Kendall
He goes on a long rant about how men are the
Defense mechanism for women
And the womb women's bodies create man in order to
Protecting of them
It's very weird
Truly insane
Yeah
No because it's the sexism of
Force
Chivalry in some ways
Because it's like this idea that
Implied
He saying is that women who hate
Rejecting their help
Buc-ee's
These bull Dyke
And what have you
They are they are rejecting the natural way
That is
Man
On a biological level are just
Created in order to
To protect women
That is basically
Then why are they so
I don't know
The violence to
It's it's interesting that you know
If we were made
To protect with
Right
His system
Abuse and murder
I think it's one of those peyote moments for him cuz he's just getting out there
Then he has another interview with the guy about China using a
It's one child policy
Interesting on one level
And then it turns into a whole thing about relative
A Birthright
People are reproducing
Throughout that I skipped
It's really not worth it
Get onto the fifth
And
Alex spent the first
. of the show talking about how Robert Rodriguez Tarantino suck
Cuz I don't like him
Another globalist
I guess
Then he has an interview with Ron Paul
And
I feel like quitting
Still be like
Look
Pulp Fiction
Actually
Easy sake
Ends up being sad
What do you make a
Treasonous conspiracy
More more
That's really scary when the
Sounds more Americana the America
That is a little bit scary
I bet
I bet it is
Americana
That's out
I love you remember
Make America Russia
Ridiculous Ron Paul isn't like hey f*** off
Tells you everyday
You can have mainstream media is lying to you but Russia
Is mainstream media
Already
Agrees with a dump
You believe
Opposing hungry hungry hungry leader as
Closely aligned
Sessions with
Right
So at the end of episode Alex
I don't know maybe he wanted to leave early or something we just replace the entire Matt drudge interview
Weak ask what happened. I don't know why you
Hard-on for me
Also kind of lame
He has a long interview with Peter Schiff
Where they talk about his dad dying in prison
Rest in peace
I'm sorry you're not political prisoner
Andy what he was
He also alcohol suspended
A lot of time talking about how David Cross
I don't know
Haha
But did he also did altitude
Mr. show was great
I think it's actually all about Run Ronnie run
I think that's what he's mad about
Look
I just had high hopes for it and it didn't turn out to be as good as I thought I was going to be
Do great
Ben Carson is done
A lot of Ben Carson's officially done
Episode
Scholarship at West Point
He's done
Alex's precluded him from being a possible candidate
Which really just leave
He was like okay
We can't let Ben Carson
Can be president
Let's make sure he's
Secretary of Housing
People dropped out chronology at this point I think only like Rick Perry and Lindsey Graham
I dropped out
Like everyone is still in the mix or everybody
Yeah and no one like you
No one is even
Close to truck
At this point
Trump or Carson
Even though he loves Rand Paul
And wishes Rand Paul was out there
Yeah but Ted Cruz is not like even
Super in the running
Cruises
You can support
Ted Cruz all you want but you look at Amir like this is fine meme
Really implicitly memes
Trump is really the only game in town
Because Rand is no
Never there
No
Creative dr. pepper
But
I believe it
The only clip I have from this episode
Yeah the only clip that I took from this episode is Alex accidentally reviewing sort of his workflow
Go against whatever the new world war agenda is
Just as a default
So
If you aren't understand what you just
Instantly goes against whatever this imaginary
Star for later rationalize
Yep that's right. That's how we create this position
Feeling and then say or do anything to just
Testify that feel
That is not at all
Insane
So that is on the 6th
And then we go
Is
Saturday
And we show back up on November 8th
It's a Sunday
It's time for a launch of a new soft narrative
Sunday's pictures
Stop out there
Begins on
Sunday
Perfect Storm
Economically
Astrophysics
Israeli legendary
Either having you in
Conference 2015
From that
Week-long conference begin
Will be closing its borders
Coming up in about a week throughout this.
The formation of the open planetary government
We only Friday I got the full text
Temple text David
Pictures of big deal
Vitamin World
And selectively
Which is exactly what planet
Eliza go inside those came out again last week and started
He said he didn't buy it completely years ago
This is about the Paris climate
That's the
Would you predict it
Would you would you
You know how when you get really angry
F****** do this s***
That's crazy
We're all dying
World
Yep
So
Paris climate talks
Alex
I think books don't even
Big still don't care
For the destruction that they caused
And they're going to do everything possible to ensure
I don't understand
Impossible unless you're a psychopathic serial killer if you been lied to and you believe
The creation of world government
Studies that have been done by Lorde
F******
I can't deal with this s*** you are murdering us I'm not
Jordan Jordan
I've always
Snow on Wednesday
Humans need to go
Because in his next clip
You start
By talking about globalist
Plops and what-have-you
It turns into a weird aggressive like
I know
Hugo Boss
Cogitate sort of man going crazy
How you doing
I know the globalists are listen I really could use a golf
Weekend
Anyways
Ice
I think he thinks that everyone who's not an info Warrior isn't about globalist
I think that's what he thinks literalism
It's f***** up not let humans develop naturally
From the ivy
Okay I know what you're going to say before you thinking
All this crap
On the head
Grunau
Getting patted on the head and thinking you're part of
The crude refers to the group
A couple times
Yeah
Because I
Makeup
Supplies
We are the group
No did because I've listened to so much of the show I know exactly what he's talking about
Which is the group that Rodger
Stone Steve pieczenik
So when you talked about
Leave
If you have that you went
Does a meeting people passage on the head
Made you take that you're part of the group
Exactly what his life is
Flattered by Russian
Intelligent
And now
He's been brought in
By Steve pieczenik
Into this organization that is trying to
Promote Donald Trump
As president for the interest
Over foreign country
And they made him feel like he's a part of it
This is all just
They made him feel like
They were party
His group
It's a prank call
Maybe prank call this is
Legally speaking Alex
Trying to
To deal with what's happening
To him by saying it's what his enemies are going
Enemies are people who
The show
That are on board
I guess
The establishment
You think you're going to pray on your fellow humans and Ascend to the next level
Are they still living
SA
Absolutely
Who's this
Cuz you're not even Spirits your little greedy bastards
Wash yourselves already
If you were alive you know
Machine to augment your help you or help you survive
A machine that makes your godson machine that takes over your Freewill I machine
Yeah you should take
Take a pill for that
And you want to believe it's artificial intelligence
All the answers were laying in front of you
What is he
I'm not sure
He's on a weird Tire on this episode
This show is a whole lot of nothing
20 minutes talking about how he's always been about Benghazi
Play some clips
From Benghazi pass
Marine Le Pen
Complains about bathroom
Espouses a belief
That if you are actually the victim of terrorism you never talk about it
Cuz you don't want to encourage terrorism
By proxy
Someone claimed terrorism it's been a false flag
He also admits that is Sunday show is the only one
That is not actively co-produced by gcn
Cuz I use a different phone line
He said
That Sunday is the only show that we entirely produce ourselves
That means
He either goes through gcn
Outside funding
He probably should
Involved
Some sort of outside
He's Dutch
Revealing
A guy who'd
Define himself
By what
And how much
He has no end
Internal identity
It's purely
I am against
And that's who I am
Person who is
I'm again
All of these all of the
Like I don't
I don't entirely
Stand those p
People that's a type of Google
The people who Define themselves
That's such a weird thing to me
Is that you don't have any
Eternal
Like you don't have it
Idea of who you are
If it works
For the
These imaginary p
Who is
Do you like do you like
A good scotch
Do you like
Beef
What does he even like that stuff or is it like somebody told him that smelly somebody was like
Is bad
Or he's like I met a vegan one time and they were like you should meet people
I love it
Baby butthead
This this next trip
Is also super revealing
And it might actually be a piece of his intrinsic personality
Incredibly f*****-up
I want more
I realize it's an awful lot about the taxes
I don't get off on it
Serious it is
That's just what it comes down to look up some phone calls here he gets off on people attack
It makes
Inflammatory
I don't know who should be saying these things on air
To see a therapist
Two man
I mean
Finished
That is
You're just a f******
Yes
I'm screaming about
Situation
Where some students were offended by people wearing a racist Halloween costumes
Had a confrontation with the head of student affairs I believe
I am he was explaining that it is free speech for them to be able to
What the f*** you're supposed to create a safe environment for us we're being
Racially victimized by people
It is a debate
You know I don't think either side is wrong
Because
Isaac that you should be able to wear
But there should be
The real consequences for it
So it is free speech
To say and do horrible things
It's also the most reasonable response
Tubi
Very mad about it
So the government should not arrest
There's that and deprived
Institutions such as a College address
It's not punishing you for your free speech
You're creating an environment.
It's not conducive to learning
Alarm
Victimized
Somebody brings in
That is not
Not a safe environment
And then
F******
So Jordan be ready for November 9th
No
My friend
The beginning of the end
Obviously
Around the world
Dining us to jail
Phyllis Schlafly of founder of Google form
Breakdown
Book
For the fact
Clinton's of had a war on women
Show that is coming up Rodger Stone has arrived
Disappearance
This is when he shows up
Rodger Stone
Yep
I don't know which I don't know which order would be a good question
The thing that is interesting to me is that
Alex
Seems to be unwilling
Or unaware
Of the fact
Or unwilling
To tell the fact
Is that Rodger Stone Works on Trump
In his interview Oregon's introduction
He only says
That's not great alternative historian
For him it's just
He's a dirty trick
Even brings up how Rodger Stone was behind
A lot of those fake
Conservatives that showed up to
The shutdown the recount
Florida in the 2000 election
Like he talks about how he got these fake people to show up
Alex
He hates George W bush
But he just doesn't talk like that
He doesn't actually get into the fact that Rodger stone is
Deeply involved with Trump
Until then
The middle of their interview
But first
Teasing motherfuker
Alex Jones to tell you a story about the gym
Welcome
Morning I was shot in the local gym
And I killed an 18 month old baby are there
Is this
I don't really care I just ignore that
I get off on it
On some cable machines
Amazon The Machine
I guess you can use that but
Which is not normal
Of course here
Not sure actually I'm done with it
Alex Jones
He was staring at me
Can I said
You know who's
Causing problems in this country it's the new left there nothing was
I said you're not
Movie where
I didn't actually say that to him I was thinking that
Myself
Knox
And just walk away
Because you're not going to help
People like that
You legitimately most cases
There was a look of concern on your face
You
If we had a psychiatrist
Sitting right next to us they be like medvetz paranoid delusions of grandeur
Recognized
Set timer
How many people do you think are those
I question whether he was actually ever
Quite frankly
It could just be laying around in bed like
I'd be like you're not a liberal, liver
All of this could be some sort of weird
Jacob's Ladder fantasy
Fix it without really dying
I mean just just the line of like
And then they walked away and said
Oh Alex Jones you the right way
Peanut and you're like
They didn't
No of course
We weren't there
I can guarantee you they didn't
They just were like
I saw you just got on that machine
We do a regular routine here we're going to use it as a personal trainer she clearly works
It's not bad Attica to be like oh you know we're going to need that machine
I know that from the time I spent at a gym
There aren't they can daddy the polite interaction
About him being like a you can have it now if we don't need it now
He's a lunatic
Like it's easy to say he's crazy but
Gets really crazy
He's like mentally ill on a literal level
This man
Needs a psychiatrist
He's high-functioning enough
Live his life and what have you
But he is
Enough to sell weirdo pills and stuff like that
He is cripplingly insane
Oh absolutely
He is both of those things simultaneously and that's why I always get kind of bothered when I see
The videos that like I love Sam Cedar
I think imma Jordan majority report is awesome
But a lot of the time when they cover Alex Jones
They deal with it like a is he
Crazy or is he manipulative
As if they're mutually exclusive
Crazy evil Spectrum
Pies you can make it
So I'ma
It's another version of the Halloween
Story that didn't happen
But you can guess what story the kind of delusional bulshit that sin is all the way story
Crazy I'm started
Weather Buckley is even a DJ
Starting to question whether or not Buckley's even real I know he's real cuz I've seen him in some videos
I could be redacted
Stone prank
There it is
So now we can register
Play no longer game
I wanted
Mostly focus on Rodger Stone because it's looking for forever
But it turns out we do need a little bit of Phyllis Schlafly
They have about four minutes of the interview where they're flirting
About how much
She love gun
It is weird
Never
Ever
Words
Never been
More desert until the end of this next clip
And then people will understand why
But if you take them how to read they'll be able to read some of the great books
Little ripped in the English language
The talks about
The principle of limited government
Fandango
Why freedom is important than important to work for
MiFi
It's a good example to the Grassroots
Fish you can win
Against overwhelming odds
I do know I have a DVD called doing the impossible
And which I show all the odds that were down
When I started the fight against the Equal Rights Amendment
Everybody was again
Against
The president's the congressman
The prayer
Everybody you can think of everybody who is important the organization
People haven't got any fighting
Boy
Yeah what it would do you want to play a game
Schlafly
Equal Rights Act
F******
Batwoman
Has done so much damage she is eight
Literal monster like it's one of those things where
We can
Prosecute
Murderers on a small scale
But somebody who has killed as many people as Phyllis Schlafly
Is Untouchable apparently
She is a true murderer
That woman
Has led to the death
So many women
Through distrust of distrust of influence
Across the
You f****** conservative lunatic
Spectrum
They picked her up
And promoted her
Laura Lee
To influence women
Was Barry Goldwater probably
F****** evil she is a murderer and there's no other way to describe it
That is what she is
And I f******
She's a mess
I can't stand that she is allowed to walk free
I think she's dead
Natsu
The reason I wanted to play that clip just to give everyone a little flavor
Of hay
So weird that everyone was against me when I was against the Equal Rights
Call rights
Quotes
Phyllis Schlafly
Because
It's like it's like a shity
Comics like
Oh man I wish I could just stay home all day
Find
F****** tear you not recognizing
The forced part of it
That was really the problem
That's Equal Rights Act worksheet
But the reason I needed to keep her interview in is this
2016 what's your view on
Well I'm kind of hoping
If there wasn't one guy
Who could really make a change of Donald Trump
He wants to make our country great
A lot of these other people have no interest in making our country great
And I think he really genuinely does want to make our country great again
I think he's got a vision like Ronald Reagan
And I wish you well
I hope he's another Ronald Reagan but I tell you
Adopt perfect
Even you are not perfect
But anyway
Anyway he's got stuff
Yeah it alright
So are we see their Alex
Refers to Phyllis Schlafly is a living legend
He talks about how much she is an influential piece of his conservatism he loves Goldwater
As well
When
When she comes back
And says that she's for Trump that is not a small thing
Game time
She gives him
His deflection
He's not perfect
Bonita resigning
Something he will use for the neck
His wife
So at this point I was Jones opens up the phone line
He wants to have people call in who have been victims of PC culture on campus
And it goes on
Even if you disagree with me if you want
Awesome
He goes on to also talk about how when Starbucks had their like let's talk
On the cops
Operational trouble man this country was so much better off we were getting along before Obama came in like
Call boy
Yeah boy
Great that's not
Cripplingly racist as is
So much and
Still doing it now that idea of like
He wants to make our
Against
I do that
Any meaning
They don't talk about how they don't talk about what
They don't talk about anything other than
I get the general
Feeling
Betty wants to make America great
Dutch
Perfect way to deny that you're a giant
It's such a
Perfect wave
To deny that you wanted
Kill poor people
It's just such a perfect way to Encompass all of this right-wing b*******
Only thing it'll like
I feel like he wants
How to make American
There's no meaning
For as much as Alex complains about George Orwell
Peace out
Do you think you'd be able to be like
Might be some sort of a cc
Yeah buddy.
The time is come
18 episodes of Investigation have been leading us to this point
Rodger Stone makes his appearance
On the Alex Jones Show
And now we will find out if my prediction
What's correct
Start supporting Trump
As soon as Rodger Stone shows up
Prediction was
Before they get into any trouble matters
They want to s*** on Hillary
Gaston has a book about Hillary having a war on
Yep
Ostensibly the reason
These nuts
This is what movie
Very short-tempered
And choose carpet
That's pretty amazing
Are you saying that we shouldn't have somebody who has a
The foul-mouthed short temper and his
Exceptional
Greedy in the White House
Are you saying that
A Bad series of quality to have in a f******
What are you saying that that's not what we
Understand is that this is Rodger Stone hot dog
This is them showing off
Yeah he's showing off that he can
Just f****** say whatever a goddamn
It shows how stupid and gullible Alex
Yeah
Carpet
That's amazing
What is 30
What is that
So
These nuts
Clips
Are essentially Rodger Stone
Haven't watched
Knowing what Alex Jones is rebuttal
The Trump bar
And knocking them down one by one
So the first one
The Dow Jones
2 is
Mob connect
Flip flops
What the biggest one is
Can we trust
Is he for real
Or is this some sort of a joke
Here's the answer to that one
Rodger Stone
He was the chairman of Donald Trump's exploratory campaign
There's no question I don't agree with Trump on everything
Ticket by Trump
Can't bully Trump
Definition of lobbyists he doesn't understand special interest
Baby's first present we've had to really work
For the American people
Corrupt
Sleep
And where he was really born into the political mainstream
That's why he's ahead of the polls to go
So I'm going to load of bulshit but
You see that the thing
EZ's deflecting Alex Jones
Concerns about whether he's for real or not and then adding on Dino's Alex
Super into racism 9/11
All those things
He's so much more than
So now we get to the Mob question
Okay cuz Alex really put together a birder's bro thing
Things that I would hate
I feel like
Curated this episode just to like
Can I destroy Jordans
Very angry
You stole from him
And leave him a
Bitter husk
Total perspective
Vortex
From Douglas Adams
See you you're looking at this wrong and I'll explain it a little bit later but we get to the mom question
Close friend
New Jersey casino control license
And hold one for 13 years
If you're in bed with the mob it's just not possible they have the most stringent laws
They put a proctoscope right up your derriere and they look at every financial transaction
In your entire life.
It's clean and they got nothing on him that's amazing
Opposite of what is true we can't be mobbed up cuz he works in casino
Staggering
What
You can't hold a license for 30
Seniors
Unless you're Bob's
Alex pies at Hook Line & Sinker
To the point where later in the interview Alex brings up the Bob stuff
As if he never believed
No fuc
People believe in the Bob
Indeed quail in the course of the interview you see Alex Jones
Denying things
Penske said in the past
Sup
Rodger Stone
Demonstrative
Sure
Alex Jones
Is the only one who can save America
Sure
Signed off on it
Sure sure
Sure
Here's where the interview gets
And they don't talk
Obviously
The globalist and all of their
Armies of
Snapchat like that
Sarah
The next clip
Realwear
This indicates
Rodger Stone 104
That wasn't salad
There is no doubt that
Keenly aware of where a lot of his
We're a lot of his interests lie and maybe the parent companies
Monetary interest fly
This is interesting
Cuz I know his views on monetary reform
I can tell you that right now.
Provided for in our government
This is wild
You're seeing Alex gets flipped real time it is it is amazing
8/8
It's
It's hard not to like look at Stone do this and be like
12 player game recognize game
Radar currently be like hey if I just lied Alex
You've gotta believe
As long as
Because what the f****** Federal Reserve does
She might
Okay you're right
Definitely doesn't know that you want to shut it down
Certainly not going to go back to the gold standard
You know who
Of course
So what what Rodger stone is basically doing a lot of levels you taking
Taking the things that Alex loves about Rand Paul and applying them to Trump
Absolute about 9/11
It's all just
Political it's all just grandstanding
Of a guy who's
Staying whatever it is he feels like
I've been repeating back what people tell him they like when you have no ethics
And your skull
That's what you do
So now now
The other thing
That Alex is always had
The bee in his bonnet
Is that
Trump has connect
Hillary Clinton
Amy said positive things about Hillary Clinton
So this comes up next
But it's in the context
Glenn Beck
Because Alex
Is starting to agree with Rodger
Stone it doesn't want to admit that he is
Concerns about that
Teresa's
Glenn Beck his head concerns
About Donald Trump's connection
He loves a man of his position he has to pimp out Glenn back in order to even
Raise the question that he wants to talk
Yeah but I like Glenn a time before Dad can we know what is beef is with Donald Trump
His business he is right
If you don't
Campaign contributions into the pockets of the politicians they don't even listen to
Used to people working for you to get your point of view in front of government
Relationship
Boat from the dock
They're fighting to keep us
Rodger Stone more things to tell him Trump is going to do
Yeah
F******
This is Dad
What is my name
Who's making me
Feel bad for Allie
It's just watching it
It's like
Santa Clause 2
Tile
Just it's just all imaginary nonsense
Meeting was
O'Hara dating Alex
Wow
I heard that
No Putin fighting the global is he's offended Christian
Very frequently said I have from
Secret sources
The secret Leah Christian secretly defending christened
How much do you think come from
Spies accidentally talked to in fake interviews with Artie
Crazy
And this is where I think Rodger Stone pulled out the death blow the whole political correct again.
He understands that freedom is on the ropes
Weird
How many death threats do you think
Sure because he's speaking out on a lot of controversial subjects o
Is AAA security he himself carries both his sons
Very active Hunters
Reagan Carey Reagan had a holster you know on his
He was carrying about 80% of the time
Yeah I'm sure he wishes he was carried when Hinckley tried to take him out or Hinckley and others try to take you out
Run has been carrying
If only RFK Sirhan Sirhan
Also Reagan husband
According to that guy whose name I can't remember
Like I you see it you see it there
Like that
The transformative moment I believe the moment
Rodger stone is saying
Carrying all the time
His sons are big gun
Amanda
Do we have a president
Who carry yep
And then he'd that's it
Giant boner right
Come back to guns
Like that
That's where we we kind of started with that couple of ideas of
Is it racism
Is it.
Absolutely but
The death blows
Why did Gatsby
Court trumpism
Are you f******
Sane
How could you possibly
We Believe
Manual dexterity
I am at the end of November 9th
Alex does not
End up saying
I support
Or anything like that
But you can't believe everything that Rogers Donuts
And this is going to get integrated into his world
I predict Within
2 days
He's going to come out and say that he supports
I'm guessing it will be that quick
I don't know yet
But
Tumi
Abyss episode
Is the end of me being curious
Yeah Rodger Stone did it
Well it's
That's right Russia setup
11 Rodger Stone was the point man who knocked it over
No just the one
But I mean I take it
So transparent it's just like
Yeah I know it like rogered
That could have done
20 minutes of research
Listening to a couple of clips
In bitlife
Like this this this
Send this a lot so I'm just
Going to say Trump.
Alex is going to believe
Because of the groundwork that's been laid by Alex's pro-russia position
Because of
Fellow member of the 45 groups
Pieczenik coming in
I'm speeding Alex
The Narrative that Trump
Knows everything he's on the right side of
Alex was Prime from a week ago when piszczek was on
You remember that Steve was asking to come on
To come on as a setup
For this press
Like a week and a half later when Rodger Stone shows up
Mysteriously on his book tour
Book much they just talk about how great Trump is
It's my investigation
It is over
But I'm going to keep going
Until
Yeah it's okay
We at we know we know what happened
Now
I think you and I
And our policy walks out there
No
Astoria vets
No one else
There is a
Massive
I don't know what the exact connection
With Trump and Russia is
I don't know
But we know damn well
But Alex has been compromised
Alex has an asset for Russia
And
He's a gullible f***
Being used by the members of the
The 45 group
Steve pieczenik
The I don't know the rest of the people who were in a Rodger stone for sure
He's being used as a puppet
Football on their part in order to get elected
Probably
Serving Russia
It's very very very clear
Yeah
Game over
Congratulations everybody
We made it to the end we figured out the knowledge that we needed and
To being impotent
It is kind of
It is kind of funny
That I
Like there's a certain amount of
Silliness
To the idea that all of these powerful
Secretive brilliant man
I have to go to
A dumb
Paranoid delusional schizophrenia
And doodle
Minimal amount of
Convincing
For then
Millions of
People
They could do it themselves
Years and years of radicalizing
Fringe of firing his audience
To the point where there are millions of people who are up for grabs
Do the brilliance
Strategic move
To tap into that
Because
They're not going to leave you
They're brainwash
Like every want to listen to Infowars
People
You can see it in the trans
You conceived it back when Alex was saying the Trump was mobbed up
The callers were saying
Started to say I like what you saying but I don't trust him
Every single caller mirror.
I guarantee within a week
Everyone's going to say Zhang
Trump is awesome
He's our only hope he's already had colors
A couple and then you also have callers that I haven't even like I haven't kept it everything just cuz
Then we don't make us a Five Hour podcast
Call in and say
The Dare that it's just
You know they talk about Rush Limbaugh fans being dittoheads
Yeah I had to signing off on everything Rush Limbaugh believes that's nothing
Compared to Alex Jones
And the reason he's dangerous
Is it smaller but more fervor
I don't know definitely smaller but varfer but yeah you're right but
The reason it's dangerous
Impark
Parcel
His indoctrination of his audience
Is convincing them that their free thing
Part of it is
Convincing them
That what makes you info Warriors
Is it you resist
The brainwashing of the globalist
You think for yourself
Wow at the same time falling in line with literally every married if I'm pushing that happens too large
Russian propaganda
F****** insane
Old episode of ours
Episode where I was making the argument that Alex
Is not someone who's involved
With Russia he's just an idiot
Full
Full circle and all it takes is listening to his goddamn show
Specific
Convincing myself at least
That like oh he's not
Sing a true thing
It's not real
In
Whether it's
Destabilizing countries
Or a demon
So I mean it's very clear Alex Smith
But he got drilled by f****** Russian intelligence
Didn't do anything about it
I mean that's all you need to know
Could be our investigation
Rodger Stone interview are all you need
All the rest of it is just
Proof
More proof
Like number of
Twisted I know we're not done
I mean with with our investigation
Curiosity
Twisted Tea
Turns all along the way
Enforced on what it is
He's doing yeah
And then
The fact that it just
F******
Funnel Vision
Compromised
Rodger Stone
Made him part of
Rodger stone that was my first prediction
Surrounding it I could never
This is not
So what is it
So now that we know
He's
Pizza Ranch
Propaganda
Is there anything
Do
No
I don't know.
Yeah I guess
India wants
The cover this
Beaufort got f******
80 hours approved to go through
But
I don't know I don't know what we can do
It's terrible to imagine they would do their job
For free tell your friend
Everybody you can let him know
Post about this on
I'm not involved in any of that red world so if you are please
Put the information out there
Weave
Really f***** up stuff no one knows
If you can get the word out that the word out if you can't I appreciate you listening
And that's enough
Yeah cuz what do we want to get killed killed
Alright
I hope you'll get killed everybody
Not everybody gets killed because they discovered Russian propaganda
I work plenty of ways to go that was not too bad ironically he's a cutout
The things you chooses
You saying so
For tonight at 8 p.m. central
It's knowledge fight it is
Purely Outlets
To get the volume
It's it's
The
Entire
Republican strategy
Doing something
Obvious
And then just saying that
No we're not doing
They are
The psychological Serta blooper
We were looking at it
With that Knowledge from the beginning
Sort of Revelation
Franklin
People accuse me of being Russian is like
Oh you're arrested
Yeah
And now that we have the information that he loves people gets off on it
Standing up to
People it really brings into Focus
Very harrowing picture
Easily compromised man
Who's suffering
So much
I want to be empathic
Hi my heart right go out to
Because it's
We are using a lot of pain
But
Because the way he expresses his pain hurt
Millions of people
Hello will we will continue this investigation until we get the Americana 2.0
Going
Twitch TV
Flash mileage
Can see how long my hair is
Video podcast
Start but we will see
And because people might be curious about that
We will not be releasing those episodes as podcast
So as not
Overwhelmed
We will be posting them on the twitch Channel they will remain there is archived episode
And I believe I'll be posting them
To YouTube
You can get them
If you can't lick I know we have a lot of listeners and foreign country
Hey if you can't have access to those things
Looks like those websites are blocked or something like that
Let me know. Send me an email at knowledge fight at gmail.com and I'll try and figure something out
Do I send you
MP40
Like that
I hope you're interested in that at all
Cuz I've got I've done a lot of work preparing that's going to be real Steve no one cares
Almost as much of a bomber is finding out that Alex Jones
Who is this dog
Yeah but my XBR website.com
It's got all kinds of things on there where on iTunes
Leave a review the shows of people can find us more easily so the rest of the world
Is a compromise a side of a house
That would be a nice thing for
You can check us out there leave a review
Send a message
I always like to communicate with Pete
Yeah you know
What I
Hear from
So many
Somebody people who are anti
You know a lot of them are Russian
But I'll tell you
There's one guy
I don't know if he's a rough
Russian propaganda
I mean we don't know anything about this
Well that's part of this investigation
I don't know who shot him
There's just one thing that I would want
Are you related to Michael Ray
That's a good question
Appointment
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color