Holding
Alex
To sit around
Little bit about Alex Jones
Yeah that's pretty much that's most of it
Let me ask you a question
So
When the the Earth was
About three billion
Immediately
Following I got to stop you already.
2000 years old we all know that
Fair enough
Family it is sick
Thousand Years
So the Earth was about 4,000 years old window old
No it was it was immediately following the Earth being just a giant volcano
Right
Are you sure I know this pretty confident that he has
Race memory
Trees that were around then our
Still around now they are with
I know a lot about Alex
I don't know anything about Alex
Through another installment
Of my investigation
The 2015 what the hell happened to Alex Jones
Him to join up with Team Trump
Learn nothing today we will learn
Zero about Trump
0 about the campaign but we will learn
A great deal
About crazy weirdos that Alex
That will be the flavor
I'm a big fan of crazy weirdo
What was demonstrated in the past last we left off on
On the show in the investigation
Alex had indicated the humane
In contact with Russia
He was spouting nothing
But pro-putin
Lime
All day.
Supported Donald
1776 0.0
Whitinsville chat on Americana
If that's where he is I think that's the end of
It is much it like
Maybe
I'm starting to realize more and more that the reality is
Concurrent
We're doing that we think are
They aren't okay
One of them today
Investigate
Alex Jones love
Yeah
Rat
Investigation about Trump
And I don't think that they're necessarily 121 related
Oh yeah no problem I don't think early Thursday
Like specific causation
Because
We're going to find out
He doesn't
Like I'm after his
The Great
All this stuff just
Divinity
I think that's
How would we do that
Okay
Remember the words were gripped
Correlation
Causation thing or maybe it's not
See now that you know
No earned it from the book Freakonomics I remember nothing
You just blew my
Awesome
I feel like I got to give you a hand
Speaking of handicap is a handicap
Colleges are basically brainwashing
Today November 10th
November 12th
Something that happened
Right around then
Becomes very important to Alex's narrative
And he gets off the
Political bent
Altogether
Victorville
And that is
That the University of Missouri
President step down
That's a big deal
It is when the president steps down
You know that's a big
You think you know what a system
Tim Wolfe
University of Missouri
It's cool the present of all of them not just
University of Missouri Columbia University of missouri-rolla
He stepped down and it was due to pressure that was put on him
Bye
It's not even necessarily black lives matter protest
But it was African Americans
Who had very serious
Complaints
About to
The University was dealing with relation
Piece of s***
He oversaw a
System
That was negligent
The student group
I came out of
It sort of naturally came together called
Concerned stood
As a reference
21950 was the fur
Universe
System
Allowed in Blackstone
There's a whole bunch of stuff that we're going to get into the
There's a lot about the reality of that situation
Did I happen to know a lot about because I don't think of any reason why you might know a lot about I'm from
University
My parent
Release my dad taught there for a long time and I still have it
Associate
Yeah I have a lot of a lot of boots on the ground
In Columbia
Pretty aware of what's going on there
Wondered about the
Nations in that kind of b*******
Right
Is like
We need you to go away so we'll hire somebody who can actually implement the
That we need done
But to me it seems more like it's just brand
You know like whatever
A company
F**** up so hard
Username
Right I think I think there's something
Nothing to that
But
I definitely don't think
Change
That much
Missouri is still a very race
Problems
Beyond even the
Demands
The students were making
Reiterate
Even after that
Course
Carol
So let's get to this year's
The first clip
From November 10th
I said yesterday the professors are getting kicked out the
Shein
The Climb of being white
Fairies become a crime
Hysteria that has been created
Young mindless adult
Black member
Exercise of power
Feminist professor
F***
Identifying their writings and what they stand for
Yeah pretty bad
What the f***
Sorry thanks for that deal with all
Walworth
Even in f****** Missouri
Which should be on fire
St. Louis should be burned
Because St Louis
Knokes to play
In the story of what Alex Jones is talking about
Cuz this concerns
Student night
50 group
Largely came out of
A lack of
On the administration
Park
Blase
Indignant occasions of violence of
Against
I don't even think they went that far because it sort of a talking about it
Master and the student
Hey recognize that this is something
There wasn't really a response
Is Ace
Decadron
Charcoal on the wall
Dancehall and I April
Richmond resident Bradley
Becker days later
And charged him with second-degree property
How much motivated by discriminate
Becker pleaded guilty in October
So that happened
Like I've brought up many many times
When I went to
Where some guys
You were right
Put a bunch of
All around the legion to believe
Agent office
That Is Random with roots
Some stuff
Situation
Why why why
Possible reasons
I know
Like what what kind of ass
That must be what it is
So they're intimidating them
Know your place
Do you because
You're not an idiot
Conceived up
Something you would want to do
But if you are someone
Super caught up in your whiteness
And you're threatened by a quote-unquote uppity black people things like
Like the clan used to do with burning crosses
Be like a workout
Where are you
Like they have to get together and figure out the best way to be a f****** races or undoubtedly was
Exactly
Photo like
Blue Sky Thinking like throwing s*** out there like what
What's the best way to be racist that's not subtle enough
I lived in Missouri they didn't have formal meetings they were just meet down by the river
Orb down by the big
Tree up which is a real thing
The real awesome
Hey my buddies used to go drink
Tree
Huge f****** tree those out in the middle of nowhere
We don't need Missouri
Great you guys where you guys were on the fence
In the Civil War I'm out that part of my history and I had a lot of great memories out by the big toe
So it on September 12th of
September 12th
These is called the n-word by a group of young people
Driving by in a pickup
Student body president
Then
They deleting the black Collegian
At a play rehearsal
But they were putting on
For homecoming
As they are part of the homecoming Court
And a man walked by
I called them all the n word
Started screaming the n-word at the
It should be decriminalized
To get your ass
You call a group
I would say so there were your honor he called me the n-word
Good
Concerns do Administration
And a lot of professors
Losing a lot of
Including a lot of these.
Humanities
Apartments that I was super familiar with in college
They started to get on board but the administrative level
They were not
People were not dealing with these issue
Concerned student nights
50 group
I came into
And
Homecoming
There was the parade
Satanic or C have
The student
Groups
You have the president of the um sis
Thank you the part of the parade
Student 19
50 group gets together and they block his car
Formal protest
Kiss car in order to get
To recognize
Their demands
But they've not
So at this point
See how deep
If you are on the right side
You are a groupie
People who
Republic
And who are just
Telling everybody like
Hey
This is what's going on
Right if you're on the wrong side you're a group of
People who in the dark of night throw cotton
Like it's pretty pretty over
Just stop in
Are we the ones I really don't feel great about what we're doing
I don't like you
I don't think that Jedediah is necessarily
Go more towards the area of like moose
Oh that's a good point
Alright it's just the brand hillbilly name
Okay
That's very different
Block symbols car
They get
Moved Along by security
But
It's one of the big things that they had issue with
What's the Timberwolves did get out of the car and address their concerns
He didn't get out and say anything to them
Or do anything
Calm down the situation
Rite-Way
F****** white dude
Hit one of them with his car
But
This is actually something that I think is very
Iffy
Because I've watched the video this and it's
The car is moving very slowly
And it also appears that
The person that he hits got in the way of his car after
After being out of the way of
Okay
I see that there is a little bit of a both sides thing on this
Incredibly unacceptable at any speed to hit someone with you
Your car but I don't think it wasn't
I don't think it would have had a
Slow reaction
Or whoever was driving
And I don't think it was like a f*** you want to hit you with the car
But of course it made people even better
Because it comes on
Tale of
Him and not being response
The students to make
And it's like even a bigger f*** you
So at that point the concerned student
1850 released a list of Demands
And one of them is with
Teen Wolf needs
To resign you have not done a good job of addressing
Our concern
He's not making
For minority students
And on top of that with one of their other big demands was
Representation
Faculty
Minority
They wanted 10%
Of the students
Excuse me of the faculty
B2B
Representative
Population representation
Right by people
Sound of the
And at that point it was
It was not represented at all 01
It was at a point
Greater representation
Event beyond that they also one of their big demand
More funding
Ford Mental Health Services and on top of that
Representation of minority within the people working
Student Health Centers and psychiatric
Psychological
Helps
Because that also
Completely and utterly
Reasonable request
Write the only one that you could act like you could Kim
Conceivably argue with
Is the removal of the president
Of the school but I do think it's reasonable under the circumstances
So after that
Jail time to
Found a swastika made out of poop
Are in the Mark Twain residence
Before and we kind of have an ironic
That kind of has an ironic feel to it right it's hard to say
The feeling that we had is like
You are actually a Nazi wouldn't make a
Swastika out of s*** and it's it's confusing but at the same time
People took that as a message of like well
It is not the iconography
And that people took it to field
I feel like the message there though is that Nazis are s***
The association
Call associate
President Bill Donnelly said
After this event
Including the others lost
Schedule
Amir month-and-a-half earlier
After this event
Become clear to me that the inclusivity of our residence hall has been
Which is a reasonable
So
Which is 6 days after the
Swastika is found
The concerned student 1950
Student-faculty president
Unfortunately this meeting
Did not go Gray
Here's a quote
Wolf verbally acknowledged that he cared for black students
At the University of Missouri
However he also reported he was not completely aware of systemic racism
ISM sexism
A patriarchy on campus
Sounds very patriarchal
How to say right it's the
Shows given the
Pattern of info
And this list
Stuff that we're going over to
Included a lot of other stuff
Of course
So at that point there was October
On November 2nd
Twenty-five-year-old grad student
Jonathan Butler
Started a hunger strike
He believed that it was that serious
And he was ready to die
For the cause and other students
Bring out on campus
In solidarity with him
Scott City
Started to
Exist on the,
And I receive Missouri security we're like we're very respectful
Do this, thing where they were not going to f*** around
They got the pr of it
No one forced errors
So here is a quote from Jonathan
Send Butler
As much as the experiences on campus
Have not been that great for me
I had people call me the n-word I have someone write the n-word on the door of my residence hall
For me it really is about a call for justice
I'm fighting for the black community on campus
Because Justice is worth fighting for
And Justice is worth starving
He ended up having a hunger strike I think it lasted about a week
Because
On
The 9th I believe ya on the 9th
Tim Wolfe ended up
Stepping down
Now that only happen
Because on November 7th
The universe
Missouri football team
Went on
Strike
To join
Up with Jonathan Butler
And the student
Two were
Attempts on campus
So they would have lost
Money
He'd wonder why
Speed football team announced
The day add pledge
To stop participating in football-related activities
For the remainder of the season
Unless wolf resigned or was fired
Head to head coach Gary pinkel
I was on in support of this
Tweeted out a picture pricing
He tweeted out a picture of the
Entire football program
With the subject line
The Mizzou family stands as one we are united we are behind our players
Hashtag
Concerned student
Signed Gary pinkel
So at that point
Situation
Is very serious
Because
The university would have to pay $1000000
The Brigham Young University
If they canceled the neck
Of course the wolf
Immediately resign
Actually that's not fair
The student football team
On the 7th makes that announce
On the 8th
Wolf is like I'm not going anywhere
He's gone
You going on tonight
But it also comes after lunch
Slater's called on him
Representative a Republican
Chairman of the Missouri house committee on higher education
Wolf can no longer effectively lead the university system
Have you called for wolf or he called wolf reaction to protesters
Concerned Alice
Missouri Missouri Republican
I mean
Two things there
Maybe friend
Also
Think about how surprised
We are
At a republican condemning races
Or any representative really Governor Jay Nixon
Hit Republic
Cancel hard because
Does everybody like
We got to give credit to
Inherently
Places that if any one of them goes
Hey racism is bad we're like holyshit you're a hero
Governor Jay Nixon said that he supported
These concerns must be addressed in the University of Missouri is a place where all students
Can pursue their dreams
Living environment respect
Tolerance
Conclusion
Bunch of Faculty members that they were going to Stage a walkout and then immediately Tim Wolfe
Yes so that's so is
Is a crime to be white
Tim Wolfe his big crime is that he is white
Weed that makes perfect
It's crazy it looks perfect it is it is a massive
Inability or unwillingness
To deal with the
The concerns are being brought to you by
So
Imagine if it was a white
Right
Would would Alex feel the same let's not even
That is the reality of the situation
Left out some stuff that did happen that Alex
Doesn't bring up
Because some of it ended up being a little bit of both
Like there was
There were rumors going around that the clan was on campus
Some shooting at windows and stuff like that
There were just internet gossip and rumors that started going around that accidentally ended up getting way more play
Play then they should have apologized that was bad information that we got
Sensationalism
The rest of the stuff is very real
And the rest of the stuff is legitimate concerns
Now we get in
And go through the episode I apologize if that was a little bit long
But I needed a reality
No apologies
To say about Missouri
My home state
That for all its troubles
I still love dearly but we can't meet you all right
I'd be happy to be a moose
We've got one good mousse so we can't get to
Call Joseph Missouri immediately
He gets really sidetracked
Credibly f*****-up trap topic
Here's one of them
I was growing up
Anywhere in the city in Dallas
Every week sometimes
Couple times a week
Jump out of cars
This is our neighborhood
Buckle up Knuckle Up
Sometimes it was
Oh boy
Many times when college-age men
What show off and want to beat up high school students
Post hole digger
That's a shovel
When people got basically you do hurt really bad
The big combo
Organized somebody else
46070 years old
And Rob them and beat them up
Discrimination
You are told
No way
Just running around phrase
Because
Working well with others in company
I love you
And totally absolutely
Your brain
Hazing ritual
Exploring Revolution
Military science
This is the most base level
10000 BC level science
So at this point the reason I left
Well I left in its entirety there because I wanted
To get the like the beginning of him being like I wasn't racist but not racist
There's mostly minorities being racist
That's white people right right how white people are the victim yet again
If you go to his
Current state of being I don't know if that's fair
But at the same time it goes into zen-like a call this tribal like how people go beat up gay that's why gay bars
Cuz they're not normal
But the reason I kept it in as a whole was the journey from the
Racist not racist gang fights
To the end or he's like
Beast
Who are
Making legitimate
Concern
And not being heard at all so they take it to the next level
Of this hunger strike that public protest
It's getting the
Lobbied for the football team 2
You know boycott
Think I might have been the wrong decision
But all those things because they were
When they were younger
F*** no closer than
Philly protest
Rites of Passage racism
Why do you want to come
Now we were looking
Love
Liberty
Informed delivery
Alright fine I'm going to go to Breitbart
Define
Conception is your on the
Like I said we walk through the history
Just a day earlier
Tim Wolford resign
He's responding
It's not the month
Lead up to this but he could have been aware of if you wanted to
Nah but
His conception is that what's going on is like the Chinese student Revolution
That happen
That one
But he's saying that this is the beginning of that
Right and that it's just going to turn us into a Maui state
I all this s***
So he's going
Kill all the intellect
Probably not
No sew
He's responding to it as
As if it was
Instead of dealing with the reality of people
And so here's how he responds
Which
Is really scary
Missouri
Over the top
The first years of Mao in China
Protest
With the young people
The most
By the system
Absolutely
40 hour are you guys
Our forebears were ready for this
We got the jump on you about 200 something years
Propaganda
Mobile.
So
Do you think he
He must not know the context at all right he's just going straight from the hip like he heard that a white fur
President stepped the black people protest
So he's just shooting from the hip this is all white victimhood
He has no idea what the f*** is going on family doesn't realize
Is it peaceful at all or who cares if it's peaceful
Something should be burned out very burned down the only thing
Lydia ever brings up really are
The poops Waze
And someone maybe allegedly yelling the n-word it somebody at a party
He brings up now there's one other thing that we should do
Cuz it does come up eventually
First of all he's threatening
That's what he's doing
Our forefathers thought about this
Yeah that's f***** up but the other thing is
Are you taking the Second Amendment
Is entirely about shooting black people cuz I think that's what Alex
The downside of what
Fenton Missouri
Alex will y'all about this later
God bless him
In for it
Saudis
Set up an
Publix
They did not want reporters coming in bothering
And so they were trying to
Reporters
Do leave
And an unfortunate video came out
I love this lady
Melissa click
Who was a professor at the University
Was trying to get
A reporter called I need some muscle over here
She's terrible
And that's unfortunate bad opt
Disagree
Disagree entirely
Muscle over there
Agree with you
It's not it's not okay
I I get the point
And journalist
Should have respected
That hate don't bother these people
They're setting up a
A peaceful place where they can be left alone
But to make a point
And they are also going to be portrayed
For how by those p
Absolutely I agree of their own volition
But it's
The same time
It's not appropriate
To contextualize it is we need muscle to forcibly remove people from a public space
More with you
Without the look
What what is it
Listen
They have done every
Single f****** thing that they could
Finally if you don't have the threat of violence
People these people
Alarcon Alyssa
In the same way that the Black Panthers
Stand around
Whenever a police whenever a cop was arresting
A black dude
They would stand around in
Full uniform
With guns
Right
In their hands now
That's f****** muscle
Violence against them
Fine
You're arguing
Completely
Point I agree with your point in as much as that goes
But I don't believe
But it's appropriate
It would be appropriate if they just had
With guns
Go ahead right scary
That would be appropriate
What's not appropriate
Is forcibly removing people from
Workspace for no
That is not appropriate
If they had a show of muscle
Down there
But it's not okay for the like let's say the Black Panthers to run people off
Who aren't doing any
Anything that is
In the situation that you brought up
Rabbits
Especially not appropriate
For this
Professor
To be acting in a coordinating e fashion
When that wasn't her position
I recognized and you do have some good
There is a difference
Between the scenarios that you're presenting in what actually we're talkin to
At the same time I think we can agree to this
Degree and just agree that it's terrible.
Gave people something to attack and Melissa click was pretty round
F*** you bought
Yeah I'm doing this right. Fire
Right
People involved in the movement weren't like
Hey great good time
You're making us look terrible
This is not the this is not what we want to present ourselves at and a
Forty-five-year-old
Red-headed white lady
So she's not even she's definitely not the one you want speak
Looking for a gallon we need muscle to get this journalist out of
Zoe
That's more where I'm coming from with all that context
I'm much more
Towards your side
I think it's
Not the best
It's just an unfortunate element of
What otherwise was a really good
And really well put together protein
I just I'm just this this place now where
It's like the entirety of the system
Is the problem
And Ever every protest that we have
The women's March was
Huge
What the
The f*** did it do
Boston earlier the
Yeah
Did it
No no but thing entirely within the system doesn't
To be effective
Because the system
Itself is
Is the issue
The system itself is
Set up
To stop
Define Simba system
And
Meaning of not respecting the rights
Of the press
Not respect
In the rights of other people
They're not mutually
Exclusive you can still work outside the system
And not
Trample someone else's
Is right yeah
And I don't I don't think that
The First Amendment
Being
The system
Is the right way to look at
I agree there's other things that should be done there's other
Disruptive
Things that we should be doing outside of
Just
Protesting
Getaround I don't know if it's the right answer but the Democratic Socialist they're making some
Real Headway in terms of organizing protests
Right
Just be having meetings
Things like that and maybe that's something
What is outside of our normal system
They could be helpful
I don't think
That
Having muscle to
Forcibly remove journalist
Outside the system in the right way
That's a step backwards
Supposed to step forward
I agree
Let's move on.
Okay I want I want I want to be angry and I want to do all that stuff but you are you are correct
This is why the podcast is wonderful
I can smoke you down February
Anger
But I don't disagree with other things not this
Matter of planning
Execution is opposed
In terms of
Like I agree with your point but I don't agree with the knee-jerk
Response you have to
Situation situation
Like we can agree on the gold immediate reaction
People have to get worked up hot and bothered
About like how she is right to get muscle over there
I think we got to we got to be very careful when we examine
The corporate media being
Again
Okay well then
Journalist
Play what is the person doing
Like is the person
Is the journalist
Being
Adjective
Something about
I'm going to ask
This team is space that you guys are
Who created on what's going on
It is absolutely different from the
Is the campus paper
Semesters
F*** her I'm out on alright good now let's see if you defend Alex
It is his claims that he's been the victim of racism
The last few years does multi-finger this
Come on guys you're just looking for trouble
I care about you and I bet you do.
No
IPad
IOS
Weather models
So
Describing panhandling
He's a victim of it because he's white in the
Right type of reparations
Has a large homeless population
We go back to over and over again
Your black people
White people
At this point everyone has transcended race
Everything stayed the same
I left that clapping just to give you a sort of context
For like
With his own experience
The raisins
Which is deeply flawed
Is there anyway
Through these guys
They're white.
Victimhood is
Really believe that
He's the victim of racism
Shows like this
Or people
Understanding more
Like I really think that
People who listen to his show
Listen to shows like this
It could give him a better context of the world in the things that
Talkin about
Maybe
Program.to Buy
So I think that if his base eroded and people really understood this
The situation
You talkin about it where the lies are
And why he
He's lying about
I think it could help
I don't know if it would ever reach him
But if you hit it
Is pocketbook hard enough of people not buying
Supplements
Right maybe
Maybe there's a chance
Yeah
President of the University of Missouri
He's still around at this point in November 4th
I don't know I don't know if there's much hope in
Educating out
Of educating
And helping
The other people
Not have these narrative
Psychological studies always put forth
Whenever you bring facts
Or any of the
The s*** towards
People who look
Get mad they just get mad and more entrenched in their white victimhood
Yeah yeah that's probably true
I'm a good answer but there's
Boy I think not
Trying is not the answer
Yeah I agree with you there
Let's get to this next clip
Cheese wedges
Green all over the
In the next life Alex Jones
His big problem is
Is sjw
Social justice
Warriors
Crop up
This
Parallel and it's really unfortunate
Such
Obviously good things into epithet
Right
Social justice
Is good
And you should fight for
They do
What how is that
How can you
Turn that into some
His belief is that the globalist
Invertebrate
This is actually social injustice
Black lives matter is just White lives don't matter that's
Entrenched in his head
I agree
Anyway
This clip
It really fun
And I will explain why
On the other end of it but it has to do with social justice Warriors
And another period of
This is a parallel Richard
Parallel
I bet you did
Witch Trials versus the social justice
Emeritus
The episode is one of the nation's most notorious cases
Political
Cautionary Tale
Dangers of
Isolationist Behavior
False accusations
Right yeah
Watch actually engaged
Look at the Inquisition and lot of other operations very different
Claiming other people
Corrupt
He just changed it over with social justice
Now the other guy quotes
Asteria
Socialism
Politically correct
Justice Warriors instead of Salem witch trial
It's
Oh this is
Well-thought-out
That's what makes notes not right
And then
Like but they were worshipping
The problem is
Like let's take the Inquisition
And stuff out of it
Because that's totally
If you look at what's going on
In terms
Special because everybody's mad about
Missouri situation
The Salem Witch Trials there is a
Glaring parallel
And it's not
This
What it is is the Salem witch trials
Were largely about
Taking property away
From people who had wronged
I always get the names mixed up
Families involved
The Putnams I think the porters with a good
Can't remember but it was about Hatfield
It's whatever you want
It was largely about a bunch of either widowed or single women who owned land in Headland
Disputes with the Putnam family
The patriarchy
Putnam family
We're the ones
Who kept getting
Pointed out as witches
Buck's social Norm
People who didn't go to church
A white lady who married a black guy
Yep those were the things 7
I can't allow her to have
Those word what with motivating the Salem Witch Trials it wasn't about Mass hysteria it wasn't
And if you look at what's going on
And Missouri situation
The people who are against it
Are trying
Power
In the hands of white people white males
Specifically I always keep saying that the crime is being
It's not you're not listening
Do what's going on at all
It's about maintaining the
Status quo that is racially and
Gender Lee Bass
Yeah well so that's unfortunate
Since you could describe it as a
Is a mass hysteria in that these people are
Drumming up amasis
Asteria
Oligarchs
Utilizing poor people
Accomplish their goals
In the same way as with
About there
The oligarchs are using their power
Drama
You know
Anti everybody but white people
In this in this case if you want to do them
The parallel the people who are protests
About the ignoring of racial incidents and stuff like that
Black student
The concerned student rights
50 are the people who were accused of being witches
They are the victims
Damascus Syria
The reporters are the administration or even Alex
Is Elkhorn
The wiser you guys are creeping socialism
So that's all bulshit
Text Libby gets take a little break
Unfortunately
God dammit
Because we have a guest
Who comes in
That we've dealt with
What is
Guess that I have met first
It is ma'am
Mancow I was actually booked to do a show and then
Metro close
Call Long's
Story and I was
I don't need any I knew a lot of I heard that
Sprite
I'd heard a lot
From people
John on his show
I got to do it for like
Did it
It was as bad as everybody
I told me how is a f****** a******
He is
People he broadcast
With shades on
In the in the middle of the day inside
Commercial breaks
Storms off to his office
And then comes back out so you won't have
How to talk to people during commercial
The two guests on the show where me
And some guy who is there from it like a Catholic charity
Any treated both of us like ask
Miserable
When I was when I was in the waiting room
Broadcast
The last days
The show is two hours
They broadcast
The last days
Last hour for the first hour
And then the second hour live
It's very convoluted
Green Room
I was watching the last
And like
Ringo
Watching computer
Play great or bad thing by Ringo Starr
And here's Mancow just treating him like it
Could go badly for Open Mic comedian
I think it is kind of funny to Trego like a dick
If I could do it all over I would have been
Anasshole back brace
6 in the morning
May be hungover for
From shows the night before
Alright man
You got it the producer kept ask
Refurb it
That I could do like
He could set me up for a bit
The only thing I really recall is how much I hated
And
How much you talked about being
I'm friends with the
Blues
The band The Moody Blues
40 years The Moody Blues have been fighting
Ringo's Pacifica Noble fight
Hate Ringo
Best there like come on man
Such a dick
And a liar
You know I would have to decide what Missouri
What they should have said is that okay
You're going to college for free
And you're done
UCF
Every year I
I pay for some of the college because it's not
Based on
I bet there's no why
Warriors command
And they took the SATs in about 2 minutes
Weekend
Commitment
You push through whatever University
Morons are usually violent look at the worst team in the NFL
Violent morons of Mizzou
Destroy this man and entice just it's it is something isn't a teaser
Strange Days
So idle employing their these violent moron
Clearly talking about the tech people is a trouble it's trouble for his argument that we don't care
That they don't care
They preferred nose
They don't like
That's a big issue
At the same time if we want to look at is complain
It is f***** up the way that psychology
Napoli's
Oh absolutely
But there's a better way to discuss that probably
Meijer
Ncaa's
Yeah something like that
What I went to frost when I went to the University of Missouri I had a couple of
Strong's called in French
But there were a couple of acquaint
Chances that I had who were on the football team
And I was in a logic class
Two of them
Super nice
Work real hard
He was in class everyday
Couple times I was walking down the
Street and pulled over offered me a ride
Coming to the movie theater that I worked at the time
Who is super nice
Baltimore super nice
Other one would sleep through class
And at one point offer
To pay me to do his homework
There are situations like that
The people who are the student-athletes
And make tons of money for the University
Get to do and get away with
It's pretty f***** up
It's pretty booked up how many hours a week do they work on
Tons
Well more than 40
So if you are like
Okay we need you to work 40 hours a week
Also we need you to do all of this s***
Right and we're not going to pay you
The high-level logic class
There's no business
I don't know what happened
But be that as it may
I'm not saying that you did anything
He's a system in place that needs to be
Maybe logic
Put them to sleep
Rather than take care of melatonin
Missed calls
Hockey massage
Okay
My wife
And I were arguing
And you're overreacting
She goes after using logic and thinking this all out and looking at the facts under your right
I overreacted
Would never happen
It's all emotion
Ride
That's so like
1980s
It's just evidence that says something about men
Are from Mars
Women
That is
So I actually didn't load right
That sucks
You can tell
You can tell how much
Assholes
Even their fake laugh
Annoying
Totally when we
It's real
No it's not
It's not funny
Real or fake
Anyway look we don't need to
Belabor this point who cares
Next clip loaded correctly
We'll see is Mancow pretending
Doesn't live in the suburb
A boy
Brother
Understand I live in Beirut
Broad City
Located low-grade
He lives in the city of Chicago
Like I said I was on his show
I know where he works
He works
On Michigan Avenue and South water that is where the
The studio was if you don't know Chicago that is a Nao block
Away from the Magnificent Mile.
You can possibly be it might even still be a part of the Magnificent Mile I don't know where that starts or ends
But it hit Wacker there
And you know it
It's much less
On the side of South water but it's like a block away from that expensive
That's nonsense
Even dead birds have to step over cuz they have
Tentatively
Cleanup Crews
All around that area
Like if you work in a building
And you're twenty feet away from my eyeball pain
Aurate
Petit Marche I would love the way that you
Obama
Go f*** yourself and pretending you're in the s***
F******
Warrior on the Southside
I work until tonight I wouldn't even claim that
Cuz it's not true
Oh no
I lived on the west side of
Chicago for a while and
I did
Bus stop
That was just
On fire
It was just on fire.
F*** is wrong with you
I'm dessert like their response becomes
Like that that I felt a little bit bad about but at the same time
I don't have any responsibility
I was walking home from
From the train and I saw a guy just laying on the street
That guy probably needs help
What's the same time there were three people standing next to him like sort of looking at him and there was a cop car across the
The street park
And the people like the cops were looking
Bring in that direction of like
Needs to be done it's going to be done who cares
What do you mean you know the one where
I don't even know if that's
Whatever
The famous
Story of a woman
Who was
Crying out for
For help o b water effect
Well somebody else's
Except for the fact those people standing next to him We're clearly engaged
With him laying back
Very important
Reminder
Not always will people last
Should have gotten some more
So at this point Mancow pivots and wants to talk a little bit about the election
Look I want to talk about Gamboa quickly
I don't believe are you ready for this
Do you talk about the different network cyborg for I I've been in these
TV newsrooms
I work for fox in Chicago for the last 2 years
Behind the scenes of CBS
Other newscaster
What Donald Trump said was correct
They do pick the winner and the loser
Again I don't know that it's Senator Alex
I was there
All the big names
Play pretty-much
And the fight was Hillary versus
Will Hillary's near Dad
He's very sick
Really stupid she's really running an awful campaign
And on the right
Jeb Bush was going to have all the money
So I don't
Believe his presentation of that
Insights
Spot on lamb.
Absolutely
So I believe is maybe he was in a me
Somewhere
That's probably the expensive
His Insider ISM says I was there when it was decided
As if
The globalist
Had Mancow Muller in for a f******
Session where they're like hey hey buddy you want to be in on the ground floor of this
The gang of 42
Bastard turned out to be f****** manto I love how I labeled one of these clips
I feel very proud of it
Repeat it on a cowardly racist
For you.
Batman cowl
Vladimir Putin
Turns out he also likes
Check this s*** out
I'm actually very proud of the American people
The Communist but whatever they requested
What was selected for them and then on the right keyboard picking Trump
And and
The establishment
Because we're not following the script
Listen
Marine
You are big supporters of the military
They have to do a lot of things that they don't like
The deal isn't that that hospital those poor kids that were killed at hospital
Cleveland Heights
Jeb Bush
He doesn't want other bush
Family
Middle East
And what what that was was the storage this is I just come from a top Marine
This sad. You know they're cutting off the bushes money supply around the world
You may remember that hospital was Bob in Syria
What it really was
Was a storage place of methamphetamines
Billions of dollars worth of
The world
For the Bush family
This is what I've Been Told
Cutting off
Establishment in the bushes
There is a underground Revolution
So you suck
Real
A great source George facility for meth
He didn't
F******
Jesus Christ man that was killed
Warren.
That they were there
Is Without Borders
Because
Ostensibly they were treating
Everybody fog of War
F*** that
F*** off but I want to point out more about this clip Beyond just that stupid
This is
This is indicative of Alex Jones's
Style
Cuz what Mancow does is making outrageous
Is
Trying to take out bushes money supply
And so this
Warcry
My dad was actually
Was actually taking out this methamphetamine
Depot
Or whatever
Now Alex
I am getting on with the interview
Say it
Heading that way he allows the audience to
The integrated
Into their worldview
Is plausible deniability so when anyone attacks him is like
You think that's f****** hospital was a methamphetamine Depot I just let him stay that and I just agreed with
Does all the time right now
Cuz if Mancow was on our show any threat that we'd be like hold the f*** on
We need more man details
Now I want to work
Alright
Who turns out my show starting early tonight
Imagine if anybody ever actually got prosecuted
War crimes
Be Wild
Idaho
Yeah it look if you do that you're going to have to excuse everybody
It's going to start getting real bad
But there has to be some sort of
Consequence otherwise why do you think I just passed
I think we talked about Eminem's come out later my beliefs on
Aggressive taxation
Millionaires
But on top of that
If we're actually going to
The world
We're going to have to do
Is prosecute a lot of people for work right
I think we're going to have to really deal with like
Getting rid of this idea of American
Exceptionalism
Like when we do it it's not that bad
In order to get the
Respective the world back
Subway
The idea that we were part of the world not above it
I think that'll be necessary but also when we do if we ever do that
One of these will have to do is
Clemency
In some way
But go through the process and maybe
Put people in prison
Instead of kill
Because it's just
Become a part of being
The president commits war crimes
Which is what we have to ask
Believable so I hope we will eventually get
The end of the show and throughout Mancow just goes on to be like
You're the best you're the best broadcaster ever I'd like to apologize for calling you crazy years ago August 12th
Blah blah blah blah blah
We move on to November
Something
Is it on each of these days
We get a crazy guy
So I know
Yeah I'm at ansar little piece of chocolate with Mancow
You will not believe
What shows up on the 11th
No but
We will get there
See his sad eyes
I know when I will get there
Nicholls State of the world because on the evening of November 10th
Is a republican debate
Right here is where Alex Jones
About these politicians
Amazing debates last night
I got it last night
Entirely
Certainly was on last week
Set my plan to it
But
And I have to say with probably one of the winners
I watched last night
Much better analysis than what we saw
So it's Rand Paul was great in the debates but also we're pretty awesome
Plug but the reason that's important live coverage of the debate
It's so much better
Another debate
You should watch our live coverage
There we go
Still supporting Rand Paul
I don't know what the f*** is happening
More
This business masturbation is
Fuct
Completely thought
I don't even know what the I don't know what we're looking for anymore really just looking for him screaming 17th
76 2.0
Beyond
Any
Rand Paul
Screaming
Nepal is the messiah
Right
Trump is the
Only savior
The pivot has to come it's
Some point
It's got to have something to do with
At this point it really feels
It has to
I don't know we'll see keep going
But
August 11th Alex gets back to the issues at Mizzou
Because I think
The 10th
He may be done a little bit of reading
They may be Googled some stuff
Zoe
Yes Mother Stephanie wants to talk about also
I can't remember if it's in this clip or a later one
He keeps calling it knees
Mizzou is Mizu
And it tells me something very important
And that is
Alex
All of this information
About what's going on at the University of Missouri
From Paul Joseph Watson
Because that is a British
Pronunciation
Of Mizzou
And I know that
Because later
Call Joseph
Show all the stuff that Alex
Learning about this
Is rum
PJ dubs
Ssj dub
It's all filtered through
That's we always do that
Man I look I'm coming in hot.
I'm bringing that into his racist narrative
I love Columbia if there was a great home
For me for many years
Teen years that I live there
Has a whole lot of problem
But a whole lot of potential
And go f*** yourself
Alex
A butt
The Mizu thing be figuring that out
I felt so good about
Cuz it's queer it's
We're that this is the cart leading the horse Paul Joseph Watson telling Alex what the broadcast
Going to take the narrative
Here on November 11th
The situation
Missouri State system
Has just intensified
Hunger strike
Cuz over several weeks you didn't lose any weight
Alex $8000000 a year year
That's right I forgot
I'm still double-checking it but it appears the railroad is parts or o sound
Of course
You've already decided everything is that
So
I'm going to put this up on the the research documents
Gone to Union Pacific Railroad is the company
That Eric Butler is the guy's dad that's Jonathan Butler's dad
At the time Vice
Chief administrative officer
Corporate
But at the time
He wasn't Executive Inn
Sales and Mark
Fort Union
Pacific Railroad
Here we have the Directors & officers
All the people who are involved we have the one thing that worries me
Is that
The one of the directors
Is Andrew Card
Who is the former Chief of Staff to GW bush
Oh that's not good
But if you look down this list I see no George Soros
I see no one
Who Alex has ever brought up who has explicit
Anything like that
Trail the directors officers
Where to find Soros
Members maybe the he's on a committee of some sort that has that control the audit committee
Coastal Finance
Compensation and benefit
Committee to corporate governance
The nominating committee know George Soros Andrew card on a couple of these
Which again is troubling to me
Mabel doesn't necessarily prove any
Cuz that is
Government work
Who knows
Yeah but
That is there's no Soros there so I looked
Oh he was on Stocking Union Pacific Railroad
Cuz you don't stop
Everything
Tons of money on the stock market
He's a billionaire
That if you want to play that game Alex
Doing is essentially just
I'm going to preemptively invalidate anyone who works at a company that sore ozone stopped
Which is going to be trouble cuz that's almost
Let me let the hundreds of
The other thing is
Sure
Who's $8000000
Vinegar
And now you're saying that his son
Is not entitled
Too political
Alex
You are worth over 10 million
If you want to use that argument
If you want to use the argument how much your company brings in a year
Which we can easily find out it's got to be
As we know it's at least over 14 million dollars a year comes into Infowars cuz that's what he said
He said that's what it takes to run it for a year so he has to be at least making that or more
If you want to do that about Rex Jones
Your thirteen-year-old son is not going to be entitled to political speech
As an adult
If he's on campus
Something bad happen if you want
Speak out about it
Unfortunately what you're saying about valid argument against your dad makes millions of dollars
Go fuc yourself
I understand that but
It's important
It doesn't
Is it just doesn't matter pointing out hypocrisy anymore
Thrilling to me
Okay alright
I'm not saying that that's going to
Or anything like that right
Cuz cuz
Left about pointing out the hypocrisy
Clearing out these
Attack
That are being made on
Necessarily on someone
Who is just trying to
Speak out
How are you clearing up
Because the attack is but his dad is made
Blah blah blah
Specious because
Lots of people make millions of dollars and they're still entitled to their free speech
To his dad's Railroad
Jessie on Stocking
So take any company that has OnStar
Find out someone who's a marketing person
That company
I meant now their son isn't allowed to speak out because it is clearly a saurus operation
Just tell amazing he's donated to Trump campaign so now Trump's children shouldn't be able to speak out
They have Works business
Altogether
So
It's less about
Apocracy
And more about a style of argument called reductio ad absurdum
Just take the logic
Apply it to another situation where I seen things
Probably
Learning that logic
Because I did his homework
I should be clear I never accepted that offer
It's just stupid idea some more stupidity about Missouri
Hunger strike
Father paid 8 million
Has had
Vice president of a major railroad last year
He was paid a million net worth
Guaranteed
Indirect
Guarantees
Melissa click
The professor
Over media
Pat's resign but she didn't really resign
Trouble deceptive noise
But at the same time I'm a bigger fan avoid avoid the deception
Make me hungry
I need more muscle professor
From a symbolic position
Affordable title
I bet you with fire
Resigned
Actual job
Like I think he's spiritually correct bad idea
Doris Miller
So yeah it's just more like
This Is The Stuff work
He's making
He's just
Making it up
The idea that it's a story. I guarantee
Immediately after this
He transitions
Do we know it's true
Real-time there
So now we get to work
Everything he says
He then confirm
Himself I got it from source
Earlier making s*** up
But that one sounds good so now it's true
I think I'm credible
And if I said it
Credible source
There we go
Jordan shut the fuk up cuz we got we got to guess
Viscous
He's crazy
Alright so
What it is is a guy named
General stubblebine
May or may not have been a real General
It's all important
General stubblebine
Stubblebine
He's he's eighty if he's a day
I bet sounds like a civil war
General stubblebine is on
Times for mail by
He is there with his wife
Is a doctor named something or other
Or something like that
Prince between the two of them
Whatever it's
You live your life
I tried to go to her website
And she just goes by doctor
Fremont on the website
Last name
Dr. Remax
That's it
So here is the intro that Alex
Gives to them
And I got to say
What they're on the show.
Talk about it
F***** up
But
Deal with it
And then we'll get to it awesome reveal at the end
Okay
General
Lesson 53
Security
Electronics research and development
Intelligent systems
I also have a whole section
For your children
Because
With their fake regulation or
Mercer's the Bill of Rights the Constitution the Nuremberg code
Come on
The great culling has begun
Fortunate
You are
Already started
Donna going to get worse
She's on
Let's talk about that
Doughboy
So
Opioid crisis
No talking about
Depression and suicide rates
Which are higher which are very high
King about
Need to go away
Oh no no
Vaccine
Course
Are killing white men in the USA
Air is out the at what happens immediately after that last
Albertsstuff
I am at now we get into this
Horseshit nonsense
Can you take a look at this to this
So he does Miss joke like four times
Also a strong B
What'd you find
Thursday
Yep okay
Signature
Rate
Years
40 + 50
World in terms of
Remember to talk about whites
White Jack White Privilege
I don't think
Statistics Arness
Fairly accurate
Sadistic
So yeah this is the this is sort of the introduction of there but they're not really giving any
Insight into what they're there to talk about
Until this next
Which is where we going to be at
Stuff
The end
Clip is not to be believed
So stupid
One of the things
United States
Mortality rate
Cousin facts
Pause right there
Statistics in front of me about tality rate is
It's not because we have a
Miserable
Horrible Healthcare System
Right here what's the divide an inch
Mortality rates
Is it
The same infant mortality rate
It seems as though
Rich people have a much lower infant mortality
Throat
But I'm going to go to the document camera
Cuz I have the infant mortality statistics
From 2016 in front of me
And what do you think she said was it
Zimbabwe has a lower
Here this is the infant mortality rate deaths
For 1,000 live births
Lucia Popp Afghanistan
Leave the pack
With 112 point
8 witches
Terrifying
10%
But that's awful
And then you get a ton of a
Can countries
Embalming
We got all this
So much Africa there
This is all Africa because
We have done a terrible job of helping them
Zoe try there's a lot better things
We should be doing
Scroll down here we get through like
There's a wreck there with 37
Still no America
Like I passed them
There's a 29
For 1,000 live births
This is from 2016 give my
What is the most up-to-date information that is available
Do you scroll down even though my God where are we there's the United States
5.8
This is just
Complete cockamamie horseshit
It's coming out of her mouth
So where did it get there
I hate vaccines
Probably start probably Nan
Probably just
Some stuff where people got numbers wrong and their divisions or use bad sourcing
I am the No 1
Corrected them
You see this all the time and it's
It's very common with Alex Jones is gas
Unofficial things that were posted on blogs
We're going to get him something really funny
Also deny climate
Great
Highest
Detection
I would call the facts
Accelerating rate
The introduction of
Enzyme
Carter the Great
Calling how is it introduced
Baby
Is never ever again
Oh boy
California
This is bad
But I want to assure you the only way to stop
The Great Khali
Vaccine right
Somebody and allowing smallpox
Another calling
Smallpox dozen
Dyathon race
But I will.
With a straight face day
Privilege
White males are dying
And just end
So inherently racist
If you've got nothing it's easy to leave it there cuz you don't want to dwell on it
Come on like
Jordan care about males are dying
Number one issue again all of these guests
I'm so much with Alex Jones
The show is really about
Is retaining undeserved Social Power
And privileged
That's what threatened
That's why he is white identity theft
She's not a race
That
The infertility
The forced infertility or whatever it is that's the big one
There's some of that are running out
Meredith
A butt
Look all this stuff is tough
It's stupid
Trust me
The end of this clip
In about a minute and a half
Hilarious
And we find out why they're really on the show
To informed consent
Where's my Samsung
Fifth
So just a pause real quick at this point
She's holding up a card to the video screen that's important
Is this your card
The trumps
We got to get organized
Doesn't work
Videos on the news in Mexico
A bunch of
This is really testing how much will put up with
Albert Wilson
Determine how much will put up with
Anything they want to give up
No
And you're kind of right
Diana Ross
Legal format
Next
Deserting your informed consent right
You going to get back
Created
To everyone
Splash the prices
Everyone can afford it help everyone
Backpack in Europe
Wallet in your purse
That bright
Vaccine if you don't assert specific legal language that is only available on this card
That we happened to spell and we slashed prices
You can't just
I don't know print out a ton of lemon lemonade
Have gone to her website doctor rimas website
Exemption card that she
She sells on her website is $30
If you scroll up
Clarify our website
That is the store
$30
For a card you can print out that says I don't want to get jabbed
Wow
Death General stubblebine f****** real becoming clear to me at least in the
This but this is all
Rema this is the lady found a two-year-old supporting
And
I can do this forever to get you on Alex
His show of certainly
Really doesn't say anything
All of these military credits
For her to just jump
Here's what you got to do
He says a little bit more that I cut out but it's all kind of boring stuff
Sadistic fly
Align
What language
Do you need to use
Legal
But that's another one of those libertarian like
It's all about the maritime law do exactly
So that's the end of their interview butts
And if you really feel like you're a f****** child
If you really look into it
Informed consent just means
You signed a form that says
Do you know the risk
And you reject them knowing the risk
Fatality for doctors hospital today
When you reject the vaccine
So if you want to get evacs
They have to ask the question
Like are you sure you're aware of it
If you signed forms As You Are
That's plenty
They won't Force vaccinate after that point situation
Can't like
I don't know become a daycare worker if you're not vaccinate
Goddamn right your situation. That's just like
It's within their rights to not allow you in
That's the consequence of your choice
Utah business
The only sign that I would have
No answer
No need apply
Sup
Let's get out to be fully vaccinated
To work here
Let's jump
UPS drop off the exit bag stuff
Cuz we talked about it too much
Like
This is fun because they they go from vaccines cause autism
M2
Throat
They're done
At this point
But Alex wants to get back into
To the last night's debate and how great
Crazy
So this is about how great Rand Paul was last night
And then Alex Jones says something
Little unfortunate that is
With our
It'll put me come out instead of pure Bowl
And it's a military operation by the globalist
Peter Popoff
Activity contributed to climate change
I wanted to stop right there today
You've made too much sense to be on this stage
I want to say that most sensible version of insane
Closer
Two reasonable but also I hate
So what's good with the sweet with the sour
Smooth
President Obama has announced an aggressive plan to cut carbon emissions
At the same time
Energy production
To continue this
And energy self-sufficiency
The same time
Pursuing a meaningful climate change program
That's a really good question as president is repeal the regulations
Fat ugly
Well I do think you may have a role in our climate
I think nature also has a role
Magic we've had time to the temperature been warmer we had times when the temperatures been cold we've had times when the carbon
Any atmosphere has been higher
So I think we need to look for
Presidents are often fond of Steve
We do need to balance both keeping the environment clean
Where to balance that with the economy
He's devastated mistake
I say the president only just joined Kentucky he's destroying the Democrat Party down there cuz nobody wants to associate with him
Really need is somebody that understands that we do need energy of all forms
That means we will have solar and wind
Natural Gas
We've got to have an all-of-the-above party
False
Coal power plants in the United States
Insider companies
Really trouble
Sure
With these guys like with Mancow and him is it just like big swinging dick
Looks like they just like a guy who just says whatever you want
And then does whatever
Guy who says
And then acts like
Equation
To see that they're trying to live out through these guys like they're always here
Oh there's all these people telling me what I can do what I just want to do whatever I want to do whenever I want
I hate the clicker f***************
People who bow down and grovel
What is attractive to them about
Unattractive
But we gotta move through this
Cuz you have a hard out to get to yourself
Yeah Christ
So
Here are we get
To November 12th the last day of our invest
Navigation
And at this point Alex's
I'm keenly aware
At the Paris climate Accord is coming up
Figured it out the Summit is coming up and he realizes he needs to make that the narrative
Global government
Being created in public absolute and so he's going to jump on
To that narrative pretty hard
But
He does that in a really weird way
Because I listen to this clip
About his climate change denial
And try and figure out or try and listen for where it's different from things
You said in the past
Exxon
Mobile
And British Petroleum
Dutch Royal shell
Are the biggest
Thunders
Call man-made
Climate change
And they're so sophisticated
ExxonMobil
It wasn't that was 15 years ago
Rockefeller
Incredible in the sense that it's not credible
But
So wait he saying that
Oil
Funding climate
Search or not
Doing something about it
In order to
Takedown col-rite
Why does he want cool so
Because he
He believes that it is like a
The most plentiful
Source of energy
How are the planet for the next Thousand Years
And the technology that we have is totally clean now it's
It's not totally lying about that
Here's the problem
What should we do know is that
Knew that climate
Contributing to 30 years ago
And lied about it
And I just lied about it
Pulled a full-on nicotine
And we're like
Doctors
Call Klim
Climate change study
Climate change is denying study
Concepcion the clip Adidas put out there they paid for
Climate change positive studies in order to take out cold
Which doesn't make sense
It does not reflect reality
But the more important thing in the reason that clip is fascinating to me
Is because it's
Not what he usually
He's saying that the climate change lie
In his mind
Is being put out by British Petroleum
By beating all those the companies he listed
Shell
And those in order to take out Cole
In the past
His frequent narrative is better to be
The UN that is doing this
In order to get climate credit
Inclimate carbon
Is going in order to
Cut off energy
Do the third world in what-have-you it's completely different
Everybody runs in he's got Rockefeller
Dropping them trying to put those
Rockefeller is 1
Right but it's not the same
Very different
Goals or storyline
Pitching in Chinese
What climate change is about it
It's f****** stupid
It's certainly not buddy
Tibet
People at Mizzou
He wants to get into protester
I believe it's called
He says something bad about them
And then something
Exculpatory
About a different
That is very
And then I sat there
3-4 hours watching the video
I don't believe you did
Others
Really screwed up damage
Victims
Above of re-education Camp brainwash
When I heard that the clan
What's going to show up at the universe
The federally-run clan of times there's usually about six or seven guys
It comes out later that day
Maybach
It's a photo album the racial tension
Center and other groups behind
SPS
Would be saying
Running in fear
Is it true
Is the clan here are we safe
And they cancel classes
Had the police on alert that me SWAT team on the road
I don't believe that
It was all completely made up
But meanwhile the very same football players and basketball players
I don't I don't believe that there were like snipers on roof
At all
Anytime
Scandalous rumors
Salaciousness
And that's unfortunate that he's sort of the problem of the social turning a
Yes they are coming and show
We are not
I'm sure that they fed into it a little bit I know I am
I also know that the clan
Does not run
First they're all true
But you understand what he's doing he's taking the agency power away from these protests
They are brainwashing
Victims of
Center
To provoke
So black people black people standing up for themselves
Wasn't pointing out institutional problems
White racism not really real it's just
Right that's what he thinks
That's what he thinks
And unfortunately even in that narrative
White people run the government
Mostly
So even that is Raisa
Even that that does not justify his position on it
Not really you're right that's an interesting
Argument that would be fun to point out to her
I think it would I think it would end up in
Yeah probably I would assume
I want to jump into the next load cuz
This is one of my favorites
Alex Jones was a victim
Throwing up
He was a complete victim
We've never known what it was exactly that
And on this November 12th
No
It is not
That is not something you could ever predict
I seen the statistics
A person is collapsing
Have no idea what's going on
Some shells
And hear from you
My racism
Privilege all this crap
Images being singled out because I was so good looking
Show me the photos online
Mencken
I thought they were to kick my butt
I think that it's it's it's likely that he was an a******
But also if that was
True which it isn't
He was attractive
But if it was
You're making a
Compelling case
About the
Evils of toxic masculinity
Cuz if you had to fight men who didn't like that you were pretty and all the women wanted you
You are entirely embodying
Masculine
Threatened
Maelstrom
Bulshit
If you're saying that you are an animal bright
Mr. Steal Your Girl
You're one step away from understanding if you really believe that that is what happened
Close close
And it gets worse
I fixed it all
Slack-jawed snot-nosed Punk
Is
And Warren Buffett
Point two million
Accomplish anything on your own is a load of bull
You're projecting
I want to help
All these people I understand metaphysically spiritual
What you are
I would want others to succeed because I understand you reap what yourself the problem is evil people
Don't understand that metaphysical Rule and they want to see others fail
What other people say
Oh boy
About Rush Limbaugh
Right every other Media Company all the time
That everybody else is
Terrible and he's only one
61%
Batshit
He's not just an evil person
He's a bad person in this
Now you're pointing out of pocket
Calling you after your own s***
Fair enough comes a bit angry tone
And now I'm angry about it back onto the climate stuff
But here is a
Classic
That's one of our
That's another one of those visuals you need to make
Cliff is
Alota bulshit
And Alex accidentally proves that's a load of bull s*** on a minute later
News about Lord monckton
The guy who Alex Jones I believe is the only real climate scientist
Disney World
Climate
Lord in front of
If climate change of Advocates get there it will kill a billion people
Six months or something like that
That's his ark
Lord monckton
That Alex always sites
Listen to Lorde
Speak he does not get into
He claims he's gone through every climate change
Study
And found underlying asset
But they have wrong
Adventure
But
Here is the b******* that Alex has to say about Lord Market
And I disagree with
I don't even know if he's a lord
But so hear this
He's probably not an ass
This is about Lord Boston's relation
To the climate
Sapulpa okay
Virgo
Can Paris
Intuit
Never stop
Doesn't doesn't
South Africa
Is the same bulb
Yeah that small town country
Absolutely that's what we need from you daring stunts
All you listeners go parachute into places do you have not parachuted before that is actually true
Lord mantra
Confirm or deny
Alex Jones
Is saying that Lord monckton and others are being threatened to not even show up in Paris
Don't come don't even
Walk into the city
Persona non grata
This point
One of his interns
Google
The climate change
The chords in Paris
And the alicorns
Usual Suspects
Felipe Calderon
Lord monckton
Foot Locker
God
Pause was beautiful Alex Jones accidentally learns on air
Invited
Did he have papers up Gunn
No cuz the the intern had the UN website open that has the list and all the pictures of the
Rolling sky
Oh no Lord monckton oh no
I just said a minute ago that he's being threatened about the UN was
Is somebody at the door very light knock at the door there
I don't know if I can hear it
You are bad attacks
Valley Construction
Retired
I know
I don't know why you ever started
I just like saying
You're busted
So after this point
He gets back on to
The race issues
Alex
Accidentally
Everything by ax
But he accidentally revealed
Huge race
Bye
Complaining about racism
Soiree
Infowars.com
I can choose
Well assured that I cannot
We are
Smooth
I can do all of these things like that doesn't seem to be a problem that like can I speak
Speak to people without putting my race on then I get flesh-colored
Are they the same color is my
Colors
This checklist should up on
Camera
I can accompany of people my race
Most of the time
I can't turn on the television or open to the front page of the paper and see people of my race widely represented
What I'm told about our National Heritage or civilization
I'm showing the people of my color made it what it is
I can be sure that my children will be given quickly
Exist
Sense of their race
It goes on like
Whether I use check
Credit cards or cash
I can count on my skin color not to work against
The appearance of fine
Reliability
So
Is a list of things
That white people
Take for granted about their daily existence
People who aren't white have to deal with
This is the conversation
That people haven't when they talk about white privilege
Edit should be the one that
Everybody right it's so fascinating
To me that Alex
Is furious about there so he
He pulls up
Doesn't understand the premise
You nailed it whistle
So in advance
Approving every single thing
That everybody's 1000% making their art
You are embodying
The problem
Going to guess
East in terms of that Band-Aid
He just didn't know
Understand what it was
I'm going to guess in that case but with the
Speaking without electric power.
My race on
Like not engaging
With the idea at all
It's just
Oh yeah I guess I do
That is interesting I do single out all the
All the people who were black
Speaking up
I got to re-examine
Is that just like
The idea that he
He's there he's
He's like of course I can
And you can't do that
Like there's one step a little bit
Further
Can everyone
Right right
Process that
Second Quest
That is the idea
Answer these questions
Guess what
These are things
Other people
Do other people
Do them
You can
That
Privilege
His response would be like I don't believe they can't do it it's all a bunch of media soros-funded Foundation
Bulshit
It's all a bunch of course you can do the thing
Cuz he doesn't want to engage with anyone else's
Well yeah but I mean the flesh colored Bandit
Seems pretty
That's why you can't understand
That's so obvious
That's that's
Mount Jordan
We reached today is crazy
It's time for The Gap
On the November 12th
This guy is one of my favorite crazy
Rogues gallery of Alex Jones's Associated team of weirdos
This guy is up there
Top-level weirdo
Professor Darrell hamamoto
He is a teacher
A professor at the University of California at Davis
Sometimes
That what happened
Was
He got crazy
At a certain point
Because
I can't imagine they don't want to get rid of him
And they never would have hired him
Induced currents
Darrell hamamoto is a very interesting
Historically
I'm not sure what he teaches now although I think so
Conspiracy
But
He originally came into his own
And was a professor in Asian American studies
Specifically inter
Terms of sexuality
He wrote a couple books
About the desexualization
Of the Asia
Hey there's an interest
Conversation
Because I don't want to
But
I do think that there that's an interest
Exactly that's on the timer
Showed up on Alex Jones Show and we covered him in a past episode
Episode
Justin Gould
I need you to listen
Into this
Clip from
Is this
Is worth Rivas
Well
Here is one of our
Solutions
We're going to use the Fowler
Guitars
Cypress happens to be
Offender a Squier guitar
Warrior rally
With my little friend
Esquire my pudenda pink Esquire
And they wouldn't let me sit in a said I'm sorry can't let it happen
And they were hired this is part of the
Cultural takeover
So that's
Yamamoto
Interested
Hip-hop and punk is propaganda
Yeah but they're trying to
Inculcate in the minds of the freshman
And
He brought you
Hit funk
Bright
Chips 02 trailer
I'll tell you let me get on a second
He brings his gay pick to play with
I think I think it was probably cuz he's like
60 year old dude
Know your f******
Every campus has
And I was thinking about it like I'm certain that he got hired when he was writing these books about Asian-American
Bi-sexual
Classes on this
Then he went crazy
And they're in too deep they can't fire at
So
I was thinking back on my college experience
And I had a human sexuality Professor named Joe Lopez
Piccolo
And
He clearly was a very
Smart
Interesting
Good speaker good teacher
In the seventies
And then he had a
Stroke
And when I had him it would pass
You could barely speak in lectures
And he was
Very ineffective
Professor
But I realized
This is after you'd left
What's Goku
Oceanside methadone
The point of getting at is like when you're tenured it's very difficult to get rid of
Until Joe lopiccolo wood watch
Retire they wouldn't be able to
Get rid of him
Even though
Like you play videos of himself
In class
From
Years past whenever he clearly different
Turn speaker very articulate
Incredibly sad
To be in that class
It made me a baby a size with him a lot
It was
The most tragic day in class he put up a slide on the projector
The show the graph
Breakdown of grades
In the class and almost everyone was saying
What's going on we don't understand what you're saying
It was so tragic
And less tragic level Darrell hamamoto clearly went nuts
I started to think about like a
Globalist
Stuff like out
What's the Illuminati have you and now there's
We can't get rid of him until he retires
I think it is something
Men at like
Around 40
Just started to get into globalist like they the old saying is like a
If your
Not a liberal when you're
20 you have no heart
Nautica
You have no bra
I'm thrilled to report that my dad is
Now it is 60s
Still going strong and I are good old liberal
Right
Religious studies
Texas
Anyway
Pink Pussycat
Pink
So
Hamamoto comes in
On the show
Because of all the craziness
What's going on on campus
Mizzou it also brings up Yale
Cuz Gail they had that situation where students were mad about races Halloween
Alex
But
Hamamoto in
A present him as a whistleblower
Because
Darrell hamamoto
I'd like a Rockefeller Grant
Or something like that
He's gone through some sort of
Indoctrination
From The Rock
Stellar Foundation
And that that makes him like
He knows inside
Stop
When the reality is
The Rockefeller Grant
The Ford Foundation grants
Are just
Things that are given out to
Apply for
And they are there
To create diversity
And University
Hamamoto almost certainly got one of these grants
Because he was
Pursuing
An Avenue of study
That would
Be incredibly advantageous
Stewie universe
Maybe they wouldn't have the budget to pay him threat so the grant comes in
And other Foundation
Hey is that part of this
Professor salary
Brett if you look into it
Hans of organizations like this
Including
The Koch brothers
Have their own Foundation that gives out grants
Right there is a fellowship at the University of Missouri that for years and years was under
1.1 million
Dollars
Was given
To pay for a professor salary
By Kenneth lay
From Enron
Call Mike
Because he went to the University of Missouri
Fred.
S*** I think someone did a
I got the Enron scholarship guys don't worry about it it's all good for professors
I think someone did end up taking it
Yeah but it's okay
Years for someone to do that be that Craven to Taco
Do you want to have some
Distance between Bellevue and
The greatest game ever pulled off let me be clear
The great so are they still around
Alex Jones believes Daryl hamamoto to be a whistleblower of the inside of the Ford Foundation
And all that
Haha
But Alex Jones
Treat him like a whistleblower
I'd like he is
Preaching the gospel
Where is as We Know
He wants to bring a guitar to Occupy Wall Street
And jam with the guys
He's going to say a bunch
Radically stupid stuff
In this let's just jump into it
Like you're saying it is a program
The students are on Electro Pharmaceutical
And it's it's no accident that whatever can't she go to it's the same program it's the same scenario
You have a shot
Sandy Hook
Baseball game
Do you got the Soros connected
Hook was Crisis actors Alex signed off on that so clearly he's not pushing back
You believe this is not absolute
You have
This
What we started the show off with
Where Alex is saying
Maybe
There's Soros connection
We're going to look into it he's reporting it just as gospel without proving
So I mean
It's just nonsense
But
Get back to hamamoto
Earlier
There's a certain
Standard shipping
Sexuality
Issa take his insulin post-gender world at transhumanist posthuman world
Sexual
That's right they're going to take us to the next level.
Gender differentiation
She's a crisis actor it's going to be interesting to see if something on your list is when a Tracker to see where she shows up but I'm still
A job
Waiting for her son's light
Do you want to stock this crisis actor
Is he actually
Interesting if one of your listeners fuc
Dock somebody
Well I mean we don't need to stalk her cuz she's
Is a public person
CDI got hired by con Saga
What happened
I don't know she's a Gonzaga
I don't care anyway that's what happened to her she's not a crisis actors
Just someone who
I was dumped In the Heat of the Moment
Did something
Viral
That's about it it's not a crisis actor
Do you know about the crisis publicly shame
Right
Do you know about the people who believe that stuff
So they believe that
Sandy Hook deniers
It's everything
Call Levine
Basta
Embalming
Everything
You see on the news
We were talking about it everyone who pretends they have a child that died at Sandy Hook
They're all crisis Act
Better run out of this giant organization by the government
The Pilates false-flag
And what they do
Their appearance
A bunch and you can tell
Slightly different appearing people
Always show up at all these places
And so if you go online you can find videos
Where they're like
Alright
I see this the principal it's
Happens to look
Just like this
Sister
I'm someone who died in the Boston bombing
I can tell you that the same people
Because what we've done is
Let's it's it's a wild world
Wow you go even
Further into it there's a lot of people who believe
Let these people are actually
Celebrities
That they change their appearance
To play these roles in the pipe
Even better at acting than we ever thought
Johnny Knoxville is like a bunch of different people who
Knoxville
Johnny Knoxville is one of the ones that I specifically remember cuz they are like
Why would you
It's fine
It just it's just it's it's
Is prohibitive
Spira Seafair is there anything like that they're just reality
Deny
Deniers
Be called reality
Climate crisis actors
It also
Legit
Like the idea
Dementia
Difficulty that it would take the.
Like how did they get there
How long did it take
Inconsistent is my
Eva's next clip Alex Jones
Maybe one
Episode
Alex
About the
Similarities
Between
What's going on on our campus
Andy
Nope the Chinese of people's Revolution
Moto goes off on a weird
Edit the lights
It's so bowl that they would
I accept your fighting
Professors my colleagues even if UC Davis are meaning to man up
Sorry for using the sexiest language
Trouble for talking to a pro
These rats are spying on me right now
This point you said is being watched
As we speak
This should just be the first indication that Daryl Hannah Moto isn't he
Credibly paranoid man
Listen to this
The thing about it though it's
Jose about that paranoid like
He's rat spying on me all the time
No that's called that's called a flat
He doesn't have Peaks
Valleys in the
Expresses thing
I'm not sure
Credibility
It's a Stein of
Basically I don't mean to sound like I know a lot about psychology
But it is a it is indicative of a disc
With the world around you
Sandy Hook denial crisis actors
Someone spying on me
Now hear this
Who by the way is deducting 25% of my salary for the next 5 months good and I call here now for her
Immediate resignation as Chancellor of University California
Spoiler alert pretty shortly not for any of the things that he lied
Appropriated camper
Hired her daughter and son-in-law
Or son-in-law and daughter I can't remember exactly
Salary
Classic
Knock-down
Nephew politics
Britain
Coronavirus complaints
That's enough.
What she's doing is
Blatant corruption we can't have that if we want to use the dark metaphor
He hits the house next door doesn't even hit the board
Nextdoor
Is an action
Federal counter
And while you're at it please take
The president of the systems
Emeritus professor
The commissar
Leave us alone
We're going to rebuild the University of California without you
So
Would listen to
To that clip
Same thing
They are probably trying to find something he's doing that we can fire him for it cuz we accidentally
That is probably what's going on
Now he protect on me
One of his classes
Hilarious
If he was
Spot-on as a professor
But just a lunatic in it downtown
I've read some smokes a ton of crack
Still does a great job
MMA go home and they're just cracked out
Ratemyprofessors
You can go on there and read some reviews of his glasses
3.5 out of 5
Yeah but the negative ones are like he will just scream at you if you disagree it stuff like that
But
He's not going to take that laying down
He's got a message for the snitches
But he wants to get out on Alex Jones Show
In this next clip
I talked about
Well in all modesty I was teaching introductory classes of 200 students
And my classes were routinely oversubscribed
Departmental Sheriff Department hired somebody specifically
Snitches assistance
To empty out my classes
And she went on social media Twitter Facebook in order to do so
Screwing with people whether it's me or someone else
Eventually they're going to roll over on you for you
Enchantments
Sabi so-called
Space spaces
Or before you turn your soul over to so-called the student Community Center
Soca
Right it's the way that Alex does the so-called minority stuff like that
He's just trying to invalidate people who has a
Community Center
So-called
Soca
I told you what happened to Linda
She ended up getting fired for misappropriation
The funds
Hear it
Be fired for
It's Looney
And you can also tell by
Identification for example the chancellor at
And by the way she holds 19 patents for antennas antennas
Archie
Are the mind control system
So
He believes
That there are EMF
Yeah
But huh
19 antennas
But but but the reason the reason for that the reason for that is because
He believes on campus
There is a dual prong attack on Steam
The first Brock is getting a ball on psychiatric drugs
The second is EMF fields
That are manipulating people and turning them into zombies
So
Alright Linda is only in the position that she's in
As the chancellor of the school
Because she has 19
Also by the way
I went and looked into these pads
They're not
Did the full thing of irie's through all of them
This Is My Mind Control patent
But most of them are for antennas
To conserve dual /
So you can get GPS
And radio
As opposed to having to antenna for
They go into great detail about how you
Need two boards
Then there to ground
One signal in the other signal it's all very boring
But that's the sort of stuff.
But she was actually invented
She was watching me
You can get a patent at Pendleton so creating some
Give me a song for
Covid-19 all of them might not actually be real
Come up with them and filed the patent
Go to to be a placeholder for
She does create them
Time somebody makes
Same thing she can be like based on her ethical status of
Are you giving her a kid's job situation
Has no intention
It's not bring
Imoto
Is crazy
So unless she's
Controlling is
To make him go
Well that's interesting
That would discredit all of his theories
Maybe she just hate Asians
Yep there you go so it wanders
We can wander all day about that but
No I got to shut it down now
We've gotten into like
What makes hamamoto
We would still make the argument that he's crazy
But maybe he's a good teacher
In his next clip describe
A really negative approach towards being a t
Let's see if you feel the same way
She is has declared herself is part of the
Gender and sexuality
Academic expertise in the area
Department and Ray and programs
That the so-called student activists are being recruited from
It's in the bag and you showed a video earlier
Start questioning you
Mind control which they are
And I'll start spontaneously asking you these questions
How to do is break
And
Crumble
To the stage the final stage
Here's an open microphone tell me what what you want to see in this class
They have nothing
By the way this is a technique that a lot of comedians
And anything
So if you are doing that
Also
Of course.
Seems like you have
Mentality
But you're fighting your students
And to me
That's not productive education
Just don't even like it when they
How do you how do you not
Spontaneously as there's no other way to ask a question
You can't like, Moto I want you into going to ask you a question
Spontaneous
Part of learning
It's almost like
The responsibilities of a professor is having dialogue with student
Hey whenever someone asks
Question it's an
Learn
My dude
Come on hamamoto
Just using
God
Glb
F*** you
Let's touch those.
Bulshit that he does
Dude we got it we got to get through this
We're fast approaching
The Moto to get through and then we'll be we'll be out
Will be home free
Next time we get into some of the reason
Why you believe
Antennas
Our mind control device
Yeah Welcome to The Monkey House
Giada
Really early on and discoveries Earth
But you have
Seen in people of
And in person
This is HAARP in action
So he's talking about a guy named Nick begich
There was actually a member of Congress
In some form
And he died in a plane crash
Nick begich jr. came to prominence by claiming that
His dad was taken out
The government taking him out
So Nick begich Jr is a guy who wrote a famous book
Famous in quotes
Call Angel
It's about HARP
Yeah I'm not going to lie I don't I don't disagree
So his website he has his dirt
Is Alex home
Angels Don't Play this heart that's like that's like these colors don't run whatever
So you have a website called Earth puls.com
If you go to it you have a listing of his resume
Nick begich receive doctor of Medicine medisina alternativa
Onerous
Plaza
Thighs honor honor 8 honor
Autorific degree in political science from the open International University for
Complementary medicine
Colombo Sri Lanka
Sri Lanka
He got a fake degree
From a
Sri Lanka in
Well
Maybe open International University appears to be a diploma Mill
And it has been described as
The grandfather of diploma Mills
The top one
Slmd degrees particularly dangerous
Lorde
Panda
Professor doctor
Of Sri Lanka created medicine
Cena alternativa International in Sri Lanka
And claimed to be affiliated with the open International University
Presumably
Name that way to be
Confused with the open University of Sri Lanka
Course you sold diplomas for various feet
I have a copy of his charge list for 19
62 / 3750 US Dollars one could by any of the following degrees
MD mdtm
Doctorate or PhD
These letters explain but it's you can get Masters
And regular degrees for 100 100 $45
So much
Cheaper
What I
Went to college
Totally
Worth almost as much
Jeffrey dumet
An Australian neuropath who bought his doctorate
Diploma Mill
Was charged with manslaughter in the death of a 37-year old kitten
Is natural detox
Navigation program
11 kg
10 days
And hasten the page
Whichever you want to talk about the liver cleanse
Stuff like that
Kidney cleanse
Gallbladder cleanse that Alex sells
Through doctor group who also has a fake
The thing that they talk about it working
Is often related to weight loss
Which could be very simple if someone was using them
It probably could kill them much like
This case here if its Australian
Australian
Nick begich started to do a bunch of bulshit
About about HARP
You got into harp
If you want to look into it it's
It's pretty interesting
Because everyone talks about Harper being this massive weapons
The can be used
The chute
It's basically the MacGuffin
In terms of anytime you need an explanation for something
How do you control hurricane
It's harp and DARPA are the two that everyone always ask that
Who cares
That don't worry about it
Brakes been done of the amount of energy that comes out of
Ruthie's harp
And it's so absurd
Bigoted
Everyone takes it
But massively powerful
But if you break it down and compare it to the amount of radiation
And it just comes from
From the Sun naturally
It's not even
Incomparable
Stupid it's just
Really stupid
The harp stuff is dumb
Hamamoto is f****** dumb
For calling
Nick begich doctor Vegas
Really think means he's never looked into this
Except
Whatever did Wild dude
Again had a great name for a book
A about got to give him that
View the doctor book
Humberto is
That's better than a lot of
Sure I'll tell you that right now
Ephesus twice-annual chorus
Remove the book
Exactly
Alex Jones
Wonderful
It is an adventure I am so glad happy honored to be here in 2015
Joining in this battle with you and the team and American around the world
The programming just disappears it's not that strong
I don't have an axe to grind or hidden agenda
Your agendas very public
Wild
A badge
So do you know about getting true
Gang stalking
I have no idea what gang stalking
So it's the police that a lot of really paranoid people have that large groups of people are stalking them
So it would be like if you keeps
Being certain
People in your day-to-day life
It's the you create the belief within your head and all of them are working together to drive
And it's
A very very clear sign
Of almost destroyed
There
I don't know if it's ever been done
Quite frankly
Maybe it has it some point someone has done that
But it is
Definitely
Hallmark
Cuz it's just random people
Psychological
I think you would fight that pretty hard
I think it probably like trying
I don't know you might be right that's too hypothetical who cares they're railroading
Who knows
Paranoid schizophrenia
Defending against
Stocks or whatever
Spied on in his classes
Is Crisis actors
He didn't do it he wants to warn the snitches we believe that Linda has a bun
Bunch of patents for antennas
In order to get harp energy as explained to him by a fake.
They will create brain-controlled zombies on campus
In order to advocate for Liberal causes
He is wild
He the comic book he is my favorite crazy
At the end of that clip
He gets into like these gangstalkers
All you have to do is say no shoot through their programming
You know what that is
No
Expressing their is like
You getting their face you puncture their
There their programming
And then they you know they just go away
The reality is
You probably say a bunch of crazies
Stop somebody like I'm out
About
I don't talk to you anymore
So we have one more clip
On this day
November 12th there's a visit from
And we have nothing from
Cuz they resolved very boring
Interview Larry Nichols just tries to get money to his Paypal
And Alex Jones
Shoutouts to people who
Mac keeps trying to do and now it's like we can't
Can't do that you'd
Just can't name everybody who send you money
Call when something like a group come on now
Special group there's a difference between what we do and what they do
The only thing that
Interesting that you reveal
Is Vicki
Dinos
That Ross Perot was an intelligence officer running a game
Ross Perot
Made a deal with the Clinton
In order to run for president
Screw things up
For George h.w. Bush
Did not split that he didn't
Take both away from either
Candidate
Provoked
Right but he
The fucken on the show so we don't need to listen to him
But
Alex dropped this
Real fun
This is this is
This is Alex Jones being
What I've described as
Strfkr
By the way
It's always bad
People don't want to come
Former
I don't want to be talked about
How many people are aware of what's going on
And last night
I got a phone call
Bye
Got to say is one of the coolest Hollywood
Answer the phone
40 attacks
I'll just say that
I just cannot beat how many grapes
So wait
So
Do you know who he's talking about
It's from The Big Lebowski
Is it
Who has the vaguely of German.
It's Peter Stormare
Oh so it's not
Now I can't remember her
Call Aimee Mann
I don't think any man has any
Lions in the movie She's just there at the diner with them
Right there is the one who says give us the money Lebowski
He is like his cohort is a associate
I am fascinated
Peter Stormare is like
A giant star
A bunch of stuff like he's a character actor he's in a lot of like
The Coen Brothers Salvatore
He's great in American Gods that died
The Big Lebowski
Yeah there's a long list of people you'd rather
Turn out to be classical liberal
Maybe John Turturro
Or notes or Philip Seymour
Philip Seymour Hoffman
Colibri
Probably not probably not Tara Reid
Peter Stormare but I got great
But now it turns out that
I'm kind of on the fence again Alex
Miss attributing a line
Like he might think John Turturro says that
You might not know that it don't f*** with the Jesus's
Peter Stormare
Invert Warrior theoretically
Transformers movies
Where was that me
So was Wahlberg
Wahlburgers
Come on
Isn't John Cena in the new Transformer
I don't know I think he is I don't know about John Cena
You don't have any Troll Music like that kind of the hornet
So will you come to the end of our adventure here
No evolution in terms of trump
Some mentioned Russian Putin now but what we have is
String
F****** lunatic
Just the lunatic
Are coming aboard
But these are people who have been on the show
Before
For the most part like Mancow and Alex are good friends
Hamamoto has been around
And I guess General stubblebine autumn
Don't get that name wrong ever
Apple bottom for fun
And the
The lady who sells
Laminated cards for thirty bucks
That's it but you're seeing like the show is getting crazy
There is
She shows up
If there's an escalation of crazy that's going on and it's
Super interesting
I'm enjoying it so we'll see what happens next time
Weather like
Will accept this amount
And then everybody else climax
I have something to tell you
Another guest
It shows up in the near future
Future episode
You can follow us on Twitter at knowledge
Twitch.tv / knowledge fight that's everybody who's watching
You can find us every Monday through Thursday night 8 p.m. will be broadcasting live in
I will be filling Jordan for the time being
Stand-up comedy shows
Do Monday through Thursday
When I will return it
TBD on those gas but I will say this week Tuesday we have Joe McMahon
Also yeah
We're on iTunes
We are on
You should appreciate it
Also just
Add Media Matters or anybody to
Just get the f****** word out about this help
Yeah it seems like maybe
I should like to be on top of that right
Fellowship
We should get one of these the Ford Foundation Grant do the Lord's work
Or we stop congratulating
Professor of knowledge
Take the great respect of death
Could be
What's
Alex
Beard
Okay