Holding
Same color
I love your work
Hey everybody hello
Come back to knowledge fight I am Dan we are a couple dudes you like to sit around drink novelty Beverages and talk a little bit of
About Alex Jones oh yeah is there is there a catch to it is there a Twist camera
That's right moving on after everybody
Complaining about how dark my camera is which fairly reasonable
You know I kind of liked it
I gave you some
Sense of Mystery
Certainly
Unlike Alex Jones you don't crave the spotlight
See my I want to hide in a hole and make fun of his dumbass
Right but now the camera so you can see my luxuriant curls
Everybody
OK Google
I know a lot about Alex Jones and user do not I don't know right there's where we find our fun
Today we're going to be doing an interesting in-depth
Exploration of a past event
Well we were going to do this at our lives show that we had to cancel
Here we go. So today we'll be going over what Alex Jones did
On December 21st 2012 the day of the Mayan apocalypse
I got on there and had some fun
Did it happen
It didn't it didn't happen
I did not we can confirm that the world is
Still here
We will be drinking Faygo today in honor of the
Greats
Descending upon DC to fight the ants
They're doing but that's what they're doing it's not a fair now everybody's calling it that
I'm clear that there today I'm sure did not put out a statement
Elucidating exactly what they were doing
It's very clear what they're doing they've been labeled a gang by the justice
Department
The Juggalos are labeled a gang and
That is fun
Incredibly inappropriate
Not just that but they
Because of that
They
Have had their kids
Take a note
All of this s*** they've lost jobs
Like urine or lost parole if any of its probable cause
To be searched
If you get pulled over and you have a hatchet man tattoo
Man that's like that it's
Incredibly ridiculous
Solidarity with our Juggalo brothers and sisters
Juggalos and juggalettes
Big whoop whoop going out to you
I love everything about you except your music and
That's what I would you rather me talk about net in
Oh s*** going on up there
Thank you so much for joining up with the team we really appreciate it
If you out there would like to become a policy walk you may do so by going to our website
Which is knowledge feit.com quickly support the show button
And we will
Take all your money
That's that's naked capitalism right they're not happy with how that came out of my mouth
What's the issue with a couple other people in the last week
All the other co-host suck and I'm so happy that I have perfect jobs
Better
But it's thrilling to be back here with you and then also just like
The work of doing it every day I started to get used to it and then taking a couple days off
I like I'm eager
For The Fray
So I didn't know what to do with you
Yourself for those couple of
Computer like you think about it
Quickly become an addiction but
Instead I just sort of thought about cleaning my room into
Did not find out I was about to
Thanks
So let's get into it but before we get into the actual episode here is a fun out of context drop from Alex Jones
Weather
Personnel
The man
Weatherman weatherman
They just screamed weather weatherman
He's Furious about Job the smallest
Dumbest thing he can
Can think of no-one is
Complaining about weatherman especially men
He's a man we have the Mayan apocalypse to deal with who cares if it's weatherman or not
That clip is actually from a 2015 episode
Absolutely
Ben from the relevant episodes but I couldn't find a good like
Slip it from this cuz there's just
Wholesale Insanity drop
So Jordan let's talk a little bit about the Mayan apocalypse
I want to talk more about this
Stop weather
How do you get to be the top weather
Was there a competition
You gotta pay the cost to be the boss
You got to go through you got to go through all the ranks
You know like it's sort of like a Mortal Kombat tournament so it is weathering
Obelisk don't step to Tom Skilling
Piano character too many a man
To get to the top of Chicago's weather man
Game
Is that better
The context of that drop was that
French weatherman
I was saying the climb
And so
To go to
France's top weatherman
To get some good climate change denial from Alex if I had taken out more of that drop again
It's really funny because he's like I don't want
Bad things about
French
Things about the French I'm sure it's never
I looked at that freedom fries thing that was fun nobody is ever called them cheese-eating surrender monkey
Because I'm sure never never
I'm so
I think Willis tree
Might have dropped
The tiny bit if it does I apologize will it'll be up
So
Let's let's jump into this we are in
Okay we are back on
Sorry about that we are here
In 2012
Then we will begin the episode with Alex Jones giving his take
On what's going to happen
And what is happening that day
Naturally
I want to I want to say something really quick before we go with the Sun
I am not
A
Spiceology
No
No is that a thing
But I would guarantee that the planets did not line up
I don't believe in the movie
I want to point out that I'm
Triggered by Alex Jones
I'm doing that voice
Like it's one of the only things that really makes me mad is when he does that freak for
I had what he says
Humorous
Those two think that's
Really f****** make me angry as hell you can't add that many
I just too many shouldn't reveal this on-air last Alex Jones start doing those things all the time
The try to make me mad
But I heard like it's an uncontrollable Ray but I get released
Subaru
In no way does he
He like that's such a
Perfect way to attack us because
It's Like Only We Know
He's coming at us so he's not giving us any publicity or anything like that
It's just like a subtle f*** you
Humorous
Nothing at all the time
Anyway let's see what it says
Massive coronal ejection from a son
Table
Comets
Thundarr the Barbarian time destruction
Play or more globally
There aren't any Mass suicides I hope there aren't any mass killings
In association with it
There weren't
Running around 4
Jimmyandfriends
Oliver top Leatherman different
More.
Massive power outage in Annapolis Market in the world
You were on a respirator in the hospital didn't have a
Backup power
The power went off the nuclear reactor meltdown
Everybody there's one
Good Focus to concerned about those are concerned about
Like weatherman
Sure
So what
F****** so so now you
Taking The High Ground on disaster prediction
It's going to be the summer of Rage
What is fine but the mainstream media
Laughing
Finally talking about how it might be the apocalypse be fair we only know the summer of Rage narratives from 20
15 we don't know if in 2012 he was doing all that stuff every year
1999 he was saying that there are secret concentration camps
In Austin Airport
Well yeah about Y2K so
Yeah but that was just responsible report
He's learned an important lesson
Is what I'm getting at
Is that like
Can't join in with this I know Ted Anderson wants me to sell this f****** gold but I can't do it I got to do it a different way
I got to try and
An outsider you can't pedal the same narrative
I don't like CNN was saying
Media that was saying that the media was recovering weirdos on the internet who were talking about Barack Obama
Had just been reelected in
CNN was like well that's the end then I'm going to take your guns good luck in December
I don't do a good Obama impression that was not great the thing that I really love about that clip
Is that he's like
This is stupid
To 2012 isn't going to be anything but also
Power goes out
Nuclear
Meltdowns within a week
And that's when we start dating
Do you still trying to get some fear in there even with his rejection of the
Frightened fear ideas
So he has it not
Take us brain
It's just the end of the calendar
But if there's a power outage
We all die I think that most of the saying weirdos on the internet we're even pointing that stuff out that it's
Like it's not the end of the world as much
It is like what is it the Box
Tune the end of the baktun
I don't know what that is one of the
God links
Sometime in the Mayan
They just didn't make a next
Your calendar it's like it's like this wall calendar ends in December
Who cares
Alex has a different sort of explanation
What's really going on though
Which you might find a little interesting or you might find
Exactly what you would expect Alex does that
The globalist
Illuminati Riders
Special Report on this last week
Title
2012 doomsday Secrets Revealed
Greyhound
4 years
Without the shot.
Aquarius show
Who's he is a very important date for the women
They're big
Quickly on a lot of different fronts are there they are
Two-way spy system
And I will come up for you there on Google
Yeah that's what Google is spying on you and then you Google the NS
Alright you bad system if you're the
So he's already invalidated kind of his argument
Not the end of the world it's just the beginning of Satan
The rain
End of the world
Many of these
Globalist Illuminati writers and pointed out that it's the beginning of Satan
Take a note before we call it the age of Aquarius which as we all know
From Greek mythology Aquarius
Alex is hurt what song
I wanted to get some
Singing
So
That's sort of where he starts out
In terms of
Entirety of the
The Narrative of
But right
It's not a disaster
But it is a
And it might be safe
But not because of the Mayans that's
The globalist
Say something really bad happened it's the global are we sure the global is haven't been around for 7000
I don't know I mean they are big into child sacrifice so we know a lot of those Mesoamerican societies involve
Some measure of child sacrifice
Cut the top of a pyramid
Unfortunately Alex doesn't have a lot of time to ruminate on this because he has to do what I would do
Described as a set
I think this is a sketch
Happening
Somebody's going to jump the Gorge
He jumps
Something
It might be reminiscent of a shark
I'll look this up layout for you
First off let me show you some 2nd Amendment news here
Again
Still absolutely off-the-charts
Irani alive Mike
Alta Mere
Pennywise plays in the secret service has been there
Warren whatever they want
The globalist
Are scared right now
Because they know that you're aware of their problem
So that wasn't what he was saying before but also
I don't believe the Secret Service
This is their why would the Secret Service be there unless they were acting in their capacity is
Protectors of the
Department of Treasury and he's been counterfeit
It's the beginning of the age of Lucifer they've come to neutralize me before it kicks off
Come on alright
Secret Service
So I shall seek
One of Alex's big thing of the size of the Secret Service
An FBI
Come by as Studio before
Because he's had commenters
Is on his message board
But if threatened
To kill the president
I'm stuff like stupid trolls
And that f****** FBI's got to come down here and Shake
Me up about it
That's what that even
That doesn't make any sense
At all no. Why would the FBI go to Alec
Give up the IP addresses of your commenters like I don't have that address
Right it's sort of nonsensical but I do believe there's a chance that they may have
Comments on Point Inn
Over something like that because I did you go to Infowars
The comments
Are not to be believed
There's a lot of vitriol and anger and threats
Well I guess that is to be
Alright so I could see only people who would come if the FBI showed up
Zebra like this confirmed
Everything I've ever said I'm a victim
Orgasmic on it
Unbelievable
What are the reasons I don't believe that it is real is because at no point is there
Well there's that it plays out and here's the next clip of
I'm talking about this
Being in Infowars studios in occupied text
Piers Morgan for his attack on the Constitution
Right here
About whatever the FBI
Broadcasting live here it's probably over some
Idiot on a message board or something
Broadcast
Is it
Hey sis are you wanting
Sad
Wow
You are so natural
It's always nice to have a visit by the
Brutal boy
A lot of news to cover obviously here today we're going to break in about 3 minutes
Secret Service
Guys have a camera
Yeah
Whatever the secret services are for
This is just a number just to go reasons why can't prove they were there
I forgot
We do have a camera mounted out there
Yeah what will those when you come back we'll play it
It's odd dad said that he's going to go try and find this
Secret Service people while playing a special report
And what it is is
The Christmas message from the Federal Reserve
And it said just died like Jingle Bells kind of music playing in the background and Rob do doing a terrible voice
It's over where he's like
We are going to take
Make your money Merry Christmas
Alright
I tried
Try a little bit
I do love a says Mary quantitative
Using
Alright that's actually pretty solid
I appreciate merry Kwanzaa
The idea of
He's clearly got a sketch
And he's trying to improvise with in Italy
To do
What
Like waiting for guffman
But he is not at all funny and
Any possible way
No
Sketch
At its core is the Secret Service
But there's no other B
Not know whether there's any plan for like
He's just where do I go service took this
His car to get her
Centra the Sentra
It broke down along the way so you don't even know where the Secret Service is well he walked all the way outside the studio
A help
Of course and we're Infowars and we're like even though you're the Secret Service
We love to help
Secret service but the other thing too is that with all those like details of we have a camera out there you know
No we can swivel it around all those details
All those things are the indications
Alex Jones
Is Classic live
Whenever you're telling a story and like I said to them
Baba baba
Then I told him to f*** off
I remember an FBI guy coming up and talk to me at a restaur
Wire that poster of Obama
Andy loser
So here's where the scene plays at
Itself out and
No more talk of the Seeker
Service after the
Trying to do
We'll just come back with a subpoena
Wouldn't tell us. Basically what it was about
10 / 4
I'm sure it's going to be a commenter
I bet money
Infowars.com
If you go on there and threaten somebody I don't know what it's a
About you
Bright
Plug
3 days before it was supposed to come out
The clipboard the rest of it so I'll try to find out what it is
There is no b**** that you're the best
But he was a little match
No I want to talk to Alex
He's even sort of rewriting what happened to the last clip
I do
Sleep last night from A Christmas party are sticking up
Pics of the FBI diet
Knockin on the door
For whatever it's about
All right enough
How do you think they don't know
Beer on air schedule
I think they could
I think that can figure out what time the show
Where did they get the
The timezone wrong
Eastern Time
Sometime sorry
Bi-Lo plan for this s***
Also I like the idea that they were just
Come with us
Subpoena
So if he doesn't grab them then we still can't do anything
Yeah that's just dumb left it all in because it
It's really fun
To see him struggle with trying to make something
I off air be real
Funny I think he's trying to be manly
Like I don't give a fuk
Secret Service
Stare me
I'm great
I think that's more of what
What is your little
Secretive stuff
Reserve people in secret
Need the address
Which is why we know everything about
Well-documented
So after this Alex Jones
Gets a little bit freaked out and
Discusses Muslim women show up in his coffee
Did not not yet
At this point
In history
Cuz it was not the hot countercultural narrative
In 2012
I guess
I guess they did still hate immigrants
But they were just they had more important things to deal with
Which is Alex Jones fearing about his own mortality
FEMA camper whatever
I know that
The following with your little love GPS TracFone
I just get the go-ahead
What's the weather outside
Sofa actually f****** today today the idea that he's
He's f******
Pulling this high horse b******* about how
Police brutality is an issue today
A motherfuker got
Off
Yeah it was like luminar whatever
And it's f****** unreal
Yeah but the cops are beat
Finish it out of people protesters no worries narratives
You sure sure that's terrible
Alex and I'm assuming that Alex is going to keep his ideological
Consistency and say police are overreaching and they are murdering people because he's black lives matter what skin color
Are they are working for Soros
It's just cultural education and everybody who's White
As a real grievance and people who are black are just you know trying to
Create racial division
I was interested in what he was talking about in that clip
If you can talk about the
Carne killing in
As I looked into it I tried to Google
Carney killing that Carney guy is what he said
That's why I tried to Google it and
I can't like I tried so many different
Spellings of Kearney
Man like
I want I could find
I found a load of weird feel like there's only one spelling
Carnival
Carney
I was going to go I
Now
I found this story and this is from
City outside of San Antonio
A man is dead after police say he attempted to break into a northeast side home Friday afternoon
It happened on this
6300 block of Aspen
Open Farm Justice
2 p.m. police say a man tried to get into home through window
But a woman Inside met the alleged
Intruder and shot him
The alleged Intruder later identified as 39 year-old James
Kearney of New Braunfels
Died at a hospital
Police say Kearney left
The seven-year-old kid in the car during the attempted break-in
Oh well that's his real crime
So there's one
The car need killing
Window
So the other one is a really
I think it has
Has to be what he's talking about
But I don't
Think it
Works
For what he saying
There was a few that doesn't make any goddamn sense well there was a 1991 there was a mass
Massacre that happened
Interesting Lee
At a Luby's
Which we know is Alex Jones favorite.
Trouble and he always helps they want money or they don't have money to pay their their food
The greatest human being
Yeah so what happened was her old white ladies there's a guy named George hennard
He drove his pickup truck with nothing
He drove his pickup truck through the front window of the Luby's
And immediately shot
Man killed 23 people and wounded 20
27 others before fatally shooting himself
It's the fourth deadliest Massacre by single shooter in u.s.
Wow so the reason that this came up when I was looking into Carney killings is one of the people who he killed
Was named Patricia Kearney
So that is a connection to a Carne killing re-send in
Whatever
I don't think that Alex wants this to
To be the one though because
It was it was very clearly a violent
Massacre again
Text women
Yeah he intentionally for those are those are very unusual
New never see those numerous reports included the council
Menards
Hatred of women
The next roommate of his said he hated blacks
Hispanics gay
He said women were snakes
And always a derogatory remarks about them
Especially after fights
His mother
Passover
He passed over men to shoot women
14 of the 23 people killed were women
As were many of the wounded
He called two of them a bit
Before shooting
So that could have been the card I can't find
News story that matches up with what
He is actually describing
But those are a couple of Kearney related murders that have happened in
Guy who runs the world
Sick of it
Woman didn't like a creative Scooby-Doo kind of way
Tilt-A-Whirl just spin so fast everybody turns
Jelly you never operate
You know you never really hear about that out they ran away
You would think though that that's got to be a pro
Herbalife
Not there
Trucking
That's good point I forgot about
Organic
Artist Artist Artist
So in this next clip Alex Jones
Sort of exposes on are that they have no editorial process at Infowars
That he doesn't know what sir
Certain things are
How to spell defeat
Alicia article
Here for you
Job application
An option
No sex
New York
Is serious about gun confiscation
Housing Urban Development
Chicago
Is that what he
There's a typo right there this is like Tom Drudge
So
Did the the thing that he thinks is a typo I'm glad that I'm glad that he has some copyediting
Scales
It was not a typo State of the State address is a real thing for Governors to do
Tibia state-of-the-union or something like that a mistake
That would be okay
If you just on-air flub didn't realize that it was a real thing but listen to this
That right there
6 a.m. this morning whenever
Just got caught doing other things
New York Times
Article
There's better ways to do things
You know because we're free things at any point
Also sick ramshackle
Bulshit that he has
Like a supposedly has
Millions upon millions of viewers
But it's still like
What will do to look you misspelled
There is no bee Hornet live
I mean it's a bad process
Play button
At the same time
Are you finding an error that isn't an error
Yeah I saw the zits
This morning I meant
Had to tell him about it
Hateful eight on drugs
This is for real like the s*** Jerome corsi right
Because you're
Too accurate spelling you on the ball this is on drugs baby
So
We're about to get to the the Lions
The bulk
Okay of the episode what goes on on
December twenty
December 12th
December 21st December 21st 12 12 12
So is mine the really bad a calendar
12 12 12
That's what makes perfect level with our white people calendar
Isn't that our calendar based on an Arabic
Is a Gregorian
Darien based only from the Arabs
I don't know we sold everything just trying to save face at this point
So
After this point most of the episode is not really had all that much to do with 2012 with that Alexei that it's really just
The globalist
Secret Service
Secret Service heavy up
Episode yeah there's a lot of just stuff
The could have been on any episode at all
But now we get to
What Alex
Going to spend at least an
Hour-and-a-half
After this show on
And that is
An interview 911
An interview with David Icke
No
Alien overlord David Icke
Wow
Just for fun I want to read you a couple quotes
From David Icke before we get into his interview
Just so you can have a good sense of the man
If you don't know who he is
He is a guy who believe that there are lizard people
That have invaded the elite levels of
Society and they're trying to
All the globalist stuff that Alex believes just make them lizards
And it's David Icke
CK revealed Dick Cheney
Where was it done run
Rumsfeld
Ratman Lucy Kay wasn't serious
Was he
We super want to hear a couple quotes that should give you some
Pause about about David Icke
Inula and the very late 1800's a controversial document came to light called the protocols of the Elders of Zion
I call them the Illuminati protocols and I quote many extract
From them in the robots Rebellion
At the robot that's a book that he wrote
Yes
Big time
You can take from that and other quote cities may he totally believes the protocols are real
Sand just like
It's not about Jews their lizards
Everybody hates Jews insist it's not about you
Right globalists David Icke doesn't says there lizard people it's all just the same thing
God I just read errors does Raptors
Right now it's
Again he's evil which means the Raptor
Is it too complicated
This is going to dovetail slightly into basically Project Camelot territory
As we get through this out it'll be a little less painful as that but the whole scenario is play
Playing centuries ago because the reptilian
Operating from the lower fourth to my
Indeed
Whatever for
Controls them
Has most of the upper fourth
4th Dimension has tears
Do not know the fourth dimension
Nearest dump
You're very dumb dumb alright so the reptilians have a very different version of time than we have
Okay they can see in plan down the three-dimensional timeline in a way that those in
Three-dimensional form
Cannot like the movie arrival
Yeah we got so he has a lot of
That's kind of fun he is actually going to end up quoting a lot of movies
So here we go here's the
Alex Jones bringing David Icke
Into the program
Aaron
Explaining what
What David Icke steak on 2012
They can accelerate your enslavement
Which I approved because
So but they're there we can just pause for a second absolutely not
Every study of which Congress does not allow
No cuz the NRA has lobbied them to make it
Illegal
To study the results of gun can
Control laws
Proves
That crime is
But even so that's that's not what he's saying crime has gone down to
Write with these stay when you take
The guns away
As opposed to
When the guns go he's making a classical fallacy of confusing correlation and causation
The saying people have more guns now which is true
And crime has gone down
He's saying that the gun that have caused
The crimes go down
And of course there was that we every reference that study out of Stanford
They came out a couple months ago that showed
The places that have rights
Carry laws
Show 13
Percent increase
Recent violent crime
So
Studies that actually look at the real thing
Say that is not true
But Alex
Being able to like
A
Be
But I must be insane
But doesn't always
Get to David Icke baby
Not true
Mobile number
Twisted his arm to come on we
Little Rock
The world
Globalist push this
Is the launch of their luciferian error
2015 2016 41
That's
Currently may be true
2015 so if they are the globalist then
Or whatever like the prophecy might be if David Icke thinks
2015 2016 that's what she's going to go down like
You might have nailed that one happy fun if he was also like it's
The Russian Putin is going to compromise you Alex what you need to do is get out now
We'll get to equip here in a little bit that actually indicates
Animated Alex
Is already compromised
Okay
I'm not sure but I think
You might already have very pro-russian
In 2012
Our investigation into
That stuff is going to be
Impossibly long
I don't know how we'll ever pull that off but
So here we go Alex's
Who introduced the David Icke
Doesn't believe 2012 is legit 20
15 is looking
I like how he says over a decade ago
As if
Everybody a decade ago believed it but
I'm 2002 evraz like dude we've only got ten years left
Mayan calendar that makes
Perfect sense
I believe everything
And David Icke
No
I am
Truth-teller
Yeah exactly
The here's David Icke
Introduction into
The Fray
Well I just think it with heading Alex to a point in the New Year in 2013
When somebody sings going to come together
Fan of his Warriors have to win
We have space
Fiscal
Clippers are talking about
Obvious agenda
Porsche on down the road
If people saw that movie that was
Rescue people absolutely staggeringly rich
NAU
Hi-Tech
Top-of-the-range luxury capital
But certainly that's the only movie that's ever had that sort of thing
You certainly that isn't something that exists
Lots of Science Fiction throughout time
It's really strange that he would
Choose an allegorical movie in order to illustrate his point
There's another reason he chose
Nocatee Love Jennifer
It's not good
Pretty great it's not a good read
It's not a good movie
And the rest of the people
Feeding that wealth
We're actually in abject poverty and under
Beyond orwellian levels of control
Interesting to me because symbolism a lot and
Soco coincidence
Should be
Enum
Living in the area of Sandy Hook signed with the connections from that into the
Dark knight rising movie when abilities
They mailed out to the media
Attack papers
The shooter of Reagan
Really deeper into this really deep into this Alex it's all about the manipulation of the humans
Subconscious mind
So
So so not only is Sandy Hook
A hoax
Right but they like is onboard Ground Zero for
Every
Plan that the globalist
Have ever had because it was named
Glee before
Well it's bad guy certainly it's wagging their dick around base
So that is a very popular narrative with
Sandy Hook truthers
Now the idea that if you do watch Batman there is Sandy Hook written on a map
In the in the movie
Really that's weird
But
It's not that weird
Because the prop Mass
Of the movie
Is from Newtown Connecticut
Okay
So there's a decent chance
You just wrote Sandy Hook on it because it's his hometown
Yeah that's like if I were a prop master I might write
Or something like that
Brad dropped out of high school baby
No I wouldn't
And I hated that
How do I
Village not that it's not that crazy
It is crazy that there ended up being a shooting in the prop Masters Hometown but that is what we call clinic
Now
Predictive programming
Unfortunately
A little bit down the road what they're trying to do is
Manipulate
Well here here hear me out on this
A little bit after the movie came out
The prop master
Whose name is like Scott Grabowski or something like that house key
He died
If he had a kilt
He must have
Timeline doesn't match up
He got killed
He was in a car accident where a 18 year old driver jumped the median and hit him head-on
And he died
Yeah that's very sad but it also
To mine eyes seems like a
Project winter
However
Our friend John Rappaport
F****** no more fake news. Calm about how this proper
Master put Sandy Hook into the movie
To tell the public about globalist plans that he had uncovered and then he was murdered
In this car accident to silence him from telling anything else
Reasonable support his plan
To warn us of the globalist
Yes
You put the smallest thing
On a newspaper
That you are not paying attention
In order to warn everybody a mapping in the movie
What do you mean newspaper
Whatever
The point being
That is a bad
It's not great
It's not a great plan
I just would like to point out the John rapaport's website is called No More
Dot-com
It's
It's not called no more bad theories
Dot-com
Play so that's fair I guess but a pre-emptive go f*** yourself John Ross Park coming in this episode
Yeah you would have to
Have news
In order for it to be
Maybe fate will the news he is just making s*** up here what the news is that they prop Master died
Yeah and he's faking the news
Of why he died
It just has a conjecture
Of why he died it was still reporting
That
Young people are generally more irresponsible drivers
They are more prone to act
These things happen
When it's sad but it's not
Not a globalist
Murder though
From everything I can tell
Stupid
Bringing that stuff up as is Alex Jones
All this stuff is a
Crocodiles
And it's it's disappointing to me
Lakers are you
Appointed whenever you get into
To like one of these guys
I don't hate David Icke
As much as I hate Alex Jones
Because at least David Icke talks about some stuff that I'm like
I'm into
Like talkin about the hypnotic effect
So television
And stuff like that there are good messages that
They can come from some of the stuff even if you saying
That these
Definitely not Jewish reptilian lizards are trying to hypnotize you through television
I don't buy that but I Do by the negative effects of watching
Too much TV
Play too many video games
That sort of thing
It can be a negative info
Not always
Bring up that that's worth of stuff
I'm into it
And when I hear someone like him that I'm like
I don't hate you
And then they're like Sandy Hook a totally fake
I liked it just drives
Insane house
Eyes are so close
Figuring out
Why we need socialist
Like they're so close to it they're like
Too much inequality there's a
The small group
People who have all the money
There's a larger
People who have no money
Serps
So maybe
Do a little bit of
Reading into
When that
For and how peep
People f****** got out of
But instead of
It's just like the word socialism is bad socialism
F****** insane you're almost there
Dead
Will make it
Totally
It's because of the idea of the prod problem reaction
Solution the hegelian dialect narrative that they have in their head which is they believe that
The
The inequality and the Have Nots
Stop being so that their suffering so much and
Society
Is the problem
Then the globalist
Come in with socialism which is the
Solution that they have pre-made for people
Steak and then they're like all we loved it we will take this illusion
Tyranny
Socialism leads to the tyranny
That just doesn't make
Any sense if they're globulus they already own every
Right so they're going to
Cause
That issue
Bringing socialism
Wherein they won't
Oh never
Tyranny
Where they will own
On everything
It's it's it's sort of like it seems like
But it seems like they're more just bored like can we pull this off work we're trillionaires who gives a s*** let's give it a shot
Exactly yeah
Style points are important
It's part of Electro Magic
So in this next clip Alex Jones talks
A bit about some
Scripture
I'm out on the other side of it I have some iffy news
Important
Expand their Horizons
To expand their awareness of what's going on this universe
Artificial boxer Matrix
Work together
I am. Not to be divided
And that's why it's so important
That we support the work today but I could doing because
Mandachord
Christ was quoted as saying
By its fruits
So I don't like you I don't like Spanish
To me the fruit
Roots of David Ike's work
Sort of veiled anti-semitism
Certainly I don't like the phrasing of like
Christ was quoted
I just don't like to interview Coronavirus
Undertaker guns so the other problem with this
Is I'm going to go to the doc cam here
David Icke in the past
Has I said this
Depress
It interview David Icke has literally said that
He is Christ
That be all right
And then whatever gets asked a direct question
Then he starts dissembling like
The thing is right you talked about the godhead
And I also in that interview if you want to watch that
It's pretty wild stuff
He goes into talking about like
The color turquoise resonates with wisdom so if you wear it
It attracts wisdom to you
If you wear black
Guess you hate
Eventbee got the guy was doing interviews like
That's bad news for four months
And that everyone laughs is that guy you know
The great thing is
Great thing is laughter laughter is so great
It's a great way to break through conditioning and
Advocate interview his like
You understand They're laughing
Accu
It's a brutal brutal f****** interview
But David Icke headset kids
The son of God
Which I would imagine Alex Jones would not be
Well I'm
His work proved
That he is
Yeah
So you judging you judge the Son of God by
The fruits of his
Is fruits are a peach but seriously
Has he done anything
Like.
He's giving a lot of speeches
What do you want
If you're going to come with us the fruits of his work bulshit then there has to
To be work
And then
Freaks well I guess so fruit if he's just done work
And it's been
Speeches where he's gotten
Unpaid
There's not really any
Fruit that I'm guessing the way it would be conceptualized as that he's woken up a lot of people's bringing awareness
Right he's Eastern people on to the globalist even if you thinks with their reptilian
Lizards some people are heroes
Bring awareness
Breast cancer
Lizardman Lizardman
And that's where he's on
So Alex asked David Icke
You know good
Evil
Lizards
How's it going for these Elites
How are things for the globalist
Read my books in the in the end
That they'll see a lot of backgrounds to the fact
This
Pools
Which
Is Manifest in our reality through these Bloodlines and you know these into breathing so cold
Elite Bloodlines and Families
We do not depend upon them
Depend upon us
It's the relationship between humans and
The parasite
216 Parasite Eve off the parasite to The Host
Humanity is the host
These all the parasites so how is it going
Greater than we ever imagined currently
Without the parasite but it can exist without us
I'm so
Energy
Which
Is the parasites
Lifeforce if you like
Is low vibrational human emotion all emotions around fear and hatred conflict
Warriors Terra
Manipulation and construct a global Society
To create situations that
Constantly generate those energies soap
You can look at Sandy Hook
So that ended poorly
Is it going for
Going gray
He spent
A lot of words
Saying nothing nothing and then answered
No question at the same time I think there is there's a version of what he's saying that if you want to look at it
Artfully
And metaphorically
He's saying something good if you want to look at it
Well if you take the
Sandy Hook part out of the end of eclipse
It just leave that alone
Just ignore ignore that he said that at all
But if you just take that he saying
The way you saying it is there these lizard reptilian Elites
Who feed off negative energy
And that could be construed as a metaphorical way of
Expressing
That these
Oppressive government forces
And people who wish to Duell
Know that in negative Circle
Santa's they can get away with a lot more
If you are attacked
It's easier to
Get your
Military-industrial complex going and make money off War that's shows that is what he's saying he's doing
A terrible job
Saying it
But at the same time it's like he is right
Wow it is
It is the global
I don't think he's saying that
Kia Kia
No no
You spelled it out clearly saying they literally feed off negative energy
Do you like Mike we eat food
Yeah but he means literally in the way that everybody uses it
Which is to say
Bright
Alright so
You might have noticed that he is literally always telling the
Literally
Haha at the end of that clip you mentioned Sandy Hook you may recall
Any does Sabor in this next
You can look at Sandy Hook
You can
Oh yes
It's about
An excuse to take guns away because of the same reason that they
Does dr.
Guns and ammunition being owned by Jewish people
Copycat
Conditioning
Yeah it was
Another one is
To to create
What
Emotional trauma
Collectively in the population
Adjusting America of Sandy Hook
Much greater that because
So that's where talk about psychic vampires
David Icke
Am I supposed to David I can listen
I can't I can't do this
I can't do a British accent
That sounds like
Tired
This is also a really like
Good call good call we're going to start we're going to scratch that we're just never going to do that again
So
I again think that he's trying to express something else
But doing it through this
Paradigm of
Of lizards
Globalist
What have you
And that is but it really
The idea that these events happen
Every contextualize it in
In terms of an evil force
Faking it or making these thing
Things happen in order to
Get their evil food
It's easier to wrestle with that
Then it is to wrestle with
The fact that other humans
Might bring guns
The school and kill chill
Because they're that
I disconnected their that abused than that
In pain themselves
It's much harder to look at humanity and see it for what it is then to it is to make up narratives about
Space lizards
It's base lizard
And they have to do these things
In order to get their food and they could only eat
We all feel terrible thing
So they create Mass trauma events like this
So that they can
Can feed off a track
Denial wherein
If you create
This
False reality of
The enemy is
Using this
As a
As a false
Swag in the same way that he
Thanks that you know Sandy Hook is a false
Aflac in order to get
Carbon tax
Right
To wrestle with
The fact that
Humanity has killed it so
Yeah and that's something that
You know if you would actively participate
Your denial only has
Stronger
Otherwise
You're going to have a day
Where you just sit down and all the sudden it
To you and your like
Everything I have done
Has
Wound up hurting
As you pointed out it as a clip was playing like that wasn't the first school she
And the other thing about like when you talk about climate change that relates to this is
When Sandy Hook happened it we didn't
Not know that could happen
Like it didn't happen before and one of the things with x
Painful about it is
On some level we had warning
Oh absolutely shootings happened and they happened a bunch
And we should know that these things are
Are going to happen unless we
We've behaved if
And with climate change the same thing
We know we have warning
And when things go as bad as they
Probably will
Will have to wrestle with the fact that like
We know we knew we were doing
Star signs
Sucking is
Much money out of
They got to believe that they're armored redoubt so I think it's more like they have to have had this idea from from the researcher
Well the worst effects won't be till 2
Well I'll be f******
What do I give a s***
Like that's one of the big issue
Shoes that I have with all of these people
Is there
Not killing themselves
They're killing us
It's so f******
Frustrating
I mean if you do
Just want to engage
With that dumbass
What is narrative
There
Using
Trauma today
Psychic
Fear vampire bulge
Yeah
Don't they know
How
F******
Numb
We've become
To school shooting
Like I remember
Sandy Hook happen
I remember being
So angry but it's
The same time
Just resigned like
We didn't do anything after the last shooting we're not going to do anything after the shooting
So there will be another
How do I
How can I process
Best ramen
Now when it is only foreshadowing for more
Perfect
That's exactly what the globalist
Right
F****** insane
You know what else
Isn't saying I want to take your
I don't have any
Okay can I have them I don't have any
Anyway it wasn't as the guy who can
So in this next clip
Alex Jones reveal
I think
Alex Jones believes
Vudu
Thousand years old 500 years old
Jewish mysticism
If you do a model of somebody when you stab
And it makes them actually get hurt
Weather is real or not
Stop
I don't believe in stuff like
Bitter
Something spiritual
Do they know 60
Earthquake
They have these cells in our brains a pickup magnetic information
Follow these magnetic
So Alex believes in voodoo
1 Apollo Huawei that you start clips
Would just as random non-sequitur like
All the things that I was expecting
To hear the first words being
Anton LaVey
Was not one of those
I'd of course it's not the doll doing it
Don't paint me with that brush
The spirits that inhabit it are
Yeah
So leaving all that other stuff aside the ley-lines and when have you had something we can
Discuss out of paranormal casting at some point
But Alex Jones
Let's see what David Icke thinks
Sorry sorry
Wendy
Create a hologram
In a studio
The information that creates the apparent imaginal phone
Is iPhone
And when you look at it looks like a fingerprint is just wavy lines
But you fire a laser at the wavy lines and suddenly and apparently the best of them anyway
Apparently
Breakfast in front of you and you know we seeing all the graphics is being used more and more in stage shows
End conversation all this stuff
Television
If you can get
To the waveform level of everything
Holographic projection
He's focusing.
Anyting
Slavery is simply
A focus on
Attention
Represents the target
Like a wand
Focusing attention on the electrical magnetic field of the dolls
You can connect that
Frequency wise vibrational wise
Then gets transferred
To the Target through the electromagnetic
When it's a reality but those behind those behind those that we see as obvious
Orchestrations of Mustafa still on Suzanne's in Pinole rides if you can actually see them
So he does believe in voodoo
Percent
Fix the elite
There's always
Always super duper relates always now a pseudo-scientific
Justification for Magic
Like that's the funny thing about science
Especially with
C Clarke's quote you know
No enemies sufficient
Matter that can
But these guys just
Makeup set
Bulshit like
A magnetic
Field do they
Could they sit down and
Explain what a magnetic field is outside of any kind of magic just like
What is a magnetic field
He could talk for a long time
Frankly I'm asking
Now if you can
No
Certainly not a little bit of prep
Okay but what I can tell you is a little bit about David I can pass
He used to be a soccer player I believe he'd know you was pretty musica famous
Announcer
After he played soccer for a bit in England then became an announcer
And then I went nuts
A little bit
He I listen to a long interview with him on Project Camelot
He does it to our interview with Kerry Cassidy
Great where he explains that he went to like a jungle or something like that
And he was on a Mountaintop
And all of a sudden he went into Christ pose
He had his arms
Extended
That he couldn't move his arms
Said he heard a voice that told him
You will stay like this until the rain come
He could see way off in the distance
Rain cloud
He's like that's really far away
He was there for like hours
Okay the Christ pose
Who is downloading information
Like some entity was talking to him and
Explaining everything to him catch Atlanta soon as the rain came and washed over him
He came back to his senses and his arms came down
He was in a lot of pain cuz
Is doing this for a long time hurts
Wright hot
And
So that's
When people started talking
What other voices started creeping into his head after the
This transformative experience more characters that we wind up meeting on
On the show The More
Become a game for me
Need to be like okay
Is this
Pure mental
Conning
Is this a mixture of
The two like who's who's where and with David Icke you're like
Oh you just haven't
I know he's not trying to screw anybody
But he is trying to make money though
Yeah but I mean
Is a multi multi-millionaire
He's one of these
Incredibly rich
Yeah he is
Is very but he might be
I don't know anything about it but I do I mean he's
Football in a
Football
Wow
Batman
That's horrific
So you but he's like one of the
The biggest people
Envy Spring
World like he is the Michael Jordan of
Absurd
Conspiracy
Instead of the Michael Jordan gambling
Right
I don't know about that I don't know how
So
You can't
You can't down play David Icke sexual
Importance to the
The Fringe
Conspiracy world
He's up there
Play up-top
Because he was talking about this stuff in like the 90s program
Words don't
Well he went on that TV show that we just dropped a tiny clip of
And got my box
Roundly
When he said that he was Christ son
Our godson and said that turquoise is a magical
What color you should all wear
I do believe
He says all that stuff on TV gets mocked and then with
Takes his lumps
Like he
Keeps going
And I think a lot of the people in the
The conspiracy Community were really impressed
Like he became a hero in that he didn't back down
When everyone was making fun of him he was like
Now f*** y'all
I'm going to keep going
I have two stomachs that I admire that
There's a certain amount of it yeah and because he
He stuck with it he was on the like
Early floors of a publicly
I mean there's a song by a
George Clinton and P-Funk
I'd rather just scream David Icke
I got the word out
You know you're good I also had a friend growing up in Columbia named David Icke
Who is just a buddy of mine that I drink with
Get high with
And
I thought that the P-Funk song was referring
Cuz I didn't know about the you didn't know about the famous David Icke
You just assumed that your buddy
Was I supposed to smoke a lot of weed
Unbelievable thing
Here's another unbelievable thing Alex Jones talking about ways you
Street cops
Oh no
I'm we keep putting this information out
The information is so powerful
In the end
Why because it's true and Josh
When your scared of government
They absolutely run
That must be because you're white
Can you open
Can you imagine the scenario
What to do with race Dan
Blue lives matter his argument
Is that he's making is that if you're scared of cops they'll run all over you
But if you talk to them like children they Runaway
Or if you laugh at them
That does not work for everybody Alex
To murder you and then 45
Translator
Murder El kabong
Chicago Hoover
Leading the abolished
Police movement no
It's
Very it's very
Sing idea like
They're point being that
The police were really just a
Established
To take the rich people protect the property of rich people
Well I guess kind of where they
From covid-19
Is that both of their first album
I meant they released one that only Martin shkreli has
Or does he
Play my God
I know is that your day just
Want to replace it
Something that
Not inherently race
Which I don't know
I don't know what that would be like
Could it be
Simple p
Keeping Force
What they would we allow the
Braided beard
I don't know maybe so
Some sort of community organization
In the house oversight boards and stuff like that
Play I don't know I think it's whatever
Whatever cops
Have a boy
Black-site
In Chicago like the fuc
CIA
God dammit
I understand it's going to f******
Far-right and they're immunize from any kind of concert
Sequences for their
Which is
Messy closet
You have
Federal crimes
Ruling on that
F*** face who just murdered a black.
And got off
St.Louis
The last line of the judge
His ruling was
It is
It is an easy as some
How to make
Betty heroin
Dealer would have a gun in his
Right and
There's no evidence
Oh no not at all
Walker discharge was just says what
Is a f****** racist
Is it lonely at Mommy.
Deconstructed Society
Because I agree with that premise as
As you phrased it
Is it
In any way races
If if if you are just talking about the general group heroin
Dealers is it weird to assume that a heroin dealer would have a gun
Okay weird to assume that
Every black man driving alone in a car is a heroin dealer
Racist motherfuking
Judge who just
God dammit I look just the cops during the protest now you can see the inherent race
Within the police force
Ripped up with all of this
Anti-riot gear
Lying about what other people are doing
So they can just
Defied their
A bastard violent
Against
And a lot of that comes into like the intersection of the militarization of police
And the classic
Like all of it
Is bundled together
Quite but
David Icke
Does not believe necessarily that it's bad
Humans
That are doing things
Like the stuff
We're talking about
Disbelieve that
He has a completely different take on
Check this out
But I mean
About this
Right
There is an area
I've been pulling together
At the same time
Find it
Very compelling
When I say I see
Very different peoples and very different sources coming to the same conclusions and talking about the same things
Which is described
Precisely the same way
By Styx
By the pre-islamic Arabian sand
Islam picked it up the gin
They calling me Central America the flyer
Christian School
The demons and so on and so forth
When you look at what he said
About these writings from 2000 years ago say about
Please
Have the ability
For what
The gnostics code intentionality what I will translate as
Creative imagination
It's like
Try to get a computer to create something Yukon
In the information to create
Does Truitt
We have creative imagination
To create
The world that they want which is this
Nightmare
And then some
To get us to use our creative imagination
That's why they
Programming
Constantly
What's up
It's not a pardon
So it's the archons or the jinns are the demons
They're possessing people to act all bad because I need to create this world
But they don't have any creativity they have to allow a they possess us
To use our creativity or something
Also
Do you want to look into it there's some really in
Stuff like
Computers can compose music
Computers can create art
Essentially of their own volition
They're granted you do have to have like
Gear S2 have access to examples
But it can create entirely new thing
Out of
And then your question because
Comes what is it
Worth
You know that kind
Is there any
Stickability roll
Although there is one thing that does make
Is that whenever you see
See so many
Coming to
To the same conclusion
Or at least
You just assume it's
Cuz you didn't f****** read anything
Think about it for a few goddamn
But the point being
2000 years ago
It's the same f****** idiots who are trying to just
By human behavior
By attributing it to something
Elsewise
No reason that my my dad
Constantly goes on about how human beings are
Fallen
Is because
It's in
Possible to just take
Responsibility for being an a******
Yeah like that's just what they
Can't deal with
It's always always been a human
Tradition to be like
It was witches
It's Jim it's whatever the f*** you want to call it
Right and if you want to take
Just because you brought in witches
If you want to look at the history of witches
Traditional
Misogynist brothers that and then also like the Salem Witch Trials was about land basically it wasn't even about the
It was using
Demonic
Language
In order to facilitate whatever
Economic goals you already have and that's what David Icke is doing to
Strange that a lot of the women who were a
To being witches were
Widows or single women
Who owned thing
Right and if you got
Killed as a witch
Guess we're all of that
Stuff went there and they had land disputes with the like
Family
Call such crazy. There was a
Guy who wanted an
Inherit something
Grandmas
I don't know if that's the same one but there was one guy wanted to
Didn't hear it stuff
But she was widowed and she married a black guy
And yeah
That one could not have been more open and shut for those guys because then the guy would inherit property
Not going to happen that's all this stuff about demonic stuff there's a lot of different brand
Chances that it covers
In terms of what
It's B one part that stuff bigotry misogyny
It like that throughout his
And then the other is not trying to wrestle with
The downside of Being Human
Sometimes do f***** up stuff
And they do it.
They do it
Their own game
Yeah like they once
Can convince
Dumpy
People to just believe in this
Nan said it so they can get what they want
It would be fun if it was all gone
Party that's what it is
Everybody back
Brought it back to politics
Alright so here's some more about these archons David Icke
Tell you about
They can be described
The Gnostic said in one word
Deceivers
That method
Manipulation is deception
They all mind parasite
Antiparasite of human energy and they
Parasite of the human mind and manipulate the human mind this is the Christian
Perception of
The Possession which is true
These things these things exist
Energetic field so energetic entities
They look into people at the electromagnetic field
Level and then start dictating through that the perceptions of the behavior of the possessed person
The gnostics
The
Able to create something that they call Hal h a l
Which translates as wait for it
Virtual reality
They have the ability to make you burst anything on actually
By manipulating the way
Fat people construct reality in the few cubic centimeters the back of the brain that's how I do
Sedan
That is been mentioned already today
Eastbay invert
Everything
Turn everything on its head
The winter bomber talks about love he's talking about hate
You got everything upside down
When the rituals are worshiping and interact
Invert
Everything
Across the Universe
Oh
Everything is turned upside down
Is why this is the force
Families in Elite families and Bloodlines are so obsessed with bloodline
Have a hybrid genetics
Hybrid
Energetic
Field
Which is much closer to the energetic
If you miss admirations because they have be specifically created on the Buddy
The level
Energetically vibrational frequency wise
Closely connected to these all come to concert is it up right outside of you inside
The possession of these Bloodlines is able to be
Stan is the general population
When you looking at the Rockefeller snow Rothschild in the British royal family and all these people
You are looking at these are Concepts
Entities
Incarnated in your remote control
Run from Houston
No empathy they have no conscience
Society
To bring about an end
Total human control
So
Why
What would you mean been around
Years how would they not already
Cuz they're waiting for the endgame
Which is I guess
Trump I don't know
Why would you do that
I don't know
Control
What
Terbium
Control when they're already in control
I know it's stupid
But would they
Okay
Again war games
More games you get rid of we didn't have a graphic
Another word video
We got to have some more
Jason Graphics look it up drinking Faygo
Okay
So
Your urine energetic
Okay first of all what does that look
Looks like this
I am an energetic being my man
Alright 7th density like being
Okay. Go ahead
Alright so if I shot a laser at you turn into a hologram something like that
No one's ever tried
So
You are interbreeding with
British people
And and the Rockefellers
And then
The goal is to
To get rid of totaled
Right
Okay
And then what
I don't why don't like playing this war game cuz I don't know it's total control
They already have
Look I want to tell you this
This is another instance of him trying to artistic
Sickly say something that makes
Some sense
But because of the way he's doing it because he literally believes the things he
He saying
He's crazy what he's talking about
In terms of these bloodline
Is his explanation
Open for ideas
Text intermarry and do that because
Their bloodlines are
Easier for the archon
To manipulate
And
Possess
Their bodies
So the archons are are
Demanding that these bloodlines
Stay pure in order that they be the vessels
For their evil plans on Earth
The reality is
That this is just a practice
It goes back to
The beginnings of human history
Where in
Rich people don't marry outside of property classes
Because you will lose
What you have
That's why in a lot of cultures you'd marry your cousin
Things like that
Property within
In the family
Answer you have these people who are like
The Rothschilds
Who everybody likes to appoint their little leggy finger at
They marry Within
Higher stratum
Because
Some reason
Don't want to lose billions of dollars to somebody in a divorce or whatever to get marry another child of a billionaire
Yeah it's no real issue
I'll have your s*** already and you can
Consolidate you also make alliances
Between Super Rich families that bring more
Into both of your families
So that is why they do it it's not because of archon possession
Natalie pathological need
Keep stuff now we get back to where he
Accidentally kind of advocating for socialism
Because
He wants to stop this archon possession
And all that s*** in the bloodlines
Disruption of the bloodline
When's or whatever and we would too but is why he wants to
To raise the estate tax
And it should be after 2000000 instead of 5
I don't disagree with that but I think that that that magical worldview but very
Very sensible solutions to it
Like listen
All these f****** energetic
Bees are, are taking
All of our money
Pulling all of this b******* and
That's why I think we
We need a return to the
The New Deal
I need to establish a 95% tax
On the wealthy
You know what I mean like you
You're crazy you're crazy I like you
You don't have been thinking about I've been thinking a lot about the idea that people like Alex Jones
The people of the libertarian bent
Back to I get into inches
The idea that if you make it
Like
If you take if you tax super-rich people then they'll be no incentive
Super rich
My response to that is
Good
I don't think that there should be an incentive to have 20 billion dollars or whatever
I think as I've seen
Our friend Katie McVey is opposed to this couple times I think it's a really good way of putting it
The choice of being super wealthy
Is Amora Lisa
Suspicious choice
Yeah I like I kind of agree with that that's very brother if you have over 10 billion dollars in your charge 100 per
Percent tax
Over 10 million dollars that you make in a year that does not be incentivize people to make business
That doesn't do incentivised able to be reasonably wildly successful all it does
It'd be like if you make over 10 million dollars in a year you're probably f****** something up you're probably doing something he leave
Google or at least like why do you need to do that and then you make over 10 million dollars here until 1
Charity
Problem solves itself
Pennywise
Just that but
If you
Incentivize
To get a billion dollars
Instead of 10
10 million that opens up more
More space in the market for
For somebody else
To try and get some of that
10 million-dollar
Or or apple or if Google is like a 70 billion dollar company or whatever
And they only got to keep
10 million
All of a sudden
But they don't want to grow as big
Well it was Allstate and they would want to pay their f****** employee
Exactly incentivize taken care of everybody a little bit more because then if you're so against paying
Taxes you can get around that it operating costs by paying people reasonable amount of money
I fully support I've been possessed by the archons
Or
The dark
Carnival
One of the two
Woop woop to my homies
This is why we should
So a in an NRA
In our estimation David Icke
Is maybe trying to
Expressive reasonable thing
In a crazy way
And we're not the only people who think God
David Icke
It's crazy here so here's what Alex says to him
This is business
Bizarre for him to be saying
But I like it
I remember
First reading
You want to hear bugs like 18 years ago
No
And
Because I'm hearing about all this occultism
Thought
I didn't even know that
So that flies in the face of how he presented everything back then
And the entire documentary he goes in
Expecting to find proof that there were spanked
But he accidentally let slip
Planning to find
Write a Jon Ronson has said that is basically what he did he was thrilled
To misrepresent the things
Defiled in order
To prove his Beast
Sis of devil worship
But the other thing he let slip that
Some TV station
Feed him
To sneak out
I don't think I've ever heard him mention that
No are you sure that
I bet
Man that sounds like a
Kauai the right
It's hard to say
With him it's always either a lie or an axe
I think it would I think it's true
Because
Fayetteville I would
Be someone else paid me to do it
Yeah that's
Takes away from The credibility of the documentary
Yeah that's now at this point has a financial incentive to
To make it more
Bulshit
But was it broadcast
Cast Ynet
No I don't
No but the people who are along with him where
From Channel 3 couple people from Channel 4 I believe
Let's do they broadcast their own thing
And maybe use some of his footage but his documentary was
Broadcast
Gotcha
So I don't know if that's weird
Suspicious
Right
The next not even Morris
Suspicious
So we we've documented in 2015 and 27
Some incredibly pro-russia
Positions on Alex's Park
He
May or may not have
I had interaction with Russian intelligence
Yep
Consistently think Putin is the last thing said
Us and the Ant
Antichrist
And here's one of his comments on Russian propaganda back
Back in 20
Love it
To article about
Was funded by hundreds of millions of dollars
Russian government money
On Iranian TV British TV French TV
Brazilian TV
Tony moly on us television when they call me or they stuff going just because half the time they cash
5 generator views that actually just say whatever I wanted to
I would suspect
Constitution was Don Meredith
Yep
So in the beginning of that clip you admits that Artie was founded with millions of dollars of Russian money
How does a Russian State media Outlet takes public funds
Swell soda
I saw some of our
Voice of America whatever go
Definitely okay for a government to invest
In a
Media out
Find the way they
It is important
9 or how they
I definitely think that there is no finer
Or
Violent incentive
To support everything The Rush
But goes crazy
And so Alex even admitting that he understands that it's
State media
Still is like
They let me say whatever I want
And they told me that the head is a listener
Yeah and
I'm right on
If you started with
Alex
I love your show
Right
You could then say everything
You say
Kneb like you know what you might have a point there I think I could pick you love me
I love you
I think I could tweet at him and be like we're big fans
Can we get a retweet and he might
I'm not sure cuz I don't know how to act
On Twitter but
So you gets into
Gets it though
He was early on the David Icke train
So I ended next clip Alex Jones even Alex says
Maybe take your own advice Alex
I was a little smarter back that apparently
So is that clip Alex Jones has some thoughts about the NRA
Bechara
You know that right
Guapo's
Show yes we're in deep trouble
So
Is what Alex Jones says on December 21st 2012
Not true but let's go to what you said on June 19th 2015
About 556 in front of me
This is a plug
These guns aren't
Idiotically
Obviously
Look at The Logical service yet.
They're now saying gun ownership is racist
At the end of the Civil War
It was race
The first gun laws were racist
NRA was a racist organization
Is again
Upside down
It's a total fraud
I'm not even going to get into the NRA history
But everybody
Black
252 Klux Klan
Again
And the party the Ku Klux Klan the Democrats want our gun
So Alex Jones sebaik s*** up whenever he wants
In order to
Those are contradictory
Unless I guess you could say
That the NRA was created by the federal government in order to arm black people to fight the KKK
All of it's not true of the federal government
At the same time
Passing
Racist gun laws
Keep guns away
Right now the government is
Responding the NRA
And
Keeping black
Getting guns
The magical part about it is a
It's all lies like all of it isn't
Begin to illustrate like
He just he's
Never not making
Stuff up
It's just
Anyway
Whatever fits within his
His narrative at any good
Point-in-time the narrative
It is like
He does
Though
Make it so it has
Sarso Malik
Valuable
That he can
Turn it into whatever he wants and any possible deniability that's not too impressive
And once again ever
Time
Somebody
Republican goes you know Democrats are the party of the
Go fuc yourself
Read an actual f******
Please
Fluent learn about how parties has changed over time
Well the Whigs are actually
You come on
Lincoln wasn't a Republican or fuckyourself
If anybody
Nowadays tells you that there are classical liberal
Oh yeah run
Fox Run
Because they are a liar
And a libertarian
I'm at me
You got to get out of there
Do we have one more clip
Trump is a Republican
He's a member of the no no
Is a classical liberal
F******
Also I should point this out over the last week
Whatever this
Bears that will have been last week
Alex Jones
That to Alex Jones has come out and said that he might so
Support The Rock
Against Trump
That's true I think we can get together on the
Not one pet stroller
Alex
He made it it'll take that seriously trying to get head lice
So is our last clip
We have
Faucet off now
Terrible
It's it's
Horrific but it's it's like
You barely even
Saw the news
It's another school shooting
Nobody's going to do anything about it
We're just going to watch more kids die every f******
Alex's argument would be that that means it was a real shooting and not a false flag because
Cuz it didn't get a lot of press
Okay cuz you know the real ones you don't talk about
You want to give attention
I don't want to go down that line cuz I
Play this last clip
It's it's a delight
And it's which one of those
Every now and again
We get to do an episode where The Parting Shot like the last
Clip is perfect
And this is
Perfect
This is great
This is Alex
Being a dumb dumb Alex man
He's finished his interview with David Icke he's gone
I've talked a lot about archons and all that s***
Anti-heroes
Here is how he tries to end the broadcast
Jay this tickles
We live in a world of wonderment
And and
Credible
Opportunity
And
The only reasonable is in charge is because good men and women
Do nothing
Do you know that
I would encourage everybody to take this opportunity
Christmas Santa we have right now.
Holiday now we can make it into something good to give the gift of proof
Whether it's a copy one of my films already in Forbes Magazine
Dot-com
95 a month
Passcode
Christmas shopping done right there and the crazy crowd all the car wrecks
Prisonplanet.tv
Alternative media system
And and
Do it
Oh that's great though
Even though it's
Been taken over by the glow
Make sure you celebrate
And giving my pride
Capitalism
The trout ternative media system
Bereavement
To me it's perfect solution of what Alex Jones is everything in there
Like it has the
Beer like
Car wrecks
You know car wreck
Everytime I go to the store car wrap
8/3 cars
Glittering our street by you can refer lousy with cars
Ridiculous
Then then we've got the Christmas and
It's been taking over it's a Christian holiday taken over by the door
Oh absolutely and then at the same time
Very much
In the
Complete opposite direction
Just go and we should celebrate it the way the globalist have told us to buy box wood from me
Text me because eventually I will take down the Christmas
Right and then all the Whos in Whoville
There's no way he would
Want to take down the globalist
Because then nobody would buy a ship
Right
I don't think he has a place in the world
After the globalist
But that's why
That's why he does the things that he does
We haven't
We picked a real one unfortunately
Brightright we're just trying to get
Through what is real and what is fake about him
That's that's what he did on December 21st 2012
I do respect and admire that at least he wasn't getting into the
Nibiru is right behind the Sun and that's why you can't see it
I respect that
The great that's what a lot of people said
Right behind
It's like why the Earth isn't moving at all it's not going around
I bet it's right behind that's what that's what a lot of arguments were for like why you couldn't see it it's like oh it's being hidden
By the Sun so if you stare up if you have a telescope
And you look up the sun will be too bright for you to see
See the brighten the Blue Roof right they're coming for us
I mean
First of all
David Icke
Is wacky and allowing him
To just like
Through all this s*** around about archons on his
I used to think you're crazy but now
York Rite
That's irresponsible
How many how many of these
Corvus wasn't there
They're outside
But I want to bring this to current day
Because last week
On the Wednesday episode I believe
He had a guy on
Who was pitching September 23rd 2017
Teen Doomsday
Conspiracies
So
He's never he's learned his lesson about Y2K
Is he just going to replay the
The
December 21st
2012 episode
Just like maybe
Riri do that either I'm taking the day off yet
I don't know I meant he's learned the lesson of Y2K which is that can never do that again
People made fun of me
Hard
You can't do that but what he can do
Is giving you no like a everyone wants to
Scared
So let's give him like a little bit of a
Talk about demonic entities possess
Sing the elites
Or something like that makes
I'm at now in 2017 diversion that he's doing his
Alright
I do want to do the Y2K
Free stuff again
I can't do it no good have to let my guests do it
And then make clear that I don't know if I believe them or not right I have to play the fence and let my guest speaker
And that's kind of what he's doing
Even though he's
Still going to at some point
Now you're absolutely right
Well I mean did this September 23rd 2017 thing
11 / 2
I'll tell you after the show replay also of September 23rd
15 they did this back then
And Weaver
Heard Alex talkin about that in our investigation it's the blood moon
Stuff it's not Jewish calendar in Blood Moon
Fox but now it's two years delayed because
I guess
King Herod needed to kill all the two-year-olds
Everybody under 2 years old in the Bible
Or maybe we didn't get the date
Always a little there's always a loophole or we're making setup wasn't built
Until like
480 or whatever the
Or we're making s*** up to get YouTube
Which is more likely
YouTube
No I'm not going to let you do this until
So you do it in a British accent
Boys Show Goes On
People do you think
Think if
We just had a sigh
Psychiatrist
You know like time traveling psychiatrist
Alright
Alright again
Next movie okay great all right
Theme song that would be
Frontier psychiatrist
Therapy
No it's like with David Icke
That moment that he's
Describes is very clearly lie
Like you're talking about the Elmo Mountain without
That's you have abscess
Compulsive
Or Break It was psychotic break
Give you a gotten
Immediately after
All of his many brain damage
I bruised under that house or after
Once he started getting those
Skip
It's a phrenic
Imagine
If you had an anti
Like how
How normal would he be like all of these people my man I don't think I don't think you ever be normal
I'm just
God bless him for it we don't want normal
This is a posture
Okay
But it is
All of these people or f****** go back in time and how many of those religious figures
Is it just like oh well if you had some
Epileptic
We wouldn't have
Like that kind
Well I mean sure but if you didn't
Like shamans didn't take substance
Senses they wouldn't have like cool
Religious
Traditions in Native culture
Instead of just being Kravitz's getting high
That's just on during a blood moon
What happened during every show with bringing force in super male vitality
Transition out of that a****** I don't know I don't know if having
Psychiatrist will help cuz I think it allotted
Does you describe the damage is already done would be incredibly resistant
Any kind of help
Like David lights
That's the point of it is that all of these people also hates
Psychiatrist
Like the Scientologist
Listing all of that if you got
David Icke after he came down from that mountain doing the Christ pose
And you tried to tell him he
He was crazy
Thought you'd be like you're another person telling me I'm crazy and I know that I'm not
Cuz that voice talking to me on the mountain
You told me I'm not
Well that's why you
Just hide in
The bushes
No
The different voices
David
Don't listen to that guy
Pictures of dick
Just pulled up at Mountain voices trolling news
I don't think it would work more with God
I don't think it would work
Tell me what does work is our website
Did you son-of-a-b**** eyes check us out over at knowledge fight.com
Fight on Facebook absolutely Spotify
We're their most
Weekdays at 8 p.m.
I will do some weekend broadcast deza is available with our schedules
Would you definitely appreciate everyone getting on-boarded
Super fun we're going to figure out exactly what we're going to do with releasing these as podcast
And as be broadcast
But I mean it's only been a week we haven't quite figured out what the what would be too much
Tracks proprietary
Thanks for bearing with us while we figure that out
But
The number of our episodes will are available on iTunes
You can check us out there
What danger
Just knocked over
I did that's what it was wrapped up in my mic cord and I
We started making noise I just saw it go down and like
Every time every time
Ruiz Falls
My room gets
Over there
Play iamsu
That's about it I drove for listening text I want to donate
Helps
Oh yeah yeah
John Rappaport thinks that they guy from Batman got murdered
Did you hear that earlier the show
That's the laziest version of this bet we've ever done
Holding
Alex
I'm coloring with huge fan I love your work