Alex
Birthstone colors
Talk a little bit about Alex Jones
Sweetheart f******
So over B
Nowhere in a post literal
B podcast.
None
Do that song no hooks
No it's like that but with bait
Shaquille O'Neal song why would I remember a shack song
With that didn't know what no hook
It was with the Riza
The jizza
Maybe it is surprisingly competent rapper
Zoo
V groove Alex Jones
Kickstart
Code Red
Yes is what we're talking about
That will be
Go to that
The surprising results
The incident
Riptide
On the
The episodes of The Alex Jones Show on
20th and 21st
All right of 2017
There's a lot of wild stuff
The cover
There's a lot of forgot to do it
We get started let's give a shout out to our new donor what's going on out there
Thank you so much for joining up with the team listen up John McCain if you don't f****** get back on board with tending
Bulshit on repealing Obamacare
To give us money
To the show become a policy walk yourself
You can do so by going to knowledge fight., quick
Sports robot
We would appreciate it
You just made me think of
That the terrible way to do that
When I asked
I would have gone with Barry Manilow
I swear to God I will do that whole f****** song
I don't want you to do that
That's all we're going to do various songs by
The point
Never get a passport
Let's get to the point
Daughter about we will never actually deal with Alex Jones
Let's not deal with Alex Jones in this first clip
Let's deal with p****
Incredible
P**** in this next clip
You got a
The spirit in him starting here on September 20th
And
To say whatever
His browser history
View that his thoughts on pornography
Dovetail
Interesting Lee
Into
Florida
That's good right
Previous generation
Logan
They're watching hardcore p***
And they are not hanging out with
Playboy
20 guys
You're stupid
Every study shows it up here on some Puritan horse telling you
That this was all pushed
Legalize
Family
Reproduction
And the ending enjoyment of sex
Everything
Need to classify
Everything is been Declassified at some point because Alex is just making up
Everything
Wild
It's just like
Peanuts that are high in cholesterol
I got it
Was created by Ronald Reagan's who destroyed the black
Classify
It means
Rick Ross got out of prison
This is so f****** stupid
Right on one level in that in that like I think so
There are some people who are into those more extreme thing
Both men and women
And there's nothing wrong with it
Exploring
So I mean there is a there is a legitimate
Concern
Burning out neural Pathways in your brain
And stuff like that
Hey man whatever you want to do go do it I always suspect
Especially with this kind of bulshit Merida
I always suspect that what we're really dealing with
The older generation
Completely incapable of dealing with the speed
But also the speed with which
Culture changes
Yeah from
Something really uptight to something
More permissive
Also I think the older generation
Having a
I wouldn't call it a stiff upper lip
Kind of mentality but it like
You know back in the day people wouldn't even admit that they masturbated
Women masturbating till like
20 minutes
The people do not understand or recognize the history of it
So ever like you know why you can read
Because of poor interesting main reason that you can replace China that's why they created work
Immediately following the Gutenberg Press
There was an underground network of pornography
That would be like
For real in the six
You would have to
Get these books that would be Underground Railroad
Unfortunately
To use that metaphor
Also house so many bibles distributor
Difference
Just been around
I get the people believe that
I think it is
Every technological advancement
Has almost always
Do you support nogra
I don't disagree with the very powerful motivator
Would we have if it weren't for what are we talking about
I'm talking about
They would draw the
Okie dokie
I don't know if you meant the Themis wrapped cookie cookie
I don't know if I have the correct terminology
Take that you're not going to get a correction from
But that was that was the way they advertised it in the way that you drew it was so important
As well so much
Of Art
Tire existed
Is built
Okay so I get it everyone everyone everyone listening gets it
You love p***
Hey we all have our stuff we all have our stuff
This is weird about it
Brightside
That is only the
First thing you super weird about on the 20th
He spends a good hour and a half
After the show or so
A co-host
With our old chiropractor friend
The one doctor group
He comes on
He loves it
He thinks it's very important
I'm just so done with the b*******
Okay
Everybody has to have this hot take on
Corn or whatever I was just saying that recently I've read about
Bunch of them about p*** and how everybody does all of this
It always boils Back Down 2
You don't know anything he definitely haven't learned anything from history
Was that that's fair but I I think and I don't know what you've been reading necessarily so I don't I don't know if I can respond to any
Whenever I was I think that there is something to be looked at
Be cautious of
Combination
Of pornography
High speed in
Because of the ability of Internet
Itself to be habit-forming
And the compulsive
And pornography
Also to be compulsive
The mixture of the two in the same way that online gambling is super
Necessarily
But
Try and save it
Let's let's go wild west
Let's let's face it
Do you like oral sex
F******* probably wouldn't
Lego sets
One of the big reasons that France all the time was
Because they're whores
His little little beads his language
Performed French style
States of America
Pornography who cares
Train re-litigate the history of sexual acts
I'm very angry just the first f****** clip a show tonight
This is so minor
Awareness is not adjusted by anger
You're going to get so much more.
Cuz doctor group group is on the show
Because he got
A package
From a whistleblower
As we know is a chiropractor and holistic medicine
Specialist
Working out of Houston
Danny's working out of the new life Medical Center or whatever
Online bypass
Clients and customers
So you got a package
Someone that
Included
Book that children we're getting in Texas schools
About mental illness
And about going to a psychiatrist
Largely taking some of the stigma and
Fear away from going to a doctor and talking about that
Boy
They take a very different approach to it
Talk about the
Psychiatric care
And I'm not going to be happy about whatever
You're not
You're not but it's
It's worth exploring a little bit
Some of the
Bulshit
And it
You know it's the narrative they want to talk about so we're going to have to talk about it
Here's the first clip where Alex
Doctor
I don't even
Call him dr. group
Add to from now on
Edgar Edward group
So Alex
Egg group
A group CPA
Sentient flies
Andrew I bought my degree
Medication
Is mine
Control
So
Please resist the urge to
Scream about any
I know it's going to be.
All of these medications
Over 780,000 adverse effects have been reported with psychotropic drugs
Put you on multiple other medication
But they also know that you're going to be in the system
There is lot there are laws written that if you have mental illness bacon take you or your kid and you have zero right
Anytime
It also prevents you from having a gun in those cases
Always only
Oh if only
And make you easily controllable
Read some reports now about electromagnetic frequency
Medications with different
Chemtrails
And the EMS stuff
That's Doctor hamamoto crazy elephant
Who's been reading hamamoto that rug really tied the room together
We do it isn't it great like the more we sort of look at these things the more we see like it's all self-reinforcing
Yeah it's all complete lies that are just like OE props up baby props update
And see somewhere in the mix there
Yeah it's actually required even 780,000
Can happen through medication
Bulshit
But he's not taking into account a lot of them are like dry mouth or headache
And stuff like that
And if you were a real doctor
He would understand the nature of side effects
And how it's
Heart
Abusing medicine
Have you learnt
To deal with them or adjust the medication accordingly
I'm on 6
Lamictal
Which is
Theoretically an okay.
It causes
Are you are you parroting Ed okay
Further than him
Can't without being
Just
Get you either
What are you saying I almost believed that
No
Hypothetical
Why the f*** would
That's not how
That's not her Medicaid
So in this next
They talk more about that
Control aspects
Yeah those medication
Try and make
Scared of doctors
.
With something
Kind of like
Kind of
The number one cause
True
And Jenny who is
The nurse that murders baseball
Kind of jocular but it's actually like
It's really funny when you know what I
Want to remind you
What do they do
The next big rollout phases here
It's chilling Rena playing
So doctor group
Before this
He had heard
11 call
How someone calling in
Just killed his chill
I don't know why you would ever want to listen to that
Or play it on the show
I turned it off before they ever played it if they did
Because I would never want to hear that
No I don't
Don't care for
That put them in another
Somnambulism
Situation
Where
Some kind of
Prescribed sleeping
Pink pill
I have no idea
That has happened in the
The past
Sleeping pills and like
Wound up somewhere
Absolutely
Detroit Burger Bar
Is it is a possible
Sing it has happened
For no one let me tell you this
Ad does not go very heavy on the beach
Explain too much
WhatsApp
The situation is
Just for reference with their talk
Totally normal people
Tommy's drug
I looked at Google 33%
Increased risk of death
Drugs
And all of these
Statistics that I could find it match
The 33%
It was about overdose
Yeah babe gone up 30
The opioid crisis
Percent increase
Andover do
I also found some
Studies about
Basically antipsychotics
Greatly reduced
Death rates
And people who are schizophrenic absolutely kept me for
The times of my life 100%
But at the same time every single study because you actually look at it they make very clear
That in no way could you study
What would have happened if someone wasn't
On the drug
So it is
Anytime you're trying to site like
This increases the risk of death
Run treated mental illnesses
Especially ones that have
Schizophrenic tendencies
Has a very high likelihood of you hurting
Turn yourself off
Over what be missed by Alex's rhetoric
Everything
If everything is Alex quotes
What's the study
He is lying a
That is a 100%
That's the result of our study
Psychotic break
Megalomaniac
Because
You go into a subconscious Realm
In between Consciousness and unconsciousness
You go into a dream state
So just real quick it's a coloring book and it's for children and it's
You know it's just animals
It's like
Kimora fires animals
Going to a therapist
It's nothing it's nothing they make it
So creepy
It's so f***** up
But it's nothing really out of the ordinary that you would see
Probably at the doctor's office
It makes sense to have
Exposed to the ideas of
Hey if you feel weird
There might be help
That's what it would have been incredibly helpful
Over
Most of the people I've ever met
Family didn't even
Believe in psychiatry
It did a lot of
Damaged
If Only They had read a children
Help you everything's going to be okay
Gave Chris some medicine
Which medicine
Everyday
And Chris goes to see a special person to play and talk
Most sexual crimes are actually create done with psychiatrist
Because of medication
It is is absolutely
Trying to find bad people
So I think
I think that's one
He is right
Drug reps
Star
Alright like a prostitute
Very hot for the manipulative usually
He was cute doing great and then he was like
It's not like I'm willing to bet that has happened occasionally but that's not the
It's the exception not the rule
Who cares
No
It shouldn't you don't need
That part though
Bad enough already that they are
Using that
To give
People drugs
Maybe they wouldn't otherwise
Because of the drug
Field for a long
Yeah tell you right now
Totally
Most sexual crimes are being done by psychiatrist
There's an article here in the Atlanta
Journal-Constitution
More than 100,000
Documents
Some other records
Across the country to find cases
They may have been involved
Sexual misconduct
With doctors
Doctors as a whole
Yes does include dentist who are creeps
Have they found
More than
2400 incident
Since January 1st 1999
People who are saying
Action for violations
The clearly involved
2400 out of 100,000 is
Small
Percentage of the hundred thousand
And it's also
Credibly small
Percentage of
Wait
That's total
Over that time span a bit I'm sure there are other every there have been other
They didn't look at every single
Complaint spittle
Some sense of
Scale there are how many could have gone
Report
Tun tun
But that's that's going to be fairly difficult
And let me tell you something
Far less likely that it was drunk
Far more likely that it's talks
Probably
But I really want to peel out of this
Is that
Those numbers
Cannot make up a
A majority
Sexual assault
Open Chrome
No doctor group is pulling s*** out of his ass
Here's how this clip in
If they just talked about the the
Drug reps having sex
And I hear your
Are basically prostitutes
No because
Here's why because I don't use real medicine here I'm not a document I can't prescribe
Arabic Alex might have realized you went down the wrong road there like you at Doctor group has no reason
Ora Ora colloidal iodine
You're talking to some guy wants a drilling operation
About some
Looking for Michelle
Next
Composite whenever we need to but it's a little bit there was no way for me
Cut it down at all
Yes because if this makes
Clip they bring out
The coloring book
Alex editorialize is on it
One of the most inappropriate fashion
He is capable
It is gross
For the antipsychotic
It's incredible
And it's on the insert
And it causes psychotic breaks
We've been over this but I just want to reiterate the reason that they have that protect
A vaccine
Companies
Is because of people like
It's because of people who caused a
Anti-vaccination
Tympanic
Monster of the week
It is a hundred percent in order to make sure that
Medical progress continue
Imagine how much
Research would be
Droid how much
If people listen
Dark
It would just be played
Everywhere
Lakeview
All these potential side effects
Text me and you shouldn't take
Medication that could save your life
Right or save other people's lives
If you have a psychotic break
Something like that
There's a Publix
Possibility
How many people died because
Because they go to a holistic
Medicine
Tucker group
Egg group
Add group design
Poop
Is
A direct analog 2
Like if we didn't
People because of
Cancel side effects
You'd have everyone with small
Humanity would be
Dead which at this point
Bring it at this point yeah maybe maybe vaccines are bad maybe we should have called
Anyway
Let's get to this coloring
It's on the inserts
Who's obsessed with the inserts that come with the medication
No no not the insert that you can find
The thin papered one
That comes with the vile at the doctor's office
Basically all the exact same
A prescription has that really long
Paper that
Most people don't ever read
Search
Has all the secret information
The real iPod the reason I wanted to
Positive
In preparation
Episodios
Doing a little bit of
And
It turns out that adult coloring books
Are highly recommended
Psychiatrist psychologist
Apparently
The people just never really paid
What repeat
Let's make our knowledge fight coloring
Let's make a knowledge by caulking
But it makes you feel your family
Takes away the impulse control
You start feeling funny colors
It's wrong balance of medication
Absolutely
Everyday
No one
And the point is you put
Explosive
Chris are you sad
Chris is sad
Prince's mom bring Chris to daycare and then goes to work
Have a good day I'll see you at home
Matt Dillahunty
Daddy
Dr Chris home
So
That the thing that Alex is a
Expressing here
Is
I don't know how exactly I want to phrase this
He's super into personal responsibility in
He's not believing
People are capable of
Because he's assuming that
Doesn't feel good
Take him to the therapist
As opposed to those things being checked off the list
Before you explore that option
But maybe he needs a Snickers
Yeah what he's describing is Munchausen by proxy
Basically
Complete like
Trust in people's ability to live their life
When all he wants is everyone
The way he wants everybody to live their live right so they're doing it
He doesn't want people to have the
Of going to therapy
Pistor psychiatry
Doesn't seem like it matches
Buddy
That's true
He's f****** stew
Mommy
Chris
Call Christopher Ogg
We got distracted
Chris was very
Sometime
Wingover is ice cream does he want the drugs
Why Chris
No
Most of the time is a symptom of
You know
Even the desert
British had trouble sleeping
Mommy and daddy
Chris wasn't playing outside
No
I can't begin to
Describe how much
Because I remember
When I was a kid
I was probably 12 or
Family didn't believe in
In any kind of sign
So
I had
Complete man
Gotten to
Fight with my pay
And what wound up happening
I went back
Scratched out
Like
And they couldn't deal with
So I got
Right I remember I have held
Basically
For three days
They couldn't deal with that so I got punished
What is
What kind of f****** lunatic is like well this just needs
To be beaten out of you what the fuc
What is
Damaged
I didn't even go get help until I was but 432
You need to go outside
Because of this b*******
My life
Would have been
Immeasurably better
Talk about it when I was
The child it's one of the real tragedies
You're expressing it
I can definitely relate to him anyways
When there's stigmatization
Mental health issues
Or in my case
Almost died novelty ization
Mike
I don't know how to describe it
Important
You end up
Wasting
How much time
And you end up like you said 22
Probably around
I'm the same age
Became more Siri
Premier League
Took a little
Realistically when I grew up with a
But I
So much loss
There's so much time there
People who don't
Struggle with
They don't
I'll have
Like they got there
Early
Without
These negative impulses
Is negative
Narratives around Mental Health
You could save a lot of people
Lotto
There's so much
So many bridges that I've burned there
So much that
Could have been
Averted
Had I not
Ifucking in
It wasn't your fault
Choice
Blame
Parents
I blame
Religion that they still f****** believe innovation.
Anyways all religion is a lie
It is it is on one
Have your parents fault but on a much bigger and more important version of it
The ideologies fall
Propaganda is the ideology
The same stuff
He's bordering on Christian
Can scientist
He's bordering on Sovereign citizen
Schitts
Tologist he's all over the place
Do you like a really scary except
He's not done with coloring
And I'm telling you
It gets worse
There's a
Get in the back of the white truck it's alright
Josef Mengele
He said I can help you that's not creepy
Chris some special medicine
Anyting
It's written for children sounds dumb
But in an adult
Especially
You're trying to be
Yeah yeah
Yeah it is
Madison
Jesus
Thank you Mommy
Everyday
Seize the happy colors
Christian growing a lot
Big zits all over his body
Having convulsions last week but now we just put him on extra dress
Mommy likes them and crisco
Special person to play
Looks like a person out of The Shining
Kris Richard
Now they've got the death education
The gadget
Roblox
Okay
There was a there was something that came out about the deputy Pope
Not have had some
Involvement
I don't care
Of course
Until proven otherwise they're all on notice they're all suspects
And I don't know if you'd really
Characterize
The Catholic Church
Let's not murder.
Right you're not quite there he's only cool Pope
Because of
The last one was enough
And all the rest of them have not been much better
So I bet
Such a load of s***
Alex I know he had nothing
Adductor group comes in with his coloring book and he's like
Yeah let's build
Editorialize on this like crazy I don't want to talk about manafort's
No
So also give us this
Paul manafort
Alex's narrative about
Is that
Mueller
His got to him
And he's like
Yeah
But he doesn't have anything
You better start making
Shut up about Trump
Or else
Diesel you
Torture you until your leg
So Alex is not against that
But Alex's version of it is that he is being told he needs to lie about Trump or else
Going to be tortured
Switch
Very reason
Very likely
Look with FBI and intelligence agency
They tortured plenty of people to death
This we went over this on the episode of Drees that had technical difficulties
But the point that I made and I stand by it
Is the Paul manafort would never be torture
He's a multi-millionaire
There's no way
Someone like him with
The connections he has ever going
Touched
Necessarily
Play so
Yeah maybe money is an issue
It is so we have one more clip here from the 20th and it's where I turned it off
It wasn't like a rage turn off right
Tyga Tyga
This is going to get better
This is where I checked
War on corruption and it's Alex Jones Dungy
Infowars 33 per cent increase in death
But see that's when you die
We're going to make money
Sorry
Pizza pedophilia
Want to give you some drugs
Easy Pennywise guy
Alex Jones bad guy with that. The group
Ustad
Arbitrary
Anybody anybody
I want to see how many people John Oliver has helped
I want to see if John Oliver can even get into MIT
I love
Movie complicated relationship between interrupting
I've been feeling bad about interrupting like I love that vacillation but Alex has
Just like
I get it we're just going to do
Evax antimatter
Some stuff
I'll tune in tomorrow
You guys have fun
I know it seems like
I guess I guess it's just that
As much as much as
Awful as he is all the time
This just depresses me because
Home right you know it's so close to me that I can have a distance
As much as I
F****** hate his white nationalist bulshit
At the same time
Raging at that in a niche
Intellectual experience I don't have that physical reaction to it
You might end up buying some internet for him that ends up turning into white
Yeah that's true now there's a possibility
Experience racism from other race
This is on me that's entirely
Seems like nothing's like
Is it because he never got on his meds
Smack to
To Mia's
Someone who recognizes on an emotional level that they're mentally ill
Can't allow themselves to
Understand it
Because of pride
Ego
Particular
What I hear from Alex is so much of like
Maybe he went to a doctor when he was a
Kid or something like that
Take or you wasn't engaged
With the process
Or maybe at some point in his life maybe not even as a kid
He's bitter about it still
Hey that they couldn't fix me they can't
Or something like that
That is also like I've been to three different
Two worksheet
Everyone does
Information I could have been like well
Psychiatry
So I'm out
And I would have gone to Ed group
Susceptible to that to a certain extent
Like I have my periods where I'm just
Yeah and
I might be
Being way too empathic and trying to
Applied Humanity to Alex
It does not exist
I need to go fuc
I'm with you but also a human
I'm so whenever they're believing
Well I genuinely have I stopped believing that
He lost his Humanity card
A while back for me Immortal flesh-and-blood person
You're an animal fine even if you're in a pin put lead Stout
Experience and output I always try and figure out
Why is this
The output
What happened
What would lead one to this
And obviously
With the vaccination
Amstaff
With almost every narrative he has it
He's illiterate
He doesn't know what he's
Misinterpreting things or Hughes
Like allowing propaganda to sway him
Deliberately
Right that's entirely possible
Opens up the other
Section
Of the mystery which is if he's lying
Is he lying what is the motivation because I don't think that somebody necessarily
Just for fun
Would want to lie about vaccine
I mean if you have a lot of money in groups bulshit beans
Advertised all leather medicine doesn't work
That's fair that could be
Commercialism
It could be
We could be and it could be just a broken person who does
Doesn't know how to fix
And super Bale
Is not helping
Sociopathic monster
So now we go onto the 21st
Things get a little weird
21st
September 2017
Because Media Matters
Does come out with an article
Expend
Almost
Tire show
After Alex Rambles about
Pilgrims to the Stars
We just played is almost full
Is it go
We are the information
Authoritarian
Across the globe
So also Alex is really Paul Revere was a s*** there was a woman
Twice as much
Well
Interesting
Is because yesterday cuz he's largely ineffectual and Hillary Clinton
Interview with her came out
She was trying to be a Paul Revere
For issues like cyber
Security
Furious
Cares
We are going to reinstitute the free market
Capitalist
Nation state system
Prosperity
And the Long March
Superstars
Also know how poorly people live
That all
I don't I don't think so I don't think he understands who web Dubois
I want also want to point out the entire intro
Until he gets to the part about drug
He's looking around
Clearly like filling toy
He's like the producer has stepped away from the board or something like that
I don't know
What's going on I have no cues
I was going to talk about going to the store
Glorious
Caremark
To the Stars
Unlocking the secrets of the universe
From the future
Enemies of freedom
Western Civilization
And Christianity
Turn control of our
Freedom is a Russian agent
We couldn't buy Trevor ourselves
We couldn't vote against
Is George Soros a Nazi collaborator
America
With Russian propaganda
I guess he infected with the New York Times The Washington Post and seen any links to everything but there it is
And they track Warehouse
Just like
Links to the media
So
They did
Is there
A lot of billing
The course of
And they found that there was a
Jump
Hindilinks to Russian
State-owned media sources
In 20s
It's a jump
From
This about 80
To 100
In 2016
And that's up from about 35-40
A 2014
Those are massive jump
They're all state-owned media sources
It's not that
Talks about like the next
Good news and stuff like that run operation
Could just be
A Mexican news source
One of the reasons why this is particularly
But interesting as
Study
The only thing that Alex says
There's like
He likes to the New York Times
Which means he hasn't read the article
The article isn't just that he licked
Do all this
Stop
It's more important
That they found
That he
Here I'll just read this quote
Judge is also regularly turn to RT and spotting
Nick Ferrone skeptical coverage of State
And other Kremlin officials
Including their denials of Russian election
Interference their criticisms
The US role in Syria and their efforts to undermine NATO member
And he's frequently highlighted the Russian Outlets favorite conspiracy theories
Hysterics
Including their reports on meetings of the mysterious Bilderberg Group
Debunked claims
Google manipulate its search results to favor
And warnings
Increase Western
Support
George's affinity for Russian President Vladimir Putin
Chinese propaganda Outlets
Drug has a rare power is
The media GateKeeper
Unusual ability to push reporting
From previously unknown Outlet
Do a mass evolve
So
Since is like all of these
To what they're talking about
And what it's really about
Is not that he made live
It's that he supported the Russian propaganda narrative
Various
So you had like
One really good
Specifically had near was
The Malaysian plane
They talked about they talk about the
The shooting shooting of the Malaysia
Asian playing
So here we go
On July 17th 2014 Malaysia Airlines flight mh17
He was shot down over
Eastern Ukraine killing 298 passengers
Cousin crew
The next day President Barack Obama
The responsible parties
Rushing back
Separatist
Seizing territory at 3
Region followed Rush
Annexation of Crimea
Obama statement game
I made a serious effort
By Russian president propaganda Outlets
Confusion about the app
And they're telling
Actually been a failed attempt
Shoot-down President Vladimir
The Russian propaganda effort
Received a substantial
Boost
Drudge
The story on the topic from
The website of the Russian
Read back to English language
Drudge titled the resulting is highly trafficked
Aggregation
Website quotes
RT
Play might have been Target
In bright red.
So
The thing that so not only is he
Going up as
A huge signal booster
Like in on the Drudge Report which I do my best never to visit
There's always the big giant
And then there's all those tons of little tiny
It's it's touch
It's such
Bulshit
Even caricature characterized
As
He's just a link
Depends really influence
How
The links links
People
Perception
As they
Engaged
Cuz idiots only read headline
But at the same time I completely support his ability to do that I think that is still within free speech
I think he's a craven horrible propaganda I don't think be allowed to do
Veteran support Isabella
To do that I I supported in as much as I support things that are just
It's one awful I just wish that we had a
A conversation in place that was much more realistic and much
More
Think that they are
Capable of thinking
For themselves
Basically
Bigger issue is the article is not about
How many links
He put up or any of that
It is about the narrative
It's about how he falls in line with the
Trickle-down effect
Throughout
Alex Jones
Breitbart
All of them take massive
Cues from Breitbart
Dusky is the
Purveyor
The bottleneck
We're Russian propaganda
Ends up getting funnel to mainstay
Yeah that's what the article is about
And it's very
It is
It is something that
People need
Whether or not it's
Actually
Collusion
I'm not saying that
You have to go far outside of America
To get your dumbass
Because they are Pat
Right
Have to have to link to art
Because reality disagrees with him and Artie love pedaling up
Shiftboard
Well their version of reality
Alexander Russia has its own version
Because there is no objective reality we have our own
Some good I've been thinking about a lot I've been I've been dwelling on foreign policy
Has become incredibly clear to me
How wildly
Complicated every
Like you think about how Russia's Russia
China supports North
Are you think about it most people if they were hard-pressed
Say why
Both both communist countries
My big brother little brother kind of thing
Could be by their support it keeps North Korea from
Even crazy well that's one possibility another possibility is that
North Korea
Be
Like if they were
China Wok
This is this is one possibility
China supports North Korea
North Korea wants
Reuna fortified Korea
Reunified
US military presence
Good weekend
Japan
Status in the Asian
Yeah so there could be an entire thing going on where there's a domino effect
Of China wanting to weaken Japan
And get America out of there
Supporting North Korea
What I'm getting at is
All these things are possible and likely influences on
And there's a simplistic version
Incredibly impossible
To break down
Real
It's like if you go to if you go to work
Studio and you
And how huge it is but and having thousands and how it's like oh well this knob changes something
And then you have to
2nd
Over there
There's so many interlocking
If you look at my board I've got way more affection I know how to ghost
There's all kinds of different things that
Can be adjusted
A tiny little bit so it's hard it's hard to
Find some sort of Harmony there
Continuing with my metaphor
Inexplicably
Vet
With without
Breaking something
Right right
Pushing too far on one thing is going to
Lose control or another
Adidas
Nationalism
Stupid that I'm getting at is when you look at like this
Situation with Russia
Mike
1818 saying for anyone to think that they don't want to reunify
Soviet Union
It's absurd tonight
It it just
Bromley geopolitical 7.8
If
There is a narrative that involves
Doing
Like what's a Annex
Part of
A farmhouse
They stole that
Is Russia an ally has intellectual property to the butterfly surprise
Explanation of like
Sympathetic explanation they are trying to
Encroaching build back up a little bit
When you have those two possibilities in front of you
You are incredibly irrational if you don't think the latter is
Just think about it man
What's lost the Cold War
Or
Something like that
Like I don't even know
Mr.lee how we would have
Except for nuclear war
Let's say the entire scenario was completely different and we end up losing
Alternate reality Cold War where we lose the Western
Like the entire West Coast
Is gone
Over the course of the neck
Next fifty years or so we
Become
Slightly more part of the global
Community but at the same time we're a bit of a hostile actor
I like mine
Hannah we keep taking a little bit of Montana
Like why would anyone think that we would want to reunify the United States
Every single country
Every single country that
Like is a
Power that is split ends up wanting to reunify
What's the equipment
Because of the narrative because of the narrative
That has arisen about
F****** the dumbest f***
Reagan
Solving the Cold War
Yeah people forget is the main reason that we
We won the Cold War
Is cooperation
Bright
Did not do that
Because they were obsessed
With nationalism
It was a Triumph of global Co-op
Global cooperation
Over Nashville
Elizabeth
Has become
It was a Triumph of nationalism right for another it was Reagan making a harsh demands
Absolutely
The only way you're ever going to solve those
So what's the problem
And any of these
Incredibly complicated foreign-policy problem
Is pretty much
Getting
Large
Coalition
Things together to work
Concert
What are the main reasons that we have the allies
Is because of our
Support for the
Another attack
Without our support following
World War II
Germany would absolutely be a
Shell
Germany
The Soviet Union
The same with Japan
Like the way that we won those
Was
Are the way that we won those words
Beyond
The end of the
Was we learned the lesson from
World War
The Treaty of the site was so cute
German
Of course they were going to start another
And of course
Because all of the people who learned that lesson
We have to learn it all over it
Just like you and I were talking about we are likely to see another new another new
Because people don't remember
How monsters
But it seems like the likelihood
I don't want to feed into that and
You know cuz I think that a lot of people
We hear that
Get scared or take it the wrong way
I think they will probably as close as we've ever been in our lifetime
Who knows
But I still think that a lot of
A lot of it has
Facility pasta
Chaotic actors there is the possibility that posturing
Leeds
EXO
Just died
And we didn't find out about it until last week or we talked about the guy from the Soviet Union.
Who stopped
He
You got an alert that American Rockets were coming in
Suspected it was
False alarm
And because of that
They would have launched at least four examples of that
We'll just going like
Maybe this isn't real
And if you're North
Korea
The likelihood of that
With an a
Hayirli brainwashed
Civilization
Seems far less everyone is
Is brought up to
Expect that
Be there in
Let's get through this
Cuz you got to show tonight
Conversation about foreign policy
Let's get in
To this next clip where Alex talks a little bit about
Usually does
Yeah man has an interesting
Theory about a
Fairly recently dead prominent
Use the word sovereign
As a racist dog whistle
They said it was over
Pre-market
Capitalism
I don't think
I mean
There was there was a lot of Flowery rhetoric in it and whoever wrote it did a
Diesel job except for it
Thirty-odd
Pictures of sovereignty
Not a friendly loving
Which one you're like we might have to completely destroy your country
Good
Threatened
To demolish
A country
Civilian
On on f****** real it's like the stuff about sovereignty that you can support you really have to wait
That against the other stuff
Can you use of sovereignty
All of this
It all the code words
Doesn't
Pre-market
You don't know
Pizza Factory
Hippie
Threatening
When behind-the-scenes their psycho
He's saying that they hit him with
Weaponized
Cancer and took him out
Once you allow any kind of death to be murdered
Cancer because he was taking what might as well have been
Egg groups
It might have been
Oh yeah
Super male Vitality does not cure cancer is the lesson of Steve
But I don't I don't think
Steve Jobs
Should have iPads
Very opposite of that I do recall I haven't really looked at
Into the studio
Alex is old version of it
Was it Steve Jobs dead
Kids kids
Want them to have it at a young age
For whatever reason
Said they were bad and that's why they killed him
Benz E-class
Bulshit has more thoughts about the Russia
Speech
The UN
Awesome things
About Russia
Big bloated corrupt
Free Speech anti
Christian
Trump's bad
And what is their sovereign
And their question
Penny pulled away from the clutches of the globalist
Bolshevik party
Same ol sick Revolution 100 years later
Car rage
Puppies
Absolutely
Soldiers
Infowar against America
It just means he was talking about
Really undermined
Barry Weiss today
Shut off your poisonous
Appendages
Isn't that great
Undertale
Jesus Christ
Lot of stuff is 50% off right now and Restore store
Totally
Probably be
Free summer of Rage sale
That's a wild bull
But also that he's still peddling that narrative
That Russia is great
I mean he's just coming out with
Same-store
Episode
Where are you
Doing that whole story about dried
Fuckingawesome
He's actually be more likely to say
Like if you didn't
Have to if you want to know
If it was like
Look at how look at how many articles look at how great
The Drudge linked
These article I would also argue that is Alex
In his heart of hearts
Suspect
Something really f***** up was going on
You was a part of it
You just be like oh course I like Russia
Yeah your self
He knows that something is pretty f***** up
Until we get to the
I don't care
My information
Russia get some information from me
Upholstery shop
How did it go
What's up
Like if they already know everything he says
Spray from here
This is
End of the military love me
They tune in cuz they already know the stuff I say and I'm the only person who said it
So they can hear me repeat what's true
But Alex doesn't have the news
D-does pro-russian narratives
People
Russia would like
But this is an important distinction that we need to make
Because whenever we talk about Russia
Just stop
We always try and be careful
You know Express babe
The Russian people are great and they're fine
If the people in charge who are
Homophobic
Proportion of the Russian people are just good people trying to get by
Suppressor
Even the ones were brainwashed we feel liniment to pity for people
Talking about Russia is talking about the oligarchy government
The Russia
And that is f***** up
Here's the rest of
I'm going to screw it back up
Are there we go
They just already know what I'm saying is true
Causes basically
Affirmation
You kept exploded
Why does your associate lose weight
So that
White nationalist organization
We got our whole group of weirdos involved with them yeah
But the other thing that I experience there is
These success
Influence
These people
Like Alexander Dugan
And whoever Alex's talk to behind this
Pivot Point
Flattery
In order to make him think that he is super important and he's
Change
Yeah he's just spitting back things
They are using
To manipulate him
Into being
Super accommodating of their narrative
And maybe drudge said the same thing happened to him
It's impossible
It's possible that behind the scenes
That might happen there too
Yeah
Part is
Especially when we're talking about any
Collusion
It may just be the interest don't dump
I want the Americana.
But
Russia
Right
What's National
Bright
So ideologically
Despite the fact that Russia is a hostel
Ideologically they line up Alex Jones and drudge don't understand
Is that they are also hostile actors
There McDonald's specials
Way worse
Because they think that they're making it better
Stupid and their Hustle actors towards
A Cooperative global
Leucine
Bike
Genuinely they just
Right
Quite literally
Explicit piece of the nationalism
They would speak
For the rest of the world
Would be Russia take back the Soviet Union
Obviously not.
If you get a mouse a cookie
Big laska no probably going to Canada looks pretty cool
I may be a Russian Canada
Hilarious
To be wild very polite
Understand that I'm
Speaking in like a wild hypothetical and
Canada back
We're so sorry
A taken Monte
Tenerife
Irish
A little bit
Trouble Baez
I have solidarity
That's weird
Alex gets onto another narrative
Cuz he wants to make a little bit of
From Oliver
Play again
Letting
He's not mad about the
He doesn't play a clip of the stuff about the senator
Jimmy Kimmel
He plays a clip of Jimmy
Getting mad at a Fox News person
For critiquing him
Bringing his child into
Discourse
Step
Hillary's
The reason I'm talking about this
Crepe
Losing his kid
Casella program
Brian Kilmeade is a phony Little Creek
So two things
1 oz of butter
Responsible
Alex's song
Has done
Infowars.com
His his narrative out there his other children
At the time
Have appeared in a gorilla suit in a sketch mocking
Trans people
On the Alex Jones Show
You're full of s***
Don't bring your kids into
F*** you
Now do you think
You can take that clip
About Brian Kilmeade
And I
Turn it to
Be about him
I think so
Ivan
I've been in major Hollywood film
Everything
So easy goes into a long random drunk late
My phone calls
Check caller ID probably coming from Trump
Room at Mar-A-Lago
The other thing now is that from there into a long rant about how like
What I want to be is the image of John Wayne
I want to watch Battlestar in these westerns and spy thrillers
Starring role
I don't want to do that what I like to do is I like
2 goliyan
Bee Movie
Intex it
It's fun for me
The only things on his f****** resume are the two linklater movies in amerigeddon so
I don't know what he's talking about if you wants to call amerigeddon Tubi movie
Agree
I would not call
Abbey movie has Bruce Campbell
Fair enough has Alex Jones
Or
Not at Movie House hours
For quite a while so cut up
Haha and we get to this
Why are you still talking about turning down offers
How to get really f****** creepy
No complaints that you have but Jimmy using
Kids
I think they should be outweighed by how bad this is
Frog
Your grandpa with a brain tumor
Your failure
You're a black
At this point
Kind of like that like
Either outraged or he's orgasmic it what he's about to say
And I think it's the latter
Want to hear what he's about
You will fall
Did you
Tap water
Why don't you find out why this is happening
Socialism
Global control
Veronica
Yeah that's
You're the dumbest
Person in the world
He doesn't
If you don't understand logic
He doesn't understand that like
Which I was complaining about I am now doing the worst
Version of
It's crazy it's okay
Yeah I'm using your kid
To fight against
Compassion
Right cuz I hate
And to pitch my
Wild
I think I also threatened
Violence
You're not mad that Jimmy was threatening
It's when our old friend Larry next song
He
Shows up on the show and it's just a repeat of he's already said it's really boring interview
Until we get
And Larry Nichols said something on the air
That I think is illegal
I think this is illegal
I'm not sure I'm not a lawyer
But I'm pretty sure
This is at very least
A threat
And we can discuss it on the other end but
I'm not comfortable with this being legal
Okay
They are all locked
Republicans in Congress
Information
Christian
Received
National
Nobody
So we'll get back
He's not dumb
Greatwood great would be if Larry Nichols
Wind-up taking down the Republican Party
F****** hilarious would that be
The legal definition of blackmail
Is an act of criminal involving unjustified
Threats to make a gain most commonly money or property
Or cause a loss
To another
Unless Adam and
That's literally blackmail
Literally is trying to Blackmail Congress
I think he should suffer some consequences for this even though it's idle threat
Kill people for Bill and Hillary
Radio show
About everything
Cuz he was f****** involved in the Iran-Contra and got caught making long distance
Call Tim Nicaragua
You repackage
Cancer having
Manipulative a******
Great
Turn your attention towards the Republicans
God bless you
Charade where I don't really care
You're going after these people that like
Okay you bring down Paul Ryan
I mean you're not going to but trying to bring out Paul Ryan
Too funny
Please
So hold on good the rest of the Clippers going to play out Alex's
Scream bathroom stuff and Larry's going to make another
20 letters
Hammer Hammer election
Just like a jury can become a judge or whatever
Wait you're making weird faces I want to
Is it a Larry Nichols hotline
What is it if you or someone in your house
Is suffering from some
Press 1 for yes
I'm going to guess I was in a different acronyms number is 1 800
2455 26
55-27
And see exactly what just happened on 900 Mix-a-Lot
Obviously
He just threat he was blackmailed Mueller
That might constitute obstruction of justice
I mean I know.
You have some sort of
Mysterious information if you don't do what I say I'm going to release
I mean in all honesty
If you didn't have to go to your show
You should call him
I love that like
Larry Nichols
For all his faults
Is a f****** Showman
Gino's
We're having a boy
I got to do something
What are legitimately feel like we should send that to the FBI
We're going to call Larry Nichols and we're going to ask
Weather and I have
Actual
Wouldn't do what I say
I kind of want to I kind of want to call him
Maybe I kind of want to do it anyways
We tell him he's on the air
What the f***
The special prosecutor
Yeah probably
Cliffhanger promised Cliffhanger see what happens with that over the weekend
But also after that I told you this before the show
Giovanni you like
I don't want to have to do it
But we're going to burn some
Stillgoode
So good such a great development in the Larry Nichols art
Absolutely I hope he doesn't die before the end of the season
I want the season to play out you don't have to be a thing where like the show gets canceled mid-season
Although you know what
They're going to drop
Of course
Buckley is probably going to talk to Alex
Be like
Dude
I talked to her lawyer
And they said don't do that
You have to say politically when you threatened
You can't have Larry Nichols committed crimes on Bonaire
I know you didn't say it
They have no problem with it is there just like
Oh yeah let's Nichols Alex
I think it's a good idea to make the same pledge
I think because you're broadcast
A crime
I think that she may have some cup ability right
Complicit
So anyway I'll research the legal standard of getting someone in trouble
I figure that out
You can check us out
Knowledge feit.com actually
Blog
You cannot find that on our website we have a stuff to enjoy header at the top of the site
Drop down menu boom posting something every Thursday and then maybe more depending
You can also follow us on Twitter that knowledge
Underscore
Nothing right
With the livestream
GameStop we will be getting back to that
My internet
Is so crappy because
Because the router is all the way across the house
Yeah the range extender sucks
I'm trying to find the chords
To fix everything else
Consistent
Product
I don't want to be putting this half-assed out there right now
Like the other night we recorded one in the internet went out halfway through and
Complete disaster
So deflating
Do you know what that was
That was the spiritual equivalent
Also by the way John Rappaport was on on Thursday on the 21st
That weirdo
He made this really f****** stupid claim
How many
I can't even do it
Toothless voice
How many prescriptions do you think doctors
Prescribed
A year
If United
Hello that's hello it's about 4 billion according
To John Rappaport
And what
Is that's not surprising
At all
Yeah now that's on
When I have that cyst in my jaw area
I ended up getting
Five prescriptions for that maybe
Yeah it would be good at with anyone who's pregnant multiple prescriptions real source of vitamin
All sorts of prenatal postnatal care
Anytime anyone gets strep throat mono any of those things
Multiple prescription anytime someone gets
Hurt or undergo surgery they get painkiller prescription
I need it so f******
4 billion prescriptions
Makes total sense
What would you like to say to you and your misuse of statistics
Dumb
Muppet looking piece of s***.
Alex
First in color