Alexandra Thurston color
We are a couple dudes like to sit around drink novelty Beverages and talk a little bit about Alex
We start and stop
And sartan
Time for everyone know who's listening
We are encountering an ink
Credible technical difficulties
We're really more.
You
That will resolve things
We will be good to go
Podcast form
So alive on the internet
You're probably thinking
Who does
The amazing thing about the show
We do give credit where
Sure is,
Midsection has a
Incredible screaming
You got to give him credit for that
We always we always go to the info Warriors
To figure out why we're why we're having
Absolutely
Yep so anyway let's go
And racism
Indeed
Going over the episode from
September 22nd
Is Friday
We'll be going over there
The experience
Sing all the wonderment
And the bizarre nonsensical
Bulshit
But Alex has a lot of narratives that are stupid
Did a lot of behaviors that are stupid
And we will talk about it all but first
Here is
Out of context
Discussing the NFL protest
That are imminent
This weekend here on Sunday
Some of them happen
I already put out a video on
Preemptively
Making a prediction that might be a little over block
News
President-trump
Field
This could save the country
Little bit grandiose perhaps
Hey I think I think
I think that the president calling for people who are
Making peaceful demonstrations
Be fired from their job
Maybe the other directions
I don't see how
Okay okay North Korea has
Wonder Man
Otherwise they're going to Nuke the
Fire the black people prosport
That's all they wanted
Yeah Lottery situation
Get the situation like finally I can take up that at take out that San Francisco
Quarterback Kaepernick
Just making that up there's no reason for any of that it's all stupid we live
On the f****** world
Is tweeting about a f******
Football player Rico doesn't exist anymore
Puerto Rico
A guy kneel during the national anthem
Break
Great we're great I want to bring up because one of his favorite narratives is a globalist
I'm trying to like kill the birth rate
What have you
Through I don't know brainwashing and putting
Give you on psychotropic medication
Like to link here I'm going to go to the research game
Here is a study that was just recently done about Flint Michigan
And oh my God the fertility rate
Among people
Since the lead
Situation
There is a
Massive
Strand from
Right around the time in the 2014
Serious serious drop
Look at this graph states that it's utter insanity
As a point outside
But make sure that you know that we added another 80 billion
UA
Billion dollar man
We can't
We can't afford to take care of Flint's f****** water but goddamnit we need another
Dumpling also if you're watching this live I do feel a little bit self-conscious
Because when I flashed that up on the screen the article from the Washington
There is an ad
For the Infowars store on there
You go to if you ever go to their website it will be on
Every single page you go to for the rest of your f****** life
Globalists trying to kill birth rates
Hey a little bit of a tent
The Flint
You never talk about it
Think about
As far as
Situation report
Like
Flint Michigan
No real water
Yam
And Puerto Rico
Has now
6 million people without water
At all
So think about how soon we're going to get on top
Probably never
Probably never f******
I just I had that over the weekend which is like
When
Puerto Ricans come to the mainland
Idiot GOP people are going to be like these refugees coming in with and it's like no
They're part of our
F****** c***
Is America
Dick we are more American than you are
Yeah I don't know when we're ever going to get
Addressing
But I do know that now is the time that we get
Get to be Friday
He's in a weird mood on this day
He doesn't reveal that possibly one of his cats died the night before
He's not these
You did say after he called shift
An archetypical c********* threatened
To beat him up he did say the next days are my dog
Relationship with
I don't think it justifies some
The stuff that we're going to be
He kills an animal ever
Blood sacrifice
Restart the show off complaining about
Ends up
Excuse me
Paul Joseph Watson
Complains about some
Nothing else
Friday
Hard to believe it's already
22nd day
Of September 2017
Incredibly bizarre world
Agree about this
North Korea threat
Cast
Hydrogen bomb Bud ground
On an unnamed
Pacific Islands
Is a real Hallmark World War
The underlying cause of his people
That's fair
It's the same thing from China
The Russia to the United States
It's the same thing
Showering
It's the same thing powering the Vatican
Towering much of the CIA
It is a bunch of weeks come
Play God trying to run our lives
With relish
With extreme enjoyment
Rapture Delight
All over Europe
Protestant and Catholic and Orthodox churches
Government
They take something
Muslims in them
Islamic Art displays in children
Muslim churches
How dare they
That is
Churches that have been converted
To Islamic
Did he didn't give any specific
No specific number
So
Magical fever dream of other government
Taking away tax
Exempt status
From churches by the way that's not in other
It's no like we have that
They do not
It's f****** stupid
Real issues with our past
Absolutely
So they're doing that they're taking away their nonexistent
Tax exempt
They're getting rid of the Christians inside housing Muslims
Then they're having
Arches
That is problem is they're having Arch Arch
Yeah but also he has kids about Christian stuff
And I would argue that's probably most every
Single
School days
Yeah
Yeah I would I would I would say
I don't know I mean
I'm never running low on my Chris
I get I get his argument that it's like well if it's all multiculturalism
And my rebuttal to that which might be overly simplistic is it's because you already have all the rest
The time is acquainting you
With Christian why isn't there a White History Month
If it's not you
Mostly the same argument but also to your question about
If he ever is going to give spa
Pacific
Tell you to put a pin in that
Because it is sort of an in
Introduction to a narrative
He's going to get to
A little bit down the line
So we're going to
Hold off on that for a second I get to this next clip
Where Alex Jones
Admits that he doesn't know what he's about to cover everything is just winging it and the producer
Please prepare everything for him
As the cruel Prince
Basically all the front page article of more than
Most of those when I come in and some through it I've already looked at it
Piles of it
So he's saying that the producers just print out articles
Page
Higher
Staff
Print out headlines and then they're like
Job.
Sometimes he's found them before
Which is a cursory reading
But
He's saying that that's only some of the time some of the time he doesn't even know anything
I love the way he puts it to like
Magic
Rob do works in mysterious ways
Satanists
Absolutely every time he doesn't get it
Absolutely 100% of the work of the devil
Came back much quicker
Then I then we thought here it is
Churches all over Europe
Islamic Center
Government-funded
Tell them it's good
Just like the police keep last week's the major city in Finland
Ted going to school
Bangla London
Refugees that came in the last two years
So this is
Finland we talked about that accidentally said it was
Is the sequel to little rascal
It might as well be at this point we learned a lot
Multiculturalism
Look this is a situation where someone tweeted at a Finnish
Police chief
And daddy said fortunately the adult Isis terrorist put in
To school with children did not carry out according to
A tacit School
Someone else
Replied
I am certainly not the only one with something done to that other 20V
Need to get him out of school
I'm guessing that's another immigrant who's 20 years old
Replied on the contrary people need to be motivated
To stay in school on the bench
Whenever whether it's a child or adult
So it's other person response
I mean what
As a police officer you support terrorists being in our children schools
Voicemail response
Even a terrorist can benefit from good learning
It might
Tolerance
I'm a guy respond
You don't think it'll poses
Security risk to children
Anacapa
Respond our schools are safe
The guarantees
Professional teacher
BrandsMart stew
These aren't terrorists
Until they've committed
Terrorist attack
That's the underlying thing
The member of Isis
It was just it was just a guy
Another person who committed like a knife attack elsewhere was a student at a school
I didn't know that
He was a member of Isis or whatever until you know that all came out
Montreal immigrants as if they are Terror
Selfie
Mentality
Also when it's all
The only place I could even find anyone making a stink about this was infowars.com
And they had a link
To a WordPress
Site Daily Independent
Individual operation called the tundra tabloids
Alright I am going to start reading
Cuz I'm reading over the
B-side bar
B i n
Independently-run is best
Reading the sidebar here
And I can't even flash this up here on screen
We have this year
Multiculturalism is a gross failure
Assimilation we're celebrating the ones own Heritage but as a full member of the dominant
Culture wins
That's a troubling sort of mentality I
Anyways so at least ethos that's that doesn't appeal to me
White
You can have your f****** dumb religion right but as long as you know that the are Christian Nation is
Bream to it
You're cool
Let's or what that that mean
That's not great
Was there like
Patient zero for this
B*******
Like
Was it
What does it all mean
The caves where
People just walked out in their life
Holyshit
Was that problem
From the
You got it was
Okay
Use with the apostrophe s on the
Kickstart is 5% Tuesday
Even in those caveman
Heterogeneous
Population
Living in tribal
Right and so they already built up cultures within themselves
Before they ever would have
Encountered
People of different colors and
So I probably
Probably would have liked your built-in tribal
Mentality before you encounter
Yeah but probably some updates back that far
System of white supremacy
Bonkers to me
Everywhere
Subtle shapes
Conforms to
It's
The big problem
Yeah if you were white supremacy
Yeah but
Just go away
Build a spaceship hate everybody
Just get away from us
You think the whites
Supremacy is a problem
I guess you would say that to me as well
But
He wants to tell you
Differ
Parties that are all teaming up because of one thing
They all enjoy
And they're the real
Cowboy
To the globalist to the pedophile armies
Because it's right there in the
It's right there that you can
But if you're an adult
Love that pedophile
Satanist
That's all it is
Nuclear weapons
North Korea
It's Titanic
Did we give them
No he believes that the clintons did all that
That we're all rubbing
His face
With
Pedophile
Celebrating
Misrepresented
Like now
Maybe think about global is Publications to the ones he always brings up our
Like the
I'm certain if you go to their website they're not going to
To have like a video of a five-year-old dancing with the headline we want to f*** this girl
Did you not see Ally McBeal
The dancing baby man there was not a sexualized a baby sir size must
Kelly has a lot of problem this is not one of them
I don't believe
Have you talked to him
Let's get on the phone
What's not doing right now
Alex has started the show with some pretty responsible talk
But also this narrative
About
People taking over
Churches
The Muslims taking over
Yeah where does that come
Well I don't know no cuz there's videos of players like out of the Philippines
Games where people are like
Tearing down houses and stuff like that
Screen brightness right if you are if you want to president is and active
Murderer
A serial killer
Who is still killing
Yep
Alarm
Is
Amazing
America elected Andrew Jackson
More or less
Did in fact
Have
Killer
Yeah someone what's worse cuz it's 2017
It feels like it's work
I don't know
Like even though as you just pointed out those contacts
Philippines
But
It seems to me that this what does next clip we're going to play
Kind of what
Actually talking about
And then he's loved in Muslims because he has that video out of Philippine
Wild wild stuff
Cam
This is liberal
Lab Rats video
He should let in the Muslim merge with it
Rosa people
The way you dress up for
Eyes Wide Shut
You know what they do Parliament
Ottawa
To carry out Satanic rituals
And so now they're altimate fun is to do it charge but now
But now
Shelf
Satanism
The only thing better is to
To kill a child
Everything else
Gods
Temple to bring demons
So so there's an Illuminati fashion show that's happening
Church
It's just this thing either give you ever gone to like the vigilant citizen.com
It's a website
Horse it's a website where the f*** are you talk
There's this whole Trend people believe that the Illuminati is coming out in public now
Whenever you see stars putting one hand over their eye if a message
Is there a part of the Illuminati
And if you see an eye of Horus anywhere than the Raptors
The thing is
I think a lot of people in pop culture assertive realized
They're triggering crazy
People to write Free Press about them
I've song Whatever you have stars that are doing me like Illuminati themed music videos
Virus videos at imagery and stuff going to be a flutter with
This is demonic and that just get
It's them
Further out into a population they didn't have access to before
Because these are adult weirdos
They're not necessarily going to be listening to Miley Cyrus
But now they're going to watch the video
If you even if you're calling for a boycott or something it's basically Free Press
No publicity is bad for
So how can you be so stupid as to not see through
Alex is b*******
They're dressing the way they would to go to a safety
Titanic
Just like Eyes Wide Shut
Right so excuse me are you saying that Eyes Wide Shut
The documentary
Like and does make
Kubrick Kubrick's daughter
He's like
He has to go
You think I mean maybe during Buckley's birthday party
Research cam here
Stop they bring
So
Spell stare
Figure out where Alex
My review of orgies
Nevermind
So I can figure out where The Narrative of like the Ottawa Parliament Canada is demonic
Cam
Starbucks
Is the smartest
Come on
Brillia
I have Unstoppable it's terrible
Word 112
The only number of words he knows episode
Power running Canadian Parliament
Yes that's the article here and it's a first-person report about being under siege
When you worked
Happy Canadian
Okay I read through it it's nonsense I don't need to read all of this to you
But I want to give you a little bit of a flavor of some of his tweets
Dickensian the sidebar here
Culture war is the ongoing Masonic Jewish subversion
Christian
European civilization
Oh boy oh boy oh boy
A picture of Angela Merkel as a as a new Hitler
A gyro
The guy who started
Going after the New York
Price
Any just went through a whole long
Number of
Is it all he did was
Nash
Modet on
Oh yeah it's
So sorry to interrupt
Which
Speech bubbles
She saying I wish you had balls
Anything I wish you had a penis
These are some of the tweets
Henry Makow
Anti-Semitism equals resistance to Masonic Jewish supremacism
That's true okay okay
What he's up to also I mean like
Like I said if you want to go read this
First-person account of occultism at the Ottawa
Bulshit
Johnson
Anti-seize
Yes
That's what he say
He's basically attack
A label you get to painted with
When you stand up against Jewish
What is real to them
It's
Also
Can we just
It's tough to it's tough to implement anything that would get rid of
Alright alright now
Here's the thing
Genocide get the bad rap
I'm not I'm not engaging with no
But I was trying to find other
Reno arguments
Instances of things
You know validate Alex Jones is
Is concern that the Canadian Parliament
Specifically satanic
And what have you
This thing called the rhinoceros party
Play Frank
I'm voting for a rhinoceros
1863 to 1993
They were parody Party trying to just have fun
They ended up getting one
1% of the vote
Cuckoo crazy
But this guy named Brian Godzilla salmi
In 2001 tri-tip
He gained his nickname because he wore a Godzilla suit while campaigning excellent
Tucson
Cham SAE space
Against the federal government a 2000
The election rules that led to the dispensing of the Rhinoceros
50 million dollars in comp
Temptation
As his name was now legally safety
The lawsuit was filed under the name state
Versus Her Majesty the queen
There are heroes still after this world so they're here are some of the campaigns with the rhinoceros party tried to embark
They tried to repeal
English and illiteracy is
Canada's three official languages
They're just f****** trolls babe
Tear down the Rocky Mountains to Alberton
Wikipedia Pacific sunset oh that would be nice
Yeah banning guns and butter
Kill people
Estrella Banning lousy Canadian Winters
I don't know dating a free rhinoceros to every aspiring artistic Canada
That
Is a terrible idea that is the work of seitan
So I don't know I think we could just ignore the Illuminati fashion show
Aspect of it I was much more interested in the idea that Canada
Parliament was specifically for Satanic rituals
I think it's just cuz they have a red carpet
If you look at the pictures like others read there
Anyway
Alex Jones gets really salacious
Is really terrible
Well you're not
At least people believe in Satan
Call Ron
This coming out the former prime ministers and others
Routine basis that Little Orphan girls brought into their offices
Floor
And I slipped those little girls throat's a little boys bro
Touch the body they just
Pleasure themselves while the child flops around
Water
Gasping for air
So you just remember that you remember that
Real good
What you're signing on to ride
His base that's just using a disgust
Cigarette oregano
Hey you got to be on my team
Because the other team is like that
I mean it's right in line with his normal behavior quite frankly
If they get Little Orphan
Right which they have to
To be orphans now
Like it used to be
People would donate them
Another stealing
Brave
And then they slit their throats
Don't even touch
The body which is
A weird sentence
Episode make fun of the body's to have that you forgot that
Turn this one off over the dead body
That's true as you're right it's a neutral Elite
I don't want to really dig too deep into that accept
Point out that this
Rhetorical style that Alex uses
In order for you to just be like
Please ignore how full of s*** I am
Because
This is the anime
Yeah they split kids
Throats and jack off to it
I think a lot of the people who believe
Why don't you was right about
I'll be right about
Far for me
I mean I don't think it's
You're right Poppy
There has to be a bottom to the level of
I think a lot about
The type that are in for a penny in for a pound
With a lot of this stuff
So I mean
I just don't like the idea that this
This is how you demonized
You know it it's the same thing that if we're being totally fair we've got a call out a little bit
I don't think this is the last
I think it's just an idiot
Like Rob Reiner
And I was at Morgan Freeman video
Morgan Freeman narrates
The video where he explains the flat Amir Putin has attacked us and we're at war with Russia
And it's a Rob Reiner the organization
Outlook
The reason that I
Feel like we need to call this out
While we're calling out Alex Jones for the radicalization
Of his base
Is because
When we when we talked about this dude is Russian
Concerted campaign
We don't want this to lead to a war
We don't we have no interest in that
A resolution
Of some sort
A return to
Exist
Sort of rhetoric that comes out of like Rob Reiner and Morgan Freeman
Their organization
Which is a very weird sort of
There is a Vite like March to war
Hawkish
Yeah I know about it it is also radicalizing
In
In a certain sense it makes me uncomfortable in the same way
Not the same way but it makes
The same part of me uncomfortable that Alex Jones
Radicalization
Mission of his followers
Right cuz if you're dumb you might buy into that building
Oh that's not good
He gets people to be dumb on one side
Some of these other people
Like Rob Reiner
If people be dumped on the other side
Interesting
Thought though
I know I did I don't like
So is is the
Cyber cyber attacks Russia
Has committed again
Are they more just an offshoot of the normal
Spying that we
We cybertech
We spy on them they spy on us
But that whole thing
Is it just a normal offshoot of
Spycraft
Or
Is it an actual
Warther
Is that really
It's not something that we
There's no
Boots on the ground in Russia
You know like that's not ever going to
Also
I get we made the classic blunders going into Afghanistan
But
Nobody's dumb enough to March
Into Russia during
I figured that one out
Yeah
Look
I don't know what people
Who I don't agree with or really I don't know Rob Reiner
I don't know those f******
I don't really
Fully know what the neocon want
Like I don't know
Right but I don't know what their endgame is
So I can't really
Speak to that buddy
Flights from the rhetoric
That comes out
Almost
Preemptive justify
For a possible
Hot War
I don't even know how that could play out it right the beatnuts
But like
I don't give a s***
That's not what we're here to talk about that it was just
Something that I need
Make clear in the state of like
Fairness
While we're while we're pissing on Alex we got to
Make sure there is some ideological can
So why there's that
If it's so easy
To get all those journalists in
Would it be that hard to get him killed
I think he has a lot of protect
Turn around him
Yeah but it seems like
I don't know
I don't I don't know
I've no idea
How hard would it
Take me to get
I think you probably do you have a Tor Browser
I don't
Pretty close to the top of difficult Target
Like hard targets way up there to terms of arms
Security the fact that he has
Decades of experience
Spy games
I think he would be almost
The most difficult person to assassinate
Professionals
Should be going for that one
Okay
Security
If you
Kill the hardest man to kill in the world
It's perfect so far I'm finding this experience very frustrating I don't know what it is but today I'm very
Frustrated
These
I think it started when I tried to adjust your camera and you gave me a f****** dirty look
Serious about that right now I've got to be honest
So much with
F****** with the Kaepernick
It's not surprised
What's going to happen what's going to happen
Weird are we done
No we had to technical difficulties at our friendship has thankfully it looks like that is all taken care of
We've got two more clips
That are reasonably short
When we enter a period of absurd
One of the clips
Is 4 minutes long
I am going to fix your goddamn camera and you are not going to give me the dirty look about it
Or I could kick your ass
I don't understand
How to frame and it's bothering me
Alright
Show me the
Let's get back to business cuz again you ever
A show tonight we got a lot
Short time to get there
Do what they say can't be done
Sing some more
Smokey the Bandit
Alright so this next eclipse
Is very much islamophobic
Islamists will be held up on the highest pedestal
And they are allowed to
With enjoyment
Ulta
Wonderful
It's 240
Plus million henders alone
Justin India
In 1,000 years
You died
So fake laugh therapy and right it's really unfortunate
Especially
Considering what's going on
People being forced into exile
Has a Nobel
And she is
If not active
Still at 8
Yeah it well it's debatable I think a lot of people are saying it's debatable whether it actually classifies a
Does a genocide
Whatever it is
It's his minority Muslim population
Buddhist
Country in Myanmar
They are having their Village
People are being slaughtered gang-rapes
Killing
Torturing
Says statistic I saw was 400,000
I've be enforced
Into Refuge
CG status
Which isn't going
Because Bangladesh
Is a disaster of a country
And it's not it's not like there's anything we can even do about it
Is the geography
You can't
Like a flood
All the time
Because of the low-lying US that like it's the country in the world has the lowest gross domestic product
Because
It doesn't there's nothing you could do that makes it stop mineral-rich there's no agricultural potential
Brokedown Palace
Yeah
100 / 400,000
Minority Muslim population
Aggressive
Majority
Controls the government
I mean
Never talks about that religion
You can't talk about that It Busta
Does narrative
I'm going to skip this next clip cuz
It's nonsense
It's about how the world was supposed to
Send yesterday
People have mischaracterized
You thought the world was going to end
The 23rd
And reality
Just had guests on that said it
Probably
You're a smart man
So now we're going to enter the. Of the show
Where
No
Love you babe
Alright
No this this is where Alex I think
I want
To get into races
Voiceover work
That's what I think is
Primarily motivating a lot of
He has some news about Kim Jeong Hoon
He's not going to do it
This clip is 4 minutes long
And I couldn't cut it anywhere
Because there's nowhere to cut
I could have got 20 seconds
And you would have gotten the full effect but we have to play it all because
This is what's on his show
Trump was fired
Organizations in the United States
North Korea
As they
Missiles
Japan
South Korea
And others and threatened
Donald Trump America
According to our controlled corporate press
He will face
Results Beyond
His expectation
It's from Kim Jong on never saw a buffet
Says notice Batman Alex Jones
Samurai
Wow you still going
Anytime I get to work
Genesis Coupe speaker
I'm trying to speak Japanese
Oh that was still doing
Korean
Home Depot
Trump
Japanese for you
So this point he's pulled up the Belushi clip
The video is Belushi as the samurai
With the with the voiceover
Let me show you actual footage
I'm going to go see hun
Probably
That is pretty funny
Get me a samurai sword now
Do you not know that
I don't think he knows what Gallows humor
I really don't think he understands that there's a
In Korea and Japan
I don't think he understands why
It's
Really disgraceful to do the
Prison Break
Right but also like that's
Three and a half minutes of him just going on his show
How do you not how much enough
Like Kim Jeong hoon is someone you can really make a meal out of
Like in terms of like oh how so
Substance of the brainwashing of the population the beatings of people who died
Turn off at his dad's funeral
I'll be killing his own brother in an International Airport cuz he wanted to go to Disneyland nobody or something
Whatever just like this surface of it there's so many f****** things you could do point out
About the with nuclear subs
Open to discussion
Then you can have about him instead of 3 minutes
That's disgraceful
Is it though well let's play this next week
So it was the end of it
The end of it but I'll let see what happens
Jobs at restaurant.com
Population
So let's take a break really quick they are from this
Go to
Uncle out of Reuters
Scared
About how
Have I talked to their Central Bank
To the other bag
China
I told them they will be enforcing
International
Yep
Strictly Implement United Nation
North Korea
For source
Told Reuters
Has not been tough enough over Pyongyang
Repeated nuclear test
A couple reasons why because I was just
Is completely lying
And saying the China is on the side of North Korea
The second thing is the Trump came out the other day
And said you were destroying entire f****** country
After that
Whenever you said The Conch
The middle
An executive order that he was going to
Implementing
Texans on on North Korea
But they were but they were legitimately just
A mirror of the UNC
China was responding to
It's just him trying to
Put his own name on someone else's project
Which seems like
Alex could be this far off
And like just
It's interesting
Is it
Just Breathe
It seems more like
He's lying about this one
No
No it's because he doesn't read the news
For he comes exactly know what China has done
He doesn't know the reason for it
He's just heard
And he's like
This guy is the best
He must be the one who's putting
Sanctions on Iraq as opposed to the International Community
Which is actually effective
And maybe going to save us from nuclear war
Yeah probably
Let's get back to the ship and see if we can find any
Is very racist
Let's go back to morph Kim Canan
Wow
Indian chief
So he can talk
Racism over it
He's playing with clip
So he has no idea what he's actually say
His audience has no idea what
A video of
Something nobody none of them can under
Understand
Yes it's a video of Kim Jeong Hoon not screaming
That it sounds different to our ears because
Completely different language
Yasso
It is just like a setting it up on a racism
Out of the park
And if you are like
I can imagine some of his audience
This is funny
Music
Think it's funny there's nothing
People like
You know I mean it takes all kinds
Do we need all kinds
I'm guessing
Fewer kinds
Takes a village buddy
Kim Jong-un
Almond chicken Toledo
So even with
Wayback Dave
North Korea these weapons which they didn't
Even if that were the case
Embarrass Trump
20 years down the line
Here's here's what's going to
Just make sure it up
He's just making that up
I don't like
You're not going to like the next 10 minutes
Knox
Gundams HomeGoods near me
Idiot liberals
I'm here to slave area makes them feel better
Also
Amistad now
Getting serious
The real world
Translate.
Beyond
Expectation
Kim jong-nam
Turn
We literally just
How is a
Powerful Jedi
Why she is
Beneath the mask
Is the cunning and guile of a master
On ninja of Untold Steel
Is Buck
Clear a code
Empire
Prosperity
Little boy
I love that
Deborah
I love that he's been doing that a lot
What's the opposite of triggering to me
You know how like when he's it's almost kind of stupid when he says Hubertus I want to punch a wall but whatever he says
It's it's a
If there was a catchphrase I could get behind
Eyebrow
So he throws out Jedi stuff
He's like doing more voices
Just call it
Let's bring back the rhinoceros Party of Canada
Rhinoceros
You know we can run we won't be Vice
Both co-president
Attitude and everybody's press
For a day
That would be our that would be our big running
There's like a long time
4 years
You're looking at what
410 2nd
Every adult in America's president
To get your s*** together now way ahead of time
Is it going to be a hassle also everyone gets to be a senator
For 10 seconds
Cuz you got to cycle through each shakes
States Representative in
Probably get like
45 seconds
But then 10 seconds
Does president
10 seconds is
VyStar
So do you think Alex Jones is going to do more voice over work
Oh God I hope
Well I got bad news
Let me speak to a powerful voice
Mission speech
United Nations this week
No
Open me expect
Unethical
If I'm being perfectly honest
As the one who can
Critiques and voiceover work
I'm not going to give him a job
Stay in a voice
Would you sliding all over the place
Substantive like he's not getting into any real issues
So there's nothing for me to really poke holes in that we haven't covered already left
The Hillary gave him the weapons
Giant racist
Will Alex yes
Because voiceover work
It's terrible
This is dog
Now
We were if any CNN
Committed to doing
If it was just doing a 11 goes on scene somewhere and it's just like
It's time
To have this
Let me be clear the like if it was somebody who is
Just putting on a fun voice
I'm all right with that
That would not be okay
Broadcast
Weather
Stroke yeah yeah it would be that like old-time
Screaming just come up the test pattern pattern
Those the 7-second delay though isn't
Tackle him
Delay is buffering argument is like
Did the PCS
You said he has an argument
No I mean
Technically
It's not good
Google Talks all the time about like censorship in PC stuff at the Cuban doing Bing Bong s*** for like
8 minutes
Hey this is straight
This is 8 minutes straight it's not like I took
Different parts of the episode and put them back up
How long is it going to do this
I wanted to call in
Please be like
How can you
Anyone is censored you
That's on the level of Rudy
Breakfast at Tiffany's verbal
Chinese face
Or whatever
Even though I know we're fine
Tell you he's
You're the one being your f******
Horrible monsters races
Global Systems with a normal finding
Discretion and compromise
Kim Shattuck
Continuing
President
State of the Trump's threats against
Cheerleaders speech
The back gives a shot.
I want to
This is kind of boring
Trust me it pays off in the end of it
I know I know it
While he's reading this dump
Trump and Kim Jeong Hoon have more in common
Then they have with
Any of
The people living in there like what they say is like
Normal people have more in common with a
Chimpanzee than they do with like a genius
Yeah like
People with
170 180 IQ board distance
2 average
Intelligent
People
And I would
The same plane
Take intelligence out of it
The two of them Kim Jeong Hoon
Alex Jones
And Donald Trump
Seem to have way more in common with each other
Metaphor
I think either they are getting dangerously close to Alex Jones
I just
They've given themselves over
No I think there is
I think it's mainly more my definition
Like if you're a psychopath
Clearly with these
They have no
Or just out
He doesn't have
Laugh
He doesn't have the ability to
Feel something
So
If you
He's more of a
Whatever that classify
Like a human being is somebody
Care
The teams I weigh
Cambria
You can do all of these things
And it doesn't seem like he has
It seems like
He's a psychopath you're not you're not too far off in your second
Sam killer
That kinda
I mean
You might be onto something but let's see if
I choose is correct
That is the one I have to follow the last
Kim added
Everybody
Millicent
Lumos
For drama what Hollywood to call
The highest levels of Hardline
Countermeasures in history
An idiot
50 Kim jong-un's in battle axe combat event
The president
Dothan is worded a calendar
Yet another voice
Smelled you when you came in here
He said
Is the North Place ourselves or Allies in danger
Boy can't read
Militarily
He found a pivot point
And he starts talking about how you got a Newcomb
Possibly realize that
What Donald Trump
Homestead
Pretty much exactly the same thing
Kimjongun said
Like if you if you
Just had those two
The speech that he gave
The UN
Didn't help
People
Whose is whose
Would you really be able to tell the
Not really at the same time
In wrestling I think it's what's known as cheap
Yeah they're both pissing on the idea of each other in order to get their base riled up
Side mad at them just because you want to
See the blow-off
There's no paper view, it's a nuclear war
Like it's really dumb
Speaking of which tonight
Nuclear war trailer for tonight's
No a No Mercy pay-per-view Braun strowman vs Brock Lesnar
I'm out
Just a couple of horses going up against
Got a frozen pizza and watch two big men beat the s*** out of each other later
So anyway
Yourbestlife
I want to be all so apologetic
Because you had to say
Sit through that 12 minutes of bing bong
We're in the clear now
We're past that we're going to move forward
With a couple of other really stupid narrative
But this next one is just a little bit of fun I've tweaked about this a lot
Lately
That's why I just need to play it to renault's I'm not making it up
Alex Jones has a new song that's been in the rotation for intro music
You're so happy about
War on corruption
Hosting
He's not ready to announce you
Looking forward to that
So I've got a lot
To say about that 22nd clip
The first thing I want to say is Tarzan Boy by baltimora is awesome
F****** height great song it's also a song that is
Very clearly about being a closeted homosexual and coming out of the closet
Taurus is night tonight
Give me the other give me the other world
No clue
The beginning of it is jungle life
I'm far away from nowhere on my own like Tarzan Boy
Hide and seek
I play along while we're rushing through the forest
Monkey Business
On a Sunday afternoon or Sunday afternoon
Burning bright a fire blows the signal to the
The sky
He's like about being isolated and living on your own like Android men are isolated
So then the second verse
Is jungle life you're far away from nothing it's all right you won't miss home
Take a chance leave everything behind you come and join me won't be sorry it's easy to survive
Jungle life we're living in the open
All alone like Tarzan
Boy
We play along while rushing through the forest Monkey Business
On a Sunday afternoon
Oops all night tonight
Give me the other give me
It is not it's about it's a fairy story of a real
It's very clear what it's about
Team in the gym
A hundred percent clear it's about dealing with homicide
They're great though
Pickett's banger
So the other thing he was talking about is this guy is going to be hosting
In the fourth hour I was totally just listening to
I forgot I forgot exactly what he was doing
The gentleman who Alex Jones
Excited as a guy who run
A giant radio station in
Chicago they have a little bit of a special thing
I pulled up 50
Percent off
I've pulled up the website of the station
He run
And it is w
Pkgam 1530
If you go on their website
You can listen to wckg on a.m. 1530 in the suburbs
102.3 FM in DuPage County or online
It's not in Chicago
Chat
Also I went to there as it loads up
You can see in this
That's how they have
A 4.6 out of 5 Stars only 7 reviews
Knowledge fight
Way more than that very least we can say that we have more snow base
I have been wckd
Suburban radio that Alex Jones is on
It was
Reference
What's EKG
Ckg great
Thrill it's not
Chicago station
It is a suburb station that is a small Pepsi Points
But I'm making it because in the fourth hour what ends up happening is comes on
He's terrible
He's not ready for primetime
Castor a butt
He-ere is an interview that he pre-recorded
With Adam Carolla
No
And then
I'm particularly heartbreak
Sing for me
Hit you where it hurts well but I've been predicting for a long time it's only a matter of time until Adam Carolla shows up on Infowars
This is technically not that yet
Because Matt do ba runs a Chicagoland
Radio station
And Adam Carolla was in town to do his one-man show
On September 23rd
So it was clearly just promotional the interview is mostly just about like
Hey what's it like with these Hollywood liberals
And stuff like that
Walking heart
Like I studied Adam Carolla like
I loved him when I was
I grew up with him as like a role model really smart
And the ability that you have
Metaphors and analogies
Is unparalleled
Elyson people I listen to Growing Up
Pretty close to right-wing
Narrative
Especially keep going on tour with Dennis
Prager
Talking about how College
Campuses are too uptight
You suck too much
Tea culture
Not funny
It's a bummer
Then
I listened to him around 9:11
That was when he was still on the radio station Colombia it was a slow he got kicked off the line got kicked
The Columbia Missouri radio station
Because of what he said after 9/11
He was cheering
No longer
Muslims you had a very reasonable response
Is very correct
Blow everybody up
Basically
His argument was
All right we got it
We're going to have to
They'll go over there to the Middle East
You guys blew up our buildings
We're just going to let it go
Cuz we could come over here and bomb you guys
You're going to bomb us and everyone's going to forget where things started
Which I would argue that's not the starting point
That is a reasonable response and someone to work this out as opposed to fighting
The generation of
Radio station
To be in this world now where I am
In 2017
Obsessed with pointing out
Catalog
Alex Jones is
Nefarious
To have it dovetail with
A hero of my childhood it's just a bummer
Yeah it sucks particularly bad
It's like a super
Ended up being
Or like 20 years from now is Chris gethard is a weirdo
Republican turning real hard right
Plumber
Sacrifices
Before they
I would I would assume
Out-of-touch
They start to believe their own bulshit
Somewhat money money is a real problem
Like even though back-in-the-day he always
Like as a bit
Barely
A million million million
Everybody
Baby K we should get
Is that part of the rhinoceros iguana of America
Let's call it
Kill and give
Puerto Rico
Really low bar
Where the rhinoceros Party of Canada in
Exactly I
So in this next
Alex Jones gets
Into a situation
What's going on
It's already a dump I could have pulled Eddie number out of I have a dream
Well I mean I was just thinking like
If I got
A couple raises
I might get there
But that's not net worth that's clear
But like $60,000 a year as a salary is not unreasonable
All the stuff in here
Not $60
I don't know how you put a price on
It's about Affairs in London
Do with Uber
Misrepresent
Situation
Muslims
Eyebrows
Okay that's Sensational and terrible
The news
That Muslims are killing people and selling
So although I don't think the passes hello
I'm not sure I don't know all the details to drain the blood
I don't think
Human meat
I don't think human meat is going to be hello
This is not wanted
$60,000 net worth
Okay
Now that's a new one
I have not heard
Look
Is a bad
Very there a predatory thing they are ruining people's lives
I've seen that there really f****** awesome
Did not know that they were raped
Know-it-all so I mean at least he's not on Uber side I kind of have to be like
And now London won't even let Hoover do stuff and then because
There have been incidents
Uber
Failing to report sexual harassment sexual assault
Problem
But also
Well we have a 30-day back
I called you there
People who are just going
Ignore stuff they think they can ignore
And that is endemic
Uber
There's no indication that is
Things to do with Islam or anything
Like that and the reason and the reason getting kicked out of London is that they
They're not in compliance with a number of
Then have to do with the same conversation
So we've had over here would like Medallion taxi companies being pissed off at like
Completely
Screwing over the business
Some s*** like that
They have Lac
Background checks for their drivers
Aldi's there's a ton of Regulation
The play into it not just
The sexual assault stop even though that he's a pizza
They're not Muslims rape wagon
Absolutely
Evil people and they're real interested in shortcut
Is that how you make a profit even though they're not
Yeah yeah somehow they're still losing all of them
I think it's probably due to lawsuits
Set alarm
But also the
Meat thing
Really
Like
Insane
They keep bubbling
To it's like
I don't know it look
When your title is weird to say
These are insane
And have it mean something
But they're insane
Paranoid fan
Warwick if you are laying in bed and it's in the dark
You wake up at like 3 in the morning and you hear a sound
Think someone's in your house
But no but they're okay take that out of it
Paranoid
Right now
Eat me in Salmiya tomarken
No no that's where it becomes
Unreason
Unreasonable
I did some looking into like in
People selling human
Could not find any connection with his
Delicious
No but there is there was there was
People got busted in Nigeria
Cuz they were selling
You and me there was I believe who went on it
TV show
Where he went around and he hung out with cannibals
I'm pretty sure you tell me that
I'm pretty sure I don't want to say I don't want to
I don't want a hundred percent but I call that being a new story
Little boy
You got to eat brains
I remember there being a big toe
Kerfuffle about a TV show about heretic
Stuff like that
Cannibal
And as I recall he ended up
For part of the TV show
But I didn't
Cuz I don't care
Probably conflicted
I would hope
Crazy
So I'm at home all of a sudden
I'm going to skip this next play Love
He wakes up in
In the middle of night
The burger just
Nom nom nom nom nom nom
To skip this next
Text clip
Because it's just
Complaints about Jimmy Kimmel
It's just nonsense
Close to the
Senator cats
Made him a promise
That he wouldn't
New version of
The bill
That wouldn't
Take care of
And so clearly
He kept that promise
That's not even what this is about
What's it about
It's about like Hollywood Elite
Alex's project
So let's just go ahead and play
You thought it was going to be about the health-care stocks
Yeah Kimmel
And you know you're a joke
And you know it's embarrassing
Watch your show in like you
We threatened to kill me
Campbell threatened to kill
The very things that happened
Did you probably know about
Cuz you're just a message board
Wiethop teleprompter
Police officer he never ends up saying what he's talkin
I have no idea what happens the day after
I don't know what that means but the way it is
Creepy as f***
Yeah
I guess maybe I'm going to guess Alex got like a threat
Oh yeah maybe
That's what I
The Secret Service came to eStudio entirely possible
Reprising their roles from December 21st 2012
To another
Look
Now
I'm not going to say one way or the other whether or not
Teleprompters are
Good or bad
But Jimmy Kimmel has never spent four minutes going
That's true so maybe that's
At the time that's true that was a possible job
Foreshadowing
Be further apart right now
But still friends
Weird
Establishment
Here's your money and now you're somebody
Your somebody
While you run your mouth
Everybody's ass
I don't like you
That sounds like you Alex
Scared
Hollywood trash
Know that you've got
The wreath of failure
Wrapped around your neck
Hoard
Sold out
What are you talkin about
Himself word-for-word you keep saying you're going to beat people up
But that's the thing that Alex has to
No I think he has to know that Isaac
Everything he does is a noble for
I think he thinks that selling all these products
Shamelessly
Is a noble Pursuit he's not a hore
Twins s*** right here we're talking about
Do this but I've labeled this clip
Projective
2 minutes left of that clip let's fucken cut it
We we hit the Salient Point yourself
Experience ehasz and
15 years ago
Top notch
Pismo's
I think he might be trying to pin the death of knock on Muslims
Strike that I could use them as the scapegoat for his murder of his own dog
Also like he's not kidding
He's lying
That didn't happen at 100% didn't happen
Also I don't like that
Casitas for the Muslim at the beginning
He's very
Right on par with
The amount
Somebody walked up to me
NSAID
A very
Convenient thing
Mermaid stories are matchup with my narrative
Crazy you know what he's like a bad, who hasn't started work
Into so someone else
I hate that s*** somebody came up to me after
Do the show
Conveniently every stand-up comic wins every conversation has Alex
Very see-through if you ever performed in your life
Alex Jones admits
But he's islamophobic
Vacations over
Was there ever an investigation
But in this clip
Admits it but also is
Arguing that it's right
Cuz I had a buddy
High School.
In the springtime
You made your case
I would not be necessarily afraid
I wouldn't drop my kid off of I don't have any kids
But I wouldn't drop my kid off at a park alone
Ever
You need to have supervision of your f*************** Alex
Would you drop your kid off at a forest where there's a bunch of Muslims
Wait are you saying you've dropped your kid over the 4th I mean why there weren't
I don't know cuz I don't have kids and
Probably never will I don't
Know what the age is
Where is appropriate to
Just leave your kid alone but I know it's not about
For and if they make it back home you can
Continue to raise them and if they don't they
They have completed the right exactly the right of passage
You know how high school they do orienteering
You know like when you take compass
You got to find your way out
No in cuz I grew up in a real place instead of wherever it what Missouri
F*** you
I know some of the walks out there know what I'm talking about
There isn't there's a. In high school where there is orienteering
And it is just
Trying to get you to learn
About compasses
That sort of thing
So you go to like a state park
You're in a group
For it's usually like
Miami heat up formula
What Woodway we had was three kids and two
Parents
Parents are just there to make sure everything is safe
You and the kids are the parents
Up with Muslim
Yes
But with the you know with the kids
It's all up to them to use the compass
Parents are supposed to help
You got to find your way back to the point that you're supposed to
It's so liberal it's awesome
It was great except
I was I was
I was with a couple guys at
The woods fun
Your buddy
No
The reason I brought the
Yes but Alex wants
How to do that at 4
That's the only reason I
That was a long walk
Admit
I just got wistful for orienteer missed the woods
Yeah that's fine
Going to be back in the water back in the woods
And is next clip
Watch out for
Alex Jones
Is lying
This is a lie
No I understand they're there
So
Cookie infidel
I mean this is the same delusional s*** that he says about globalist
To sit next to him on planes and help
I hate me but they were
What the f*** are you talking about
I mean when you have a made-up
Fantasy world you're living in you just
Characters
Put whatever we want
But he's never said anything like that
Before then radical Islam
People
Have
They respected
When is man
When
Having a conversation with these
I'm playing
Okay so don't know cuz he said he said on their main website
Oh okay
Maybe he's getting messages through website
From Isis
But say they respect him
Synonym like
Bro
We're going to get you
Al-akhbar
That's more logo
Nuts yeah
Looks like he's got a very John Wick kind of universe
We all respect each other we're all International
Will kill each other for my
Bonnie Brae
Paul Joseph Watson
A couple things about Paul Joseph Watson that's one of them
The other thing is
About a month ago you said he was quitting YouTube
Because of the censorship I'm glad we never had this
And everything is so terrible that he's got a quit
It's now currently a month later he's
Still there
Hasn't no ant
You change the title of his
Video that was about quitting YouTube to I won't be here much longer
Also
In April he said he was done with Donald Trump
If he allowed
Do you know him to get more involved in the Middle East
Quit constantly.
Where's Molly's wrong about everything he makes me sweeping pronouncement doesn't follow through with
Eat so much paper
Right I know it's probably make bold pronouncements he doesn't follow through
Retention was like I'm quitting YouTube
I'll be here for the
Wheels fall off
Yeah yeah
Narrative
Conservatives
Trump supporters
Are being targeted on YouTube
Is patently false
Is there argument hinges on the idea that their videos are being
Demonetized
What have you
Just happening to lots of a
It's not happening
Conservative accounts
As we've talked about in the past
The progressive liberal
Broadcast also has had their videos demonic
It's just something that YouTube is doing know whether it's right or wrong it's a whole nother thing
But it's not targeted
Also
If they're trying to turn it into a TV
Free platform
Liberal talk
Generally is
Far more palatable van
Muslims are trying to
To kill you
Let's Race
I don't
I think that's probably how everything is
There's a left and a right
Everybody's talking about
They're saying
Muslims should be killed in a large numbers
Healthcare is good
If I were an Advertiser
What would I put up
And I would drive
Towards my dollars
I was already
Weirdo who believes
The Infowars
I would never want to put my money behind
Not being put off by
Reason
Discussion of policy
Or something like that also put your money behind reason
Discussion
Nobody's watching
Enjoy watching that
Turn on TV
Also
How popular we ever get I have no interest
YouTube monetization of
Our work
They would never even really be a
The only reason to call Jose
Start about it as be
Because
He makes a lot of money
He makes a ton of money from it is
He's afraid
This thing this business that I have created
People are starting
I don't have my own thing
He doesn't
It's cuz too many
Too many liberals are he doesn't have his own thing I don't know why
Paul Joseph Watson dozen
He has a successful YouTube channel
Because
He's sensational
He's a bigot
And he makes really fast cut videos
Where you live really fast
It's too late
To look into it
Cuz he's already onto another lie
Right it's the classic
Distraction tactic with fat
Cut videos
And you can just Jen up your base really hard with
Not hard to do
Anyway
Here's a clip of him
Complaining about Hillary
You don't respond
YouTube
Get over it
So the reason I wanted to
Grating piece of
Yeah I really don't like him but the reason I accept
Cuz I want to point out that
And don't do
If you ever want to watch Paul Joseph Watson
Videos
90% of the points he tries to make
Are on the back of a random
People Twitter
Like not celebrities Twitter's often he just has someone who I
I have to assume
100 followers
Or something like that just a random person saying something
DWP Mimi Mimi voice
And then launches into his point that like how this person hates Trump
So therefore everyone hates Trump
Him saying that Hillary Clinton is bent out of shape about YouTube comment
It doesn't hold water when the his journalistic
Standards are
Random person
Twitter
It just it's it's
But again this is just pointing out hypocrisy and it doesn't
31 more Clip Joint before we get out of here because
Cuz I have not chosen
To include any of the Adam Carolla business
Cuz it's not really important the actual interview isn't
It's not super offensive
And it's not
If Alex Jones talk to Adam Carolla
A pre-recorded interview with even have proof that Adam Carolla knows that's going to be played on Infowars
Right so it is a thing where it's like this is
Tertiary
Is not good
He's dubious
Yes he is
Also
Interview with Tommy Robinson
He works for the rebel
He's just a Muslim bathing a******
London
England
For some reason
Tommy Davis
Just popped into my brain
Not have no
Tommy Robinson is a prick
And a real disaster
And because we have a number of listeners in the UK are decided to put them through it
To ruk peeps
Robinson
But we do have one more clip
Interesting
Historical attack
In this clip
On the other side
It the clown
Pennywise in the number one movie horror movie ever
Whacked-out
Because truth aw Stranger Than Fiction
Not be long impression
Except all of us
Greece
Babylon
And Egypt
Child sacrifice call
Red outfits
Names for blood
Whiteface
Tell the villagers you bring your kids at the ultimate Act of submission
And God said bring me your son so sweet
Metal play
In front of the idol
Flights from
Everybody
Elmo song
You wear a clown mask
With a big red mouth scary
Illuminati satanic Illuminati fashion show
Was another hinge here
Now I see
Finally
Stan Bowes other
Well I finally get that show bring me your children
And I will make them toss
Look into the history of
Clowns
So I did
On his
Request
I found this.
Article
Smithsonianmag.com to magazine
The Smithsonian in
Institute I assume that your ears
We can start off with
Clowns
Does pranksters Jesters Joker's Harley Quinn
Mythologize Trickster
I've been around for ages
They appeared most culture
Pygmy clowns made Egypt Egyptian pharaohs Laugh-In
2500 BC
It needs an Imperial China awkward clown called youtsey
What is according to the lore the only guy who could poke holes in a king
Plan to paint the Great Wall of China
Whatever
Hopi Native Americans had a tradition of clown like characters who interrupted serious dance rituals with
Ridiculous and
Ancient Rome's clown with a stock called the stupidest
The court Jesters of medieval Europe were sanctioned way for people under the feudal thumb to laugh at the guys in charge
And well into the 8th
Did the 19th century the prevailing clown figure
Western Europe in Britain was one of
Who were the sort of bumbling buffoon
The Clown
I've always had a dark side
Does David Kaiser
Director of talent for Ringling Brothers and Barnum and Bailey's
So we'll get into that in a little bit
The history of cloud
We will cuz there was a very
There's a very
Simple explanation for why
People are afraid of clowns
Assassins
No
But
This stuff about these like
Cultures
Putting on
Makeup and
What have you
Is ritualistic fashion
Like the group
The clowns
But look at
Look at how
Look at how people
In Muslim Church
Witches dress
Rabbis
There's ritualize home in every religion there just is
And if you look at like Native American
Much more flamboyant
Ceremonial dress
You look at two cultures that
Haven't
I had their roots
In West
Cultures
They generally do have more colorful looking like a terrible SNL sketch Pennywise the Pope
Hair
But like if you look at the the monks
In Yemen there are in tobacco
Very brightly colored ornamentation
What I'm getting at is that all religion
Completely separate tradition
Then clown
Tradition
Clown tradition
Is
This tradition of
A pressure valve on a pressure cultures
Clowns
Are not the same thing as religion
Just figures
Come got it largely from that gesture roll after roll over
The emperor has no clothes typeshift
But the Dark Side of
Clowns is actually pretty interesting
When you get down to
Cuz it comes
From one guy
The guy who is responsible for the modern-day clown that we know of
Face paint all right before this guy
Carnival clown with
And the
I can't remember the other word
Terio.
Alright whatever
The that tradition does exist to but a lot of it come
Comes from this guy
It's from the mid-to-late seven
Ended up dying in 80
But he was
Basically credited with the
The modern-day clown
He's a guy named Joseph Grimaldi
And I heard that name before
Yeah he was
Give me the big
The big clown
Never say that again the thing is before that clowns were Side characters
Stop that would come in
To like
Like in that
The you have a very serious thing and then the clown will come in and just do it
Joseph
F*** this
The clown is a star
A massive star
Clown front-and-center
And he did all that like
All that characters
LV like
The mohawk
At sometime
But
Because Grimaldi was such a star
The character he'd invented
Can closely associate
With him
And Grimaldi's real life with anything--but comedy
He grown up with a tyrant of a stage father he was prone to bouts of
Depression his first wife died during childbirth
His son was an alcoholic clown who drank himself to death by the age
Jesus and Grimaldi's physical gyration
Dileep Santa
Violets elapsed
Stick that it made him famous
Left him in concert
Pain it prematurely disabled right
Ask her Baldi himself joked quote I'm Grim all day
But I'll make you laugh at night
Louis
Grimaldi Grim all day
But I'll make you laugh at night
The road is not
The Tears of a Clown
Took that Grimaldi could make a joke about it
Highlights
How well did his tragic life was known to the audio
The young Charles dick
That's right
After Grimaldi died penniless in an alcoholic in 1837
The Quarry
The coroner's verdict quote died by a visitation of God
Bethay
Wonderful line
At a terrible car
He should be fired fired
That man I want that on NCIS but actually the next time they have like the autopsy done there like he died
Goddamn visitation
Visitation of God so I will never solve this crime
Alcoholic
Dickens
Was charged with editing Grimaldi's my memoirs
Dickinson already hit upon his dissipated drunk
Clown theme in his 1836
The Pickwick
In the serialized novel
He describes an off-duty clown reportedly inspired by Grimaldi's drunk son who died at 31
Who's Gastly wasted body
Contrasted with his white face
Clown costume
Unsurprisingly Dickens version of Grimaldi's life was well
Dickensian
F-stop says
Imposed
Economy for every last Iraq from his audience
Grimaldi's suffered
Commensurate
So
Basically Charles Dickens took a lot of creative license
With an already very
Sad
I drunk
Clown story
Katie created this mythology of
This really f***** up clown behind the scenes of The Desperate sad person
And people's imagination
Ran wild with
They created the archetype of drunk sad clown people
Made even more artistic representations of it after Charles Dickens
Took license with
Joseph Grimaldi
Right
So beyond that also people
I think they've done studies on psych to percent of the population is
Sincerely
Afraid of clowns
And the rest
The second most people grow out of it but everybody is afraid of clowns
To some extent
Because
Well it's
Because they remind us of
People that they are now
Well there's that but also children are afraid of like
El characters at Disneyland 2
The people in suits
Costumes
And stuff like that universe
Sleep scares children because
And their brains can't process exactly until the age of like three or four
You maybe even later than that
Children
Tell what's fantasy and what's reality
It's so this idea of these overblown characters
They just think they're real
And it's scary to children
And some people don't grow out of that
Exactly
As a comedian
Right Alex Jones
His version of history of clowns
Very not text Babe
Conn's drink blood
I want to be totally clear
If you say that you're afraid of clowns
I'm going to take you
Clown
And if you're not scared of that clown
If you're not scared of that clown
F*** you
Because I
Ice
Hey you guys both very serious I hate people who claim to be scared of clowns
Because it's become a social meme
Yeah become a way of replacing actually having a personality
You just like I'm scared of clowns Isn't that cool
It's the same people who are like
I think
Moist is a gross word
Oh you're f****** interest
You came up with that yea or people who are like Oxford,
Like all that stuff is just short-handed people have like now granted the Oxford, at least is a real thing
English major
I know about the subjunctive
I thought about that
Right because
Greek and it's an actual
Comes from eating and drinking blood now where is that to be true of using the subjunctive
But like all of this stuff I really think is a is
The dangerous
Trend in society that we see where people just take shortcuts into creating personality
No I think it is a trap
And
Full disclosure
I tried to do a bit about this background
So do it now in the appropriate I can pull the pieces of information out of it and never conversation
Salt Lake I think
Originally
The olden time
There were
Like memes
Like
I could tell you but I'd have to kill you
Little catchphrases
Jokes
Dallas Mavericks
You have those
That are just verbal
Little indication
But like
I got the
How many other about
Shared
Whatever
That's one
Stuff like that
Like I could tell you but it it's Kelly I don't know why that's the only example I'm coming up with
But it's
Perfect for what I'm talking about
Or rectum almost killed him
Rectum damn near killed
Right
The funniest thing in the world but
Based on
Your response
It proves my point
Verbal memes
Sprite but they don't indicate
Personality
Necessarily
I'm scared of clowns
He's trying to
To put something about yourself
Into a verbal mean
And that to me is
Is pathetic
Anderson evolution
It's an evolution of just saying a catchphrase
Anything like
I want this catchphrase.
Say something
Deep about myself
That isn't true
You're just picking up Social
Cuter
I don't know I don't know if it matters but it really bothers me
Describe High School
But I'm talking about adults
I mean High School
It should
Adult
The adulterer
Just as dumb as
I disagree. I do not think it is a new trend
That's all
I don't think people are dumb and they always have babies
Evolution of that verbal meme s*** and I f****** hate it really deal with the fact
Internet
So
Sigalert put the graphical
Start
Hey honestly I can't tell what you're making fun of Isaac everything and nothing at all
Hilarious and we should all
II
Memes are happy get over it
That's right I'm Lenny Bruce on the site ask people to come up with your own personalities
That you think it is
Alright
Let me get started on listicles okay
If you can actually write an article if you got to have number one you're joking
Bored
Why not just let people do their dumb s***
Because I think at the end of the day if people stop doing dumb s*** that they didn't need to do
Maybe it would give them time
Come up with
Sincere
Deeply found personalities and that might fit
Fix the world
Did Alex Jones thinks that Trump yelling at football players taking a knee is going to save the country
I argue that maybe everyone finding their sins
Answer your core of their Humanity that could save the country
Is pretty obvious which is hard that maybe there is
Or maybe I did something that I don't want to find out
Maybe I find out that I have been a bad person
Let me tell you I
Not a good day but it is
So there's that
Anyway
There's nothing really to be afraid of as long as you are open
Open towards progress
Self-help
On today's show
That is probably true yes
Or we labeled it like clickbait like
I'm leaving YouTube f*** you Jeff Paul Joseph Watson
Anyway if you want to find no clickbait and no memes
Single.com we would appreciate it
Does not have any means but
Flicka bleed and still does poles from time
The time is at knowledge underscore
Baby
Go to iTunes
Do the whole thing
Or you could watch it on Twitch which is
What you guys are
They're doing thank you so we're doing we're doing this for the
For the people who are
Should I be
Either this park
But we also want to listen to this on the podcast
Okay if you want to find us ideally Monday
Thursday at 8 p.m.
And I intermittently on the weekends whenever we
Depending on how things
Ending so I very close tonight
I'll be back to broke here very shortly
But until then we'll have some guests toast
It'll be fun
But I want to say this
Do you know this.
I'm sorry I think it's time
How to get rid of the Rapaport
Cuz
He sucks
Okay but he sucks
But he's not really as much of a villain
Like that kind of the fun of the b no I
I don't know what the green want to sleep don't know what the fun of the baby.
I have no idea
But look here
Here's the thing
Yes
I've been
Wrestling with the fact that like I watched a bunch of John Rappaport stuff
Yeah I really all he does is a
Anti vaxxer don't trust
Madison
Type stuff
Really
You big bad
The biggest villain of this whole thing it's not even Alex Jones
It is
Larry Nichols
Is the
You're going to the phone
The biggest problem of all of these people
So I think at the end of our show a sign of really should be
Something to do with how he should
I do so
You have to admit at least say you're on the air
And word according
This is scaring me so much
I am freaking out
That's the answering machine we can't broadcast his number
That's right
Son-of-a-b****
But you know what he didn't answer his phone if that means
This is harassing
I called him twice that's harassing
F*** you
That are here
Freaking me out
The phone
If you didn't have his f******
Phone number there
Leave a message
But
I could like mute your mic.
He's not going to
New viewers look seriously he is the villain
He's and now that we have evidence of him blackmailing Congress on are we really need to make more of a
Concerted effort
P******
Show is about
Like documenting Alex Jones
Clouded on his dumbass
Honestly think we should try
To take down Larry Nichols
Like honestly I think that should be a much bigger focus of what we do
We have evidence of him committing a felony on are we have evidence that all of his s*** for the last 18 years has been la
To go to prison
It is a foreign National
The end of Die Hard
No we can't we can't mess with Alexander Dugan
Come on it's been revoked
No he's not diplomatically immune
Skyping from Russia
It's been revoked
Under Section I'm just trying to reference the greatest moment in movie history
Nichols needs to be our Focus as opposed to John Rappaport
And so that is my point
At the end of our show we should tell Larry Nichols
Himself
Yeah but do you know
Do you know what I'm
Really frustrated by
I'd love for you to Aaron
Any grievances really all of the the argument
Is made is really Jon rappoport
Go fuc yourself
Alex