Alexandra Thurston color
We are a couple dudes like to sit around novelty Beverages and talk a little bit
Is there a twisted there is like
Why would anybody want to listen
Two dudes talk about Alex I don't know
I don't. I don't I have no idea I appreciate that everyone does
Forever red
I guess those possibilities of Twisties that we're saying
A mentally ill person
With reality but it's
The same time
We have
Explorations into being crazy and we can empathize and identify
A lunatic like Alex Jones interpret the world
Straddle sanity and insanity
I don't know a lot of other mainstream media Outlets
They Don't Really wrestle with like
Well here's what's going on someone is trying to
Just trying to
Express
X why was he when he is actually saying
Fabian
So they just showed the crazy funny Nicole
People are too afraid of the idea that like saying
He needs help and he's hurting
Is somehow validating him
That's a good point I think
I think that's a criticism that I have in my own head
Ivar show
We're giving him a
Excuse by saying that
He's not wrinkly you can say that about every
They are crazy
They are hurting and they do need help right and part of that help is getting
Punched in the face as much as humanly possible to f*** out
And you know more about Alex
I want to be perfectly clear with you
Our investigation
Alright
Something has happened
My investigation into 2015 has a hit a little bit of a snack
Yes and that I am losing
We've been doing it a long time
You too long and it's
Getting to the point where in
In November of 2015
It's just
Boring it's getting to the point where episodes are very repetitive holding pattern
Nothing really matters that we can cover
And
At this point I'm just I'm not hitting
And so that's another huge part of the you know it's Russia is
Again.
That is a white supremacist
But also
There's nothing interesting else for him
Him to talk about
Colonial
Spoiler alert
Like
Right where we are in the investigation is
Is right when
The Battle of Clan attack happen
France
He sends Paul Joseph Watson
Joe Biggs
And
They don't belong
Anywhere near
These reports where they are
In France and they're saying
Weird stuff
They don't prove it
Right like they go to Belgium
Powers made
Weather like at the bank they go to
They go to Belgium and apparently enter like a Muslim no-go area for white people
And then
They're in a real funny
Alex is like Paul
You've got to go back
And get video
You have to go back
Nope around by
Muslim
I don't believe you
You've done this before you said that the cartel was chasing you in South Texas
And if that was happening you wouldn't be back
Now you would not have a head or hands and
Right thing is true of like if there a are Muslim no-go areas
Where you're threatened for going just because you're white and you're going around and you're being journalistic
And then a bunch of these
These Muslim gangsters as they would say start following you around
You're not going to just
You're either going to get f****** footage of them following you around or they're going to attack you I didn't know Point does that happen
It just watch Gangs of New York I was like
I bet this would work over here it's just horseshit and it's it's the most
Predictable thing
I'll have the coverage of it is
Disgraceful but it's also boring
At the same time
So like we could do a whole episode about his coverage of
The Francis
But most of it is hey
Look I sent Joe Biggs
Rise give us money it's expensive
Either
It just it sucks I mean they probably got an
Yeah sleeping in the same bed
And so after that
Yes
I mean it's just
The same thing as Muslim beta
It's just be
Becoming a cycle for him
Like him
Trying to like we got to talk to
The friends of these people into the friends of dylann roof
Like it's just very clear what's going on
It's just
Boersma
It's not productive to
Our exploration of why he signed up with Trump
Outside of
Like
Okay
Maybe his fear of Muslims had a part in ending up with Trump
Yeah it's not like us going through this over and over and over again
And ruining the entertainment value of our show is really worth
But see that's what I'm saying maybe another factor in that is
He's bored
Baltimore
You got a f****** this up then you start screaming 1776
2.0 and all the sudden why
Right
And we're like where we are in the investigation is like
Maybe two
3 weeks 41 Trump
Ends up being on the show
Fast forward Trump is on the show pick up from there
Never want to hear his voice
Final boss
As they say
Snoop Dogg says
Yeah Jordan
Bad way to put it we love to do an episode
But I don't want to do that investigation stuff
So
Here is an out-of-context drop of what we're talking about today
That they will kill for anything they want
Including chocolate
32 forever
God damn you Dad I love you
Will kill you for Chuck
So it's alright it turns out
It's Saturday the 23rd of September 2017
Yeah
3 days ago
Kerry Cassidy
Posted an update
About
Captain Mark Richards
Prison list
She went back to the prison and had a 7th interview with him
Posted the results of that interview and we got a lot to go over
Mark Richard you haven't listened to all of our episodes
When we can't take Alex Jones anymore we have to drift into
3 Fun World
A Project Camelot
Which of the website and videos
Interviews
They lie to her about secret space program
All that we have heard
Is such a sweet lady and believe
All of this s*** with her whole heart to seems
Nice yeah
So if you if you didn't hear that
The episode that the Prelude to this Captain Mark Richards as
Secret space program using ducted because his dad
Heal the World from destruction 450
Exactly son went to prison
Because he was framed for a murder he did not commit though in the real world
He totally got himself
They were under his influence the Run
He got this sateen who's working a nuke
Construction crew to murder a guy
Who owed him money listen to the dollop episode about
Call dipendra
If you want to find it more easily
Also want to give a shout out
We talked about this on one episode
I'm not even next episode after that
We talked about how Alex Jones was wrong about the guy who
Who played Crocodile or the real Crocodile Dundee
So check that out too
Anyway
I don't think anybody has heard about the dollop Alyssa
To us
They're much bigger than us
What you say
Alright
So Mark Richards definitely is responsible for the death of this guy in prison
430 gears
He has a wife named Joanne Richard
Who goes out on the UFO circuit
The lies that he tells her
His narrative about the secret space program and how he's friends with a alien race called the
Good and doing war with the reptoids
And reptilian
It's difficult to say I will say that based on our out of context
If the Raptors are going to kill you for chocolate
They're not good cuz it's very available chocolate is all over
Although I
I need to give a real
Sirius f*** you
Eminem
About evidence last night
I I love novelty
Free stuff
Limited-time-only
That's a whenever Eminem's come out with something I get excited
Good like a caramel Eminem's are great pretzel Eminem's when they first came around
Hot Fire
They're still good
Peanut butter Eminem's are great
Quartz blue classic
Do you know that's never going
Whenever Eminem is like
Check this out
Come on now
All right but they're whatever they whatever they
Threat
Whenever whenever something new from Eminem's comes out I'm like
I'm going to have to do this
Ratso lately they've really been f****** it up
Like strawberry nuts
Those were discussed I tried those
Griffith disaster what is this Japan Eminem come on
A weird flavor Bluetooth
That be good
My point is the chocolate one is an unmitigated Trainwreck
I do not recommend
And if a f****** Raptor killed me for them I'd be like
I feel like that would come into us
Chewing on mic
A little bit
Let's not go down that road
But
Let's go down this other road which is Kerry Cassidy
God just giving us some updates
About her
Did Mark Richards and prism here is her introduction
The video
Hi everyone I'm Kerry Cassidy from Project Camelot
Yeah you are today I'm going to be giving you my Total Recall
Verbally kind of information I got from Mark
Richards
So I this is Prisoner that I go and interview in Vacaville California
And he said a prison there
And he has been framed for a murder he didn't commit he's what we call a political prisoner
Captain Mark Richards
And he's worked in the secret space program
Along with his father and grandfather so he is that third-generation I just
You might
If you are lying
First Defense
To get into Harvard
So 29
Is that surround when the murder
Pendragon
And also we left out the part where he also wanted
To take over Marin County California
Laser weapon
So he's
God
So I feel at this point
Before we get into the Moon
Of what
He lied to carry about this time
I feel the need to defend ourselves for like why is this relevant
2R podcast
We need to take breaks from Alex
That's understood
Why you go to Project Camelot
Here are some of the reasons that I have
There's a very high overlapping
There are a bunch of people
Peugeot on Alex Jones
Who are also on Project Campbell
Alexander Dugan
He probably does sagami use on boat
Talked about Robert David Steele
Both of them David Icke
How about
I bet you been on there
$30 for anti-vax got a lot of similar faces
Between the two Jordan Maxwell is another conspiracy theory guy about aliens
He's been on
Like you just see a lot of overlap
And the reason for that is
Because they're all,
They're all con people
And in the case of Kerry Cassidy
Mostly believe
But she's innocent
Unlike unlike Alex who is
Hey I've deliberately inciting
But violence Terry's just like the world is a fantastic and magical place in
Wish more people news
But there was this Secret
The soul of humanity going on because part and parcel of that in her mind isn't there
Alien races that can help us
And bring us to the next level Range Rover
She is a I think she's
I'm guessing she did a lot of drugs
Now doesn't know
What direction is up Track entries
Sweet person and believes all this nonsense
The people who are con men are telling
Alex
Alex on the other hand
Is willfully a piece of it which is why our show is more about Alex
Terry is just
Come on it is it is a fascinating
Like
It is it is the same thing
It really is
And yet
There is a
Element to carry
Like she is a hopeful person
Yeah like she believes that the world
And will be a better place
The more people know about
Once you have
And of course once the war's on Mars
I'm not sure you really mad at the words on Mars
Lesso about Afghan
I'm not I'm not sure I can flashes up on screen
Share the link on our website
2A
A GoFundMe campaign for a guy named
Peterson
Is allegedly a whistle
Blower
Of some sort
He's raised $53,000
In a month
Because he claims to have secret information
About all kinds of secret military projects
He did an interview with a guy named David Wilcock
And that's what his
Given tons of
Any scroll down this GoFundMe
All proceeds will go directly to
Peterson via David Wilcock
Talk to some cause for
Concern
Crazy we actually do have
Secret information
Or at least public information that nobody's paying into an idea
About all the crimes
Nikle current
Alex give to white supremacy but nobody is talking about
And yet we can't get $53,000 on a GoFundMe
But
Look the reason that I bring that up as relevant is the David Wilcock is a f****** huge con man
Running a car with this guy
Whistleblower
$53,000 in a month
This is the game that these guys are playing
Right because she for whatever reason is built up quite an audience with
This project
The interviews people on question
Fittingly about
Sensational topic
I do not
There's a psychic
Edgar Cayce
Back in the day
He was called the sleep
Alright I just called the sleeping psychic
Okay
Leica automatic writing in that kind of thing
People psychic readings
And there's a lot of stuff about people having past lives
Atlantis event beyond that there was also a bunch
You diagnosed
PPL medical condition
While you was asleep
I don't like that I don't know if we can really
Fully
Figure out how accurate he was
But it is interesting
Because all
Was recorded
Not like audio recorded but there's transcripts of everything he did
And so like you can go online
A f****** months
Reading the sleep
Sleepy dude
But
He died
And David Wilcock
Came around
And said that he was
The reincarnate
It's b o I knew it
Yeah I knew it he's Edgar Cayce reincarnated
God damn what a great day a lot of people are like
He's just someone who I've looked into a bitten
In the past
S*** this guy
So he's
Running this Kickstarter
GoFundMe
For this other guy has been on Project Camelot
You know Carrie is put up a link
Two on the site
It's just all elaborate fraud being done
And that is relevant
To Alex
At least something
That's because I believe that this podcast
Well it is
Primarily
Anti-fascism
Anti-whites
Soupremacy
Anthony
Capitalism at this point
And Auntie Alex Jones and what he stands for do you want to add what I'm antique
But I'm in the shower
Where anti-global
Absolute installs at
Will be in the Alex Jones
The bigger Cent
2 we're against
Carmen
We're against fraud
That appears
Largely in the right-wing
Because a lot of these other people are also pretty right-wing
Piano
They're all so pretty right wing
Obama's Obama's evil
Beautifying
Field theory behind a lot of these people are not a lot of
Project Camelot
Black president didn't
Expect
Fire concert
So let's get this first clip
Kerry Cassidy
About to her interview with with Mark richt
That have to do with
We talked about Hillary Clinton
He thought the real real reason Trump won was
That's because no one really like
Hillary
That's actually really smart not trusted
He acknowledged she does report
Bush Senior
And also to
Soros
He does not think she's mj-12 are which is contrary to some other information
Been given about her
So that was interesting and
I've Been Told
That
Mj-12 which goes by men
Is quite High
Totem pole
He does not feel she's
Quite as reading
As I do
Sounds for what that's worth
And then also says that he thinks they're a lot of John Wayne
Types in the military that don't like her
Partially
Because of her
What he says black magic
Drug went running with
Her husband
Clinton and pedophilia
Issue he thinks that
She is evil and has
Trust issues
He also thinks that she is backed by
The black magic witch
Is he called them
European
Illuminati
So
That's another thing that makes this very relevant
Very similar rhetoric
I hope you don't get Infowars a
I hope
But like
You know she brings up Soros as a bad thing
At least Mark Richards
The Narrative of a
Police and military or more woken up
That's straight out of valley
Hillary Clinton is a witch that's Larry Nichols s***
Pedophilia that she
Absolutely like f****** world that we dwell in with Alex Jones
Free thin now to our fun Oasis
But thankfully that's the only place where they talk about
Hillary but I needed to bring that in because
I mean it is
Craziest
Overlap
But Alex
Would agree with these things
What is MD
Do that but I can
50 Majestic
I was here
And UFOs
Conspiracy theories Majestic 12 or mj-12 is codename of an alleged
Secret Committee of scientists military leaders and government officials
That is a
Abbreviation
Majestic
12-year mj-12
Grammatically incorrect it was allegedly formed in 1947 by an executive order by
US President Harry S Truman
To facilitate recovery investigation of alien space
The concept originated in the series of
Supposedly leaked secret government
First circulated by UFO ologist
Upon examination Federal Bureau of Investigation
Declare the doctor
Quote
Completely bogus
Hey many ufologists consider them
To be an elaborate hoax
So that's what it is
It's a fake organ is
Write a blues song
Sherman was the Roswell
Perfect Futurama
Some people have actually done too
Interesting theories
About these documents
And one of the things this guy
Here already this
Author Brian Dunning investigated the history of the subject and reported his findings
The 2016
Skeptoid podcast
Episode the secret history of the
The Majestic 12
He concluded that rather than a hoax perpetrated by the UFO community
It's likely the papers were actually part of it
Information camp
Of the US government
To deflect attention
Secret Air Force projects
Referring to the mj-12 documents
Dunning state
Quote
They were classic disinformation
False documents created to play a role in real National Security
They were designed for
Pacific mark
Who did with them
Exactly as they were meant to do
They took advantage of well-meaning Patriots wanted in
National Security
And who
By being the fool ended up providing
Exactly that
Not as hard as you would hope so the theory is that these
Supposedly
Classified leaked documents
It's were fake but they were released by the US government
Go to Starbucks
Is there UFO
But sounds like a really good movie
Yeah
Movie Theaters 8
Greens or less
Smallville
Little bit of personal information about Dan
I spent like 5 years of my life working
Forum 8 movie theater
Columbia Missouri
And so that's my
8 is where I pop a top out
Enough
Next clip
Captain Mark Richards
The Dutchman
The Dutchman Sun
But the show would be called
Vine system
Artificially intelligent
Spacecraft
Minerva yes I don't know we don't know we don't hear from you
Learn a little bit more about Minerva
Here is that
He said
There was an average crew of nine
I'm not sure what
Skip that one
Score
I'm afraid I didn't get that down in my notes
He did stay with Minerva she doesn't like crew
Besides Mark so in general when he flew Minerva
I would only be her and
Him and
It would only be marking one other
The person
But she does take groups
Zoo animals
Onboard
For study
And she can morph her interior to make room for hundreds of animals
She asked
As his translator when he is
Traveling virgin
Flying her
And going to other planet
Another system
The furthest he's gone in
Stellar he says was with
Companion named glasses
Which is out around
The Alpha Centauri
Ask them about Interstellar travel to other planets in the beans he's met
He said he has traveled to the
Three stars of Oz
Albertsons
Tori
Hazmat 20 difference
Species
He said there are four different
Colonies
In the Orion constellation
Installation
However that when he's traveling
Minerva is very poor
Detective often won't let him leave the
Due to dangerous conditions
And she treats humans a little like pets or chilled
He also said not all wormholes are the same
I didn't
Actually get an elaboration on that
Hopefully willing
Future
So another thing
A second I thought you was talking about
She was talking about Freddie blassie
Maybe the pro wrestler
Of course
Where is Lassie
I love to talk to him
Digimon
Project Camelot
The got2b
That's the other day if any of this was real
Of course
Just like the UFO ologist
It's a disinformation
You have them in there so late The Narrative to Kerry Cassidy
Who's telling the truth right
Inside
Course
I mean It Isn't Love
The way that I am
I don't know how to
With hope
And love in your heart then
It's not what inspired I love
I love the idea of hope this makes me profoundly sad because I know that she's being lied to by a murderer
You don't like that that part of it is like why you got to bring everybody down
I know I'm interested in what's real generally
This is about
Piercing the worlds
Right for me
I mean I don't really care that much about Mark Richards
He committed the murder and he's in prison
In for it like to a certain extent the sink.
The system has worked
I don't really care that much
That Project Camelot goes and visits him and let him say all this
He's not killing anybody else
He's not telling Kerry Cassidy to murder for him he's just
Creating a weird board
He's creating course creating a story in order to alleviate some of the
His guilt
Maybe try to rehab his personality
His eyes character in the public eye
I don't really care about that cuz if you're not an idiot
You can see through this pretty quickly
And that also like
I don't really care all that much about the Frog that's being perpetrated on his wife
Cuz she seems to get something out of it too
There's a positive
For her
Meaning in her life
She gets to live out thinking that eventually these Raptors are coming
He's pretty happy travels around
Large amount of friends and people who support
She seems to also get more out of watching Jurassic world than I did
Hello
That's something
Right I couldn't have been enjoyed it as much as someone who thinks
No that's entirely entirely true
Anyway I don't really care too much
At the same time
Outside of
My stated objective
Recipe like
All nervous real
Here's my
Here's my reality
Reality is the worst thing right now
Where is nothing I don't hate
On this f****** planet at this point
It's it's fun it's genuinely fun because again
It is banana
If Mark Richards was was telling her lies and
Trying to get her to do stuff right is he was like you know the reptoids cuz they have dark skin
Or even just like
You need to lead the fight
Against the Reptoid
Instead he's just spinning a yarn
We could
We could make a graphic novel
Based on the b******* that he says
And it would be just as much fun
I don't think he has intellectual property over this
Rudy whatever we would have resemblance to characters living or dead
Aprilia Falco
Neither of us can really draw that good
Not going to happen if you are.
Be that as it may
Reality being good or bad
Decide
There's another update that I need
Need to give you the tags
Gary brought up at the beginning
Other episode
She's no longer allowed to bring a pencil or pen
But you had to take her notes in
Crayon
I think I think Mark bite of misbehave
In prison and they took away his pain privileges godso
Did she
Later in the episode she says if you want to see
See my notes there on the website
Pictures of absolute
Anyway
Rotondo's next clip
Weirdest costumes
Signed
Page
Of crab notes
Absolutely
So
As we discussed
That's the new like seal of approval.
Some of the wars
That we fought in
History of America
Have not been
Stargate
Stairs
And I as we've
Learned there were Beetle being
In Vietnam
As we called them
In this clip
We learned that there might have been
Other
Bug beans okay the formic War possibly
She's trying to retcon
The Beatles
Turn them into something else
We did talk more about the spider beings
He I wanted to know about the
Relationship of the spider beings to the Viet Cong
Leaders
And also to
The recall of the troops
And he said
Works with the spider leadership
And after become leaders and he also said
A used mind control
To get the
Troops to
Forget
What who they were really working with and are they use gas
Forget so that mobile
Most people wouldn't remember anything
Do with the spider being
It's possible that some soldiers will remember how
However
And I talked
About one soldier
Previous
Show that I did I did a show on
Yes spiderbeam
From
The Vietnam War and
Christine
Soldier on my show as well as
Smelly people calling in
And smother
Interesting recall from
Serious
Soldiers in the Vietnam War
Seems to be leading in that direction to
Validity to what Market
Corroboration up
Not corroboration
Fatte's Pizza
Yeah and crazy people calling you
That's not corroboration.
Because someone
The same crazy s***
What someone else says
It's possible
42 Liars
Could be
Suggestibility
Yeah because you know you have this
Fantastic
Narrative
They are
Putting out there about rap
Being friends with us
Against these reptoids and
You have beetles or spiders apparently these Fighters are the size of ew
Spyder leader
No
I refuse to
Divider leadership
What do you think what do you think tell me what you see right now
Is it a group of people are spiders
Yes large spiders largest
Big spiders Underground
Somewhere project
You've got six
High-ranking spiders
They all have hats
Google store
No Road and Podium how do you deal with the legs
It's worth aerobics
Spider-Man
Are webinar whatever the f*** it is
Assistant on the app I'm 50-50 on roads
Because roads
Roads really indicates spiritual leadership military leadership
Did this is a military operation is involved is involved
With spider leadership
I believe that the spiders are Tibetan Monks
That's the dog whistle the next
Right democratic
The spiders
Absolutely not
No absolutely not
Not a trip you think it's a military junta
Yes okay
People spider f***
7 -
Spiders
I don't think that democracy is necessarily A system that penetrates other alien races
Isaac
I just might be an unpopular opinions
This might be an unpopular opinion for humans
The circle 2017
But democracy might not be where we end up Landing
It's a great system in some ways we might be able to find better it's possible
We don't
I don't know
Anyway
It's anarcho-capitalism
Now I'm against it firmly against
You're a Raptor
I would be a raptor if we're fighting anarcho-capitalist spiders yes absolutely
If a spider live
I live in a world where we get to say
I would be around if we were fighting against anarcho-capitalism
Giant spider that has Stefan molyneux had and I'm just like
No no
Getaway
I have a giant rolled-up magazine
Their one weakness in this one we she's
Discussing hurricanes
This is bad timing
That is bad time
Much like Alex
Believe that the government has weather control
She has a very interesting narrative for why portions of North Carolina
Had to evacuate recently
And I don't really want to go
Okay
Alright it's
Not like a throng and it's yeah it's disgraceful
But
Particular lie
Is fun enough
He said in this recent
North Carolina out of Outer Banks
Island
There was
Ipower
Supposedly that was the news item
So what I've done on my notes
Just linked the two article
About the recent
Empower
In that area
And the fact
Is that the governor
Actually evacuated
These people out of the area
The real reason they were being vacuolating
According to Mark is
Is because of portal opened
And
A very dark group a rogue group of aliens
Came through and started actually eating people off the beach
Rogue alien
Rogue
Eating people on the beach
What alien
What Rogue alien is there any specifics on which road we actually will get a little bit information
Absolutely
So far so good
So Rogue aliens
Rogue from what
Great quest
No response of those I'll get back to you on that
Aerospace protocols
Charge run
Looks delicious
That's true love the climate
Around America
Vacationing on the outer islands of North Carolina
It's not a situation at all
Yeah
That's the ticket
It's not a situation of dangerous inclement weather
Caused by climate change
Mark once again reiterates that he believes in climate
Episode
So let's get back to this there's more than our president
Yeah well he doesn't have a vested interest in tax cuts for the rich
Oh dude also
I want I want to get into this really quick I hope you
Tax cuts for the Raptor
You know Alex Jones about
Lies about how like the
The climate change lie in his word
Is this
Looking into that and it's that work it's kind of interesting cuz
South Africa taxes starting its
September of
15 how they've been doing China has had a carbon tax and
2012 climate
Carbon tax
It was initiated in July of 2010
In 2014
Japan has had one son
2012 missions Ben
You good they're improving consistently dropping South Korea's had one since 2000
Taiwan has had one since
2009 or started planning one
Australia's had one
2012 New Zealand 22005
Xavier
Clearly those countries have
The European Union has been trying to implement one since 19 1990s
Denmark
2002 F150
Started in the 90
The 90s
The curve France they had a carbon tax
Interior research
France
Initiated
Starting climate carbon taxes
Germany
Adoptive ecological text
Perform in 90
T99
King country on the goddamn
Yeah
We're officially dumber than North Korea
In Sweden in 1991.
The United
Kingdom 1993 they started tax
Petroleum products
Norway
Switzerland
That the dude to do
Central America Costa Rica
Costa Rica is got a carbon tax going in 1997
Canada
Has Dave no federal carbon tax
But their province
Have an active carbon taxes
Of their own accord
So that it's right for hate
According to the carbon tax enter the United States
Is one of the few
Large industrialized Nation
Things on earth that do
Does not implemented carbon
I can't think of any reason why
We wouldn't have
Well because
We have
Way too much
Have way too much sway over the government
This is all things.
Consistently
I have not been able to get this out of my head
We don't live in a democracy
Order corporate
Corporate kleptocracies more like
Steve's well but it's more generally
Focused around one person
And granted Trump is doing a great job of making that a reality
But we have more of just like
Plethora of
Steven organizations
Betterall Corporation
Monopolies in the lake because their corporations they dodged individual responsibility for the crimes
Absolutely
So position is
Why the f***
I don't think this is why all of our protests have no real
Affect
Cuz we need to go because we don't have a democracy
The idea of protest
Like like whenever you look on Twitter you need to call these six senators
Who are a maybe
Right now the larger problem is the other 44 don't give a fuk cuz they're just own
They're just owned
So go to the f****** Koch Brothers headquarters
Protest
If we had 20,000 women
Sitting outside of Wichita Kansas
And I got the address again if we did that
That's a real effect
That's something that really bothers me
We don't even know where I think you would find that it wouldn't bother me as much as you help
No cuz he hears it here let me give you my dark
Thought
As of this weekend
Is recording this on Saturday so I don't know what's going to happen tomorrow with the football game what happened
El Presidente
Trump
NFL owners
Should
Fire these players
F****** clearly white nationalist rally in Alabama
You know we're still the games are tomorrow and buy guesstimation of it is there going to be a lot more
People taking a nap
F****** hope so
Steph Curry and LeBron James team up to call Trump a piece of
S***
Phuc yea yea but here's the here's what I'm getting at
I think that there is a decent
Chance
They're what we might end up seeing
Is a larger-scale version of the University
Missouri
That's possible because
There were legitimate protest
And people
Growing dissatisfied with stuff
President
University system
The step down and he didn't
Until the football team
Tell the football teams are going to play anymore if you lose
Money
Now if you get the NFL going on strike
Or something like that or a large portion of it
I think you would have millionaires
Who are like we're losing millions of dollars tens of millions of dollars
And they would start putting pressure on senators
In ways that we could not
I meant it makes me profoundly sad
But at the same time
I mean if we can do that if that could happen
And then once that happens
Change the fact that matters more than once
I don't know
I think that you might end up seeing these moneyed interest
Being what ends up having to
Imagine imagine a Sunday where the NFL the players
Just goes
No no
Cluck-U
That would destroy America
There was literally in the south
Probably yeah absolutely
Just blame
Yeah all my God
Dr. Everett
In the Barrier Islands
Area
He said the whole area had to be
Evacuated under false pretense
So the military could deal with it
They found that they couldn't handle the situation because it required
As if they didn't have any
Collateral damage and usually when they try to close the portal
They are
They use a nuke
Are they having
In the past
I still there
Enlisted the help of the Raptors
To help
With their high-tech
They have special weapons that allows them to Target
Individual
Individual beings and not have collateral damage and as well as
The clothes portals
Our technology wasn't
Sophisticated enough
To avoid collateral damage
Here's the thing that she assumed
In that
If the weight more important
If the way we usually close portals
Is by detonating nuclear weapons Japan
How many nuclear weapons have we detonated
Secretly
Well-known
You're that you're not taking into account
Nuclear tests have also been frozen portals
Well they just wanted to know do know
We'll get to that
Put a pin
This is now changed
So this seems like a rather
Recent
Maybe we
Technology
Raptors
He said The Intruders coming in through the portals were
Stubbs
Another
Species and that we don't know this be
He's very well eating people on beaches
Other species
Not interested
The name of the species
Is but it was
Crayon that you couldn't read it
I don't know
Bruno's
He said
The situation he believes
Husband handle
In that area
He did not tell me
What kind of aliens
And
I am also wondering now if the recent
Allowing of the
Hurricane
Very destructive hurricanes
Irma
Harvey
Start of another episode in this
Portal
War with it
A certain group coming in
And not really about
Actually not
It's nothing natural
That's natural we do know that there are weather Wars going on
Constantly
So I'm going to
To try to see
I can find out
Something more about
Secular disaster
America
Because
The evidence we have is that
They have plenty of
Technology to be able to
To turn it down
Storm
Back out to
And the fact that they didn't do that
In the case of Harvey and Irma
Is rather
Auspicious
That's why they were turned Irma is actually happening right now so I don't know what the final
The results of that will be
So
This this investigation is ongoing
Dr. destination you are just listening
Alina crazy over that
All of these ideas about
Being able to
Create
Stop hurricane. What's up
Largely has to do with misunderstandings about HARP
Yep
My friend
Do the Raptors
Now we have a little bit of
That we have some news about the Raptors
Involved
Some others
Some weird stuff
They didn't get
And I asked him if his future I asked him if
If he was ever
Hooked up to the top
Technology
That the Raptors have
And many other race
We're told
That allows a human to see like
History of Earth in also
Asadero
Reincarnation
History
And he said yes he was hooked up to such a machine
Are the Raptors have that
Technology
He said he did see
Summer
The true history of Earth
Deeper question
Contract
And whether or not
He felt that he was
Victim of circumstance
Azure weather
He chose the path he's on
As a soul
Coming in and he said that he
Felt that he chose
To fight the powers
And that is why he
Became imprisoned
He didn't choose
To be in prison for
For 30 years
This is weird
But then he was like search
That was too long this is not what my school signed up for me
Conception what you talking about there's a lot of people who believe 4th member of Public Enemy
No no I mean
That's fine I should have allowed that to breathe
You dumb talk about the soul contract
I have a belief in reincarnation
Yeah and that's
Reasonable to some extent in terms of spiritual beliefs
Reincarnation one I'm going to just go ahead
Is it
It's fun static L problem if you wanted
Fanciful
Sort of spiritual belief that's not one that I find particularly if I
I mean the only problem I have there is there's roughly what like
2 million people who think they were Cleopatra
Ego
And I agree that the problem but then also the
Numbers of
The new people that have been
You know it turns the population growth where the souls coming from right
The belief
A subset of the reincarnation
Kinfolks
It's something that I enjoy I like this
I'm not saying I'm a hundred percent
But I like it
Some percentage believe no I would like to believe it but I don't like
The cold hard
Skeptic in me whatever certainly.
But there are there people who believe that
You go about your life
And there's a soul group that you have
Okay whatever you meet your
Soulmate connect to those are members of your
Your soul group
And you're going about your life
In a way
That you guys all agreed to before you were born
So in between why
Your soul group gets
Together and you come up with whatever the game you're going to play in this next life
Hey what's up let's go
Let's go get abused by religion bus and then eventually
Meet each other doing comedy and then start a podcast
ER plan that we created and then we would sign a soul contract
Karmic debt repaid
So we're getting close to bocona nism
Come from
Kurt Vonnegut
Yeah yeah
You just like
If you would
If you like
You know killed someone in a past life
Then you're
Soul contract with involved in your next life
They do something to you
They ruin your life summer or whatever
Thousand here before he was born he had a contract sign
But I didn't want to go to prison
30 years
Richard Philly
But even within that framework that I enjoyed the ideas
Because it is it is fun it is a fun it is
So what you're saying is
To be reincarnated his soul group
And they're trying to pay the bill at a restaurant and
Feel sad
You know look into his future as they have the ability
He feels his biggest threat
Questioning Authority
People tend to want to follow him
And so the powers
Find
That
The greatest threat
So just like we talked about last time that's like that little bit of guilt coming up but he can't quite
Yeah it's a problem that
People want to follow me any
I think I think it is a problem
Yeah
Yeah yeah I am a sociopath who is
Weirdly charismatic apparently
And was able to
Convince 270
18 year old do to kill a guy for money
Probably well-meaning
Secret space program researcher in
Heavy quotes
Is following him
Essentially
And yeah that is the guilt that
Trying to wrestle with the fact that like
I am so interested
I'm so his version of it is like they saw that I was going to be problem
In prison
They don't let me up
He was a problem
It was not because
He's questioning Authority but that actually that comes later I don't have the clip of it but he was explaining
Quest
Got kill
Authority alien he loves
More or less
Wow
Alright this is a classic Revenge Tale
So you might the Raptors they got this future technology and when have you for real
This would be the best Bollywood movie in
Musical numbers
Kill you for chocolate have a present
Who Among Us
Has not wanted to kill
Me
You want to kill after eating chocolate
Just tell me that
Do you have a dollar
You can get chocolate
Really acceptable
But not the good Raptor
That's bulshit that's bulshit
They would take whatever they're not like
I need a Wonka bar
They be like
I don't care give me
Whatever I
What about the road
Now they want to eat people
Okay so the rapper
Have a presence
And modern-day
Global
They have to
And turns out
The Raptors are in play in
Syria
Disclosure Aleppo and the
Chileans that are pushing disclosure I discussed this in my last interview he had
It said that the
Forcing the issue in Aleppo
Set the battle there was
Very intense battle
In part because the reptoids
Building what is Nessun tsegay
ESATA Stargate
And they were looking to bring
Troops and crafts
Into this dimension
He said they have aircraft
Styes
Carrier
Craft
And that they can bring around 5,000
Have their own Troop
Oops in that way
She said they can take back
However through the gate
As many as 30,000
Human prey
Dead or alive
He says they
Trade human slaves
Other races
And those humans are used
Slaves in
Engineering
Purposes
And if one of their business
They have been dealt with
For the time being
Vet
Discontinued
So
This is this is sad
Reptile
Are the
Originators of the slave trade
That's what you're telling her stellar
Dimensional
Around here
For long enough you make a very valid interesting point of what are they trading for
That is a problem
Might be chocolate it might be chocolate Goods
Yeah
I don't know
Truly that's the new if a tree falls in the forest
Cacao beans
There's other ways
Mark Richards has not confirmed that.
Call me
Out into space
They genetically engineered to create
Look
Straight
You just f****** rotateq officially onto the main stash
That is
Why Minerva is taking it
All makes sense now
What's what's classy
Exactly
A giant anthropomorphics jar for milk
So
You might be
Concerned about the fact
That the reptoids are meddling in a business
The concern is that their meddling and
We don't we don't
No one season only right
But there's a reason
I want of his remote viewers
Aziz
Area 51
And apparently
Aziz was aware enough to realize that when he was looking at a
What appears to be a Reptoid or rep
Chilean
Being down in Area 51
In one of the lower levels
He
Saw that it would
Make an attempt
Over his mind so that he would forget and also not see the bean
However he was
Managed
Bibiana
So it's clear that they
Have disability
The human mind
And also make humans
Forget
Doctor Who which obviously helps
The secrecy
It obviously helps the speaker
It couldn't hurt
The secret very very convenient piece of the narrative
Make you forget the Silence from Doctor Who
It's Men in Black
It's a common literary tropes
We got a little bit of
This is where we find out that the Raptors will kill you for chocolate
Surrounding
He did talk about the Raptors and what they will do for chocolate and or for any kind of Technology they desire
He said they often
Steel
Borrow
Technology for mother
The races
Said that they will kill for anything they want
Including chocolate
He said the Raptors can see the past energetically they
I see the pastor birth and
Have anyone there
Shoes
I would argue
Because he's also said they can see the future
Exist outside
Time
Space
According to the Raptor technology that they have
I would argue is that
At least one time
That a raptor has killed someone for chocolate
And then seen the future or past in like
The very very minor things to kill someone for
Is there on Mark Richards
Notorious murderer Mark Richards
Like I said
Very available
Cherry red dog treats
All the time
Just in case they ran into a dog
Like just in case
I got to keep that dog treats as the world gets more and more chaotic
Always keep some chocolate audio
The complete opposite direction ever killed
Is might be a diet thing maybe that's what Mark Richardson started encourage people to get in shape
Carrie lost a lot of weight
Following
You know what they hate that like sugar free chocolate
Inexplicably they like
American chocolate more than they like European chocolate
Despite the fact
So we all know
European chocolate
Is better Belgian
Yeah
Here's the here's the only issue there
So if you can see the past and the future
Outside of
Four dimensional time
All things are happening
Simultaneous
So you really don't even know if you have free will
Because everything has happened and will happen
And he's already happening
Same time price
They're killing for chocolate but they don't even know
Part of who they are
Some extent that's true of everybody and everything
Especially if you can see into the future that doesn't fly predestination
On some level it is that weird
You know like
Gyros
The TV show Style version of a dystopian picture and if we met
Make one decision difference
Infinite Multiverse Theory save the Raptor save the world
I'm still confused as to where these Rogue aliens are coming from
Nevermind
They're From Another Dimension they want to go to the outer islands of North Carolina in
And don't really know all that much about
Because Mark was like
Water stay there bezel board
But that sound paper over this
Yeah I'm good
That's a hundred percent what's going on
He's like
Every day he goes to the library and just read the
Hannah sci-fi books
Taking a little more
Whip Nae Nae in Fort Worth
Getting all crazy
North Korea
I did ask earlier about North Korea I have a feeling I'm going to regret
With regard to North Korea he said the only reason they're being so aggressive is that they're backed by
Alien group that are powerful
Of the u.s.
And he said there's a definite group of off-world beings
The back them
Musically inclined to say which group
In which case
It does not sound like it's the Reptoid
When asked about the North Korea
Nuclear testing earthquake
He actually didn't answer me directly about
She kind of smiled when I asked him about that and didn't
Say anything so I
Ask him in essence does that mean
We're actually in
With North Korea and the beans backing them
And that these so-called nuclear tests are more like
Fourth
From each side
And again he didn't say anything
Smiled so
That's my impression
That innocence we are already at war with North
Korea
Who that's my
No it's not true
Dude
Difficult to deescalate by
It's very sci-fi and that it is kind of allegorical for what is currently happening
Like they are being bags exactly
Relatively
Logical analysis
Behind his b*******
It's like him confessing that I'm a manipulative cult leader, Guyana
Metaphorically saying
Guilty of murder
Artsy's
Expressing
Real things in an Artful way
To some extent
Yeah I'm sure there is China back in North Korea
His version of some unnamed alien races really just
Remnants of the
Communist Bloc
But
Here's my also want a reminder
Everybody else cuz I have tickets
I'm all of this is real
I don't I don't think of people understand this
A lot of people don't know if Kerry Cassidy is on the
Tip
Is this the cheese farts a lot of stuff
It's very similar
To this world
View
With the aliens
Alternate
A lot of people who believe in that believe the
The Jews are real
God dammit
Spring-trap
They believe that the Hebrews
Are in outer space race that was in
Installed
Into like Atlantis
Send lemuria
Because
They needed a balance
Between the draconian
And the Atlanta
Feminine race
Abeyance
I measure Conan's or these
Worshipping
Folks
They came in and they were really male
Destructive and what-have-you
And they were like
As I understand there were like 9 or 10
Spot-on Atlanta
Be filled or where they'll be like population
Centers
Another one
The Hebrews
Lower super magical
I'm good at good at math
And that what have you been were a very evolved
Race
Look who is this
Positive
Yeah
No
Neither
It's not good for the Jews always involved
The Jews are always like
It does seem like no matter how wacky or evil
You get whichever side on Spectrum
In this conception
From what I've been able to glean
Cuz I've done
Some diving
Into this this world
A little bit
Doesn't
Seem like it's negative
Hateful
The space
Hebrew
But it is
It's not negative in the same way that like
Somatic
Population
At the same time
When did still singling out the matter where you are on the Spectrum from crazy
Easy to evil no matter what
Seems like a through-line through all of it is like the Jews aren't
With us there's something else
I just left
Don't understand that
A bowl because
Is it cuz they killed Christ
It's because they killed Christ
Goes back to the money
The goes back to usury
Probably
Betzer thing existed before
There might be something else too that I own
Fully understand but
For me in terms of IUD
Population
You think that they're the they're the cause of all your husband on McMullen
Destroying all right
Whatever
I just
If there's one lesson that I've learned from all of history
It's
Leave the Jews alone
Man
Typically when you hit a Tipping Point of people being mad at them
That's one really bad
Everything goes wild
Yep and
Might be like of course it does they have to fight
Fight back
Because we know even Alex Jones thinks the Jewish Mafia was involved in the Holocaust
Anyway
They were the Raptors and play in North Korea
But guess what
They're also involve
Another
Very dramatic nuclear
Incident
We talked about the Cuban Missile Crisis
He said the Cuban Missile Crisis
I just was not about a Russia
UFO
Us
Stand-off with missiles
3/3 nukes that went off
In outer space related
He said the Cuban Missile
Crisis involved
A fight with Anita race
And the Kennedy was well aware of this
So that's why.
History
Appears to me to be
Rewritten
Clarify
So I think
It would be
To delve into that
Closest Safeway
Corroboration
I bet you can't find some corroboration because your version of corroboration is
Crazy people talking
Corroborate that
It'll be great I'll corroborate
Like my favorite thing
About her versus
Is that
Alex wouldn't
This is bendy
Declassified
And she's just like wolves
Yeah nobody knows about
Yeah like it's not busy
It doesn't matter if it's the classified or not
It's all happening around
Information comes from is so f****** Beyond
Classification
It's coming from come from is Mark rich
Or these others
People who have undergone
Traumatic
That experience
Calling them
I know this is a lot of notice
People are mentally
They're sympathetic Yahoo
You don't like all of this stuff
Like it's hard to say what is I'm not going to
Normal
Something that
Has happened within their their brain can
That is fuckshit up
Yeah like glued them from being happy or set like this isn't an emotional
Allstate this is just something within the way that they are brain
Process
What is the world's most of them at least at this point mark Richard
That's not what
For them
If white supremacist jurors would just turn their Supremacy
The angle towards rap
Could never stay that way
Who knows what
Other things
These people believe that aren't in the
Because we know that
Like
F****** members named Robert David Steele
He believes that zionists are attacking
Bring him all over the place come on about a secret program
In his beliefs are
The Jews around the world and they're trying to attack me because I know the truth
I bet a lot of these other people who are on here have similar
Awful
Just aren't being
Are because the interview is about spider being nombre
They don't need to talk about how like
Also
Blacks don't deserve
I mean
Wizard
This is good there is also a certain amount of all of this is allegorical
Race pace
Fear and Hate
Like I mean
You can believe it in spider leadership
Spider l
You can believe it all of that but ultimately with that guy
Get back to you
This is not white people's fault
This is not
This is all done by other people and we don't have to
Any responsibility for our own Acts
Chanel the flip side of it is actually fairly interesting is there when he's talking about North Korea
He's saying it's not North Korea's fault right
They're just working with the wrong so to some extent
Unifying of humanity
Right we are all but the playthings of alien races
A lot of ways it's just
It's
Is lame in a fun way
Aries
It's more fun than not to
To blame aliens for North Korea then
And insane
Religious dictatorship
Theocracy built around a god
It's probably less scary because you get to a point where I like
You can't really be scared of giant
Malevolent alien races
There's just nothing you can do about
You know what I mean
Yeah that is kind of
And in many ways like there's not going let Raptors
That's what I said
There's not a whole lot you can really do about Kim Jong-un yourself either
But he's still human
Humanized
The threat
It allows you to sort of be
Worried about it
It takes you out of the game
Criticism of Alex Jones
People live
Think is really real
Super Bowl
Is
By creating like this giant globalist
Cabal that it has their fingers and everything
Are controlling stuff
You do is you breed power
Audien
Yeah because you can scream all you want but the end of the day all he's trying to do is get you to give him money
So he can continue to fight the global x-ray
By screaming and having you give him more money
It's a self-perpetuating cycle
Whereas
Do you know it just like we create terrorism in terrorism
So we can spend
More money Fighting by the way
Military
We can't have college we can't have him
God dammit if we don't need to spend another 200 f****** billion dollars on goddamn
R700 billion-dollar f****** budget
Them Jesus Christ I like you
Why are you doing this
Because it's politically toxic not to
What are the big criticisms against
Bernie is always been
What is foreign policy
What is bulshit
And he came out and was like
America's foreign policy is b*******
UK
Who are you Ron Paul
But
What I'm getting at I think
Is Alex Jones really believed in the global
I really wanted to
Encourages audience
You would actually
Pinpoint
Specific Acts
Edible things
The people can do
That would help
His fight against
Globalist
Instead they're all
Child murdering pedophile cultist
Members
It's a spiritual Battle Ground is nothing you can do to
Yeah I mean that's that that would be pathetic if you saw that on the left maybe you do
Dude I just don't know who that person is
But generally when I listen to things
End of the day is that
Isn't it
Democrats and Republicans are not
Enter
As a concept
Did I find them
Tiresome
I think
More
I think Progressive
Conservative are much more applicable
Cuz they're not not the end not not
Sure
I think I think that's true also but there's like they're not parties
So it's not something that you sign up to be a part of it
It's just the orientation of your beliefs
Yeah do you want to
To move forward or do you want to try and make
Maintain a false
I think those are the truth
Those are the true parties
Yeah but there's no membership at any of them
Let's go back to rappers
So in this next clip
I think I think ultimately my
My analysis
List of all of this
This is all about removing
Personal responsibility
For Mark Richards cuz he murdered again for all of us
Listen all of this
We can't
We can't comprehend
The
Total and
And just
World shattering evil that is within every
The potential search
So and so they create all of this stuff about how Alex
Narratives
About like
Social indoctrination
Should really work
Towards like
Hey you might
I hate black people
That's okay
Because brainwashed by the globalist
It's not you right
Right
It's totally fine
The functionality of it is
Give you powerlessness
Except with a twitch
Serve his immediate interest
Yeah and to make you feel better about bigotry
That already lives within you
Both of those are profound
Relate the personal responsibility
Do you have
Big
Your book Hoot
Address though
Look at them
I'm trying
You can't I do want to do something
With our show that is
As you would say a
A fight against that s*** on the Koch brothers lawn you can order policy walk in
Organized organized
And f****** there's
There's a real enemy and it's the oligarchs who control the government
Real Adam gets a little bit bigger before we try and like
We need to organize into a political action committee
But there should be like we should try and explore possibilities like
Action thing
Or action items
Something
But if you are if you do have bigoted tendencies
You are listening to this show
Don't kill yourself yet
Why it is that you feel differently about different people
Zack Snyder
Feel that all the time like am I
It is one of those things
You know
Treatment towards women
All of these different things and I constantly re-examine every opinion like
I've had like I just
And
Yeah
I was a dick I'm it was fantastic
It was it was
Funny it's so good
I had to I had to think about it because I tweeted straight from
Frederick from my dick Behavior massage but I had to think about that
Mediately after like I had to go through all of my thought process there
And trying to figure out what
A marine or somebody who could
F****** straight-up murder made like salute
With much thought process at all
No but it was fun
I got Talking Dead version of
Personal
Look I'm not trying to brag
Look
But that's that's something that I do want to make sure that I think about cons
Why am I treating people the way I am
And is this influence
Buy a bias that I have forced that's a good thing I'm not sure about thinking about it
You don't need to be mean it's not like it's not like every single conversation I have overwhelmed
Something to keep an eye on anyway
I had a point but I'm coming from
Raptors are real
Raptors I've been a part of the world for a long time
Actually I asked him about the dragons
In the Middle Ages
That are written about
Of course in the mythology
Having to do with knights
And all of that
And I was curious
What
Were
Like which species
Are draco's and
Raptor
Is that were actually
Dragons
They were fighting in the
Apparently
Of course England has
Alarm history
Surrounding the
Dragon
Fastest China
It isn't
Variance
Fascinating
And Raptors
Let's go with Chinese dragon
We're going to call those Raptors
Draco's
Stricker's don't necessarily fly though either a part of the
Suggested
Sure
It's fascinating to me
Like
What won't she believe
That is a real
We should try and repackage ourselves as like whistle
Blowers
And see if shoot interview
I feel like I could send it
I couldn't roll with it
I wouldn't
Calendar
Item for today
The outro of interview and this is
Revivalists
So that covers everything I believe and I want to thank everyone for watching
And for being interested in
What Mark Richards has
His wife Joanna.
Circuit she has a website
And I
I will put the URL
Here
Encourage you to
Purchase used
Written materials
He writes
Constantly
And is
The prolific writer
He's got lots of information out there
In written form
And he's always riding more
So I
He is a very
Principal Darren
Fascinating
Individual
And highly intelligent
And conducts himself
As a military officer at all times
So thanks again for you
Watching a
And for your support
You know who made a lot of crazy people
Conduct themselves
Military people
Sheriff
I really think I mean
At the end of the day it is harmless
And it is just
Fun narratives being pushed out
But at the same time
She's legitimizing a murder
Murderer con man is trying to make money
It's his wife who's making money
He's probably not done that access to a lot of that I'm fine with her having a career out of it
She's not getting out of prison anytime soon
So
I'm very conflicted though because she's like
He's a principled man
That's where the stuff at
I don't I don't like the reclaiming of humanity
Makes me a little uncomfortable
Coming to reclaim it he would have to have had it
Yeah
Probably
The thought though
Switching gears into alright we're done with his dragon
Raptor bulshit for now
Not until there's another update
Richard the 8th visit to
I like somehow we're like
We're all Mark Richards when we go to Project Camelot
She doesn't post things all that often
She was just at like some
Seminar
Speech in Ireland checking on that
But
Supposed
Sings All That
Lake
It's a big deal we got a new update
But these buttons
Repeat it out a picture of them
They're amazing
And if you would like one of these buttons
Here's my proposal
I need
For you
The Listener
The walk
Instead of donating money
To get one of these buttons
I propose
That you send us
Knowledge fight at gmail.com
Argue Malik
Proof
But you have posted a link
To our website
On a Red Bull or a message board somewhere
Something like that
You Craven Opera
Why not though
Text help get the word out send that send a link somewhere give a recommendation
Not on Facebook necessarily
Halo
I don't know
Wherever so message board connectivity don't go to one of these dead Reddit
Puerto Rico
Or if you have
Absolutely I don't care about charity
Northport that there's so many things and
You know as much as
As much as we're hoping to turn this
Well as
Cuz you want to
No full-time
Except every night there's also a lot more s*** going on
Yeah that was
Protest
Go to if you s*** on the Koch brothers lawn I will send you 10 button will make a shirt for you
Ritual shirt Hillary for prison
Hillary for mj-12
Wow
It's not real
Butter
If you
Send us an email address
Some sort of
Acknowledgement that you donated to one of these islands
Puerto Rico is not the only one that needs help me get going
F***
Proofing posted a link to us on a RAV4
If you antagonize The Alex Jones fans on the at Infowars
Reddit Infowars
Something like that will send you one of these new buttons also send
Your address
Promise not to Doc's you that is alright
Return to me
And I lost the address
So
Send an email if you haven't gotten the butt
Cuz I was a parent
Only $0.20
Okay
Understand
Emailed us about the buttons again gotten at 2
Pretty much all of them and I got one
Bailing is hard
Toxic male
What's our website
No don't reply
Where can you find us
Facebook
Where else can you find can you find us
On the street
If you can find us on the street out there chopping should upset tripping with rafters
Are we Raptors
One more
Sing for you Sam
Jordan
Does boba
That's ridiculous
Why are you
Pretending I'm Mark Richards.
Alright
One more
If
They're like
Bet Jon rappoport
Doesn't have denture
Okay
I think
Here's here's a good theory
It's quite possible
That he doesn't have human
What I think that it's
Within the realm of Pop
Possibility
That he
And Raptors are actually evil than that mean
You know fuckyourself Jon rappoport not going to kill me for chocolate
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color