Alex
In color
Sit around and talk a little bit about Alex Jones
Like a
Oh man like a
Turn like a hard turn
Alex Jones going over
V
What I'm going to call
Not totally correct about this
But I'm going to call this the end of our 2015 investor
Combination of discoveries and
Complete and utter exhaustion
It's not exhausting I could I could do this forever
Quite frankly that's if you really look at it the
Well we've been doing this investigation
20th installment
What is installment of his investigation we've learned so much about Alex Jones that has nothing to do
Who is Donald Trump
We've learned tons about his Civil War revisionism
He's learned a whole last episode of Ken Burns
In honor of the Vietnam documentary
Yeah
So nothing the thing is we we learned at under we never expected to learn we didn't expect
Defeat all of the pro-russia sentiments we didn't
To see him be debriefed
Food Services little things that we pick up along the way in
And so I am going to I believe
I think they're what comes next after
I think until the end of
We need to keep investigating
To try and figure out when he loses his mind
He still hasn't quite lost his mind
And I think
That comes
Probably pretty
Him started to scream all the time all the
Renaissance
2.0 until the end of the year
The investigation will take a horse to Pivot
And I want to go over starting in January
The entire year of like
Okay just jump back
Further in time or even farther back if I can figure it out
And then try and cover the month
Of January and January
Month of February
Alex Jones
Your optimism on us reaching January
Is delightful
It's
Yeah I know
We'll see anyway that's that that's where my plan will see what happens
I have another plan though and that is
To give a shout out to our new donator what's going on
I'm a policy wonk
Very thrilled to have it is delightful to hear
Absolutely
Burlington back on Henry V8
I don't I don't believe that's the same
I don't know what you doing I don't know what to do in man
Thank you I really appreciate it means a lot to have you back on board
Before we get in today
Installment
Primarily
3 days
In December of 2015
We have December 16th
And then December 29th
Which is an absurd
Set piece
Okay but another one of those episode where Alex Jones is clearly doing drama December 30th
I think is RI closures
Before we do that
Here's an out-of-context
Drop of Alex Jones
Adolf Hitler Joseph Stalin
Photos
Hayward complete stop
Not talkin about a football offensive line
They were just f******
Stud that's
Not great in your Blind Side do you know why cuz he made people blind
That's what Stalin did Hitler
Hitler you got to have front-and-center he's got to distract you got to take all of those people
Mouth Mouse quarterback in that shed
You see Hitler that guy's got cardio for days
Daikin just go
No that's crazy
Not great
The globalists I get other people to do their bidding
The badass
I don't like that
No
Making really where was it
Right I don't think you want to associate that with
Positive in that camp as well
Definitely motivated in more billionaires
Alex is really dumb
Is what I'm getting
I think it's
Always
Andy is a boner for strong-armed authoritarian dictators
Absolutely
Write whenever he talks about how much you love these dudes like or that they're studs
He'll just walk it back like
Right now it's the same
He wants authoritarian rule
But it has to be
On his term
That's what we get to know he has no idea that it will in turn
A hundred percent
You know what one history authoritarian regimes are not loyal to their propaganda
Get killed every f***
You go off the reservation a little bit
I don't understand how stupid these
It's pretty crazy
Fighting against the very thing that they're pushing themselves towards
Human beings at our psychology is
Spectacular
And it's going to get us all killed
So that's nice
It's very depressing
My favorite extinction-level event was the Busta Rhymes album
Ele extinction level event
Great as the great song with Mystikal is they getting rowdy with us if you want with us
Again Busta Rhymes head that song where they saw who could rap
Faster
Nelly
Get to the episode
Start today on December
16th 2015
On December 15th
There was the final
Republican debate
And here's Alex opening up the show giving little bit of assess
Congrats
Was on
Revealing
It was one of these
Are completely unstable
Launching giant Wars
Let's be clear
Really wrong
On so many all the levels
They did and this isn't even the conversation where he calls them studs
He brings them up
Not good
Other countries
Superpowers aircraft
What is John Kasich
In the
And the debate says that we need
The punch Russia in the nose
Right
But he was speaking metaphorically and was he
What is argument was
The Weave let them get away with too much
And they're being uncheck
You who has an argument now
Considered a hindsight is interesting
And lamp
Really powerful information came out yesterday
Clemson
Doesn't play very many of us
It's interesting cuz he plays a number of them where they're like
Trump
Just sort of
Going locking horn
I want to become such a sad thing to remember
Never had a chance
No but you know what's really fascinating what
Jeb was getting like
Applause break
Like crazy when he was attacking
Trump
Like you told Trump is
You can't insult your way to the present
The place went crazy
Everyone was like
They were a man
Yeah well I mean
Trump hadn't yet seated all of his public appearances with his own
There was part of it and then
Think also there was a part that was like
I think they were
Cheering for blood
Other close to cheering for Jack absolutely
But the Optics
The clips it really looks like everyone is into
Kind of is weird
What is narrative
A f******
Horrific nightmare
Idiot yelling bulshit at each other
And then
Jeb Bush wants to raise taxes on poor people now that's not true you do
So In that clip even he said that
Which is what we would expect from him
Paul
No but I don't remember rampaul evershine
I will give you a spoiler alert the only reason that he says the Rand Paul shine
Is because
Kasich
Maru the other one was but someone else in the debate said negative things about Russia
And Rand Paul said
If you want to elect
Someone will bring us to World War 3
Right but he was just basically saying hey let's not attack Russia
That's the only positive thing he has to think about Rams
Appearance of mr. that's so suspiciously
Is there a what happened
I think it's going to blow your mind everything that we already know
December 29th
Might be one of the craziest things I've ever heard
Alex Jones
Thanks the Donald Trump
Spectacularly
Cuz you got a Big Sur
Queen
Trump
11 Troost
Jailbay
And I told you that
So bored
Let me tell you something
Last night
Disguise
Now he's for real though
I went to the real f****** simple
Easy easiest person to f****** fool
Granted apparently it took a while
But I can't imagine
How easy this was 9-11 truther
I love it
VSCO
You get the sense that like
Someone around Trump was probably just like
Hey throw a couple bone Alex Jones will f****** love you
You just a couple crazy things
I kind of believe those crazy things
Exchange
Whenever Jeb Bush looks at him
Will
I don't think he ever finds
People hate mango
Because they own the fraudulent delegate
She will get the nomination
They are bragging
About this
Another night and that did not happen
Is that kind of cute
Although we were so we were
Well it took was one bad video to destroy Jab
I mean he wasn't doing great before that but that was a death blood
That's what killed him
I mean he wasn't doing good before that it was like
So sad
It made me feel awful for a war criminal
Watching the coverage of it
And hearing
Jeb Bush say like
This guy isn't serious
Right like talking about
This is not a serious proposal he's talking about banning immigrants from our country that's just not that's not something
He has no policy experience experience from television what are we doing
Man I hate you but
You're the hero here
Yo it's just like what the f*** it's a very conflicted headspace to be in to be like I don't like any of these guys
Batman amazing that more people remember that media is
It's f******
Off the rail
Like the whole reason that they wanted him to stay in his because he was great for Ratings like
Les moonves from CBS said
But he's good for us
Billionaires are monsters people who don't care about how many people died in the f***
Don't f****** give a s***
About 3.6 million Americans in Puerto Rico
Which American
Because we spent 800 billion dollars on her f****** military
A little bit of an Elsa
Inspire no
Instead
It's f****** let
People
Yeah
Fear seventeen
I mean
Just because it's like
Everyone else
Look I'm not uncaring
Support all sorts of
Relief efforts and all that stuff but
Quite frankly I think there are tons of organizations that do a much better job of covering
So I don't want to
Who's Trump
Commuting with now it's he's a f****** f****** killing people
Direct murder
And I hope
Mike it's my dream do you want to know my dream
What
I imagine that
The FBI
Somebody working for it realizes
And they go crazy
And then they go assassin
That's my dream scenario
That's problematic for us
I mean
Deer now playing into Alex Jones's hands
Enjoying a little bit of a quick second to have an on-air show me
Believe that everybody who's against him wants to or fantasizes about Trump being killed
Optically
Where Alex
Defined our show
I've been here that
That reaffirms his belief
You understand what does it matter
Lie about it anyway
I don't like the idea of you
Are you fantasizing
Man so many people I fantasize about being assassinated I honestly think that's a little bit negative
I know you think it's a little bit negative for me to fantasize about somebody holding a beheaded Koch brothers
Aloft on top of a mountain screaming
I have control
Sometimes
He's got to do what you got to do
Alright
The Dollar Tree does not stuck-up
As a show we don't
We don't fully support
Views that are being a Sprouts
I don't want it I don't want to say that I don't want
I want Trump gone
Not killed but gone I want him out of powers
You f****** up ever
But
I don't know what's wrong I want them all
And they're all they're all thieves
They've all stolen so much money from us
They've all they've all contributed to the deaths of
Thousands of people
That's bad
So
Let's get back to this debate coverage
I'm pretty positive
We also started
The Show by saying
Rampaul shine
I think I've isolated the
The exact makeup
Actually
That could be what he's talking about
Took over and Alex
His mind
Alex flips
Script
Grandpa
I think it's right
A 1,000 people in Syria and Libya
Hillary
Revolutionary sex that's why I'm
O'Reilly
Just like you said
And I'll just jump on this
Wolfpack
Shark
Attack that is so sexy
And no
I know you're a gentleman
Russia
Your father I know full well
You got working for you do that
Your father
George Washington material interview
You know that and your dad brought you
Little boy
More fun to talk about Jeb Bush
But I mean I think there
The cracks are showing he's
He's cracking on on Rainbow
Absolutely stupid Trump
Safeties defending Trump as a
Supposed to Rand Paul
Supporting
I would rather defend Trump
Play Eli Kyu calling him crazy that's what people say about you that's a big
That's big
Yeah he even said Ted Cruz is smart witch
Something that you only say
Whenever your guys
Failing away that you didn't know it's off
The extent that
He flips on
Cruise once it comes down to just Cruisin Trump
That's fair I lost my eyes red that's the equivalent of a Mickey
Yeah first kernels of Alex Jones
Insanity
Start to emerge
I think you'll see where it is
This is a n a
He has kit Daniels one of his reporters
I have to talk about what he thought about
Debate
Do we see one of these
Edwards make it probably first appearance
Debate
Is a microcosm
I mean
What song is focused on the fact that he's pulling the Overton window
Towards Liberty
Researching history
Since the Revolutionary War
We see a populist like Trump showing up
Sorry
62.0 and acts
That's fair
That is sort of a catchphrase that he has in terms of like
The answer to 1984 1776 Morgan yelled at Embassy
1876 will commence
If you try and take our guns
He does bring up 7
1376 a lot
But this is the first time I've heard him reference
Trump
In relation to 7
Of course and that's big
That's monumental
Right knowing what we know about the future
Yogi's like
He is the new George Washington
Is the beginning of that narrative starting
Oh I should also say
That
Trump was on
Alex Jones Show before this
Yes
He came on at the beginning of
December I believe it was December 4th
And the reason I don't have any clips of that
Is because we've all everyone's heard the eclipse
The big one
Did people attack him with it or like
Trump saying your record is spotless
Yeah yeah
The reason that I don't include a lot of that
Is because
That episode is really just strfkr like Alex being like
Believe Trump would be on my show
Worship heavy
Call celebrity
Bright and then
2 days later on December 3rd
He's like I don't know about drop I still love Rand Paul
We thought would absolutely
I think it doesn't subtle ways I think his mentality start
Lean much more towards Trump when he realizes like
Come on my show all these crazy things that I love
But I don't think until after this debate
It really crystallizes and I think a large part of that is
Is because
Like
Bringing up 9/11 truth
Right he's yelling at age
Wichita
It is fun he's living vicariously through
It is and I think he's just gotten to a point where the
It's like why am I fighting this
Rand Paul is crazy
He's not going to do what I wanted to do track his heart is pure
He's a loser in a rom-com
Yep he's been a long relationship Grandpa was very reliable
Says a lot of the things he's liked but guess what there's this flashy new lady now
New York
Juggle both her job and running for president
Now gives off all of her responsibilities to her kids and it's time for her to f***
And who's there
Whatever happened
Alex Jones now if this is a traditional romantic comedy which I like this picture
The third act has to be Alex coming back to Rand Paul and realizing he was
By the big-city guy
I should have never left Kentucky
Trump is impeached
Then we go right back to R & B Jones for not seeing through it until it
I was too late now I don't
Think so I think Grant got a big heart
Is dumb
Psyquel
Do you really want to be sidled up with the high-profile Russia connected guy who ended up winning the presidency is
Probably going to get indicted for it
Or do you want to go with the down-home
Pure libertarian guy who you love who's also
Suspiciously connected with Russia
Which one do you want
You go with me
The under-the-radar guy
I think that's the smart money
Also I'm bringing up Russia because I just whenever he says like
The libertarian there's something
Things Trump says that I don't
Libertarian and conservative and Republican
All these people really want is to watch whatever liberals
Wanted or did
Liberal tears
They don't have any ideology liberals
Trump
Movement with you want to call it alright alt-lite any of that nonsense
Yes certainly
Organization
So much
To the internet
Trolls of the world
Is because of that
It's not about productivity it's not building up anything it is just about this
Rule destruction those online communities are really into
They're into
Needling and and hurting people
They don't care about games or
Ethics
Gamer journalism
F*** is that I don't know they care about destroying some young woman's life
Because it gives them a sense of satisfaction
Not just one
Oh yeah
Russia came up
When my Alaska
For the ramp there
His little thing about Russia
Incredible
And this is the most powerful
Because of this statement
Respond
Calmly great lovingly
Bloodthirsty piranha Behavior
So they go into like
The clips OKC
Chris Christie saying that
Blood
Oh yeah Chris Christie's things that if
They shoot down
Or if they fly in no-fly zone
Cuz that's what a no-fly zone is
Who's against no-fly zones
Just a way to start a war with Russia
I don't want to unpack that
That very well might be the case
At the same time these aren't like bloodthirsty cries for war they're more like
We need to have some sort of reasonable pushback
In the Ukraine whenever they just go
Yeah
A lot of other
That's a lot of other pretty much the entire Soviet Bloc
Yeah
I think
What this demonstrates
Is that he's turning on a little bit
Inasmuch as he's lashing out at him
In favor of threat
Also
Write Rand Paul has won this debate I think it's meaningless
You pushing back against
Criticisms of Russia
Okay great
The only run the who win who won the Republican debate
Was the America
Absolutely I think we got everything we wanted at
So other than
That I mean there is there's a number of things that come up in the in the meantime
Before we jump
But a lot of it is really not even worth covering it's also repetitive
There's all just nonsense like pro-russia sentiment
Muslim sentiment
Anti-immigrant stuff
Hillary bashing
It's just
It's log
From the middle of November where we last left off on our investigation
December 6th
And even
Up until December
A lot of it
It is a little bit more exciting
Hello more entertaining
And the November 5th November to December
Braves
It's the third period of this first playoff game I guess
You understand
It's just
I could we could spend the next six months talking about how lord monckton loves Russia to
Or you know these various other things that I've discovered along the way
Well I've I'm sure that he wasn't invited
Paris
What's
But I remember Alex
Alex Eclipse only remember the first time he tells me something
Edline
So
We jump to the 29th
And I have a series about what happened on this
I don't know how to lay this out
So I'm just going to go ahead and play this first clip
I will confuse that advent calendar went all the way to the 29th
That's not it
That's not the confusion
There's a big narrative going on
This is going to be very difficult for us to untwine
Okay but I have a fever
With a wide-scale across-the-board attempted takeover Infowars a different accounts
So I'm going to just come out and tell you I don't
Attack happened there is
A hack attack
But also can happen in a hockey game
Right right
As opposed to a basketball game which would be a shack attack
I don't believe this attack happen
I think it's
Details a little bit
Evidence
The only evidence
Is an article that went up on infowars.com alright was later taken it is
They got some
Combat intelligence
Wroetoshaw article
And this entire hacking narrative
Is b*******
To use as
Cover
And to validate the gas that they have coming up
Which will play out throughout the next couple clips
But I think Occam's razor tells me that's the case because the next day off
Does not bring up this happy at all
He just moves along and Hillary sucks
Behave at later on to show how much he's being attacked all the time it's like
Well yeah he's going to get into some stuff back
And it's troubling
Understood
Across-the-board
From our Facebook account
Twitter account
And we are writing stories about it right now
Comware one of the fax was successful
11 minutes
And of course I had changed
Account
We'll put Paul Watson Twitter account
Prison Planet
Islamic
States currently
On-the-ground yesterday
Watch your six
I basically already put my finger
What's going on here
So
Because it was very simple
PJ Watson tweeted out some b******* and they were like
We got to pretend that he got hacked with Watson put out was about erdewan
It was about
There was a UFO
Iambadder Dhawan was taking shelter at us
Air Base
Participated in the fake narrative that put out so that he could jail at arrest
All of his
That might not be something that you want
On your own belt
You might want to pretend
Now
Actually I don't know if these dates match
Like I don't know what the date is for like when the coup happen
Fake to in
Interesting
Fulfill some
People still believe that was a real coup like
If you see every action mode on Facebook doesn't match up that was 26
I was in July of 20
This is a different
This is a different thing that he's evoking but
Dicey
Yeah this seems like something Paul Joseph Watson
Might have gotten the bad tip on
As We Know
His DMS are wide open
At least they were at this point
And we have repeated evidence of him just taking anonymous source information
Then writing about it on Infowars about 3 million immigrants
Absolutely
Also from my Twitter
True Souls there
I think
What we're seeing here is
A little bit of ice covering
Let's get this because Alex needs to make this deliciously convoluted
Article
A bunch of others
Operation
Calling themselves the Syrian electronic Army
Gmail
Thousand colleges with 2000 plus
Syrian electronic Army
That's not what happened
In concert American Patriot
Do you see what's going on here
So he's acknowledging
Russia
Attacking the American cover
But not the Patriots
G
Is
With Russians carrying out massive heckenkamp
And using said influence information
To influence
A couple of those things that you bring up War propaganda
Totally on board with them
Using
Fake information
Witches witches fascinating because
That means that he believes in global
Cooperation organization to root out the globalist
Yeah
Interesting
There's a lot of there's a lot of
I've never seen that before from Alex this is incredibly weird
Just
It belies so many other things
He claims now which is like
Irisher doesn't
A bill when you said that
Legoland stuff is it's crazy
The Syrian electronic Army
Are you now saying that
You
Is that what you're saying what is the case
I don't know
Do you think
That is that is interesting
That's so many patriots
Of America
Freely Russia
Absolutely happy with another country taking us over
It's a very fascinating patriotic Arkansas
Well it's just because I mean
I'm
Starting to believe
That about 90%
Of the people who think that way
Think exactly the same
Yeah they think
Our country is taken over by
Right and that Russia is the are the only people who could say because
It's already
Anatol
Cockamamie line of b*******
Most likely put out by
It's very interesting
Oligarchs alone is
Crazy
Maybe he kicked out the other oligarchs
Play balls
But I'll be goddamn she doesn't have a whole network of his owner
Not know that
He just doesn't like the liberal order of the world doesn't like the idea that freedom is come
The shape that it has
In society because they're f****** weird to him
Yeah or Christian or Christian or
Male shoe against the Catholic Church
Do you want them to feel the exact role that works for men
Dino there's a lot to unpack in that word it's accurate but it
It's more you need to play the role that we need you to play
I guess that is subjugation but it's
Booked
Perfect order
And he knows
That the only way to get that is by bringing liberty and prosperity
Riordan Salisbury nasm
Could be that those two things are capable of freedom is oftentimes chaos
I suggested that last clip like the Russians
Is the Russians hacking what's the narrative
And II
Very high-level chess
Definitely not
We knew at
That we can get the military informed of this
Christian areas of Syria over Al-Qaeda save everybody
Not okay
As the Syrian electronic Army continued
Infowars.com
Posted
Skype
Twitter account
Response to bet
Out of Turkey
Infowars
Electronic
Which hasn't happened yet
Okay that is
I believe
So
Right
They just
Did Infowars know that was the Syrian electronic Army who he knows is Russia
So the Syrian electronic Army
They hacked
BNN what-have-you in posted Infowars article in an attempt to spread the truth
So they were on the good side of things that was wrong that was Russia nowcast
Okay this is a group trying to pretend to be the Syrian electronic Army but it's actually
Affiliated
Right but doesn't he not know that so many of his boys have
Problem in a few clips
That is going to snow again
Not Al Qaeda
Productivity
Do not work without absolute I think that's true
I agree with him there
When he's right he's right you got to give him that looking at you guy whose name I forgot that was in the news for a long time
What's that guy's name
Know that guy that white guy who went over and joined outside and his big media sensation for a little while
Remember that guy's name whatever happened to that guy probably alive
Alex Jones discusses the actual article that was put on Infowars by this alleged
Which again I don't believe
US Airways
That was
Someone
I began running around
So that we can survive attack
By the way I'm going to Facebook
Great I think he's talking about a Hydra not whack-a-mole
Totally
X
Prairie espresso
Find any loses track of metaphors a lot but
Like
This doesn't
Strike me first of all all outside of the normal for something they would post
Journalistic standards are in the toilet
And have been for
Nayan two-decade
Sanders at 1
The idea that they were supposed to be like oh
S***
Someone sucking with us
Secondarily
The idea that I was running around trying to sort this out investigating a pre-show then get on air
And be calm like this
He's not yelling
He's not making threats
This isn't how Alex Jones behave
If you had a narrative in place
And he knew nothing was going on
This is this is bulshit this is a Man actor
You would not
It's easy to figure out if it's an actual Infowars article
Read it
Sound the same but they're all written by the same voice
No there
That's not true couple Riders who don't know how to read we find out what
Defensive like
We haven't distributed across multiple platforms
To protect against
The tax rate
We are expanding across all of those who we have to go check them you take down one at 5
Take down 550 pop up
He's saying that he has a lot of tentacles again
That's what he saying he's one of our tentacles five of our technical pop-up attacks
That got that backwards
That is very dumb we get to learn what exactly happened with this hack what was what was taken in
Downtown Augusta
He forgot it at bottom
The Flash
Show they clearly.
Someone account
It had
.
Triple security company show
Secure and safe
Riverdale
I've been saying that they're really the last 20 years
I just don't I don't
Believe that
At all
It's very convenient that like
There's a high level
Super
Organized
Cyber-attack going up against him
And everything important
It it doesn't
Cuz like if I was putting up a fake article right that's the worst hacking out
In history
Real hackers can get into Banks
It's not like older to Triple protected by a bank agency
It's not it is just doesn't ring true it smells real bad
In terms of like
The truth test
So
I told you that I think that he's lying because they put up a bad article and they want
To pretend that they didn't
Conspiracy theory
Okay
Was
Pjw
Guessing really well and make
Picking up a narrative
That
Turkey was eventually going to have a fake coup
Get the idea
I don't know. Maybe it's
What was that that was the fake propaganda baby it's neither
I don't know or both I don't know I can't unpack that although I do like it is
Conspiracy theory
Because must be in
In contact with manafort and those guys in Flint probably
Maybe put it out and they were like
You got to take that down I would like I would like for you to hold onto this
Conspiracy theory especially the direction you're going
Four clips
Cuz we are going to get to
My little bit
Okay it's crucial
I got to follow the money
No go to follow till I
Back
Bead hack Eli
So what
I think they're covering to this story but then they also want to add gravitas
To a guest that they're having
Because coincidentally if he's a cybersecurity expert
Whistleblower
Who is
Allegedly
He works
On getting people out of Isis
In Turkey
Which is very convenient for Alex's theory about who is
Fake hacking
It's weird that he came on to talk about sex scandals in the Vatican
Not in a wig
But
Adorable
They end up coming on over Skype
And it's terrible
Skype connection doesn't work
But he also has the guy who hooked Alex with his Turkish
Whistleblower guy named Pat Riley
Nope
What does hair
Is guinan Kirsten I landed LeBron
Now I'm going to Lantern
It's a guy named Kevin Booth
And we don't know who that guy is yet
And I will find
Are on Showtime
And on HBO
Networks
Shop
Documentary filmmaker
HGTV
Producer
Studio
So
The reason that I am bringing this up
More evidence that this whole hacks thing is
Is fake
Is if we work all about
Let's say 5 6 months ago
We did an episode where Alex Jones
Clearly fake
A GoFundMe
Being taken down
The song man Sawyer
And his attempt to out pedophile
Or whatever their plan was
They put on a piece of Theatre wherein they knew they needed to a up the real
Holiday Inn quote
Of what they're doing and so they have the external stimulus
Which is
They put up something on gofundme.com new would be taken down
Like what
Stride Rite
We went through the terms of service and filed at least 6 in fraction
At the very least it was extra vigilante
GoFundMe does not usually support like you can't put up a GoFundMe for getting together a poppy to Roundup them Barman
They
They have a tradition of doing
And I think
Especially because we see no evidence of it and Alex drops the narrative
Pretty f****** fast
I think this hack
Is fake
In order to be like we're having this Turkish whistleblower on and they want to take us down
Because we're having
This is too dangerous and the Turkish guy is hiding
From isisaurus
From Turkey a f****** everybody
You hiding out here in the United States
Pencil that's fine
But here's the next
There's the next clip where Alex
Talked about how under attack he is in general
Realization and lies
Local papers
So
I want to tell you what I think is happen
For twenty years
There was a tacit agreement
In the world
It was an uneasy truce
Between Alex Jones underworld
And that was
Stay in your lane
And some people will make fun of you
Bubble leave you alone
There was just a thing
Scream about
Conspiracies
Scream about chimeras all you want right
Fear fun
Some people will enjoy you and they'll be led down the wrong path
But we don't care
Whatever
A couple months
Before this point at the end of 2015
Alex Jones
Start
Get far more active
Interim
Of politics
Then he has been in the
He screamed about politicians in the past
But there's never been
What appears to be
Coordination
Between him and people involved with a presidential candidate
Well there's that too
But I think it's more like
People started to
See
Like Rodger Stone coming on his show
People like
All right we got it
Look at the wackamole metaphor
We got to knock this one down
With people start
Situation
The infinite whack-a-mole did workout someone
Put back I think it's just that he breached
The social contract that you may be unaware of it is like
Just just don't
Just f****** stay over there and we're fine he started to get involved in the real world
We got to pay attention to you and we're going to make fun of you
Right
We didn't want to be doing this Alex let me stay over there
You were fine over here and we got to we got to do something been spouting
Borderline to over racist
Bulshit your worldviews clearly based on Let It Go
We've allowed you to make a lot of money just
Just stay over there and now
He's creeping in
Creepin in
Starting to affect things that people are like
Shut it down
That's not being a
Text message Sara Lee
That's just like you're out of your depth
And unfortunately
Yeah unfortunately I don't think people did it the right way
And it's lets us to where we are now but
Popped up and then form
There was such a better way
There's a better way to defuse Alex
I think missed our opportunity we might be able to
Some Headway but back then it would have been
Bearded man here's the clip where we find out it is very similar
How we're dealing with every single time I set up a few interrupt me
Conversationally little frustrating
Prefer
It's that there are pros and cons to eat outside
I'm just saying it
It's interesting that the way we deal with the disinformation
Is the exact same way we're dealing with
Hurricanes and earthquakes
Texaco in all of this stuff is
We could have
We could have gotten there earlier
We could have prepared for all of the
We all knew that this type of ship was going to go down
And instead we're waiting until the
Catastrophe hits
And now we're trying to go back and
Actually do something about it when it's too late
Worth interrupting my deduction for sure Alex gets down to who he thinks
Again
Alex
8 who he thinks is behind the attack
His.
And it's wild
Welfare
Plus from
Taxpayers
Charter School
Islamic
Caliphate
Arnold School
High School
Is it connect
President of Turkey erdogan
Because
Because everyone
That's
That's amazing
Muzzles are always fighting come on
We get it you got crabs
So
Alex
On real shaky territory
Call Owen
Well
It's
Airgun
Did he just say that he is suing
Schools in
America
No that is that
Turkey
Erdewan
Is doing
Cuz
A caliphate
Which they're not
I mean I would assume
Live with that I have a lot of school
Established Charter
Schools
United States
And
Your ears yours if they would that that they say about them
The Islamic
Aspect of it
Play Darko New York Times
Pakistan Islam in their dormitory
And describe the Turkish schools as offering a gentler approach to Islam
They could help reduce the influence of extreme
However
Schools are not for Muslims alone
General curriculum for the network schools
Prescribes one hour of religious
Construction per week
Well in many countries
Schools do not offer any religious instruction at all
With the exception of a few
Schools abroad
And not in the United States
These Institution
Hardly be considered Islamic schools
Any strict
Considered illegal in the United States
I think
Without headlines
No there's a lot of
Also the ones that are in America is 100
20 of them
25 States
There's no formal networking of the
The schools
They're not even collected
Together they don't really even work together
So
Not formally
Not in not in the
Public eye but if you're going to
You activate those
That's bulshit but the bigger issue is
What's that
Mike Flynn General Flynn
Vallarta 18 extradite
Gulen
Exactly like what are you from
His clearance forms
Cute
Out of money
To try and do this because it would be illegal to extradite
He is the one who in 2016
Erdewan blames for the fake to that
Alex
Cultural revolution what's Alex doing
I think
He's giving him cover
And saying that
He's the bad guy
Christine I can't imagine why interesting
He loves them I think there's something Smith suspicious
Who has that
Power about how we are funding ice
Course
Because Mike Flynn
It's crazy
Crazy in the same way that Alex
This is really a big problem
The fact that he's blaming to pin the blame on this
On the gulen
People
The gulen
Organization
That's probably behind
Which I don't believe are real
That's f***** up
That's really f***** up
Very f*****-up
It is so tight into all of this s***
Yeah
He's so tied into it
How is it that we're getting an angle
Walking chimeras I know
We're not really getting to the bottom of it but we're seeing indications were getting a view
There are probably
Reno Paper Trails and
Much further Evidence
When you see Alex Jones is Almost
Like I hate
We're like
You really connect to this
Anti-bullying propaganda
A guy who's
Superpro Russia
You got
Trump
Hahaha
Pro ortolan
Pro Putin
It's like a Clearinghouse of all this s***
It's very bizarre and I do think that it's
F***** up that more people are
Deep dive
I think we should be doing a lot of this weird conservative propaganda
Diane
Quite frankly someone
Soros give me some goddamn money
Like I could do this
I can't do much deeper dive into this
If I had the f****** time I didn't have to go to work
But be that as it may that's a plate for another day
He brings in Kevin Booth
Who as we heard was that he's a filmmaker in
Worked with Bill Hicks wink wink
Formerly Kevin Federline
Wink wink
You worked with Bill Hicks
I get it
Link
He has a couple times
It's called Alex bill on the couch
I get it.
I get it I was going crazy I'm watching
It's hilarious
But the one
That is actually subtle
And fun
It's not subtle
Point of course not actually doing it but the point that it is
Rare and
Silly
Xavier
Comes in
Oh boy
This next clip
Bitconnect
A couple of dots
Accidentally
Do you would never pick up on if you weren't paying attention
It's troubling
Robert Steele helped us get in there Fleet or not
Outland kalugin
Umbrella
But I'm all these things connect and then Robert ended up getting us into the Russian Embassy
And so we've actually been meeting with
Bring the door inside
You know what that implies right there that end of the clip
Implies that Kevin Booth knows that he shouldn't come on to Infowars
Trout it implies some foreknowledge
But that is not what we do here
To make Putin look bad when in reality you can just look at
No the other thing people who don't understand what's going on with notice
Is that he says that Robert David Steele got him into the Russian Embassy
Must have connection
At the Russian Embassy who doesn't
That's
Troubling that we don't have connected Robert David Steele believes that the zionists are trying to diss
Destroy him and the globalist
That guy
Come on Alex Jones's show and now in present day in 2017 Alex fix
Might've been trying to
Set Alex up
Yeah of course with that Mars base stuff
That's that's the guy who connected Kevin Booth with the Russian Embassy
Wild
I mean that's
That's obvious
Now what's the Bulgarian umbrella
I don't particularly
But he didn't I mean like a MacGuffin in a James Bond movie
Maybe
It's probably
Assertive
Fish bass
Delicious got to go to the shop downtown
On the corner
Very dry
Clip we find out how Kevin Booth Matt his guests
He's bringing on to Alex
Guests coming
On a little bit later
Well I once again Ray Roberts
Professor I'm at yala he is recently had to flee the country
Because he was interrogating
Former Isis Fighters
Isis Fighters that have defected
And some people that here involved with have been hunted down and murdered and so he decided he needed to leave
United States right now
A little bit
But it is like I don't I don't care now about this interview
I don't I don't care at all it has no credibility it's no wonder Roberts
That's not good
Crazy
No
There's a high probability
Strongly disagree with your assessment
Strongly disagree
There's a chance
No
Robert Steele
It's possible but unfortunately the interview ends up having a lot of difficulties and I didn't keep any of it
And because it's just like I don't
I don't care what this guy says
Because I'm willing to believe that yes there are Isis people in Turkey
Of course I'm willing to believe this guy
Has worked with getting some to get out of ice
Possible that has nothing to do with the substantive claims
Alex is making
Pactiv
Right cuz the former Isis people that this guy do on behalf of ice
They're all together right on together
Put together
Here is a dictators and fascism has taken over almost entirely
Kevin Booth talking about stuff
Alex said something
And it wasn't even our plan to go to Turkey
Turtle frog
I said you better see the West
I need a film
Bombay Grill
You know what happened right after Putin took power in 2000
Cracking down on the Press really hard so stories like that wouldn't come out
Jesus
Is actually
Actually the same p**** Riot is in our movie
To tell the whole rest in the story was quite a big deal to get them in early I just like saying the name
But it's
Messenger
Geezers
One Direction
Oh boy
So I understand the old geezers at the cia's plan properly
The complete Nutter opposite of a boy band
Apparently
The CIA thought of p**** Riot
The old geezers at the CIA were like
I know
P**** Riot
Put series old guys at the CIA
I mean look unless unless
Lance bangs playing out your thought
So then they do that
P**** Riot
Then
What
Carries out the CIA plan of being
Alright playing a punk music
But
Perhaps even better at
Social activism yes
They will play in a
Russian Orthodox Church
Putin will then arrest them
Bright for no reason
And then
He will look like a thug
Did the CIA put together an entire plan to turn people against Putin
When
They could have just like shown
Any number of situations where he is already at
Pre-existing ones remind everybody about those apartment bombing
Here's the thing known soros-funded p**** Riot
Just making me look into that with a clear
Alex you're dumb
The other thing that we need to talk about
Is
That
If you trace a line
The people that he says are soros-funded
Soros
You'll notice
That the
Impetus
Behind that
He's trying to take agency away from women and minority
That is why he does this
Things he says that p**** Riot is run by Soros
Because it's unfathomable to him women would have political ideas
You never be
Couldn't believe that they would of their own volition
Go out and do social activism making themselves
To try and help
Haven't can't imagine that these African Americans that he obviously on some
Visceral level thinks are dumb
Would get get together and
Protest
For a battering of their social
Situation
He can't imagine that so he has to believe
That there is this Shadow who is directing all of it
Because they could never think of this on their own
And that is
Classically racist
It's classically misogynistic
It is just this idea that non-white males
It's impossible that they come up with this on their own
Boogeyman
And that
I mean
Somebody does all the
That's a bummer agency than that means
Or at least wrestle with their point as opposed to being like now
CIA
Get proven
Cruise ship
Prove anything
I listen to 10 months of Alex Jones Show proved anything
Not one thing
Julia Hsu
You just said it to the Wikileaks everyone knows the sea is known
We've proven more
I think that's all you trying to
Frustrating
So that's the end of the 29
For our coverage
Just
There's no resolution to the hacking narrative
You just let it drop
And again
It's
Just attention
Campaign
It's just him trying to
To make himself
I just can't stop thank
About
The writers room in the CIA when they're trying to come up with
Female punk band
Russian group
Haha like
Hey let's go with let's go with vagina dentata
That's already movie
That's too bad let's go with a vulva
Velvet
Yeah
Vulva
P**** Riot doesn't even rhyme
Not even alliterative
Sodium
And now I think we will see Alex Jones
Deciding
Full hog
To be a trump
I don't think that there is ever a moment
From everything that I've listened
I'm too I don't think there's a moment where he says
I support Trump
Unequivocal
I think it just
It's just creeping
December 30th
He knows
I'm about to go
It's the New Year sucking just do this
Do this and I weekend
Come back in the new year
And I'll have you can really absorb the respond
From people and if it's come back in your life
Full force and if not you can come up with a way to get out of it
The best
You know
You have a couple days to come up with
But the narrative you got a couple days for the Riders to sit down
You're the angle absolute
Exact moment
Sprouts Jones realizes
I'm on
I didn't add any
I didn't pause it
As long as
Super long
Still gone
I can't stress this enough
In the video
He's staring into the middle distance
He's not doing anything you just like
It's almost like a like a
Wiring didn't
It's pretty creepy out of that I would say
9 second pause probably maybe more
Jumps back after the fake line
The fact that the
You need to go after Hillary
She was on the ground
Trump replace
Sean
You can't
Roundtable discussion on what we should do with the Patriots
With the truth with a narrative the fight the blob
Just generally
So two days after this
The beginning of the new year
One of his economist
He says
The 2016 will be the worst year for the stock market ever
Dating
To the Great Depression
2016 will be like we haven't seen since 1930
I remember that
Track record is open Bowl
Buy-Back coins
Pentecostal Doomsday Preppers
Who continue to say that mathematically the end of the world is happening here and then they're like
Everything is outstanding
Like if you think that I don't know hold on we haven't seen the end of this yet
You're describing
With doomsday people
Is absolutely not the case you have made them use made discreet predictions of all been wrong
You
And all of your guests Alex have the worst
Track record of any
Hyundai I've ever heard that's including Rush
Savage
That's including
Glenn Beck even
Impeccable
In that they are consistent
And they are always wrong
Sometimes sometimes Rush
Got it right
They're dirty Infowars
Never to get it right ever their track record is amazing and as much as it amazes
Is 1 lb wrong they can be every single step of the way
It's it's impeccable work
Next clip
We take a break from anything serious and Alex Jones
Thinks about his daughters and how they're growing up
Washing my daughter's
Camp
And I am free
This morning
It is the number one most dangerous thing in their life
As I watch the
Not art camp SUV Broadway
I Hold On
Hold on
This metaphor is going to get really weird
But before we get into the metaphor
I would like to explain to Alex
But the reason
That automobile deaths have gone down is regulation
Reviews
Belt laws
Emissions test a
He's evil break standards
Things that explode
Proposed on the automotive industry let's say or the reason that those deaths have gone down
Prosperity
You're against regulation is the thing that is
Going to protect your daughters
Statistically f****** metaphor
That kids make
I got to go out and hunt
Don't wander off too
Traveling
Operation manager
Go to user race memory
I don't see what you think is going very serious concern for a parent
That
Made things
Crystal clear
Does very weird
I think you could probably come up with a better analogy parent misogyny in the younger male
Tell telling them not to wander off he has no idea
Just doesn't understand that
Call Andy ideafit like
I would like I would prefer to drive them around all the time cuz I know they can't
Cuz they're going to get eaten by Sabertooth sabertooth tiger
Reverse of the you got to let them touch a hot oven
Burn the f*** out of yourself and then they'll be like
That's not a good I
Right
It's dumb
I think I either weird parrot
I'm so now get back into politics
This is a troubling clip that he has on the
December 30th
Until you obviously talking to folks
Trump use genuine
And actually knows
Trump wants
And you see the relationship
Oh
Establishment
So
Follow through with all
Proposed tax plan
Billionaires in the oligarchs roughly
2 trillion dollars
Nope
He's got to take him down
He's draining the swamp he definitely didn't fill the swamp with more Goldman Sachs
Even as
Early
Or whatever
As December 30th
2015 Alex's
Do you know who are the Trump is working with Putin
He says as much on his show and visit where is he
Have to have gotten
From one of these birdies but he's talking to
If you don't leave it at that you're going to get f****** subpoenaed out
Got a subpoena Alex
Adelaide clearly have some awareness of course this is right when these attacks were starting to happen
Is when it ramped up that's when the influence campaign
Was getting going
No man Alex knows about
No there's no chance
Exactly
You know what would happen
You would probably request
A
Private
Interview
And then he would lie about what he said in the interview
When Rodger Stone deadline
He would probably request a private interview and f****** spill guts
Because he be like I'm in way over my head
Starting globos. Real
S*** I've been LED down the wrong path
Why am I
But it's so many times where it's like oh man
These guys
Could accidentally like if Larry Nichols accidentally takes down the GOP
Alex Jones is the linchpin Witness
In the case to take down Trump
And impeach him
How f****** delightful would be the easiest
Horse
You'd be super easy
If they gave him a public interview
He would grandstand it Scream by 1776
Heltah skeltah Robert Mueller
F****** great
Just Elizabeth Warren having to deal with
Golf Ranking
So in this next clip
Alex Jones has Paul Craig Roberts
And we talked about him a little bit in the past
He's a cookie weirdo
And on this
Day
Call Craig Robertson
In this clip he expresses some suspicion about our
Alex
He loves Alex
But suspicions about Trump
And then Alex
And by doing so accidentally reveals something
That I think would also be germane to being
On a
I should come in and help because
I mean I mean obviously
Obviously
Not scare the establishment as much either
What is that
I don't think you understand
Open Mike Flynn
So
Robert David Steele and
Beyond
Not understanding
Conspiracy theorists
That need apply
Is that
Alex Jones reveals
Whether it's real or not or Alex's perception
He has some sway over
I sent you the stone stone stone send you to him
He has a line
Within the campaign
And may or may not be
In Athen Subway influential
I think a lot of it is probably Alex's grandiosity
Overblown
I would say
Communication well and even beyond that
Take away the reality and Bluster whatever it may be what's most important is Alex Jones now I
Identifies as being part of
True because I was using an interview with someone on his show to spell
Policy advisors for Donald Trump now is not just someone who likes him
Ostensibly
Piece of it and legal aid
He is a part of
No I don't know about that but
I don't know about that I don't know we were legal lines are drawn but in his head
He is
And that's important
That is a big chain
He's not a part of you never was
I don't think I've ever heard him say would you like to advise
I spoke to rent on the show
That's f***** up that's f*****
The evolution
Completely
Taken place
He's now in Trump campaign I've two more clips
To play before we get out of here for this invest
The first one
The second one is a f******
Huge
F******
But the first one
Alex Jones has an interview with Seymour
On this episode
On the 3rd
Hirsch
Disgusting the past is often been tricked by fake
Intelligence
Sourcing issue
Is also broken some massive stories can't take that away from me
He's the one who when he's talking is like I don't have to tell the truth
Well
Right he hides a little bit of that the context of
But he's made behind
And idea that like when I'm speaking
Can fudge
In order to protect
Information
Doesn't hold water
Course not
They have an interview
Really what I think is
Is Big scoops
Listen big journalistic accomplishments
I think he might be now at the point where he believes a lot of nonsense
And the might be crazy
And here is the clip I'm going to play from
The interview that they have that leads me to believe
That this dude might be
Well
Remember the president is the current president joke that
If you know his daughters are getting to be dating a charmila humor
It was one of these annual
Needing prayer
Given the White House Correspondents Dinner
Which I think is Scandal
Like to see which guy can be at their table
Minnesota Vikings
Come by
You have
Diver watch
Funny they're dating his daughter
Very attractive
Women
You better watch out because you can always say the schedule Jones Friday
I thought that was
You kidding me
You know that
Best over the line themes to me
Okay
Is troubling because about the fact that he has the power of life
Life and death over innocent people exercise
But in that context
F*** off Seymour
It is true that our president
Literally orders extra. Extra.
Judicial today
I don't know what it is
Listen
It's Gallows humor
Ecstatic
Look
Correspondents Dinner
Is always hosted by a comedian
I don't understand
There's a lot of
Comedy that takes place
At The Correspondents Dinner
Also
Okay Aiden right
Probably absolutely Hasbro
He's not a comic
I know that's what I'm saying he didn't write that cuz he didn't even write the joke
Do you know you don't think that's actually a negative
Know every president is
You're going to have to call you later if you're not Obama
Timer doing
All over again
Why would I do that
Because you're a mistake.
The thing that I I'm getting Atmore is it Seymour Hersh
Is taking
Very clearly a joke and being like this
This is very unprofessional
No
You're not telling a joke has not improved
You're not you're not
Serious
You're not a serious investigative journalist if that is something that is holding you up
I mean call Dad narrative recall that criticism at the time
Also a selfie
Glenn Greenwald
Take on it as well acupuncture exactly
I'm not playing
Glenn Greenwald doesn't have his Seymour Hersh moments
But he's also broken some huge stories Olive
Seymour Hersh
Reality winner
Yeah
That you make about
Drone strikes not being a laughing matter
Is valid
Seymour Hersh
This complaint is not
So anyway
And this
Steam
Alex Jones
Entirely in Trump's case
Put the mic down for this clip because
He accidentally says the truest s*** I've ever heard
At the end of this December 30th episode
And this is such a bummer
I guess Brothers
Wonder why
He's on a journey getting more sophisticated
That's not why
Trump
Then
I've been cool
I think Trump should be dangerous coronavirus I think Trump is a wild man
Definitely a dumb person
Loyalty
Sociopath
Rules
No
Royalties
Live in squalor
No
That's not what loyalty is
That's our loyalty is
Nope
Are you sure
I think that you could make an argument that it is but I think it's a little soft
And it's unnecessary because
Let's stretch when you don't really need to go that far
Is like that's
Loyalty
Is it is not an ingrained desire not to live in squalor
Sorry stuck in sentence I've ever heard is Trump's real or I've been fooled
And I don't get fooled very often
When we have
A long history of him
Just kidding.
Like if you really break down one of the one of the parts of logic
I'm studying logic
Is that true
About truth preservation
That's what the main emphasis
Sentential
Predicate logic
So whenever you have a sentence
That hasn't it when you have a disjunction
We have a or b
That sounds is always true as long as
Is one of those things is true
Both can be true but as long as one is true that babies true
Trump is real
F******
You better believe it that's
So sad
It's so sad
Alex is so dumb
Is that
Ultra
And they were all fooled
The people have been fooled by different Republican comments are going to make the middle
Classic splode Riggins voodoo doll
Stupid
The people who fooled by Rick by f****** Mixon
Stupid every single one of these f******
People has been stupid. Food multiple times
You're right Alex's number two
It's always a bigger idiot
F****** bummer
Where we are in this investigation
We jumped ahead
We found it
We found the point
The hinge and the jump off
Yeah this is where it gets very real
Even though you still
Dumb
Still not crazy
Or he's crazy but he's not that crazy
He's not the crazy he's not Unleashed
I'm so we will pick back up the investigation
At least for the next couple months
Barring a nuclear winter
We will pick it up at the beginning of 2016
See what happens
And see where we go in this second phase of the investigation
Now that we when does Alex lose his mind
We've figured out
But he joined up with Team Trump
Out of ego
Because he thinks he's a part of it
Because he's being lied to by Rodger Stone and Steve
And because
I don't think I don't think anybody in the world
Quite frankly
Any journalist
Anybody who covers
Outside of you and me
Listen to all of our episodes anyone understands this nearly as fully as we do
A lot of people think likewise
They're both bigots
And there's some truth to it we originally thought we thought
Bigotry
Money and what
I thought sure.
For sure
I mean there is all those things are little tiny pieces of it but I don't think
I don't think
Are people outside of the knowledge fights
We are really get the
The event also just be Celestial body play
All These Little Things add into it
But the things that are the most important are Alex's
Ego and Russia
Barber
I wish more people understood that but now what's most important to us
Is figuring out where he
She forsakes all out
And becomes
Only about Trump
Because at this point
Still talking about you still talking about that how we scared about his kids
It'll probably still always be there at what point
Is it like until it does
She say f*** you Ted Cruz you're not smart
Yeah
Is it just one
We got to find out
So that'll be the next stage of this investigation
Alright
Do you think we make it out of this
You and I
No I mean like just
No
I don't see anyway
Like I know it seems every generation thinks the world is ending
Parallels between this and the Civil Rights Movement
Not
Regards
Certain
Spray different Charles Nelson
Riley didn't become private
That's true or someone else on Match Game
You don't like 80 and it didn't you didn't end up with Richard Dawson
Is he at least I kissed all the women
Dawson was a bigot
And became president back then
Then you'd have an argument for every generation feels like shift going south
Sounds of life
Where are
Rex Tillerson said that we are talking to North Korea and our president went on Twitter to say
Don't worry about it
We'll take care of it
Is own Secretary of State
It's not good
How do you even deal with that
You know you talked about normalizing Behavior but that's f****** outside of anything
If I had to give my process that it's still eluded
It's wild
8 minutes of subjugation of your own past
Decision
The layers of like what are you fighting against
Cuz it's clearly
Yourself on some level
Shadow Boxing with all sorts of weird things
I think that he like one of the things that Alex Jones got
Sing now in 2017
Doesn't really matter it's the movement
If Trump goes out
Then we still have our movement
Yeah I think there is some truth to that I'm obviously Trump has to go
He is
Destroying everything in his path and he is a National Disgrace
But at the same time
Your question are we
The Earth
Your question
Are we going to make it out of here
That sort of thing
Yeah I think there's a chance
But it
Contingent
On people understanding what the actual battle is
And I don't think a lot of people are
Because I think there's a lot of people who are still hung up on this idea
Republican vs Democrat
Very right.
Because a lot of
Direct action
Is really required in order to preserve a lot of the right
And protect a lot of dis
Franchise people
So I don't think they're doing anything wrong
But I do think there is a greater awareness
To be in the Public's mind
That we are coming up on
And
Unfortunately might have already entered
What will be
A make-or-break
Moment for civilization
And I don't mean this to sound like Alex Jones
But it might
And he related to me unpack what I'm trying to say
Throughout our history
We've had
Not just America
Human history
Sure maybe can't go all the way back
Rihanna
We will born
Is this your Attenborough impression
Publix throughout history we've had a lot of different versions of
Social
When you had
Do you know
More primitive people they had liquid just got this you have matrilineal societies you have some that have
Representation in the underlings to vote for
Some of that are just
Very
Much like
Alpha alpha male gorilla community
You have those in the Primitive times
Monarchies
A lot of that has gone away and like towards representative democracy that's how.
Gorillaz
Right
Just get rid of them
I understand
I threw out with
The representative democracy is but a common sort of
Replace most monarchies
And you have like people like we still at the queen
Figurehead it's not there not running thing
You still have dictatorships around
Do you still have remnants of that sort of monarch
Breccia
North Korea you have a number of those places
What I think is going on
If I can be
Totally blonde
Is we are in a phase
Much like
I wouldn't like it it's a 1776
I wouldn't I wouldn't like an inch of that
But I
I think we're
Kierkegaard is belief
Is that the human matures
Through Christ
He believes that
At various points in your life you have a crisis
Can you grow through
Like one of the crazies would be separation
Fromjapan
Right and then you you have it
Terrible. Of time
Where you're freaking out and then eventually come out the other end of it and you mature
I become more of a whole person
I think that what we're seeing right now
Is possibly
A crisis of democracy
I think we're seeing a crisis
Capitalism
I didn't receive those systems
Are not working anymore in the same way being a child
And having your parents take care of everything
Doesn't work
At a certain point
And I'm not saying
Is a condemnation
Welfare
Or any of that sort of thing I actually think
But I think they were coming to a point now and
Who knows when it'll bubble over
But the crisis
We have to
Come up with something
Capitalism
Late-stage that we're in now
Doesn't work
It's exploitative and it kills everybody
But it's more aggressive than adorable
It goes like this is a
Marauding cannibalistic system that is going
Destroy every
We're seeing the democracy
Representative democracy
Wild Wonderful and ambitions
Very clearly
Converted
Unchecked
Totally
Because the people who have
Tons and tons of the economic power
Find it very easy to
Gerrymander for example
Don't have it
And so I think
That
This is one of the
Wanda problem
I'm not certain
The Democratic Socialist
Are the right one
I'm not sure
They intrigue me
As
What sounds like a better idea
And I've looked into them a bit
Centrist
No this is Dan be cautious
Cautious River
I think probably to implement a lot of their ideas
I think that
Does create a better world
I think that's probably true
But I don't know if it's enough
Because right now
His forces that are against the progress
They're against the coming out the right end of growing pain
It's like
Alex Jones
Donald Trump
Russia
All of these figures
In many ways
They are the child
It doesn't want to get out of their parents house
Ffi
Seems
They are the people who want
Cole they want harsh capital
They want this
Cruel brutal system
To stay in place
A bear
Trying to stop us
From successfully come
Completing the crisis
I would say the crisis already
And I think we're at the point now where is
It's very strongly disagree I think we're still made prices
I disagree I think we are I think or we are past it and now we have event
When did it end
I would say it ended in 2008
I would say that all of this is
Is ultimately a reaction
Iran deal
No it's a reaction to
Reagan
Beginning to dismantle the New Deal
Which is what allowed
The oligarchs
Consolidate so much power and such
Such a small
A group of people
And then it was in reaction
Right
LabCorp
People still further
I agree all the games all of the games
Since 2008 have gone to the wealthy but crisis Point pass
Now we're in
We're in very narrow pathway hypothesis
Or if it is blood I posit that that's
The beginning of
Of the crisis
Okay
I don't think that's
The end of it
I think that's the beginning of when something new must
To be birthed
Right
So I look at it
Weird spitballing here this is not like
I don't have
I don't have a degree in predicting things
Whatever we're we're talking about our ass to ascertain
Dum-dums in Chicago
I do I choose to look at it is
That is the MoMA
Capitalism
And the oligarchy
That we have in our own country was a step too far
And something needed to be done
Right and the beginnings of
The crisis
Came into effect
You choose to look at it is the end of a crisis
And I would disagree I would say that it's
The end of when
A crisis coming could be ignored
I respect that
And I can see I can see where you're coming from
I'm going to look back at
The Great Depression
And all of the people who starve to death and died back
That was the price
Collapse but was the crisis
No end to get out of that
FDR Institute
Strongly disagree I don't think that is I don't think that was a civilizational crisis
If I think that was a crisis with capitalism
That's my that's
Kind of my point
Okay
That was some
Something that can be grown
Herbert Hoover's disastrous response to
And so
Through
Democracy
We did a beta
Even though
The stripped-out by
The same oligarchs
I think we're dealing more along the lines of
Old-timer
Monarchy
A much larger
Where in
I've the
The monarchs
Controlled everything
Sooner or later they treated their people poorly in
That they started robot
Yeah that Rebellion
Always ended with
Blood or surf
Pretty much where I think we're at right now
Well that will be the end of the
Your argument that the crisis ended in 2008
I don't buy
I think the closest we've come
I'm sure there have been other times
And and maybe even
I mean you could look at the beginnings of like workers right
And the unionization
And stuff like that
Temperature
To shift things
Entirely
But I would argue that still living
Existing framework
And just trying to gain power for the people within it the possibility of destroy
Bring your world right entrance of worker
The stakes are so much higher in the same way that I
Describing the
The feudal listed the feudal system
In older Europe
And then we're literally
Life-or-death if if the castle is if the Monarch Falls
You're going to then be taken over by your neighboring
That's the type of
Who sings we're dealing with in which
America is going to
Fall
Yeah and that's that's all
That's why the crisis happening
Because that was the moment we're really we could have stopped America
Falling
V just inertia of History
End of the way
People working the way
Generac
That's the way it's going to go
Well that with
Climate control with climate change
National disasters that are going to
Multiply
They're already so bad
Can't really deal with them
ShopRite
I don't like
How is it
Why aren't people in Puerto Rico rioting
Cuz they're on a Nile
Under hungry imagine 3.6 million people in Chicago Chicago
All of us are left without homes or power
Wego
We go somewhere to start
We go to Gary Indiana to buy guns
A raid
Porto shop
But I think I think what you're saying
But
Thing that I would put on it
I don't think
That
Throughout our our illustrious history
There has been a time
When it's been abundantly clear that we need
To change everything
Except for the 60s
Enderle 7
I believe that was a time
Social movements
Was towards
Throwing out
Baton of s*** that was unnecessary
And making a fundamental shift
And the way that ever was
Everyone lives
And forcing it but like making
Making
A foundational different
As opposed
Changing something within
A system making a new system
I don't think we finish
Everybody who is
Kilt right and I don't think
I think I was Martin Luther King jr. RFK and Fred
You're going to
Yeah and you end up with math
The distance disillusionment the first
Attempt at Accra
The first
The temp to the crisis of growth in
It was held at Bay
Held back
And now I think it's bubbling up again
We're going to
Seeing what we have been
Like I said
I think the Democratic socialists are a big
Piece of this
Attempted
To do some of that stuff
That was done
In the
The sixties and seventies
On a more organized front
And doing it without
Flowers in Your Hair
Hippy dippy nonsense
All that stuff that everyone attacks
And this to me is the Azan
Sense of what I'm getting
I think
We stand
Rip
A past example of what happens if
If this doesn't work
And that is
Nixon
Reagan
That sort of
That's where we end up going down if it doesn't work
If people get this illusion
Submitting and ending up pretty disappointed in we have the pasta
But we've gone down since
There is
A force that wants that
And that is Alex
That is
Be alright
That is neo-Nazi
That is
Well and their minions
It turned
Well no it turns out
These people who are super rich and holding people down
Quite frankly I'll probably thrilled
If people like Alex Jones
Horse they are they absolutely
Encourage this
Yeah of course they do they would love the neo-nazis paying for Milo yiannopoulos
Every
Even after everything that has come out about him is come out
That's because he still
Eddie still angers liberals
Prescriptive
But I'm going to put it
Like like I said
What amount
More less crossword
And one one way or another something's going to
Crossroads
Look weekend
Look we have
We have
I don't know I don't know what to do
Prescriptives
Creating and hilarious and tragic and an
Deal with all these emotions anymore the thing to do is
Herbal Essence
From
4050 years ago
What happened
We can we can take one lesson
And that is
Folk music
So I can change the world
Is avoid dissolution
Avoid the
If some positive leader gets killed
Don't let that stuff
Don't think that means that the world is
Because I
Do think
Vet in the
There been less
Investment
People as singular figurehead
Right then there would have been
Stop would have been followed through a lot better
The great man theory of History
No
Beyond that
We must fight
We must fight them on the
Yeah
Ultimately what you are looking at it and or or serfdom
Well that's pretty much I don't see any other option
I think that that is our inevitable future
Unless we successfully passed through the crisis
That was present
To do us fifty fifty years ago and we sailed to growth
I believe that
Society
As a whole failed to growth
I mean we did get Medicare Medicaid
Play past and the Civil Rights Act
We didn't actually solve the issue
I would like a monster is awesome
Awesome and I'm not taking away from it but I would argue
That's the equivalent
Getting a c on it
Yeah cuz I don't want it I don't want to impugn the Civil Rights Act or anything like that
It's not the it wasn't the revolutionaries
Upheaval of everything that we need
That I brought that up
Because I do kind of find that to be in a certain way home
The fact that they
It did do things
It did get stuff done
Look at how many lives Medicare and Medicaid have saved
How many
The Civil Rights Act
Definitely didn't do everything at f****** needed
But you can't argue
I'm libertarian
I'll go f*** themselves
Yeah
It did accomplish something
And so if you want to if you want to argue that
Incremental change is possible
Then we'll good example the flip side
The flip side of it is yes it did all this great things but it also came along with
Pretty much
Perpetual War
So
I don't think
I think they're
You know you don't throw the baby out with the bathwater
As they say
But at the same time it is
I think
A little bit foolish
Think that that's
Progress
Is completely overhaul the entire
Ideas that we have about what our means
Overhaul the entire idea of
Capitalism is one of the bigger
Yes problems of this entire
And I don't I don't
I don't know what the answer
Socialism is the right answer but we have now does not work
That's the crisis we Face 50 years ago
And that's that's why I'm saying that it's
It's too late
The inertia of capitalism is such
The only way to actually defeat it
Would be with something that is strong enough to move that office
And that has to happen
Amelia
I would hope it's the cancer of capitalism has
Exercise so much faster than any of us are really willing
To deal with
And so it's
Where are responses going to be
Bernie Sanders
It's still saying you know we need single-payer healthcare
But
What we're going to have to do is fix Obamacare first
And then gradually move towards
Socialized Healthcare
And there isn't time
There's not enough time
Bishop needs to
Go down
Soon
And the only way to organize enough of a
Enough of a
A large enough group of people to do this
Is
I mean eventually through wide-scale anger
Right
Once you get too far on that we're talking again
About
Cuz it cuz
I mean
We live in a
Very very
Build a comfy
It does not build agency does not build
Anything other than the
All cities of the America
Almost like that some of the messages Alex
You should have taken from A Brave New World
Yeah what I thought
And so it's just it's just not going to it's just not going to happen
But I'm the only
The only question is
PowToon
What happens along the way
Cuz cuz
And there's another thing to remember
Go to the runner
In this case
In the sense that
Like the status quo
Get something they win ties
Salute
Nothing nothing
Inactivity doesn't work
It breeds further inactive
We're rambling here
Or not rambling we're discussing the inevitable end of the world and who thinks it's going to come sooner you take a negative stance on it
Take positive stance I think there is a possibility we grow through it and
Name something beautiful come
Out but in
In the meantime
There are growing pains
And blood
Is inevitable
Serfdom is not nest
Sara Lee inevitable
It is
If we don't
But the Blood
Probably enough
There will be
There was a retired but let me tell you some
This is the role of his career man
Trump
Daniel Day-Lewis
Wood
Rush that row
Seriousness that Daniel Day-Lewis well he's got range
Tony's gyro
So
Optimistic stance on at UFO
The guy who started with
Dreams of headless Koch brothers is going to have a negative assessment of the world
I know and I will see what happens
My doom-and-gloom perspective is
Probably will end up with the tie going to
We'll be back to where we are again
I believe we will
Climate change
Say it
2052a
Entire world
Destroyed it's just
Climate change
That the world is going
Half-alive beak
People are going to eat
The world's going to be fine when we're gone that's the world been around 454 however
Billion years or whatever
To think if we grow through the
The crisis that we're supposed to grow through
We can adapt
The climate
I mean I mean
Photographer
The runner right everything by Evanescence
I mean I don't know
Time does speeding up a little bit
And maybe
Maybe we don't go through this crisis we have it again in 10 years as opposed to 50 years
Just because of the inevitability of it and
And the increasing pressures
The climate-change putting on
Yu-Gi-Oh
Growth
It's it's possible but
I would like to see
CS go through it
I think
I think that the traits
But you'd like
2cm precise
Is there a thing
Empathy
Things like
Care
That's things like
I think those are the things you'd like to see
And if we do that that could be
Revolution
Possible
I don't know
But all that can go away
Already loose
All of it real
I will finish
If you want to find out what f*****-up thing Dan is about to say
I might write about it on Thursday
But go to knowledge, all of our stuff
You can also follow us on Twitter that knowledge underscore fight
I've given look us up on iTunes Road Facebook
Leave a review we are of course on
Facebook
Yeah and then
Quite frankly
I think wants to be a fun exploration of Alex Jones being an idiot
Not peddling pedantic theories that I have
About how we can save the world
Right
I mean
I think these are really the conversations that everybody should
To be having pretty much all the
Time right now
I'd like
If we're going to do this
How are we going to do it
That kind of thing
Angela
More thoughts about concrete
Steps
Stuff like that the weekend
Can take really helpful
Maybe another show
Yeah go ahead
One guy who has never grown through a crisis
His teeth definitely didn't go through a crisis
Evil guy with a crisis of should I put up this picture and he fails at every single time
50 years ago there was a movement to put up that picture
Didn't succeed
Did not go through that, now
And
What would you
What would you say to this
You should go f*** himself
His name is John Rappaport
Jon rappoport
Alex