Alex
Birthstone colors
And talk a little bit
Today's yeah we're both a little bit hungover
Very hungover we went out to have a few drinks
You repeat it
Gridley dosed with
The mayor may not be true
Regardless
Cuz you had to go get your own board you're on Scrabble board for the bar
Walk around with your own Scrabble board everyone was telling you how cool you are
Also for those interested Jordan did beat me by
Spypoint
Furious
Very unhappy about it
Series that you didn't like my words
I didn't I thought that your gameplay was
Possibly overly defensive
I was I was working to open up
The boardroom
The possibilities that we could collaborative right word
My girlfriend
No
It's a it's a game to your a capitalist man capitalist
Okay alright I'm more of an arc
Speaking of capitalism
I'd like to give a shout out
Are you transition
God
Like to give a big shout-out to Heather thank you so much
Heather
You very much
Don't get mad until you're brilliant
Yeah
Congratulations
Ever happened to the best thing that ever happened because
We talked about this not mattering is recorded but I've still self-conscious about it
So we have an episode that's going to drop at the end of the week that I intended to drop at the beginning of the week but I switched
So if you get a little bit confused by that
Don't worry about it everything is cool
But today
We're not deliberately f****** with your head
We're going to put out on Friday
I think we might say it's Monday
Or something like that
Alright
I don't know but
Jordan
Got to play this out of context
Okay
Excited about what we're going to be going over today okay
2015 episode
2015 New Year's Eve
On the Alex Jones program
New Year's Eve is the best
Kind of holiday
Because it's a holiday that everyone
Concelebrate
Has nothing to do necessarily with religion has nothing to do with
Nation of origin is nothing jingoistic about it
All it is
Is a time to reflect on the last year that's happened in your life
Talking about
A calendar is white nationalist Chinese New Year's Eve tattoo
Holidays that are really just about reflection and about like do better next time around
I'm into celebration
Dave remember syndrome
None of this will be relative
He hasn't yet
I think I might have cut out some of that stuff
He has a guest on that I've been itching to talk about for the entire
Podcast
And he comes on
It's the first time in the coverage
The era that we've been covering
His name is James David Manning
And he has number two
On my list of my favorite crazy on Alex
See the third Manning brother is not but here is an out-of-context drop
Make me laugh
Five minutes earlier today
I mentioned this
Someone
Someone sodomites
Get me a bucket of poop
Did I tell you I left
Directions from the pulpit
Somebody said this dude a bag of entire story when when we go
Get there
He is a he's a preacher he has it all
New York update
Open up in New York
He is
Amazingly crazy best kind of crazy
He may have
Accidentally sent himself a bye
I wouldn't put it quite frankly
Anti-gay
Preacher is in trouble
Also
Anti-black
I should be clear about this
Hates black people
It's fascinating and we're going to get into all right but we got Noah
He doesn't come with
The beginning of the show
So we got to start as the show starts
We got to find out Alex Jones
The last we left off we talked about the 29
We discussed
Did you days prior to
Receiving
Alex Jones has accepted the years
With Donald Trump
Right
Who was like
How long does it take him
To go from there
To Americana 2.0 I think you're going to see
It was very quick cuz I think it might even be in this episode you start to see like the show is
So much more about Trump
I would say three quarters of this episode is about
How great
Gotcha
Very fast
But
Alex starts the show by talking about John Wayne
Sun
And how he is one of the elite
Anchorage
My son lives next door
The monster
Here Comes John Wayne's son
Hispanic John Wayne
And
It's not also if I were the elite
Don't think I would care about John Wayne's son
I think he would be very low on my list
Press release
You have no respect for
I don't
This is why the West is dying
Everybody knows you're not
John Wayne movie stars and their offspring
Americana
It is but I bet
I can't tell you
How funny I think that like
James David Manning not to jump the gun okay puts out
So many f****** videos on his YouTube channel that it's impossible for us to cover everything
We could do an entire podcast about him I think it might be more fun we're right on the
To find like
You know fun stuff that he said over the years
What if title was
Lights tent me a bucket
Is how it starts
To tell anybody about
You don't have to tell it just look at it and be like it's not like these.
Publicized
There's nothing funnier than that video
Alright I have some Madea movies
My friend
Wait till we get to Savannah's other staff
But strong
Through
Alex Jones episode before
It's there in this clip
Expresses a good bit of
Ambivalent racism
Assertive
I guess is a way to put it
Alright
More aware of
His bigotry then he likes
Flashlight on
We need
Arab Spring in America
What is the radical left
Yeah sure
Black lives matter has some good points and you know sunset
Stole that it's George
Of course it's going to have some legitimate
What
Crazy
He's just going to be right you know he's got some good
Soros don't worry about that.
The points are about how you murdering black
People don't worry about those good points
Now there's a Civil War coming
And it definitely has nothing to do with the fact that we are f****** over black people nothing
Put the put them aside and I want to make you racist
Spring is happening
The radical left
Is the thing that I
I think it will I think we're exactly
Right even though they were funded
Till the cows come home
They were radicalization.
Coming
The foot
So in the next Club this is
Buddy visit Mike down
In this clip
Alex says something pretty terrible
Before he does he mentioned
Another one
Children
Apparently I didn't look it up
System
Whether he did all this or not
Gimme a Break
Give me a break
Where all this is going
Any photographs I shouldn't be laughing
Perform
And
I don't know what's going on
So I don't know what's going on fairly accurate
No but it shows that no no no no
Community kept saying take this pill is like
I don't see what's wrong with that
Run your even missing
The point in that what he says they're the fact that he understands
What the allegations and the reality of it is
Cool with it rape
Bright
Spine
Tell Mom not to
The drug women just trying to take away their male vitality
Or something along those lines
Like not even like is like
Listen
It's kind of primitive
This is his f****** insane
It is
It would be better if he just didn't I'd that
As opposed to being like
Yeah he totally did it but it's fine
Look
OJ is allowed
The kill one wife
It's just from caveman days man of always
Female property with another man
From a timer case but as we all know it's fine to live like that nobody ever had
Had an issue is no reason
Progressive
It's not even
There's everything wrong with
Everyone understand let's move along
Shut you down or anything like that highlight
Did the problems of Alex get to the more fun stuff that's coming next
Alex
Trump
Invitations
And
We add to the
But I'm working under that is
Mostly
It's Rodger Stone lying to him
And then
Interfering in our election
Business Holdings
Huge Hotel golf courses unit
Yeah
Just like Iran size
Hardcore
Rochester
Diction
And Bush 41 Administration
Typically talking about
He's literally describing this person and not saying who it is after he's already given
Exact credits for Rodger Stone
Great
Look I'm not going to say who my source
It is done
Also I'm pretty sure
Sure that Rodger Stone doesn't
Listen to Alex
On alok
He's not listening
Certainly
Serious
Yesterday
This is the song
Hershel Greene
No he didn't
Greatest living journalist
He has to clarify that because
He's like
We didn't
View
Which even I have to point out is bunkers. Credible
This is a claim and no one's going to believe
It's okay to
The bolt
If you go you mean you can find it if you want to find it you can go listen
The entire interview with tigers
I am. He doesn't agree with Alex he's conflating interviews that he had with Steve
Pieczenik Non-Stop
Steve pieczenik also was Bill heck
It's true
Text Alex
I think you've got some bad information
This is the beginning of the
What I would describe as
On
Provable undisprovable stories about Trump
Elaborate strategy
Right.
He's been a patriot 430
Well this is last trumpet this is more the secret Patriots
That helped get Trump elected
And sort of work
But they were doing
Not great
Shed
No
You want to give weapons
And they deliver the weapons
Urban tropical
Sabotage
Any further
It's not good
They're taking license
With their orders
If we imagine a scenario where in Alex
This correct
These people are giving weapons
The terrorist groups
But they're their way of lashing out is to break the weapons
Before they get there
I think that the bad people within our military who are ordering these weapons be delivered
Are going to figure out that pattern pretty quick figure out who's breaking the weapons on the way it's not like
Communication
Nothing's broken and the generals
No they got us
Dairy Queen
Resistance
If you're on board an aircraft 777
Put on
Absolute
Uniform
So
Check your white privilege
Hope you get big head hope Habibi cuts off your head
As a
Freis okay to use that in my daily
Well I'm fine with that
As long as I get to say that
Because that is a fun center
You're on a plane back and then you're like chick flicks bro
Don't fight back against this terrorist
Listen
Honky
If you get your head cut off
Hey we're moving on up that's all I'm saying is a minority you got to let him
If it's a plane
No it's not mutiny
That's not harm you
Text Julie on boat
But it's also weather to Clear Lake chamber Brew
Then that's no longer mute
The guy who hijacked the plane
That's all.
Of Donald Trump insulting
All the other candidates
I'm the last
Person she wants to be running
Yeah that's true so he says that this is Alex's
Response
I love Donald Trump
I'm told
Real quick
Monetary distraction is Rodger Stone
I'm feeding him a line about why he
Or something like that
Yeah you know the Secret Service isn't letting anyone near him now you know sweetie I'm sorry Alex you have to wait
From Full Metal Jacket
After him
I'd like to oppose a alternative explanation for what Alex believes is
Is the globalist
The major threat
Some people care about
People
A lot of people very early on
So how bad Trump would be
For their rights
For sure but not to globalist
To all of us
People surviving
Alex
Also
A big threat because
Donald Trump
Love's nuclear
Seems that way
Doesn't like that everybody
True
Everybody's love
30 presidential
Doesn't bode well for all of us
Let alone
Threatening
On Twitter he's even said recently liked
There's only one way to solve this problem all negotiations have failed so there's one way to solve it which suggests
He wants to do that
Posit
We've then
You know what I mean like
I'm not saying we should obviously
Stan I think he's I think it's still all blustery blossom
But I dye my fear is that it's not
She hasn't
Kind of means there's a reason he's not
Yeah
I think it's because
AT-AT
Sandpoint some jazz
General has brown
Wally's been like so who's carrying the nuclear football anybody over here and he's been beaten
Fake codes.
Take everything
Just put him in a small room
With a fake
Fake Twitter account
I will call on Twitter right now to build a fake
Twitter but only Donald Trump a Neo-Nazi
You got one job left before you go away
What's an outdoor
Then we have seen here on this stuff 31st
New Year's Eve
Day episode Alex Jones
Onboard now
He loves us
You love him
Formal endorsement that we've been waiting to sign
Absolute and it's a little lackluster cuz we already kind of felt like this Eureka moment
Even if it was
Eclipse
5e appearance
Of Jane
David Mann
I first
Discover James David Mann
Because
He really hated Barack Obama
In the lead-up to the 2008
That's all friend of mine found a video
That was a compilation of James David Manning screaming
And Reverend Wright Obama's preacher
Screaming
Have a tooth have just a ridiculous s***
What the f*** is this his big quote
Barack Obama
Women out on the stroll
Okay
I started to look into him a little bit and I
He does not disappoint in any way
In terms of how insane he is
And how onion
Diaz
And from his own video podcast that he puts out called The Manning Report
We have so much
Fun
To get into celestolite Alex let's let Alex introduced
James David Manning
Obama got in office
Muslim
I just think you're going too far
Problems
That was years ago
The year before Obama got no
So this is Alex giving a lead-up to his his
His appearance being like I thought he was wrong but
Barack Obama
Love that I love that
Idea that so many
People throw out all the time
Create
Right
You're just
He successfully made you look at it
Well but that's what this whole f****** country is
Narrative who did like sitting
They're like we're inciting racism
Yeah you know revealing how racist
As You Are
All throughout his
Terms of trying to I
You know
It's not even criminalizing
But like
Stigmatized
Denigrating black exist
It's sad how awful is it the vice president
Blue to Indianapolis
20 seconds of a f****** football game
And then
Angry about it was not a f****** publicity stunt
3 years
I told him to go
If not then
That's crazy
Is blind
Stroup no nope
No no we all have it because we have not yet delved into the Fun Fun World
Irreverent
So here is the proper introduction
I'm coming into the
Infowars
Airways
Corsi's
Teaching
Kids there
Going up again
Straightforward
Which is God name for Harlem
He created his own
School of course
AP gave him himself a doctor
So there's that
It's not even that look it up
We are in a fight
We are
Difficult
Because you've got both
Power booster
Not sure not sure that's the case
Maybe in his troubling if true maybe in his tiny insulated Church
Right of combat
Yeah maybe that's the case maybe he's been able to swing
But I don't believe the African-American
Community-at-large
Thinking of trumpism
The man community-at-large
Been proven right along at all political spectrums for good long while
Especially
I regret that a little bit earlier signs that
Maybe you didn't take seriously
Reverend Manning
Explain
McDonald is the man
He is the man for America
The only
America
Can anybody else
And continued
Anderson Cooper
Spring Aldi
Egyptian spring
Join the Russians
Corydalis
Until we examine this
So someone needs to go to trial
Probably probably rather it be Barack Obama
Continue the policies of Obama I would prefer
Can you the policies of Woodrow f****** Wilson
Couple things I want you to hold onto
Two for a second
Cooper
Go back to that
And then also
The trial
These are two things
Do we have we have
Three more clips
A reverend Manning
From Alex Jones Show
And then we're going to get it to Reverend Manning
Oh yeah
And those two things are going
Very
For future clips
Put a pin in it myself although I really want to talk about it already
Reverend
Explains that he also believes the black lives matter is trying to cook up a race war
Is trying to see which is the most
Issue a race war
It's a beautiful statue
The sons of the Confederacy
We give you
10 Dalmatians
Right
Crazy
Situation
Jeeps that's not
But yeah
They will shut you down
Like a cheap to wear a cheap suit
Not like you'll have a fever or something I think
Just mixing metaphors
I mean look at that look at that matter is being created
In order to try and and
They are there in the first place is a bit
Are there dormant
Big issue
Look we don't want black lives matter pointing out that we're being murdered by the
Confederacy
Because if they do
The sons of the Confederacy were going to murder black
Right if we keep it under the surface it'll just keep happening but if we talk about it
Terrible
Look
Don't antagonize racing
Don't antagonize these archaic violent races
So just be subservient
That's not good and I wish I was
Might be beautiful statues if they didn't have a contact
That they did
I don't know
They they are
I don't know if you
There was a
Incredibles
Stalin
So
It was made perfect
Now yes
It does represent
Tens of Millions
I would like a statue of that bucket of poop
Terraria Mana delivery
The shortest
Sadist
Bucket of poop
Adan y
Does Reverend Manning
Support Donald Trump
It seems weird
Seems very weird
Valley
Brother
And what they do is they support
Democratic Republican
Alicia
People
The reason why
Is
The people
80 songs
Various
Behave
Want to watch
This man sat in a meeting with
83 preacher
Most
Except for me
We're telling him he needed to apologize
Roughing up the block
Alabama
I think it was
Dr. King
Patient
But risky
Nothing
Identify
Garbage
Any meeting ran over time he's
Steals
And listen to what they had to say in a dress
I said this with my man
Because he was
Wagner's
The Ike
Yuck he likes him because he went to a meeting and all these other black preachers that he doesn't like we're mad at him is like
Oh well
A billionaire lying about being a billionaire landlord
As we all know
Is a man
Connect
Right especially their billionaire landlords
Are always like
Hey let me listen to your concern
Especially a millionaire pretending to be billionaire landlord who's had the frequent
Renting to black people
Realtors whose father was a registered member of the
It's a lot of course you can
Sit there and listen for that long
Because in his mind all he's doing is
Is playing a loop
But his favorite song
Trump is great
I am a lalalala
I'm sorry what was that
Say something that is accidentally
Alarming
America
What he can do to the America
Yeah
Do you not see how
You nailed it
Office
We're Fox
Yeah cuz what you did in the campaign is like a destroying
Decorum
Bucking every convention
Everybody
He suggested that people shoot people people should murder Hillary Clinton
All of this
Care of her
How bad
EXO I think you speak
Ugly enough it's not Mariah cry I don't know look
I'm so I'm so Furious
I just
Hamp
It's like this behavior is so
Stupid
So silly
So ridiculous promise you
I promise you at the end of this everything is going to be alright
Okay everything is going to be alright
It's not the world still going to suck
This Arc is going to be really interesting that we're going to go on
Reverend Manic from his
Releases thumbs-up all the s*** they talk about all show
Another Noah setup necessary
This is f***** up
Broccoli
So she is sitting right behind him
Uyyala
He goes with it
Royal boy
Is so crazy
Terrific but it's
What is it's so crazy
Evergreen it be without
I would give her a left hook
That tears at the very least and over-reaction absolutely
Not by this he's sitting there like
It seems like
Don't give up James
If you if you were here
Witcher
Because you
Situations
I think I should releases this video because that's
Publix
Allegations
Kind of accusation
The closeted homosexual
Self-loathing
Those things will be borne out over the course
This next one is a little long
But it has
Play as this entire long clip
Cuz it's it's what
I think he thinks that this is a really intelligent
Deconstruction
Of why he is not a homophobe
I think he's
Thanks everything
Is the most
Absolutely
Elementary logic
Problems with
I need to call
The same way
Which is
Walmart, Colton
Listen to the
Example
Let me ask a question
I think we're spies
You know
Do you sense where this is going
Stand where this is going
You look like a nice visit
Is this man haha
No
I think you know why
I think it to be very simple and Pacific
Let's Get Lucky beaver
Who are you
Jesters
Someone who you know
Actually
In Owasso
I said you know
Is that racist
Stereotypical
Perceptions
I don't want
You know
Sexual
Is that
Successful
Someone looks
Is that
Passage
He's got a number
People
Don Lemon
Remembers
He looks like
Bigotry
Free
A young boy
This guy is crazy
This guy is
Exactly right that's so f****** so
Missing piece tap of like why is it different a businessman in a homosexual
Erase part out of it
Missing the part of the argument be having
Represent is
What is it about these
Two nouns that are
I think if you were to
A little bit of become very clear very quick
A lot of things homosexual
Irib
If I see a man dressed
And I am going to describe his dress
Very specifically
He's a business
That bigoted
Also also if that businessmen were gay
And I punched him cuz he was gay
A little
Also on the fringes of the black community
Now is he a businessman
The unpacking that is like
Right or wrong about the business
Do you don't have any
Judgment that you're placing towards whether or not you
He's a businessman
Well with James David Manning
Whether or not someone is a homosexual
Is very important
In terms of his judgment
I was actually.
Also I didn't have time for you
I didn't have time to pull all these clips
Like cuz there's so much more you can find there's a clip where he admits
Like doing Deja.
Like Vegas just a crusade against that he was
He feels guilty about giving some dude a b****** want I think there's a big piece of that sounds about right
He's talked about struggling with Gay Thoughts
And stuff like that
Every single piece of it is this massive self-loathing whether it is for being black or four
He just lashes out at all these
Community season
That part's not funny but everything else is
F****** hilarious
So this next play
Next clip
He's responding to a Pisa viewer mail
If you realize it's pretty quick that the viewer is mocking him
And if you rolled with it admirably
Sort of renounces his blackness
We will be introducing our new product
Purple stuff
Community
And would like
To place your image
You're overheated attempt to gain National exposure by
Barack Obama
2 out
Around the election
It's okay makes a big deal out of the idea that
Not a problem
No
Okay
That's what that's in reference to about the idea that your campaign against
Barack Obama's parents
Fell on deaf ears
Oreo
S***
Person can choose their parents America still have the right
The true Veil favorite cookie
To whip
Disingenuous
Don't call me black
Call me
Stop
Kick it up one more notch
AAA
Gamma quadrant
And I do not think black on the end
That's right
I do not
I think I think
On the end
Are you sure
Have you seen how the
Decrepit
Have you seen what you're doing
This is exactly
So is he not this color of the skin
But judge the man on the inside
Someone
Answer
Purple stuff
Make me a quadruple
.
Okay here's what
Don't think
Do we live
Inability to write
Being number one on the bottom of the world
Song
No no it's problematic
I think that maybe
He has no connection to music
Whatsoever he likes the Rhythm inherent
To a lot of the musical genres
I don't know
I don't know I can't unpack anything other than that song would that be
I am
You see him just
They came back the other night
Damn
Recant
It's wrong still but not wrong anymore
Oh man
Flippers not crying
Right
I don't know man
But it is I think
Not world
Are we fighting the Civil War
Civil War really dangerously close to Alex's rhetoric and I'm uncomfortable with that but
Nobody
In this next
We get we get them at that would be a way better if Alex
It's 1861 2.0 out of them like
Alright
You are correct
I don't like it anymore
But you did mail
Reverend
He's back behind the pulpit
He's giving it given his wife one more time
What
Naruto still on Plex
If you think a scandalous
You absolutely cannot understand why I how to pronounce his name
He's he's hitting the Quan
Exactly like alley
I think it might be giveaway you're into something wrong
Quite
Turn all that s***
To check his white
I mean going back to the club before the Martin Luther King said it's not the color
The cookie on the outside with the color of the cream
Bizarre
Such a remember to the opposite
That's the wrong lesson
It doesn't matter if you're black on the outside so long as you remember
Junior specifically saying
Let's all be white
On the inside
Reverend Manning
Detox a lot of s***
He talks a lot of match
But he's also a man of action
Well that's worse
Find out about some of his action
And I assure you this is going to lead
To a very funny story
Who's coming in from
All bus
New York
Of the universe
So
Where you take away from that
The date from Idaho
Receipt tracker
Who's broke
Is going to hitchhike all the way from Idaho.
Go to Harlow
For the trial
No
Put on
Mock trial
But he pretended was real
He was putting Obama on trial that he is ineligible to be president
But I have a right up here they might as well
Thousand people were going to show up
The actual attendance was somewhere in the neighborhood of 75 salon
Was there or at least
Some pictures that you took documented
It was supposed to be a seven-day March
I don't know if you made it all seven days but he was predicting it on the 7th Day when they March
Chrysler
About the determined
Trial
The Outlaw World Ministry Church
Call
Greatest trial in American history
He says the proceedings are not a mock trial and are permitted under the US Constitution
Make no mistake about it
Big Brother this is a mock trial
I mean yes
Clearly permitted
Show me kids article Obama's lies fraud
Can special counselor Patrick Fitzgerald open investigation
Countryside to quote
The trial which will include a legal legal Scholars and retired Court officials will examine several issues including Obama's
Birthplace is citizenship status
His academic credentials
Ties to the CIA as a student
Dr. Manning coined the term the long-legged
The represent Obama
Reverend Manning has intestinal fortitude in the face of adversity
He stands on ordering principle
Having the courage to face the Obama machine
This is one heck of a man of Courage with convictions
Despair
Obama's Marxist agenda and Obama himself cannot prevail
Let the trial begin and may they find Obama guilty
Is not covering this trial through there a couple articles on Salon Bernardo
Tobler is on a WordPress blog
What's up
Not covering the trial
And very little information is being reported
Conservative monster that's another blog
Is attending the trial and blogging information in writing the updates on the trial
Let's get the information
Emails and whatever other ways are possible
I thought WorldNetDaily was covering this trial but haven't seen any articles as of today
So we got we get to some updates
Protest March around Columbia
Later on the indict
Midsommar Reddit
The indictment by Grand Jury know they weren't
Anderson
Directions it was not a real grand jury
By the cracker on the outside
Absolutely
The indictment
Please please read the vault
Columbia University
Fraud and mail fraud
Columbia University knowingly concealed the fact that Obama is not a natural born citizen
Columbia University 8th and obstruction
Justice
The president of the United States
Sensitive material posing a danger to National Security
Also of note
The prosecution charges of treason and Espionage to avoid complications with a death sentence
Wonderful even in the fake trial there like hold on I don't think we're going to get them on these couch
I'm going to be too complicated
People marched around Columbia University
A couple people walked around Columbia University on day one
Navigate to comes along
D2 the Columbia trial started off with an alternate judge presiding over the case
YouTube what is 1
Loyal Church followers and she's also aspiring to run for governor of New York
Judge hunger is reportedly returning for Sunday's hearings
His name is Dave from Ida
Are they should remain
Keep an open mind not to make a decision or final determination as far as the verdict
What is a horse and pony show
The prosecutor is not going to be a partial
Tributary bands
I don't know probably like
Sack of potatoes
A big bag of Oreos
George Washington never had the powers that Barack Hussein Obama has
Mannington mentioned that Obama has an ability to manipulate the media and people unlike any other politician
Today this is given Obama even more power
Manning's them suspiciously state
But he would not be surprised if Obama Center
Undermine his trial
Easy dessert
I don't know
Malia
Zehnder's
Do some
Not credible
Don Lemon wearing a blond wig
Non credible
Judged at Jury
Witnesses
Can the Judge also be the witness that's Jim Johnson
You are the judge but I also call you to the stand
Okay
Vet
Obama's fingers stamp
With a two digit
Year and no one would ever do that
So he got his mailman to go on record it set
Well that's
Concrete case
Testify
Investigators later determined that Obama reportedly had over 30 different Social Security numbers
They came up in the computer what his name was entered
Bentley then alleged that the number Obama is
Currently using is
I was born in 1890 in Connecticut
He then noted that Obama never lived in Connecticut
So they also have to bring proof he never lived in Connecticut
Otherwise they could not definitively prove a 120 years old
Real vampire
Because he's lived for thousands of years we also mentioned that if you ran Obama's social security number
The results came up as Barack Obama
Did not belong
Not sure
That doesn't make sense yours where the postal worker gets involved
Jeff Smith to take the stand
Ask him about the controversy over the two digit and four digit years
Smith testified that the post office always
He was unsure how Obama
Tube service card at home
Show me a two digit year
There's a bunch of nonsense
If you lived in Harlem
And you all the sudden
Discovered that your mail was being delivered by a black white
To promise
It's interesting to me that the coverage of the case
Just stopped
After day 2
Stopped after day to they may not have made it today
Entirely possible
Court was not
It was nonsense
Picture of
The original judge was supposed to be there I don't think was a judge
You know how like if
If you run the show
When someone cancels last minute
Yeah it's trying to get it taken care of find replacement I imagine
F****** Reverend Manning just sitting there like
You knew fake judge all the Elders of his dirty ass
You got to come play a judge
That's where they
This is one of my favorite things
That James David Manning his alleged over the year
At this one actually went a little bit viral
So some people may know about this one this is great
Inform you the song
Liberty protest
Sunday
Shocking
Several members of the
Pennsylvania
You know the fellow that was with us
Special meeting this Sunday here at
We were meeting
Someone
Church
It is
Straight
The Inquisitor
News
Paper
Because we had stated
Ground Zero
Homosexual saltemike person such as
Who lives
Who is a sodomite
No
Nope
Mail
And they were
There are
.
You think that use milk that ship expensive
His argument breaks
His argument breaks down to basically the gays like to eat semen and I have a great time XO
Because they want people to have more of a fun time
I'm so they stealthily put it into Starbucks
Lattes
But because of the cement and because people f*** in the bathroom
Yeah but
I think
Okay
Also easier than that
You can
Can sexually transmitted
Airborne
He's not a doctor
Demonology degree from Heaven actually have
This is just
This is classic
James David Manning ship
This is my kind of stuff
Going out
It is putting in the pike roast
And you know that you always do fibroids
Call Gerald
And the sodomites
You know it's true
Cuz I would drink
India
Information
F****** sources
He's at he's letting it loose
This is great really like drunken hi Alex
More life
So
I think if we break it down
I think
Reverend Manning
Field left
I think there's a big piece of it that like
Aldi's sodomites
Unlike targeting
Starbucks
I don't get to have fun
I don't get to enjoy whatever one else if
And he's bummed out about it
I met on top of that repressing homosexual
Stand that
He's the reason
Yeah
Yes he thinks that everybody else's the barrier
All the while
It was him
Or perhaps his wife
Yeah they all that cream
When I say that I believe he's a repressed homosexual I say that based on having listened to
2 tons of clips of him
Where is like
Really talking about homosexuality
I'm kind of
Like the way you speaks about his hair is a like a sensual lysing of stuff
It doesn't need to be sensual
In that text
Jeans
And that
Any talks about how they're going to get you and stuff like that
Come on man
It's very clear he thinks homosexuality is zombies
More or less
In 2015
December 2015
He comes on Alex Jones a show I think we've laid out pretty clearly he's alert
I'm like
Three other disease
Is Ebola
You're like a present because I mean if you're going to be a homophobic monster
Hugo with HIV
Caribou Coffee is Ground Zero for the whooping cough
Go to be a high-class disease like consumption
Nevermind
So like I said
It's freakin hysterical people
Okay so he's on in December 2015 Alex has made his full jump
Turn on team Trump
I've made it a mission to try and get Trump in the office
Right here's what's interesting
Track of James David Manning
You just blend into the background since
The time that he said that that's out of my for putting semen in lattes
I went to his YouTube page
I found a video that he released just the other day
That is a little bit interesting
Okay
I think
Does he regret perhaps
Trump getting elected
I don't know but this clip is actually about Alex Jones
Ocean
I don't want to go on Alex broadcast
Strongly disagree with
And then
The state of
Actually
But
So he doesn't
Call Tim tribulation Trump he believed the times
Which begs the question
Did he support him originally secretly in order to bring it
What does
As a man of the cloth
So to speak
Maybe a little bit too close
To the end times
It's possible
What do you mean a broken Oreos today
Quadruple
So I want I want to just pull up real quick
His his YouTube page
Give you a little bit of a rundown
Some of his recent
Videos
Because the titles of them
Include stuff such as
Donald Trump
Turn
And I don't know exactly what made him turn
I don't care to go do an investigation
Videos
I'm so glad I'm coming out as gay
The two days ago it's collusion everybody
About how Russian collusion is real
Hairstyle Trump
Black white
Just hate him
There's no hope for people
Get your little hands off Twitter you nasty little critter and his picture of trump with tiny hands
Classic white trash a picture of
Picture of trump supporters
Goodwin
Here
Is the voice of racist in America
I'm a victim of police brutality
Contacts
He also used to be a really big advocate of being against
Socialism
Socialized medicine talks about how
He has a video from a week ago Healthcare is a right
It's a picture of Bernie Sanders
Something's bucking happen
I mean I think
Maybe
Maybe he found out how awful we actually
Trump calls athletes SOB's
Will trump pardon Paul manafort
There may be Russian death threats
On it now
Like is he
To have a come-to-jesus
I don't f****** know
Tribulation Trump is creepy
Will Mike that one's a little bit
Lake Hughes
He's on
Bucked up
It's so f***** up I like Sanders insurance plan
Michael Flynn never expected to be in government
Reasons why I'm kicking Trump's rump
Well I don't like
This is
He's really bad it right
What happened
Lake at the end of this episode You couldn't possibly have imagined that the end result would be in 2017
He's going against Trump he's going after him
I guess he did
Know what white supremacy
Really was possibly or maybe got a payout
Or something like that
Fluoroscopy
Okay I got I bet that's what Alex would say
Yeah
I don't know but I'm going to play for Alex
Really wanted a black
Brandon Tatum
He's got that guy who put out a video about how the NFL players need to shut up
Gravity is the new
He's gone white male guide
I'm not comfortable with that
This is from 2017
There is
Further and
Destruction on the way
According to God's word
Tribulation
And the
Donald Trump
And the office
America
Yikes
So actually it's not reasonable
And what he's doing is that you realized
Is Brandon works a lot better if he
Always been
The guy that you can go to
To get your daily dose of being attacking
President
He was significantly smarter than Alex Jones in that regard
I hate Obama cuz he's
Is the president so I'm going to support the guy who hates
The most
Becomes president
Supporting
Trump
He's like well I hate the guy who's president now so I love the guy who hates Trump the most
Bernie
Right
And propaganda
Like these guys
Legitimately only work as under
Right they can't be in power or else they realize that they become an apparatus of the state
Alex
What's the difference
Pass that they've gone down is Reverend
Element of the game
F*** I've got to turn on Trump
Or else this game doesn't work
And whatever amount of money he's making is enough to run a church in
Can Harlem look at the big building
Yeah so he's making enough for that which is
Which is something all so he doesn't pay it
Second
Well I mean
He doesn't have to
About it
Governor
The false narrative
Someone in power
So now the tax thing I want to leave everyone with it
Is an article from Cocker or not
Splinter
Splinter news has the same layout
Is Gawker that's what I thought
Yeah well it's the actual website
Is gone but
Jezebel
Spending all those webs right
Okay so it's it's one of the family is essentially
After a year of a couple of years of Gawker being gone there like
That's fine but
Right right
Article from February 20th
16 this homophobic preachers worst nightmare is about to come true
As about Reverend Manning
On the coldest Valentine's Day weekend in Harlem
19 C
Pastor James David Manning has
The fires of Hell on his mind
In less than two weeks
The church was due to be foreclosed upon
Quote
This is a sodomite government landgraab he told his congregants advertising the church
The Force 4 story brick and terracotta building on the corner of West 123rd Street and Lenox
6th Avenue
Reed's Jesus would endorse Donald Trump
As the chief pastor of Outlaw world
Wide Ministries
1981 Vanagon
Is Infamous for preaching homophobia and vulgar
Conspiracy theories
Not just from his pulpit in Harlem
Live stream
Twice each Saturday on YouTube
But also his daily internet program to The Manning Report
Before the recent foreclosure controversy
Church
Was probably best known for hosting a mock trial of Barack Obama in which the president was considered
Convicted in absentia on 17 counts including treason fraud and sedition
It's possible that this reporting is a little off cuz I went to the appeals court
Throw those out
Today's sermon have begun begun benignly enough
We thank God for making it back from the ski trip safe and sound
He said to about 70 worshippers
Nearly all of them black women
Many of them with young children
His own wife was seated behind him at the altar
Soon though Manning had to address the elephant in the room
Last month a state judge order the building at
It's a foreclosure 102 million dollars in unpaid tax
An auction is scheduled to take place on
On February 24th
Venomous stroke of divine irony
To lgbtq service organizations
Launch fundraising campaigns to buy the property
The Day of Reckoning was getting closer
Manning says he believed the court order is invalid on legal grounds
Cuz he has a law degree from School Of course
He says it has to do with water and sewage taxes that should fall under religious
Exemption rules
But according to public records obtained by the website
There are there
Least nine federal tax liens against the church
Among other dads
Despite 186
$6,000 in tax
Benefits already granted
Manning said he believes the case to be political retribution for his attacks on all Bob
Huiclaims
We believe is a Taliban
Who killed his own grandmother
Shut me up sees my ability to amass power and influence
He said in his sermon
But he pledged
To fight I will continue to pursue Obama until he's in prison
I believe God has given me the power to do that
Then Manning apologized to the congregation before he said in describing President Obama's late mother
Stanley Ann Dunham
Not only was she a s*** but she but she was a pair of dirty underwear
He said
There were murmurs of all men from
The pews in the third row a toddler in a three-piece suit played with the rings on his grandmother's fingers
Richie at I held behind her back cuz she
She solemnly about her head
Alright journalist
Set a little bit of a flourish
Continuing to read this article
We'll get you something that I
School
This is 26
August 26th
Virgo
I think it might have been
I'm not entirely sure I should look like
You know what I should have looked at up
And I will in a second
But
The reason that I want to get through this
Or get down
Intuit
Tacular
Piece of that
Fun
One of the groups
That's what I was trying to buy
The other property
Is the Ali Forney Center which is lgbtq
Organization
That we have donated to in the past and we encourage people to donate to absolutely Ali Forney Center
Lgbtq youth has raised at least
Thousand dollars towards the purchase of Outlaw Church
Rivers of Living Water in lgbtq
Spiritual group nearby in Harlem is raised
Significant
The Ali Forney Center is a critical organization
Open estimated 1.6 million kids
Experience homelessness
40% are lesbian gay bisexual or transgender
The Williams
A sex
Syngenta research
Search Group at the University of California Los Angeles
Lgbtq
New York found that about half were black
The most common reason they gave her being homeless is
Rejection by their families Williams
They're more likely to drop out of school due to harassment and bullying
Facing poverty and unemployment challenges many of them turned
Sex work
They're victims of disproportion
Violence to
Hey 1997 the Ali Forney Center has nickname
Namesake
A gender non-conforming
To the city shelter system was shot
The head in Harlem
Does 12 blocks away from outlaw
Before he was murdered Forney would sometimes sleep on the hill in Marcus Garvey Park
At the end of Outlaw block
He was known for agitating
I've known for agitating for police investigation
Into the deaths of
What is queer friend
Still 200 homeless gay and transgender youth are on the waiting list for a bed every night
The group says
Covenant group another New York organization that caters
Bahamas
Has to turn away
7280 young people every month due to lack of
Capacity
Taking over the outlet Church would allow Ali Forney Center to
To put a roof over morehead's every night
According to Carl system
Siciliano
Its executive director
They also wanted to run a catering business
To feed
Homeless
YouTube
I am. That's her.
It would be awesome if Christian
In the f******
I'm looking this up okay so
Here lucky
Here's what it says on Wikipedia
In January
Tina State order the outlaw worldwide Church would be sold to public
Foreclosure auction
After failing to pay creditors more than 1.02 million dollars
I'm sad for the New York
Recording a lot not liable for
Define citing the Court's ruling of
December 2000
Purposes
Lgbtq
To youth homeless services
They're all this
A temporary stay on the sale was granted
21st of April 26th
In September the Judgment of foreclosure was
So they still on the prowl
Goddamn
Yeah that sucks
God dammit
That could have gone to helping right
Jordan news for everybody but the good news is
I mentioned
Outside
Someone sodomized
Sup
There's always that but I wanted to ask
This episode was about this horrible
Massage
Self-loathing
Homosexual probably
With you know just a reminder that there are great organizations out there
Amber Alert tons of them aren't necessarily the ones that we
Support
Absolute
And stuff like that really is a reminder of the realities of intersection
The world that we talked about this crazy bigot propaganda
Conspiracy theorist world
And people who were really trying to help
People who are not being able to help because of these
That is a reminder
It sucks that we have to live in the world we live in but we do
Anyway
Redwood
I don't either
Everyday I eat
We should be
Burning ship
Like the we're at the stage now towards
Insane it's all crazy
We're all just we're all this place where we're at
Kind of like children
Again
Just like we were in the in the run-up to the election if it's like
Will sooner or later later there's going to be somebody who's
Reasonable
Who is going to get in the way
And there's no
There's nobody,
Yeah
There's no reinforcements
Go back.
And there's no it
Like we're trying to say is be the change you wish to see in the world
It's just a lot more fire
Sincerely considering starting August
For what
Is a generalized General hungry like that
I had somebody
Text me earlier
Well
If you want to make a change you need to
And I'm just sitting there going like
Until we get rid of the oligarchs
That does not match
It's not doing it like this
The people that we f****** voted for
Enduring a cross-check in those sorts
Disenfranchised
Champagne
Buy these
Oligarchs are lesser of two evils
But also
The amount of people that you could probably influence
Is
Not as much
As will be invalidated by those
Exact that Venus area
People have put into place yes you should encourage
To fix everything
It is a toppling of all this b*******
It has to
To go it's system
Broke
B from scratch
Write a couple of them Amendment
That we have in their constitution terms of freedoms like that
Especially
Yeah
And that's
Special
Hehehe
Is is
There is a war coming
And it's not going to be us
Does Russia
It's going to be red versus
Blue
And right now
All the guns are available
Haha
I'm just saying while they're available
Maybe get a gun
Because there have
But a lot of them
But I mean even Alex Jones is talking about
You seen upswings of liberals with guns with
The shooting range
How much of that is just a
Fear and paranoia is unclear but I do think you're seeing
I mean some liberals arming themselves
Kind of that kind of situation
Yeah
I get I get where you're coming from and I
Tivity of discussing medicine
Feeling these sorts of things but at the same time I don't want us to
Descendant 2
That's not where the show
Works
Because then we're doing the same thing on the flip side of the
The thing we're fighting against her though
That's what that's
Rational I mean more like
It is
It is something
Where are
Genuine like at this point
I think one of the things that I am holding onto is not
Beer
I'm not afraid of
Of this is
I'm in Rage
Yeah that is the thing that is
Inspiring
Me too actually f***
Like that
That's inspiring I called Congress
I've donated money
Whoever left that
Bucket of s***
I hope so because you advocated for shooting multiple
Totally possible we got someone to
If you are a policy wonk that left a bucket of s***
On his doorstep we won't get it
Yeah but a lot of buttons
Let's let's wrap this up
Those
I'm tired
Go to bed but we can go to
Malijet.com Twitter at knowledge underscore fight
Please show we like it when
People listen
You do
Occasionally get grandiose
And some of your
Regarding our
No no no no problem
Slightly grandiose but that's
That ameur
You are still making
I can't do takes anymore
There's no Take that is doing it
Twitter
And f******
Goddamn
Or just f****** Reeds at
Do the work
Cuz they're shipped
It needs to be done don't don't like
Include bigotry
Include being an idiot
Sources of
A lot of those problems
This is steadfast
Refusal to read any
Refusal to check into
And
If you don't fall in
Trap
The world be a better place
Which is another good point
Well accepted by the fence man
Now and now he's turned a new Leaf
I'm still not on his side
That on his side he still talks about like
The sodomites
I can't get on board
We are on, wasn't going to do that
This is coming out on Monday we will be I will be live you will not be you're busy but Tuesday Wednesday
ATM
Please come join us
Have some fun
There's a lot of fun stuff that happens in
In the chat room chat room are f******
Fantastic
I was a little bit
Regarding the
Haha cuz I wasn't sure what would
It's on wieldy I wasn't sure how that would check out but we Act
I have
So many smart
People in there
To the show
Which is
I really really f****** cool
I love it one of our walks out there
Big shout out to
I don't know what screen name is
Abused and I don't know their real names
I like the idea that's real cool anyway
Let's wrap this up
Prove that
Usually invited
Jon rappoport to f*** himself but
I think in this instance
Reverend Manning
Really takes priority
This guy I've been waiting forever
Bring him into your world has all of his teeth
I believe so yes
But you know he's he's officially number to after professor hamamoto
Favorite
Are your favorite type of
Well yeah but like the reason that I'm emoto's got to be up at number one
Is it he has the anarch to him
What is fascinated
Respected scholar in the world like a very interesting area of study that he sexualization of Asian box
You just goes crazy again
It disrupted protest at there's f******
I brought my
Guitar and they wouldn't let me
Napolitano is involved with
Weird raisin electronic pulses that are going through
So he's never I don't think he's ever going to be bumped out of the number one spot but number two
Very close behind him is this Reverend Manning
And we might revisit him again
Cuz he is
Either well that is
That we got another Carrie Callahan I believe
Unfortunately again Isabel
Wanted to that.
Unfortunate massari
The untethered soul that she's a thematic
God dammit
Go fuc yourself
Reverend Manning although I think a lot of things
Incredibly funny for the wrong reasons
You need to go fuc yourself you dumb
Piece of s*** in a bucket outside your own church
Alex
Birthstone colors