Holding
Alex
Everybody welcome back to knowledge
Brad we are back in the saddle once again hope you're having a great day out there today we are going to have
Very special episode of this podcast
Where
No Maybe
Obsessed with race
Abortion
All sorts of other
Conservative issues
Conservative
Alright alright remember
Episode you spoke prophecy
And you just did again is a lot with energy
Brighton
How right I am
Becoming like the more we do this the more Alex Jones
Start the war game also by the way
Bluetooth
On Friday show
He actually had a Gaston is like Alexa
I think you look sexy with me
I got to check the statistics of every download some occupied Texas
It's not like Austin it is occupied.
Yeah there's no doubt that digital drop box office
For the first time
Is the show where I listen to way too much Infowars Alex Jones
In particular
And my friend I have no f****** clue what he's on about and we are getting to the body
Explore A Day in the Life of Alex
What
For the longest time Joe Rogan has been trying to get Alex Jones on his podcast
You can't because
Austin
Like to do Skype call
Call Sophie
And lo and behold it was her episode 911
Of course
Horse
Joe brings italics
And join them along for the ride is a young man by the name of
Eddie Bravo
Eddie Bravo martial arts
Instructor and all-around with all due respect
Totally
You could beat my ass like a rented mule
I have no doubt about that.
Call martial arts
Instructors
But I'm also saying that all Idiots Are Marshall
I believe that's how that works
Come on man
Like you really believe the Chemtrails we've been listening to Alex Jones and this guy to you is the first time you're like
Come on man I have a special relationship about
Connected or energy
Like the
I wonder if
He felt something weird the day I was born
Pictures like a premonition
Just like that old gypsy woman said that he would be taken down
Cross-eyed dick hole in the Chicago
Specific
Sweet cakes
Eddie believes in like Chemtrails super into that
And also apparently doesn't believe in dinosaurs
Maybe not totally of a headlock total any beliefs
That's what I do I don't know that for sure conversation should
Stop in determining somebody
Idiots
Studied Eddie Bravo so I don't know if that's for sure but they bring it up a couple times on the episode
A little bit
But you have that like
Six-year-old boy phase of liking dinosaurs
Stegosaurus
Not real
Here's
I overheard a conversation at work the other day
And this guy was like
I'm not sure if I believe in dinosaurs
If that was a non sequitur that's the best thing to hear
If I was just writing on the trailer
Woke up like The Manchurian Candidate
Just like dinosaurs
A lot of people who don't believe in dinosaurs
Believe it like Jews bury the bones
And so you know that like a lot of the anti dinosaur stuff is
Is antisemitic
Nothing that isn't pinned on the Jews
Nope literally everything
Literally every
Yeah
Dep the media
Why do they have to make us like that I don't know
It's so f******.
So the show starts out on a boring note
Because Alex
He wants to make his presence felt
So
They start the show off
And the first clip I'm going to play is
I would I would call the first lie
First lie and exaggeration
That is the new segment of our show
This one is about Alex Jones assertive
Political leaning
George Bush jr.
And you were always against the power structure the media
President
What's up
You said we were going to do the first lie
I believe we're on lies
One through 44 right now
Does he think
The Communist Chinese
Saudi Arabia are all working
Gathering
Absolutely
Or does he think they're individual actors
All of them coming to the same conclusion
Then drop
Then Alex and Trump
Two of them
Yeah I think what he would say is that they're not Nessa
Sara Lee working in concert but it's
Some enemy of my enemy is my friend
For a dollar
Not more
Yes
Southside
Because
Hillary and Obama
What's up
Where did he lose you
How
Breakfast he is on
Somebody else
The show
Barrage of nonsense
The same as social engineering is that like a
Of course
He wants real Prosperity not social engineering and I don't know how it is those things are related
They're not really but they aren't his social engineering
He's trying to keep us poor
The social Engineers are doing things for our advantage
They want a dumbass down they want to make us
Pay too much in taxes
All this stuff
Why and how
Super Bowl Li
How far you have I believe it's Super Why
Before out as I was using metric
Social engineering right one of these social engineers
Let's go through this all right you're poor now
Oh god dammit I'm pouring out how does that
Cuz I'm not you
Fremont
Then your loss is my gain
What's the Celtics score
I mean is the engine is in the hole
Why are we having
Quit never one of them already game we had a lot today
That was us intelligence
New York congressman
I said
Yakima computer
So this is the direction that goes we're going
This idea that he predicted or he had sources the told him Anthony Weiner was going to get arrested for child
That's like him saying he predicted 9/11
Feels like everyone knew something was coming
Ever since they found
We looked on
Humans computer affordable
New emails
Yeah we're looking on her computer was to find out if he had
Pictures of that underage
That's what the child
That's that's what the article say
11 stroker kit
Nachos
17 + 1/2
To me and I'm not saying
This law is bad
But I think
It's a little bit weird about
Support child
I'm not I don't know what has a prophecy
I'm not at your child for not going on though
Fake news
It is weird
Illegal is that there are different
Use of consent in different states
Federally you know what I mean
Ginger Alden
But you can't take pictures of
That's bizarre.
But it's bizarre
I don't think
If there's any part of any of those laws that isn't bizarre at any given point
Human history
There's no doubt
Human beings
Especially Anthony Weiner
Especially God he was so good
For so long
He did good things the problem is
Who doesn't
I don't think that's other stuff
Yeah it's all that other stuff that really bums me out
During his time in government
He was kicking ass for good people
It did seem that what he was doing
But
We now end up
In the murky Waters
Something I hope we never have to talk about
Time baby first 40 minutes of the show they talk about
Pizzagate
And it
So
Bucked up
Cuz here's why
What video wrestling
Joe also Joe Rogan
Alex Jones
Are all struggling with the fact that pedophilia is
Like
Ascensore in like a is this reality
Sort of baffled by it and because they have to be like
Now it's listening this is real
Make discovered pedophilia no but they think that no one else believes it's real
Or whatever everyone else
Whitewash
I think that's the number one fear for literally every parent
On the planet right now
Parents so it makes sense
Yeah it's fine but I don't think anybody doesn't know about good job at all
Tracking from point A to point B where a is the pedophiles exist
And some of them have been high-powered
That does not lead necessarily to
There is a ring of pedophiles running the Democratic Party
And
All of our staff
Worldview is contingently based
On
Pedophile blackmail
Keeping people in mind and underlying Narrative of everybody's a pedophile
No no no no
Whoa not getting married
No because I don't want you to pay them in like the
It's not representative
What he has said
Is that
Pedophilia is used as blackmail
So people in power don't get out of line
He has in the past multiple times
Set the powerful
You have to like
Soccer kid
In front of the elite
So then they know
Then you are
You're have no moral
And that you can be trusted and
If you get out of line they've got that on
He said that before on the show
Yeah so
So let's say I
Run for governor governor
Let's not even called a good steak
Let's call it Rhode Island
Because of Governors houses
Alright I am running for Senator of the
The great state of New Hampshire
Which has
The population of nobody knows
Most of the country lives in New Hampshire most people can't tell the difference between
It's the one that goes down while the other one goes
How can I help
I'm running
I'm on the cusp
Unless they get
40%
The only way I can get over that last
Really
Control Bureau
Slugworth in Willy Wonka
Everlasting Gobstoppers
People that it stretched out another kid inside the trench coat
I mean like
I don't want to make light of it
This because it is a horrible thing
But I believe
Sincerely
Also makes light of the real problem that it
Exists in the world
Cuz he's using it for political gain and political point
As opposed to treating it as a real
Yeah but not least if you are if you are all the time
Then that diminishes the effect of
Actual people who are pedophile
Let's hear a little bit of
Females that Alex
Pretty much lies about
Okay
$5,000 in hot dogs
Really
How to make a male prostitute
To keep the f****** mouth shut well Cosentino's bad things happen if you don't
Federal c********* charges possible for Anthony Weiner
I'm on record months ago
Look at 4chan
What's up
You confused
Fortune
You know what 4chan
Yeah
A lot of investigators
Air quotes
What what's
Do they know about Fortune
I know he said the words
Yeah he knows it exists right he's heard of it
You haven't gone there
In my experience it's mostly people posting like
Pictures
Graphic pictures and then trying to bully people into killing
Large part of what
There are separate boards
B discuss anime and paranormal show
I like how we said that at the same time
Kentucky
Does look back I don't know if you knew that when you look at it this morning but the
The thing is that a lot of the
Stuff about the
The codes
That were used in emails
A lot of it comes
From quote-unquote researchers on 410 and Reddit
And now vote
See that website
Reddit head over to this
But they talked about
But there was a whole subreddit dedicated
Pizzagate
And then they started dachshund
10 people
And so
They like your band
We might close this thing down
Play started.
In the TV show Heroes
The second season
Actually disagree I think
A lot of legs
I have no further noblest Faith argument
Today
The thing is like a lot of the codes
Were found to be
Completely made up
A lot of it wasn't based on
Any
Slang for the world
Well here's the thing that wasn't email but it was
A guy was writing that last
Year Obama ordered
Like pizza and hot dogs from
Chicago
To be flown and it was $65,000 worth for a big event
Right now
Sure it could have been
F****** gay prostitutes to stuck off
That's possible
Also seems like
From Chicago it was actually be pizza and hotdogs
We are really weird about
And hotdogs
Is something that people
Notorious the especially people are plastic you have a way of making hot dogs
Are you saying that he might be ordering those two things from his City that are most
Well known about his Paris and he's ordering
Plan I don't know what's playing
Character Mexico
Call David Swan let's go with blonde
Took that that is one of the emails that I think
Really
Probably unfairly
Misrepresent
I'm baby
Flat-out bowls
How much leeway as possible in case there's some
I don't understand or whatever local b******* food
You're going to order pizza from Chicago
If you're from Chicago
From Chicago
Chicago
Islamic senator from Maine
Ordering $65,000 of
Crabs
It's not dirty p****
Ordering $65,000 worth
Pizza and hotdogs for men
Photos are frosted
How do you know if
Well there's that New Haven style pizza
Network
Looking for all of us
Joe responds really well to a couple things
But overall I've got to give him a grade of likes
C-
Actually calling
Not true
I don't know about that
I give Joe way more leeway
You can't know everything
In this particular instance
Joe does not have that
He is a pure this friend entertainment
And this is all like
He
Cheerleader
That's crazy
Going to say
And he is perhaps the only person in our field of vision on the Alex Jones
Situation
By no means
Himself to be adjourned
No. Never once said
You should listen to me because I tell only the truth
I still
Curious and he likes learn
Chupacabra
Yeah I will say that after listening to this like
3 *
Yeah
Hate Rogan
I don't think
I don't have I didn't lose
Ton of respect for him but I think what he did was bad
I think having Alex Jones on a platform like that
On his show
Really
Can only serve to humanize him
And really only serve to normalize
Can I pick up a dangerous absolutely
I don't think
It's a positive thing
To do
You get this guy on your like
Is going to be like in this
Situation
You pointed out the
Jimmy Fallon singing
And then taking another
Another piece of it
I heard he's a paddle
Come on man
There's a lot of people who I think probably would respond to what I'm doing
Why do you care
And I care because I was Jones's incredibly relevant
And everyone's ignoring him because he's a joke
Because
Can joke
The country
But I like
Like to the point that Joe Rogan has a huge audience
Rat King
With his appeal
Like really
Plus people who were streaming it live
And now a day after the day after that if so came out
It's been watched over like 1.5 million times on YouTube
A sideshow
I understand that
Alphabet
You are bringing Alex Jones on because you like
Looking are weird
Discussion of why
Pizzagate
And Joe being
This is what
This is where Joe Rogan is
Actually pretty dumb
What the f*** is pizzagate
There was this very angry
Did you see
He did
Do you know what he's talking about you
Okay so this local news guy benswann did a story about
It was like about
Justino the broad Strokes
About what people had found on Reddit
And stuff like that
Okay
People is like a primer
Yeah it's a lot of complaints about it but I'll get to them after the Clippers
Alright
And he was making some connections to between that book for child pedophilia
And
End
He also made
Confirm child molester
Important stops
So true that hastert in jail
Extruded hamster is a known pedophile that a judge called the serial pedophile
Is 100%
That's a hundred percent
Yes
If you look at it dispense one guy with his
He's just kind of expressing
What is weird about this
And
I was kind of shocked people calling him a moron
So people were calling him a moron not because he
He covered a top
Did not adhere to any of the rules of Journalism
When you're doing the story
Yuri
You fact check
Text thing
And when he did this
Did is regurgitate things that were found
On conspiracy blogs
And on Reddit and vote
And these are two things
Without doing any
Absolutely not
So you're saying that he was a moron
Yeah absolutely
Such a misunderstanding of what journalism
Very hard job
Resume have to
You have to you have to try and get people to talk to you
In order to publish something in a mainstream publication
You can't
One source for things
Yeah
I have friends who are journalists
It's
Did they do
It's too fake news
Here's what I think it is here's what I think it is
We've got to the
Now where everything is
So
Australian
Lately baffling
Sing to the baby boomer generation
Other Generations
You were the same for like
All the way from your great-grandfather
Your
You pretty much live the same life
Our grandparents went from
Horses
To where now we can
Fly with our feet
Like
Really really quickly
To somebody who is for somebody who is
Let's call that let's call them simple
Okay
So rather than complicate things with
Multiples
Verifying
You just want a big
Strongman
But I think it even goes
Dad to our generation
Younger too because with the proliferation of the infant how easy it is to set up your own shop
You can just report things
I'm just saying
Yeah but that's not exactly a
What's more powerful now
You know William Randolph Hearst all the way back down.
Our Generation Now is much better at filter
That stuff out
Then you might imagine
I want
Statistically speaking
Crime is gone.
Everybody stinks
The opposite because our personal experience tells us otherwise.
Statistics is bulshit world so I
A bad sample
Is an education and all this stuff anyway
Prevailing narrative
Mission is always going
The actual
It's always true that generation
Wind up getting better at educate
Yeah it is
It is hard to divorce ourselves from
That like
Mass is
Map all the time
It's not all the time
It never stops
Talkin about
I never saw that
Seems like poop
Let me know he's referring to an email that does exist
Totally misrepresenting what it says
The lady who sang that these kids will be dropped off
To be looked at
Babysitting
Whatever I
But not as entertainment she says
She's like saying there will be these
Three kids
So you'll be entertained
And it's like a
Parrot saying like
Good luck
I think you're not going to be bored
Cuz he's kids
Is our ages 7 to 11
The rambunctious as f***
Right
They said it's interesting how any ATMs that we use
Just like in Daily conversation
If you pull them out of context
Is any kind of a ATM looks like
Emailing
They will be in that pool
Which you could take a
All we're going to get those bodies
Or it could be like a swim
Right ever again
Look at me in the eye for the next
10 minutes after you said that if my parents had email back when I was a kid
They would have said something like jam going to be in that pool
I love to swim
I loved it and we were too poor dead Dan.
It's fine whatever you want to find wherever you want to fight
Perfect instant and the way that he's lasciviously
Presenting it
Misrepresenting him is so f******
It doesn't have that ring of disgust to it it has more of that
Tablet ring of like no almost
Quit later when he's like
Almost going into a
Yeah where he's talking about like globalist taking your kids out of backyard
And then like
It's just a big guy comes up behind them
Punches him in the head like that
It's like a
Timmy is in the original Matrix
Where
They go through that office
Lobby and they can shoot everybody up
20 minutes of just slow mode
Yeah today to discuss that other than the second every moment
Lovingly you like just
Master
Vader mask
The differences in there was sort of like
An interesting artistic
Thing they were doing
And in this case
Alex is just trying to convince you of things that aren't true
Where your you're turning it into a fantasy
You're turning this
Horrifying things
People being shot again and again
This
Oh yeah you know you don't
Two things that Alex is good at
One of them
Slander laws
Is
Completely contradicting
Himself
In this club
Now be careful because the
Second part
Microphone.
Megyn Kelly went on and took a cliff
Hillary
With me Hillary Clinton kill children
Did will get the Apocrypha
Did that happen
Not quite
A perfectly honest version of what happened
Send was
Is spiritually correct
And that
He did
I just want to say though first before we talk about that
I'm not doing anything
If you eat
That their c****************
I would never say such a good way to not have to go to court
But the story is that I'm reporting that other people
Timezone is episode smart but it also shows
Your cards a little bit and that you don't believe what you're saying
Smart
No it's smart because of
He didn't you could get sued
You open yourself up to
Dangerous
Well I mean yeah it's it's
It's self-destructive but it's not smart
Knock knock
Do this
He's not like Dinesh D'Souza
Destructive a spot and then the thing about Megyn Kelly
Yeah no doubt
For the 10 millionth time
Okay there's not Isis
Is Al-Qaeda
No no
Okay
Feel similar if you don't know anything
That is it
Nailed it
But the thing about Megyn Kelly
Hatchet
Job
On him
What
Correct in a sentence
Who's my favorite Judy Blume
The thing about Megyn Kelly
Something sort of out of town
So in their piece about pizzagate
But they were doing it about how
The
Internet his sensationalize things that I have you
They play the Clippers
Alex Jones
He's coming in from break
Atlanta
Gorilla
I got a message
Search for Hillary
Do like a f******
Shoot promo
Honor like you the f****** wrestler
Are you just doing this
I'm not afraid of you
You
You know you kill and murder
Hillary Clinton
Who killed
And murdered thousands of children
She's personally raped
Children
Is he safe
Personally
What you're saying personally
Lexi the person now they cut at the end of that
And then on his show what he ended up saying is
I'm not talking about
This pizzagate kind of stuff
I'm talking about
Her killing Christians and funding
Islamic terrorism and stuff like that
To say
But what I mean is she did this like
Twice removed through the military or her
It's
It's a tactic
You know it's sensational
Gets people into taking you out of
Ridgeway
Which then give Tim the grievance to act
Like the victim
Yes it's
Just like or or Milo complaining that people don't want him to speak on their campus
Cellulitis
Wow that's really blatant
It's Not Butter
No I forgot I forgot the
I don't have is prepared that well at all
We're going to get to is the rank hypocrisy
On display and Alex admitting to it
Who cares
That's where we watch this where it where is it that they did that. The comparison the two up
Alicia
I love you
You don't like that you don't think Megyn Kelly's house
No
Yeah that's not okay
We have Illustrated on multiple occasions the
Credible
She goes to installed her based on her appearance
And all this stuff
Amen
Admitting
Yeah she's really pretty just want to make fun of
Know if you wanted any pretenses of Journalism if you want to pretend that you're
Standing up for the truth
And you yourself
I'm a bully cuz he's on the other imaginary side that I'm against
I think his rationale
At least
If I'm going to try and engage him
Even though
She is a woman in journalism
To him
It feels like punching
Very beautiful woman
She's a very successful woman
She's not psychotic
She's nuts.
So she's not relegated into having a business entirely safe
Stone selling fake pills
So to him that must feel like he's
Punching up
Instead of punching
Probably
Now
Humans is crazy
At least understand why you can rationalize that
His own my
Alex doesn't believe in prison
So he doesn't
Believe that because he
He's white and male he has any
Any privilege
I do my best
Succumb to his
Defense you immediately come back with why that is
The dumbest thing I could
In his worldview that is
Also if you're listening we're 40 minutes into this
Don't turn it off
Cuz at the end
F***** up are you telling our audience to turn it off
I'm getting self-conscious
Two and a half hours
Alright how about we do this
F******
Run the jewels
Let's try
Okay this next clip where it we've now got out of the murky Waters of pizza
The gate and we are getting into
Something about
A man
About the Iraq War
Anna and Afghanistan
I would save this is about Ally
Weird
They're not going
Production
And then look at the latest 2014-15
The 7%
Look at the ha
Memory
The reason that's a lie about a lie is that I don't think that most liberals
Deny that at all
No the idea that
There is a real
Weird thing going on with opium production
Weird at all
Absolute result of demolishing a country
Also Auto
Switch to something that they can do without any f******
Of course and we seem to have a vested interest in
Protecting
And helping it
A little bit weird
Most liberal people that I know most
People on our side of the fence
I don't know why we all know there's only one real
Alex Jones
But then also the lie about the it went
From 3%
Lights to ninety seven percent
33%
Jessica taken from when we were
Invading
Destroyed everything
Yeah
Easy to do
All your bones do all the stuff
Super easy if you look at the graphs of the percent of opium production so it's like flat
Like what year and then facts
Like I don't know what it'll be
Like 40 or so and then it is
Big Rock
Really
They make tons of opium
The perfect climate for it that's the thing that's
A lot of these
Codependent
Opium is
Smoke a lot open
Pima College
To opiates
Yeah I mean
Because it's not great
I took painkillers a couple times in my life and I didn't really enjoy them
Enemies there opium was really it was just
Do you smoke it with weed
Better than just being high
Mel was amazing
Is so
Delicious I remember correctly from Legends of the
The fall
I know that you can do it on a boat real
Yeah I'm sure
But also
This is important I Mad Men
Best drug use
Repentance become up later
But I wonder as I will not
To bypass
I want to be clear
We're not squares
I'm sitting here drinking
And some wine
You've got some whiskey
Author of how drunk
Alex Jones
Has been
Oh that my job
Straight
You so mad that people think it was drunk
I think if you're mad that people are drunk that just
The Earth
If you're mad that people think you're drunk
That just proves you're so much more drunk much bigger problem
Like if people thought that I was way too drunk
Regularly
Legitimate
Real talk
My reaction would be
Please talk to me
Me more about this
I want to know your
Perspective I want to know if you think I should get help
Do not like
F*** you I wasn't drunk
This next Eddie Bravo
Question
Eddie Bravo his questions ask Alex about why
Here's my here's my ass on the clean take
Can we
Isolate all of his questions
Create an Eddie Bravo's questions corner across talk
I have dreams but will more work
I saw physical hard as it is
Like an idiot hours of prep show
Anyways
Infowars is fake
Fake news
A lot of people out there think Infowars
Funded by Soros
Liberal conservative Administration
Israel
Call Sue
That's not an answer but
Happy that he's against
I don't think
Killing I don't that we were supposed to take away 4
Furniture but I
I think you started studies Fair
But I don't think that the track record really backs that up
I like that I feel like
Was
Kenny was Bravo being
As smart as he possibly could there
Well he gives away that he literally
Allergy forecast
You know you know
He repeatedly says that he listens to Alex everyday
It's all real
Anyway and then there's also the WikiLeaks
The u.s. leaks not the Russians
Always have
The Russians are take
People inside the
Part of his counter-coup narrative
Anyway the Clippers
Call Dad
Why do they think Infowars
Really intelligent
The real news is pmf
Soros
Which again
Is not true
No
George Soros
And they always ignore real facts I talk about
Only had one lesson
Breezy news
Competition with someone who has an independent news organization the operated
Well that's one Theory
No really is
If you don't really take
Okay
What is there is a monetary interest
You say that these Independent News Outlet
So don't go listen to them come listen to us
That makes sense
On a
Pure level
Wow
Till
You think for two
And you see all of the competing news Industries
Very many there are
Mysteries are united in saying
Alex Jones is full of s***
Yeah you got to put that also you look at all of the people who are in alternative media
Fairly
I don't know how to describe that they don't do their due diligence
In terms of Journalism
Like they just spout bulshit
Sensational and it gets
Posted repeatedly Raditz all attention-grabbing
S***
I would assume
I don't know if this is entirely true
But I would assume
The people who are legitimate journalist
Would f****** hate Alex Jones
Because he doesn't do the work
Jeff doesn't do the actual job ilysm
And it didn't
To work that they do
It is it is interesting go how
Turning journalist
Diamonds
Like
The only people who are
Still in journalism
Arnot
No journalist we have now
Exactly
And now it's even less than in their heyday
And the ones who are doing investigative journalism
F******
True Believers
Like these are people who
Will fight and die for a story
So I was one of them
I would put out
Like you're you're making a mockery
Everything that I believe
And I think that anybody who has a full awareness
And the importance of Journalism
Acknowledge the danger
Of someone like him
Becoming super popular
Especially because
Disposing
Is there
You guys
Are fake
Yeah and our enemy
So if you're demonizing the people who do the actual work
Well you don't
It makes total sense that they would hate him
Take away the financial aspect of it
Yeah
It's nonsense
The financial aspect
But you're much more you're much more
Effective
Getting that kind of gullibility
In-N-Out
Edit a legitimate criticism for literally all aspects of our lives right now we're done
It is always that
Instinctively
Yeah
Cui Bono
Okay so here I got to say Island
Requeeb owner
Here is where the show gets good up till this
Ladies and gentlemen
Distaval this previous hour now it's time to get it on
Preamble
The little bit
Now we start cooking
Let's do it
Is the fur
First instance
Alex
Teasing when he's about to break some big news
What is what do you think he does he reveals all of his sources
And tells us exactly what it is he's about to
You're not close
The basis of what's Happening
Okay
What a total a******
You are f******
To Be A Millionaire level ball
Teasdale unfiltered Alex Jones
I can't tell you how can I figure out
After the break
Yeah might as well be on Deal or No Deal
I told her I figured out the
Truth of the universe
I got a pea
Let me tell you
You know what the
Herbalife
Universe and everything
I'm going to tell you after
Years when he gets back from bathroom like three minute
Translator
A mighty might have been doing something in the bathroom
It's only a long path of your
News today
Precious
Super male vitality
Man with prostate issues
Left to right news Alex coming out of the bathroom
Represents
Never given
He comes into it
That's what I was hoping
He comes out of the bathroom with a bottle of Jack Daniels
Gentleman Jack
And from
From this
Point
He does not stop
Excellent
And like
You know it's it's not like
He's chugging it or anything like that
And it's
Really mark
You can really tell
Hellboy
And this is where we're going to have to start introducing us
Light
Little bit
Of pity
For Alec
There are a couple moments
That actually made me very
I believe that he has a problem with alcohol
Some of his behaviors
Suggest that he is unable to
Control himself
Listen
I don't want to go around diagnosing people
Responsibility
Dangerous for Layman
But what I glimpse
From this
A lot of these behaviors remind me of some of the worst drunk
That we know in
Year
If anybody other than
Joe Rogan Eddie Bravo were in that room
I think
There was
Be the potential for Alex Jones's career
Be ruined
By his
Yeah he
Real drunk
Excellent
The next clip
This is a hymn
Teasing information again
And then we have some evidence
Joe Rogan
Never listen to Alex Jones Show
Freddy
German cheers
Butt stuff
People were so
So much anticipation regarding the show much house
Do it
We don't make those noises
No
We do not
We don't do that
We are perfect
Grossest thing I've ever heard we all want to die right now
Breathe
Makes me sick
Well I mean
Outlook
Under braids
Telling me that they don't want him to breathe people that we know did a podcast
Podcast net worth
Dude
Half of this podcast
Is you guys breathing in
So hard to listen
So much of that now
Here we go this is where
Alex
Gotcha
Even heard you say a racial thing
Consequential
Ever
Almost I've never heard you discuss
We can just leave that without comment I don't really think we need to get into that we have
Refer to Oliver last episode
Let's just let the next episode this is a clip we're either talking about the Gravity by the p****
Alex does markable spin
Job for Donald Trump
His ever-lovin Volvo
That is friends with him
20 years ago it's all just completed
At the RNC speech he says Republicans
Executive order that they removing anaganaga protection
Do the lgbtq
Well
Complete
The opposite opposite approach
Brett
Actions speak louder than words
I don't believe
I don't believe the trouble necessarily hates gay people but I
I think he doesn't
I don't think he has anything to do with it I think it's purely Mike Pence
Donald Trump
Anyway
Call my b
To use a real
Yoruba
So again I wanted I didn't mean to cut there but I want to cut
Just to
Talk about this for a second
There's going around and Alex
Pictures of the lot in a lot of like Owen Shroyer is really big on this one of his
Reporters
This idea that
Being called a racist
Is worse than racism
Essentially
The idea that it's like an attack
On YouTube
Have
Some racist behaviors
Pointed out
Nvidia stock
Control Mecca
And I think that is
Dumb on one level
Test response
You could possibly get
But it really is it
F******
Denny's
Abusive
Sing to a wife-beater like
Oh you know I
Just don't don't point out his
Failing
You know
He's trying hard not to be a wife
Not awake
He slips up and be forever down again
To do it's not that he does
Time to have
I'm not sure that that analogy
Because
I am
Offended by your insinuation that I'm not
Well I think it comes back to this like
Refusing to acknowledge the Privileges
Like 88
It comes back to that
Different
We're talking about Alex
Right
As well as defending straight I want to take that away from it slightly and
You just look at the idea that calling someone a racist
Is away
To gain power over
That is not what people are doing
If it was
It would be a lot better by that
You can shut them up and
You can other
People by calling them a racist when they're not racist
As opposed to just
Authoring them by
Right
I mean it's
Located
It's the same as this idea of like
Calling the alt-right Nazis
He's trying to other them
When people were calling the Nazis are doing that because
Seem to be in bed with some literal Nazi
So they're not
You can't be offended in like if I look at a rock
How can I go
Tree no
Not okay
Is it really bad
Octopussy
He's a man
And those kind of do their type a hyper aggressive personality
Frank Demeter
The big one is in consonance with that Billy bush.
Laugh
Bushes and wait for joggers
Mindy
Wrestletalk
40% of all men should be murdered at this moment
Opening us up to attack now
Now
Here here's
I think Joe is doing his duty and I think some of his negative
Viewpoints
Just showing a little bit
Because
That's not accurate at all
In any way
Joann
Eddy racing about women
I bet that is comedian
So we can Circle discount that a little bit
A tiny bit
I am very much like they were away on the go
So I'm going to let that go for now because the the bigger issue is
I hear
Was describing
He was talking specifically did not want him to do that moving in on her like a b****
Movie times I kiss them I can't stop myself
Yeah I just
Kiss them immediately
He describes
Describe
Correctly describe a sexual assault
You saying
When you're a celebrity they let you do it
That's not describing somebody
Who's all up in your s***
Upon
You do it
Not they want
Or something like that so freezing it like
Really wrong
I meant at the end
When Alex is like
And there's a guy outside with a recorder
Tiana Micon
There was no there was not a guy it was him talking into the microphone
He agreed to have on him it wasn't confident it wasn't said in confidence
It was
Part of a building case but a lot of people have that he's gone senile
I don't even necessarily
I think he just doesn't
He's not into me he's a lot like Robert Durst
Like when you want
V a little bit smarter
Murder over those years
Man I bet Hillary Clinton is personally gotten away with a lot of murder in life
She's done
Go back to episode
Goddamnit varsho
This is this
About
What he did
On Y2K
Ono
Well here's the big enchilada
I forgot this also is another example of
Play music about to tell a big story and then
Bravo.
FEMA and Joe
Also this is aware Alex
Retreat from the whiskey and also starts doing drugs
There is a whole Breakaway civilization
UFOs
Hold on
How many times did I tell you
Conspiracy theory is just not trusting Criminal
Computer expert
House waiting for that goddamn power to go out
So this clip is going to be kind of long cuz he does
Describe scissors
Experience of Y2K
A total wine
Non-Stop about how he was wrong about the concentration
Camps right now
Own up to the fact that he was pretending the ad sources
Howard Lee kind of dog does he have multiple sources confirming
On the road
Nope none of those
But I want to save this
Because it AA Bears mentioning
Like when you're listening to Eddie and Joe talk
They're having fun
And like there
It's it's
Different it feel different cuz
Would you even in this case when they're talking about how the two of them were idiots and they believed in 2012
Having fun when you bring
Alex bringing them into superstick
Bravo
Strfkr
That's why we talk to use a tiny bit but I also think
For as much as beginning of the show said you was an idiot I would hang out
Even his
Even if he seems like but he
You seems like a congeni
Sure even his even his life
Be right all the time
Such a lie
Little like I'm going to rub your belly
Kind of
Oh you can't be right all the
If I know a few of the things that I do know I would suspect that he was
Resetting Alex up
Like that kind of behavior would be like
Who's playing
Doesn't believe in vaccines
Does leaving chemtrails
Hiralal
Is
Wild
I did I was just very strong tobacco from Mexico
Michael reasons and legal
Also there it's for the rest of the show he pretends he didn't smoke weed although it's on cat
You can hear him
Let me be clear I don't give a fuk
If you smoke weed I'm actually for him smoking weed
Care about is when you are a self-appointed leader of the information War
And you go on
Biscuits
Hundreds of thousands millions of downloads
Comport yourself like a f****** professional
Don't go in there
And get high when you know you can't handle weed
Drink
At least
6 glasses of whiskey
Rome situation Rogan podcast
Uur
Everytime I come
I don't know
I'm trying to do your job
Stop
Most benefit of the doubt I can I'm going to let the rest of the split place
So feel free to take notes
Let's not interrupt it because
I want him to be able to get
His words out and speak his peace
About Y2K
How can I keep in mind
That the sponsor doesn't know where
The sponsors that he had back then
Many of them are the same as he has now also keep in mind when they mock the idea of selling survive
Bible stuff
He still sells all of that now
Keep that in mind when they laugh about it
It's important to be reminded of that uptown
Admit
That he's delusional
I'm going to put the microphone
That
It's important. Inhale
What is Nibiru
This is one of the few
And so I was wrong the wrong reasons
One radio station
Allstate Howard Stern
Huge ratings
You're not what
Endorsi sponsors
I just kind of went
Okay okay okay
Especially
Producer
Right
Missile fired from Russia
Which one
But
Government
Then they use it to demonize alternative
It was BS
Arrow
Apparel
Jordan
Judaica
The yelling was prompted by him basically admitting that he is malleable
And key
Is
You can just talk him into believing
And then I believed it
Is what happened it is believed but also I let them tell me that I believe that
I believe that
Did not believe that at the time
I didn't listen to my gut I don't believe anything I believe everything I believe it all my friend
It's time to pray
F*** him so very important to note it doesn't bring up
How he's changed his tune on Putin
Also very important I brought this up in the middle of the click when I got to repeat it Midas resources
We played a commercial from his show
From night from Y2K
From Midas resources
They still with him
Well they convinced
But now they sell like the doctor wallet
Products like that
Still gold mine
He's a bunch of notes
Okay also
If you're listening and you haven't listened to our episode about Y2K
Go back and listen to that it'll give you a lot of context for why
That clip was full of
Feel my rage
Tactile level
The top show with huge I don't care
Don't think so
Nail guys
Say okay
Panic inducing
Buck
Telecommunications Act of 96
Later
I'm guessing he knows
Broad Strokes
Right listen to The Joe Rogan podcast
Right there
Just randomly throw that s*** out of me like nobody's going to follow up on
Give a f***
Dbm
If you knew was it
I don't know anybody I can confirm this
No always makes me think of a cold shower
IC bowel
I hate hearing missile discuss
Are you ready for the next one
Apparently so at this point Eddie takes the
Jesus Take the Wheel
Bravo
He wants to give you
The chemtrail
He wants to ask Alex
About what
The deal what's the reality with chemtrails
Mmsbee
But they're doing it for different folks
Weather weapon programs for 27 years
Austin
Sean on YouTube
That's pretty gangster pastor
Wither chemical
Wine or hurricane or typhoon
Holyshit
Which I'm guessing realloc
Lubbock
And then they got it
Villa Monte
Bill Gates
Oh boy
Bill Gates owns the weather machine that was emotional for you
To the first Connery as the bad guy Adventures
Bonaventure
The other one
It really is before it is the plot of The Avengers
80's clothes in that movie
He's seen
10 movies
And that is all of Is referee
Weather
Bill Gates got it
You got it
In-depth that you can control hurricanes
Alex
Say they can come
Control hurricanes
All I said
Because it's not
When he has whiskey and weed on Joe Rogan show
And we're going to get into
Believes
He said whether weapon immediately pulled up as much as I can
Here is the best reference
That I could find
Immediately
The former Navy
Steel who turned pro wrestler
The only then to become governor of Minnesota to be clear I love Jesse
What's up brother
I know
What is thing
Who talks the gorilla Gorilla Monsoon
That's right
Alright
Neither of us are dummy
He did a special even on the
Beersy website it says
It's a bit sensational
Questions everything
TV show about
Courtesy stop
And they looked into
2m trails
HAARP
This is dumb
They have
Really
Weather weapon
Sitting in front of everybody and every time City
Russians and Chinese are just discovering.
So
This clip is really long because
Does a little bit of debunking
Porter
Yeah
That weather
Are all times and every small town every small town
One-tenth of 1% are used for Doppler radar
But if your power goes down even a little bit
If you live in sin
Centralia Missouri or Macon Missouri small town tomorrow night
A way to clean information about the weather
Yeah find out if there's going to be a tornado every every
Better to him seems like a like what
What's this magic how much pressure there is
We're going to get to Alex
It's not really believing the people can figure
Things out at some point
This clip is pretty long
Demystified by Alta
I wanted to say we're going to let this play
Because
There's something
Super bottles
That Rogan makes
And I want to be able to
Mitsubishi Greer
The simplest
Is that the
Quintessential
Sign that
Alex Jones
Is if he says
You could kick
Old guy that is
Installation of the only thing that
Respect
This guy looks like
Could beat me up also
He's such a
Pure like
This is the only whale.
This is the only way to deter
Determine male dominance guys of Miami lunch with me
Vegan
Meetup only the greatest
Also I don't want to
I don't want to body shame people
That's not what I like to do
Do but Alex look like
S***
You look like anyone could kick
But I also that that guy who flew in
Tornadoes that he's talking about
Are hurricanes at work
The event being 90 does really call into Quest
And what he's telling
The ones that I work with the elderly I don't believe
S*** there 90 and they're all there is a relative thing
Admittedly
Flying into a hurricane
Sure there's no
If you did that also wasn't the first to ever do it
Probably didn't
They exaggerate
Possibly the f*** is going to call him
Alex
Nope but anyway
This
Earthquake news
I'm just going to let it play
It's important
Is Joe rebuttal
And then Alex tries to readjust
His argument
And then when this clip is over I'm going to explain
Why Alex Jones
Is a filthy liar
Control the weather
Ideas for barges to pump cold water from the depth of the ocean to create some sort of a roadblock for the hurricane
This what he has done is Google's Bill Gates weather
Control
Hey Joe is found
Uncle about how cold water does stop game
And so there's a possibility
Great trenches that release
Coldwater
Started again
Wreck cuz Bill is trying to do
Weather Athens
Weather Rapids
Target pool Power Commander In The Water could have theoretically
Coldwater
In the front of the CFR it said we were doing this
Because global warming
About
You're wrong about dinosaurs
But hey what about that
Yes
Livingston
Finished
AR
What is drunk by the
Until he's drunk
Oh yeah he's ready to eat
As long as you don't ask him to
He will talk about it
His bring us
Oh actually
Play can't I don't have the Improv skills to you cuz we've been watching him drink
Whiskey like its water
Behaving exactly like he doesn't make clip where he's yelling at that
He's acting and sounding like he does in the secret of 2017
So it's like it's kind of reaffirming all of our
Like what
Quick question
What is the secret of 2017 you just that she's not so I do
I don't know
Interrupting
Ariel
Program
Get this done with a real program
And
It doesn't
Chinese
About various options for controlling
Don't you think they would have measuring these temperature
Blitz
I think what I'm saying is they're absolutely is
Frank
What is a theano directions for global warming
Mobile cycle
Astrophysicist
Big Spring
Carbon dioxide water sunlight they have total control over the whole life cycle
Let's play the video
Solutions
What is the CIA
Question what do they have to do I don't know what to say
Stop the spread of Communism
If they got hired
To assess a threat
And its threat being from global warming like what would we have to worry about it we really going to lose cities do we really have an issue with her.
He was that was Alex Jones just totally gone
Yeah there's a
There's a
Like whenever Alex's
He really doesn't
Don't know what to do
That was that was
Completely.
Completely different conversation
Yeah. And then we're having the same conversation with each other happens a lot
Always pure chaos
It's not even over yet
No I'm going to go
Is 1
A lovable
Yeah I am fully on his side as a hug
He's such a silly little goofball
I feel like he's the most an Oculus person
He knows a lot of things that he's ready but he's one of these guys who just watches
Like YouTube videos and thinks their
Yeah and maybe his read a couple documents
But doesn't really understand what they say
To do with global warming you're like
Don't
No but that don't have anything to
But if they did
Joe has a good response to that in that if there are
Rats that are posed
Dubai global warming
The intelligence Community should be
Yeah they should be but they're good answer to a hypothetical question
But be that as it may
Wait for this
Alright conversation takes
Turn on Alex pools
What do you think
Is a trump card out of the closet
We'll get to why it's not
As
George Soros
Project
Chemtrail geoengineering stratospheric aerosol
Soto
Council admits geoengineering the form of stratospheric aerosol
Is taking a place I eat kenturah taking place IU chemtrails
And the robot
Maintenance
Elements of instability in the world
Asai program if ever implemented could penetrate conflicts and security threats if misused
All types of Concepts
Concepts for potential the science oriented concept
Is it possible
Boy saying is that there are potential issue
You can Google
2005 the department of energy program
Testing $5 a year
U.s. code
Brings out
He uses as a
That
His argument
What is
That
These people call things studies
I have pulled up this
Subsection a
If so
Subsection 128 paragraph
I have found it
Google
I'm assuming that he quoted it perfectly and agrees with everything
Restrictions on use of
Human subjects
For testing of chemical and biological age
Prohibited
Activities
The secretary
They knock
Conductor directly or by contract
Any test or experiment involved
Civilian population
Any other testing of a chemical agent or biological age
I believe this was probably
Shortly after that
And let's say that
Let's go through
That the government has actually done that
I don't know this
I don't I don't have a date
But let's just go with it
If it wasn't
It should have been
And it wasn't
This is this is
For the government
Has absolutely tested chemical agents on
Unsuspecting peep
Here's where Alex's argument comes into
Soccer paragraph be
Today
Subject
To subsection
CBN
The prohibition
Subsection a witch I just read the prohibited
Activities
Does not apply
Experiment carried out for
For any of the following purpose
Any pizza
A purpose that is related to a medical therapeutic Pharmaceutical
Agricultural Industrial
Or research
Any purpose
What is direct
Play related to protect
Or biological weapon
Agent
3 any law
Including any purpose related to Riot
Now that's disconcerting
I don't like I don't like that number three at all
Do I do very scary
Let's not
Let's pretend that three was not allowed that's
Scary
Now
As long as you're testing it out on right control
You can do whatever the f*** you want if it's related to
Do medical therapeutic pharmaceutical agricultural
Those ones are fine
Because those ones are beneficial
Control one is very scary
It doesn't really matter though because
Help subsection paragraph Beast is
Subject to subsection
Cd&me
SoBe
Is subject
Comes after it
Right
Let me read you Steve
Informed consent required
Secretary of Defense May conduct a test or experiment described in subsection
If informed consent
To the testing was obtained from each human subjects
Got you or using this
Chemtrails
Population
Yeah
Bulshit
Hold on one second
How many times have you
Agreed
Ma
Subsection maybe it's in there maybe in the iTunes Apple re-up Shoreline
Hey
Chemtrails you go with those and you're like yeah I'm not going to read this whole thing out of nail dystrophy
Conspiracy ever Trails is Apple
Subsection D is about notifying Congress
Amy is
Is just too really
Put into definition what
A biological age
Is Brad Pitt
Definition
Siri used to kill all those people
Sure those two are just sort of definition
Paragraph B is super in Port
If you were if you're using this
Statute
This title 50
Chapter 32 Subs
Section 128
If you're using this
You have to mention paragraphs
Cuz if you don't
It's not the full payment really important
Mentioned
Beholden to
You can't test ride control without informed consent
Yeah actually a very well-written
It is here's my favorite part of that
B b Q's
Equate
And Wednesday bring it up
Pulls up the statute and they read it
They don't read every
So it looks like
And at this point
Drunk
And he gets this
Smug
Smiley look on his face
And at this point
Joe becomes his ally
This is when your righteous Fury Unleashed
Is itself a worse
Half hours long
Is it
Everything Alex says is true
He pulled out this subsection
Paragraph
And oh my God
He's right
He must know everything
The actual Tech
Fighting
Does not agree with what he was saying
We talked about this on the last episode he's winning the battle of
And it's f****** insane
No one looks
You're saying
Yeah
Then you'd
Just get to say whatever you want
I am
I'm so mad
Just discussing our roles earlier prior to the show is like
Is to try and make this
And then you went on this
Fury rent bikes
That's your f****** job my friend hours of batteries in your f****** job right there
Your job is to
Be filled with
Samuel Jackson
Eureka Pacific study says
Felipe
Evil show
Like that's what that is
It's banking on people being dumb
But here's the thing about
That just like the the thing that I immediately thought of was all of the
The executive orders
Trump has pulled out
And the past cup
Yeah
Blatantly
Clearly either
Unconstitutional
Orally
Take a step back
Weird weird weird
They've all been
Steve Alban
Seemed to suit actual
Using part about that was while you were reading that
Whole like
Subsection
How could anybody
Possibly paid
Detention list
And then you realize oh that's why they're all on
He doesn't read those subsection that were built in there
This is a thing now I like that that's what happened
It's legislating by order as a
Social order by order like
It shouldn't be it's like there's all these
These little rules in their government should work
Essentially by negotiation of
Because conservative
Point
Anymore
Conserve
No it's all they've all lost their by the political philosophy of
Small government
States rights
And I think I think that there's a conversation that should be
She had and
That has to do with that
Could have been had where we not where we are
Political philosophy is
Better government
Especially the federal government
What is best
Buy disc
Degree invoices
Having an argument
Negotiating with each other
Compromising
But that's why we're losing
He don't you and I both have this idea of a
Effective governance
He has lost their mind and gone like hey how about instead of that we
Look at this
This code
About restrict
Interviews of human subjects
For testing a biologic
Chemical agent
Really well-written but if you also look at it
Didn't exist in the original version
The greeting for
Consent
In those very small
Tails
To put this
Somehow all of this
Would be right any it's not
If somebody didn't give a
The fuc to that my level
It would be chaos
Is the people who run things do not give a f*** to that much
Level dislike Alex Jones
Go on Joe Rogan show
Characters
He's bad news.
Clip is pretty fun
Transition out of me yelling about it
So I need to know I need to know
And how much are aliens real
Okay
Camp horno Charlotte
What is Donald Trump
Oh yeah it was he know now right cuz he's in the office
The first thing I did
The office
Who's got the documents
Who's who's
Tell me the first
Also did you hear Alex repair
Get yelled at
Yeah
Starting to lose it
Let's follow this route
Also this
Deflecting and one of
Damn drunk
I just want to seem drunk
Show me where I'm at right now
Talk about boring
Jeep research Proclamation on Spotify
The real
That still cling to
Is Bigfoot an alien
Dota 2
Yes
Call Daddy are you ready
Yeah
That is vacant
Enchilada there
Dick mean it's f*** you it's just it's just another instance the b*******
Call
Tiny little weak
Bulshit
You're the alien
Keeps doing that like
I Hold On
Ord
You're couple times also deflect with
Jokes about him being
Dicks
Bill heck
And have you like
Why why do people actually think
People don't
It's a joke
Alex music app
It's crazy they don't it's crazy they have
He's not gone all over this
It's weird I haven't
The joke
ICampus
Deflect away from
But you can't deflect any longer
Still point where he's drunk
And he sort of press
To the wall
Questions
About what he believes about the elite
Please don't interrupt this
It's a synthesis
Of a belief
And
Some thoughts that I need to
Explain
Already
I will allow this
Enjoy to happen
Right
Metaphysical religion
Play is on air
He prays on air
He said he didn't
Beatles
Yeah I'm sorry
I told you not to interrupt your internet so f******
The rest of this is
What's happening
Okay
I wouldn't use that word with full confidence
I've never said that let me give you a basic just stalled
Defraud
The Forever at the secrets of the universe
But the good ones don't ever want to organize
Powerful
Consciousness is don't
Until things are really late
It's a false hologram
Artificial the computers are
Ascensionpoint
He's bleeding in
This universe
Such a wisp in some computer program
Species
Destroy
Which level we want to go to we
Believe
Where they're going to merge with machines
Which is kind of like a full transmission
About building
And so
Google setup
Is the longest
Stream
Uninterrupted
Insanity
Heard
Since I got off the
But also
Can see the length of this clip that you cute
I can see how we still got
11 + 1/2
Million more minutes to go
No there's like three
That was taking notes
I halfway through that because it
It's clearly
All of One
Dimensions don't work like how he thinks dimension
No but if it does
He saw Doctor Strange is like
What happened
He is f******
12 Dimensions nobody
What no
Einstein
Play Selena
What are constants
If there's anything that you can say about plank it is at plank
Never said there were 12 dementia
StubHub
Transmissions
Yeah below the third dimension
Into the third dimension demon on the 5th
They're six dimension
I feel like he's confusing
With Lord of the Rings
With
Dante's Inferno
What's going on right different
Max Planck
Only one other than
Challenger
Length
Of things
Like it is constant
Is asked to do with
Yeah
Yep Mike was a vacuum
And stuff like that
All regular stuff 00 mention of the twelfth dimension
So Jordan
What you need to know about this
Is a lot of the stuff that he's spouting
Comes from
An anonymous post
That was put on Reddit
Exactly
Years and years ago
I read all of this
Like
8 years ago
Or so
Honestly him spouting this stuff
Andre
Show while he's really drunk
And being like this is
The big thing
It's actually disappointing
Bandannas
Bit worse
What we've been talking about for the rest
These episodes where it's like the globe
It's worse than that
No
Yeah that's Pure Fantasy.
That's a f******
Dragons
Song novel by Ann McCrary
It's important to point that out
Because
When he says he has sources
It's very
Always
Has
And they are
Very
High up there always very high up
His sources are so
Buried
Yeah and expert
It is hard to imagine that he is not in
Infiltrated every single level
A government every single level of Technology
Everybody possible to your like
The only place
Doesn't know a lot about is
Guatemala because he thinks there's a f****** wall there
I'm not sure that I actually have this
This clip but Alan the episode
Rogan
Podcast
You like I was talking
Come to a head of state
Which
Name
Donald Trump Donald Trump would it be
God we're all going to have such great sources
State
Yes yes
Righteous anger
Okay I need to be clear when I'm talking about all of the
Patrol post
Nadia's already years ago or so
She's taking from there
But saying he doesn't believe it's what the elite
Believe
But will you have tubal would you have
2 take away from that
Is that he believes that the elites believe that
Important
The fact that he says
Is kind of a dog
Believe it and there's some power in
When it's a fantasy narrative
Yeah so anyway the rest of the script is going to play
He talks about this and a later clip which will get back to at the end of the show
Eyewear
Kind of invalidates a lot of things
Let's enjoy the latest
Let's get on this Willy Wonka at boat into
Enjoy the ride where Joe calls him out on
But not nearly enough
Artificial system
The first artificial intelligence will be
Based on the neuron
The billions of people
Walmart.com
Future prediction powers
The future
Consciousness
Everyone knowing our hopes and dreams
Delivering
Pleasure
The shutter shop
Cut off the pedophiles
Control system
What is a population
Why is 40 weeks talking about
Explain that you just
Preacher tells you about his tummy control
Porsche
Rather than the divine
That's not an answer
But also I will say this I didn't
Keep this particular cuz that was way too long but Jo-Jo does bring up the
Understanding where technology is going to go and sort of
That was
That was the robots of dawn
Timeline described
Literally from iRobot
The foundation
And Isaac Asimov nozzle
I think that's what he read that's what he described every single step of the way
Was going to happen we're going to have
How to deal with and I think this
Document actually
Takes Alex
A different category in my mind
Like I really think it's important interdimensional beat
Nobody
I I think
List
Experience
I hate hearing him say
Crazy Legs
I have to deal with him on two levels
Cuz you're the propaganda
The 3rd
There
Footlight I believe
That he is a propaganda
Yes but I also
Have to wrestle with the fact
He knows the difference
Between fiction and reality
No he absolutely does not he constantly brings up
Lots of movies like pointed out
Huge part of his phone
Alright
We're going to go with now we've had it
Isaac Asimov Elysium seems to be really and is a Zeitgeist going to go with
The Matrix
I really think that I'm not saying
Phrenic or anything like that but I think that there is a part of his brain that is unable to
To grasp what is real and what is
Fart
Like I really don't know if he
Until
Because when I read that
Huge
Long
Post that was clearly famous sacrifice yourself so the rest of us don't have ticket
I went around
Then I enjoyed it for what it was
Oppression of
Oven
People online
Indispensable interesting way that wasn't abusive
Did that long postumia seem to be like
This is someone f****** around but doing it really well
There's another great example if you guys are listening are the guy claimed to be a time traveler
I am
Gave a bunch of
Very wrong prediction
About what can happen in Spanish
But it was real loud house really interesting
It was fun
Yeah and like I like all of those like all the times already see that pic
That's like
Nextel phone
Verily like Nicolas Cage
But also got an idiot
If you're unable to realize the variables that
It exists within a population of
Billions
We live in a world
Statistically anything that could happen
MaxPrep
Realizing that he's got a few gradually running out of righteous
Okay this is Alex realizing
Somebody's got to put on
Alright
The globalist are in
Do with the luciferian Freemasonry
I thank God for you and brother
Go for it
Alex
Walmart
Just to give some context of work
Smoke weed earlier but also.
They were talking about how I Buzz Aldrin
Interviews
Just talked about Heather
Buzz Aldrin
He eats whether that or he's nowhere else
There's a formation on Jupiter's moon or Venus
Is the moon Phobos
Or whatever there's like a
Or demote earlier in the show
Alex was talking about how Buzz Aldrin came on his show
And told him a bunch of Truth
And they pulled up
Video of him saying
You set a reminder show first
Gears world give Eddie Bravo some really nice
The whole time he's like
These fight with you
I love I love Eddie Bravo's it like The Narrative of this episode has been dead
Bravo going from sycophant to
Hey Alex
Topic attorney wants to know
Yeah
As a curiosity that is
I think Eddie realizes that
Music Charming little hours ago
You shouldn't believe in vaccines are terrible and also
Chemtrails are stupid
He's one of those
I'm gullible
Makes him so susceptible
Yeah he means
World to be a better place
People are screwing people over
He believes
Then his fellow man
Underneath the Tyranny that is m
Imaginary Trails of
You're so right
I mean like I don't have this clip but it
At some point in the episode he's talking about one of his interest
I have a kid I don't want my kid to
Live in a world that I could have
I'm so you are you're right there where is motivated from
Good-hearted
Lex Luthor
He word me calling him an idiot you put him in like
His life
Has this one very
Simple like fork in the road where it's like
You give him one set of information
Kitchen at 1
In his life
Publix
Defender giving up everything to defend the
Poor in The Help
Has one angle
Asking Alex Jones whether or not chemtrails
Pure-hearted
Martial arts instructor
In the world
Well Joe If Logan knows him
Joe Rogan
Because people have been murdered on his
Anyway
Is there a
Subspecies
Darwin stuff came from
Restaurant
And you sit there and act like you don't know about it
Motorsport
So that was Alex realizing he had to show up do you know he's drunk and he's like
Alex
Going
Winter break
I've got a shift into my own mode
No
Well there was this is going to be Isaac
Does he believe all that nonsense
Descartes
No thank you
I also want to give credit I don't have the rest of the clip
Ramble the whole bunch
Apparently the guy who
Newton
Within 2
Answer that
What the hell I mean
Darwin was into a bunch of weird
In that
He was part of a club that was all about eating as many
Different types of Anna
My weird to me
Have you even asked
Never would
How to write interesting
What are you doing
Can I walk I don't know
But imagine that you know what there's no point
The thing is they
Plenty of insane
Like they're mentioning of test
Tesla was not somebody who believed in the
You called and then became
Smart Tesla with somebody who is so unbelievably ridiculous
Wesley capable
Holding
Purely
Physiological images inside of a
This had that week
Can't really like
I can't
Even comprehend the idea of
Holding entire me
Schematics
Inside of my brain
Like he couldn't even write it down
Was a f****** genius
It's like he figured out Wireless power and we're still work
Working on it I'm 100 years later
Then I am too
If you were that guy living in a world full of the rest of us
Why wouldn't you believe crazy nonsense
Straight
Now Descartes on the other hand Descartes was a meth
Not a legit
Even then it was
Because of his Affinity to Mac
All of all of his
All of his syllogisms word purely if
It was already
Exactly
Now Isaac
And was a Purell
Alchemist
Where is like
Gold
God
The whole shebang
So what's your point
As it relates to Alex my point being as it relates
To the nonsense that Alex
Is that
At no time does he engage with
What
Did
Call about the Sierra mountains
Beautiful
Interested in the fact
They get this information
They get it
Transdimensional
Dimensional being
What to do
That's the end of that question
Right there
Here is a fun clip
But it's short
Inside
Women
Versus a bunch of Potbelly
That's the one that's a war
But the war man
Steak
Cigars and p****
Versus
Potbelly
I didn't know it would call that an over-simplification
Yet somehow that is not a strong enough
Yeah
I didn't isolate this
Because what surrounded it wasn't
But there was a point
Alex
Probably like 2 hours into the episode is like
Black
Full grown women
Of course
I get it you can just stop
Almost like
Can be a very
White version of
The lady.
Protest too much
So we have a couple hang yourself
I will get back
Text to
The dumb
Weirdo Illuminati narrative from earlier
But this one
Is
Alex
Drunk
To f****** make a cup
Argument
The discussion
Obama's birth certificate
It comes up
And it's
So fucken bizarre
I genuinely think we should start to
Save all of my notes pages
Auto be too because I had to talk
This looks like the ramblings of it this is like
The Notebook
In the movie Seven is what this looks like a legitimately thought like
Patreon giveaway
Gordon's notebooks
Field
You might need a whole new sheet here cuz this one is
Excellent bring me fire
Sure
Cheerleader
Trump
Yes please
Just a warning this clip is
Kind of long I want to let it play Jay
So we can hear
Like I don't want to interrupt and get rid of contacts cuz
It doesn't make any sense I'm going to fill up a note Pages latest Joe
Patreon and you'll be able to receive writing angrily
Freezing point
Okay I want to smoke
The full scoop
What do you think happened
Okay I will
Text Georgie mr.
Time signature
Maybe not Alex come on
How many protons does the moon
Jesus Christ
Restaurants near me
What Donald Trump told you
You were just you or just give up
Power to figure it out
What is it
Twitter
On average
Weed eater out before then
A minute Gap
Get some answers
Voicemail
Buzz Aldrin
Kenya
I am writing this
I'm sorry to interrupt I did Google all day
I'm just like you
Okay
Also that is not at all how he presented on his own show
At all
Generally speaking
.9%
Incorrect
Global
Obama's
Running for office
Bookshop
That was thoroughly debunked
Over and over and over again
How many times
25 million would you stay over and over again over and over and over and over
How many overs Against Humanity over
I wasn't early on Obama supporter
Dads
+ 6 + 7 is
And then
Harvard Law review
Oh yeah
What song is this
Across
Which is still
Country
Okay she saying is this home from Ireland
What did someone like me
Maybe made an incorrect judgement
Information
He did
Wow why is that
Front
Communist famous pornographer
Somersworth
And so
I mean that's a rambla goddamn
Why there
Is the birth certificate
Alright
Alex
Bye
Whom
Frank Marshall Davis
He's dead the CIA
Maybe isn't it
Obama's mom was a CIA operative
A groom by the CIA from birth
Alright
Now 1
Apple juice
You keep saying
I'm cute I feel like he's not just drink
No and
The end
Drinking it like water
It looks like
It sounds like he's drinking it like
Pictures of him just pouring shots and see like
Joe's face
Like there's a couple that dope
Play on audio so I didn't have plenty.
Okay
So Trump got involved
Because he got caught
That's the story that you will
Get out
The whole thing is Trump is in nocuous ruin the
It all came it was progenerate
B*******
Straight b*******
Alrighty so
Somehow
Alcoholics are mad at him for drinking too much
That. Came up
Joe Rogan and clearly
Yeah but I mean
Alcoholic
I'm still up
Already
But yeah that is very lovable hero in this
In this all fake
Between an alcoholic and a functional
You know that those two things are very different
Behavior is indicative of an alcoholic
I can drink
And not really be a professional alcoholic
As opposed to might be part of Arkham
Median life.
Alright
I like that
Alex Jones said that he
Sure because I don't know if that's a
Thing that's
Will my therapist like to tell me that shame mean
I'm bad
I did something
So when you're ashamed of that means that you're indicating that you are bad
Your behavior was actually bad it wasn't just an action it was something about you
Yourself so what you're saying is on her next podcast
Your therapist is
Is going to be a guest right
I wish
Sing Lady
There's so much
There's always another clip
That was the thing that I listen
Thinking
Every single time
Every single time that he
It's because you didn't watch the right
The right thing
If you watch this rainbow in the sky
The clip
Not at all
There's ice that supports whatever I used
From about
Our point
Restarts drink
Throughout this episode
Okay
His face
Is this smog
Smogon
Whenever whenever
Title 50
Chapter 32 Subs
I haven't written down that's why I can
Are you remember
There was a look on his face
I've convinced
I have been to the Mountaintop
There wasn't it never asked
It didn't look like friends interaction
15 from Josie
And it really looks
Someone who's like
Like I made it through this trial
Well yeah go everything is okay I don't
That lead to anyone
Who isn't
Drinking the Kool-Aid so to speak you look like a
Total idiot
Cuz
Default position
Explain
Sing to me
There's a
So every it
The amazing thing about
That long list of
Was that it
It seems like
Every single thing
He said letting
To the next thing
And yet they are
Completely
And utterly unrelated
And I should say it does go on
Frank Marshall Davis
But have you
Frank Marshall
Right
Is that safe
They put up
A shot
A picture on screen
Davis Obama
Dad and Obama
You looked exactly like almonds
I don't know
Is Joe is like
I don't know I think it looks like his dad more than he looks.
And there's no response cuz of course
Would you say cuz of course
I withhold judgement I don't
I'm sure you've done research
My job is to please
Listen to this
I do
I can't fully explain it
But I didn't know that
A lot of sources I've been able to
How to find
Site
Fake
College ID
Alright that has that name
That's all I ever
Be at the aliases theme to be photoshopped
Identification
It goes back to the idea of that there was this whole narrative that
No one that went to college
Remembers
Except for all the
Right
Don't worry about that
Because his actual
Barry Soetoro
I don't I don't know
I'm not interested in this narrative cuz I I dip I dip
Cool and I was like
Smelter
Down all of the you like little Angela
And I am
To see one that's related
Can you
The other ones
So that the whole
Idea behind this
Question and an
Set up
Yes
Okay
Was there any
Like
Evidence
So all all the
All the time I wrote it more like what
All the stuff that I rode
Do you like one
The first thing I wrote is Bravo's
That's what I that's
The only thing that ate all of my nose I can confirm 100%
My favorite character so far
It's like a lot of our friends who get high all the time there
Being high in all of our episodes
Braless is our hero at this one
Does Bravo not Bravo's like it
It's Game of Thrones
Eddie Bravo
Keep me from saying his name is Kevin Bravo or Eddie Bravo
Three more clips
Okay
Here's my ultimate
I have no idea what the f*** he is trying to say
Neither do I
Anyway
We get back to the elites
What their plan is
Yes
And Alex brings out
Example
One of the evil
Members
Of the elite cabal
Interdimensional
And then I want to get props
Joe kind of
What's the movie with the big picture
Please admit
Have Regional Wars
Play people off against each other
Send it
Who are the Elite like when you say the elite who are these people how do they get together
Who votes to the Superbowl
The same thing
Bilderberg Group
Davos
Club of Rome is a population reduction group.com right now
There's an article
Or she's part of a secret
But I like killing people
Yeah that's hilarious white absolutely
Okay
Facebook
Turn on the news
When someone like her says something about reducing the amount of
Birth control
Construed into population control
Start saying she's
She's pushing
Like to have you ever been in here what they said
That's that one
They just pulled rrtiming on that didn't
They just pulled our fake news.
Ending ISM I want Eric back I want to wear you out
You say what they want
Yeah
Construed into population control
In control
Time
Have you ever been in
He's too drunk
Was August
Did you just say
He stunk
Into what
McFlurry
Mangrove
Yeah and antonym I recommend everybody look into the real story
It's insane
No. No one cared look when you
If you go after Oprah
Shitz wrong with
Any best nightmare
The king you best not mess
Yeah
What are you doing donuts
What Oprah
He's becoming a 6
Whatever he's mad at her about that
There is zero
Of all the people
Maybe Ellen DeGeneres
Is the lesser of like
Okay
Do notice
Direnzo that people who eat attack
Text are pretty much
Never widen
Mail
It's not a coincidence
Everybody credibly
Santa that you would
Say that about RS
Race-blind
Alex
Who is never talked about race
On his show how Cody why would somebody label him as a bigot
There's a whole episode we never cover
Screwed by Don Lemon
Because I don't know what yeah yeah that's one thing
I know I don't want to I don't want to get into that argument there
Area where we find
Together
The clip is the
Listen for it
Joe says
Just isolated one of them
It's the gray
Nail it
Junior size that can make you think
Stock dis I'm going with
Eddie is talking about hypothetical situations
Where Jeff
Cave kid died
Before
He started going after
Anyway
Sure
I'm coming after you
Just because it's like
Couple times
Glasnost
What's
Just keep bringing the whiskey
What's a good Eddie Bravo is our conscience as Bravo is our guide
Yeah I guess Eddie Bravo and every aspect of what he say
Houston
If your kid dies
Basically Eddie Bravo is giving you life
To believe that taken
Israel
Easy
Let you know
Pushing
3 hours
We were always going to
This next clip is where at
The ghost a little bit
It shows his cards
Let's play
Globalism is like neocolonialism but it's corporate
Colonialism
Humans individuals government States
Old World New World
It's worldwide, is it raw
Depopulation
Centralized systems of Monopoly
Why do they want stop innovation
Because I see it
How's your knowledge
Powerful consideration
Bubbles bigger that BS
Challengers
They seized control
To the Stars
Brian authoritarianism
What happened
How is Donald Trump going to stop this a bolt came off the
Blocking Dead
Course
You got to sell a car where people have to buy it
This is this pronounce this tax plan
Yeah
It's on his website
And
What's on there
Previously presented as
Like
There's going to be lower taxes
He's going to be
Ohio tax
Sims 4
Did not do any of that
Economist
Broken it down
Tax plan
People who make very little would have to pay note
Riches
Through now
Will not
People who make
Very little are exempt from taxes
That's called a progressive
Texas.
Exist now
For a good reason
There was somebody else that exist
Way better
There's a bunch of
Assistance
I'm done on
Trump
Proposed
And
Whatever
Sound is
The bigger tax cuts under Trump
Who would have guessed
The lowest
Income group
Would be
Point6
Percent
Cut on there
Yeah
Percent of whatever bulshit they're making is almost nothing
I mean when you make very little 6% is more important
Yeah it does matter
But when you make a lot
The middle day there which would be what
Are we okay
The analysis broke into
La Quinta
Pittsburgh 55
What's the top 5
Let me take a guess
As to what their toys
Percentage-wise
Laurette
Are you going lower
Ultimate tag
Okay the top
Let's go with
3:40
No
They're great
The top is 31.1
So they're going to lower it to
Streamyx
Write 27
7.9
The three-point
2% drop
You know what that's not as bad as
It in the top
Quintile
Let's betapa
Group
Now if you break it down even
Further the top one
Drops
6.5
Course and the top of one
Point one
Percent
Drop seven points
Wonderful
Keep more of their money
I was really concerned that they
I had to
Proposal
Lower tax
For poor people but Inn in Council
Got rid of the mortgage
Income tax rate
F*** everybody
And our rivers are now poised
Yeah. Rivers are now on fire
Exactly going to go back to the old days of Cleveland are rivers to be made of Fire
Instead of water
Yeah but the
But there is
Is like this
Text thing that
Super
Progressive
Is b*******
Complete
It's it's an absolute live
Sounds good
Like the way that represent
It does sound good
But upon further analysis
Decent
Review who want make
Things lightly last night
But there's huge tax breaks for the rich
Slightly less
But you're going to wind up getting way fewer benefits
One more
The ultimate clip
Where Alex
Weaves back
To his
Weird Illuminati believe
Some b*******
Excellent
Trays
His own point
About what he believed
This clip
Is just labeled Bowl
The biggest shoes in the world
We're still on Aliens
What do you mean
What I say is not political
And it's not from my particular
Okay
Alright
Galaxy photograph
Universes
We live in an amazing
Yeah
It's not in the third dimension door Bailey receiving transmission
That doesn't make sense
Beetlejuice
Beetlejuice come here
Much closer
To fold space
Coronavirus
I don't believe it
I'm simply telling you what
Baby bloodride
We're really powerful
Closest Sun
Radioactive
The very short lives
Because we're like a
Aerospace
Channel live
Because we live so close to the Sun
So
To the next species
System
Shoreline
In this continuum
And we're trying to progress
As a species
Accessuh
This this we are other dimensions
Well let's just say we're not in Kansas anymore
Whoops
His whole thing about like not believing this it's what the elite believe he just admitted that he does believe it
And all those words
I did those words are not connected to other words in all of those words
No not not money I've heard a lot of those words before but never in the order that those words were said
Those were the crazies
Call the word does make total sense
If you know it makes total sense if you have access
Like a lot of this
Weirdo internet
Like it so it's part of the
Acres Acres Acres
Resources that aren't real
Do this thing where he believes his
Listcrawlers
The call in the tell him like
Hey.
Build Memphis
. she is out on the road maybe company received
Something on a message board and it becomes reality
It's the same thing over and over and over again this is the thing
About this episode that makes me
Question a lot of it
Things that upset another episode
Is this is him with his guard down
Yeah like this is not him performing this is him letting
What he believes
Performative
Well no not even that like me speaking from the heart he's drunk
He's f****** high
He's letting it
Apologize for
Rhyming
No I I will
Never forget
No he's
Reviewing
All of those deep-seated beliefs he have
Which is
Ratchet
Saturday like
He's as like
Simple idea that dimensions
Exist the way that
He's described him
It's so insane
That's exactly that's the least of the insane things he said
Like he's adjusting said like oh we're on the third dimension you're like well that's the least crazy
Crazy thing you've said we exist in three dimensions like I meditate a lot
Just like lucid dreams been things that I
Tapped into that
Just my brain something from outside myself
It seems like that idea of like
Cured existence
Maybe there's something to it you know what I'm not going to
To base my world that is exactly where we become
Fred
My Spear of the government
The old
How is it that inter-dimensional beings is the least of what we're talking about
Believes in interdimensional beings
Beetle
Googlys
Yeah from
Batman is drunk Batman
F*** off
He's very drunk I'm not going to
Listen to a lot of episodes Logan
I never heard him
Cut someone off
Batshit
Like I've never heard him be like a bar
And be like
Okay alright alright
If he lets more he's gone
Let's let's get into our final like this is the final part of this pie
We are done with the clip
Alright
I will say that the show does go on a little bit
I didn't want to play bikes
Some of the embarrassing
Front clips
It's really embarrassing
In the shoulder
Like its 8
Why can
Idiot who don't want it
The party whose
Like trying to
It actually made me feel very dirty and it's part of the amp
Apathy part
Lakewood Manor
Yeah
And I don't think
Man I've been there
Castle being without looking it up
There's an episode
My friends
Some friends
Of mine did a radio show
In Columbia Missouri
That went from 2 to 5 in the
That's the wrong time to have a radio show it was a local access
People would show up
Get drunk at
On my birthday 1 year I went
Getting wasted
Access
I just start
Talk about a Great Neck
Where was
I ramble
I'm I don't even
I'm embarrassed
And then they keep cuz you're out
Alright
I did that
On my birthday 1 year and then like
Year later
I found out that my brother had
We of the audio of
The people because he thought it was hilarious
It's probably Hilaire
I can't I can
Can't muster the courage to listen
Intuit
But
It's
Real talk
I will put that out for them
I get the idea of being too drunk
Broadcast
That's one thing I empathize
I get that
When I was on that broadcast I wasn't
I'm trying to explain
Plain truth about the globalist
Well that's just talk
That's the conversation for us
To have
Right now
At what point are we going to get into the the hole in vino veritas
Like literally no
Like okay
Is he drunk
Look and high enough
To tell the truth
Or is he drunk
Too high
To make a
Here's where I would draw the
What I was on that show
On my birthday
Pikachu in the morning
I didn't say anything that I don't agree with
How do you spell nickel
I might have said some hack
Joke
I might have repeated something
Things that I heard other places
I have conversation
Unpredictable
I believe
That I don't think of it when you're drunk
Your your truest
Form right
But I think when you're wasted
You're capable of coming up with some
Okay
That's interesting
Interesting idea
I think that is
It's a middle ground
Mentally ill person
Of the bipolar
We get it yeah
For the rest of your life
Jordan get a f******
Impersonality I thought you was diagnosis
Dumb
How about develop your own
As far as my experience
That right
So when I'm manic
It is not that I am accessing some sort of inner self that
He's not allowed to come out
Whenever I'm under
Control
So much as it is
AA like
Constance
Aspects of creation
Every single moment
Is me creating some
Pneumonia
So what are oppressive
Yeah
Recipe
To the point where the moment that I've just created his
The only mama
Everett
Another one
Is going to be way better than the one that I just said
Yeah
However not what I would describe
Drunk ass
Like to me being
Drunk is
Is just loosening
All of those
Those guards
So to me listening to him talk
When he is s***
When he wakes up
The next day say
I was drunk
And I shouldn't have said that
Not
I was drunk
I made all that
Today
He only had the only thing he said about it was that Joe Rogan
Podcasts
Most downloaded
In the world of cars
In terms of that
I don't like
For me
Drink
And baby it's
Physiology or whatever but
Hungover
Play truth right
B i g really think that what wound up happening
He got caught
In a couple of
But you didn't
Get caught
Not unlikely
He got caught got your wife but like
In in his
Would like physical brain come
He got caught in
In two ways
One he got caught into
To the spiral
Staying
The the underpinning
Things of what all of his
Which are that if you if you genuinely think
They're interdimensional
Spell being
Yeah exactly
That justifies
Every single
Conspiracy theories
It is
The underpinning of it doesn't
Propping up
George Soros
Doesn't matter
He's not
Anti-semitic he's not anything it just don't get it mention will be
Understand it
You couldn't
They're interdimensional beings
You just don't
Get it exactly
You don't get it
Get it because you are living on this
2nd Dimension noise
Fourth finger on The Drifters
Yeah
Now there's that
And then there's also the part that is the exaggeration
The where
All my horses are amazing
He doesn't really believe that 12 dimension
What do you believe is that there's six dimensions and he's just
Going over
Like that kind of
I genuinely think
Let's use cardio
All of the stuff that he
He said is
Exactly what
He believes
But just
He exaggerated
To be cool
Like he wants Joe Rogan to think
You cool so bad
Joe Rogan
No Doubt
No doubt it is
It is pathetic
Against his whole Narrative of being like
Like I'm not impressed
Stars
Here's the new one
But that's that's not necessarily A
Like that song
Like I have to I want to think I'm cool
And all of their names are
Beach
You did the joke how dare you
Both a Time
We're at the end of the show
Aspire euros
There
There's a bunch of
Anything goes back to what I was saying
How many years ago was the
Guthred
The he's weaving
He's trying to do them
In his own brain
Andy's job
One of them is the narrative
Trump
Being great
Texas
Immigrants
That's the propaganda
And then the other thread is
Is kind of what
Deep down he actually
We Believe
Matt is that the globalist
Are a bunch of
Pedophiles
And they believe in trans
National being
And he believes in that too
And he has to fight it
The passion does
Come from the
Trump want
What's to lower your taxes
Depression comes from the b*******
Yeah the passion comes from the
Fantasy world
Make them up
And Heat
Yu-Gi-Oh how to make those
Threads intertwined Rags actual show all he can talk about
Is the taxes
And all that stuff
Of the other
Horseshit
He's not that.
He knows that if he brings up all this other
Dimensional b*******
On his Infowars show
Game over
So he brings it up on Rogaine where it's like
No one
Who hate
Pam is going to listen in
Call it out
Right
Going to be like that was hilarious
The two
Stop listening
Kenny Bravo's
That's what them Safe Harbor and
He lets out a little
From my purse
Perspective
I really think
Do a much better job
The internet
Communities where
Crazy how
That in
Same person that we just
Dementia
National beans
Has more influence over our
Right now
Not
He thinks he does
If he's
If he's in with c
Steve Bannon
What's the farthest
Dark
I think we're already too
I think we're going to be
The ultimate knowledge fight
Is the tide turning or not
Let's wrap this up
Can follow us at knowledge
Underscore fight
We are on iTunes of our knowledge fight
Can you subscribe
Give us a review
We apologized
The show's been f****** longest
Also you
If you want to send us an email with
Join email even if you disagree with
Gloves
Engaged
With you
Regis at knowledge fight
Gmail.com
Other than that mine
And your business
Don't try dock me
I don't know
For someone to tell us we love you
Yeah I guess so
Jordan
It's of course
Until then
Love you
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color