Alex
In color
A little bit
Is there a
Play some Revolution
Because hopefully I'm
Going to convince
Sponsor a small Revolution
Custom Revolution a revolution against the dumbass Republican
And libertarian conservative propaganda
Please join up with us
Revolution Brewery desperate off of the out of the gate
Fair enough
Today's Show I'd like to give a shout out to Revolution Brewery
My butt
I'd like to give a shout out to our new daughter what's going on out there Kieran
I'd like to also say it's possible that his name is Chiron I'm not entirely sure
It's spelled like it could be either but is he scrolling along the bottom of our screen right now
My heart is thank you for the donation we really appreciate it if you'd like to become a policy wonk
You can do so by going to our website knowledge fight.com
And cooking me support the show button
Keeps the Lights On as they say
Alright Jordan it's nice by the way thank you very much
Excited
10/10
October 10th
I have a very interesting
Exploration for us to do that I don't think you want to do
I found
Let me just point this out
Before we started Dan was like
Did you go get some more beer you might need it so that might be why you're angry
Investigation
You remember of info
The trim is going to go crazy and say call Larry Nichols and we should say we called Larry right before the show
I left a message hopefully he will call back or at least respond
We called because we knew if we just called and you didn't answer on the show that's anticlimax
And on top of that
There's a there's an ethical thing where you need to warn him
That sort of stuff so if he calls back at any point during the show
Lyrics to remember if yours is gone at Larry Nichols calls back in
But we'll see we'll see I hope
He calls tomorrow and order in honor of
Give him
I'd like
Somewhat popular starbucks.com
Really sexy
Yeah I dunno
Somewhat Papi
Waited way too f****** cookout your own guides has Alex yeah he's somewhat popular
Not sexy chat room
Sexy sexy truck political
Truck that says go fuc yourself Paul Joseph Watson
He's in Barney Rubble
I get it
Alright
Do you need me to fill you in on what's been going on okay
So
Alex is spinning his wheels about sat Las Vegas
Because
He was kind of getting bored and not being creative coming up with new elements of it
When your narrative is
It may have happened and everyone I don't like
Yes
He's Rich yesterday onto a narrative you is misleading people about about
A measure that passed
In California
Where they made it
Misdemeanor instead of a felony
Knowingly transmit HIV
Well the situation is we talked about it on yesterday show motivation
Behind
Stigmatize thing
Because part of the law previously was you had
To know you had it to be illegal
Transmitted
Which would discourage people
From getting tested
So that was the thinking behind the law
Okay
It's it makes sense
And all the advocacy groups are behind a tell everybody who is a note
Alright well then I shouldn't have a f****** pacon
It's just a way for them to get HIV blood all over the country and killed millions of
That also makes
Sort of Defending Harvey Weinstein game
Which is contrarian as hell I don't know why you doing that
But
Right.
But but that's where we're at
He starts the show off by getting back to
Viva Las Vegas
Situation
Galaxy wear
Not as important
Today on October 10th
Broadcast
Garrett anywhere
It's because
Take the lead on this information while the same time
They're running
Monday
Where you can hear the
Looks like a muzzle flash
That's not what they were doing
This week
On
He's talking about an article that was in Newsweek and if you actually go read the article it says
On Monday Alex Fayetteville
Nothing specifically say when he said it
Bright lights
From from from writing like nobody else
This is just amazing how to SEPTA
These people are
You're not paying attention to me
They now come out and completely contradict the official story
And basically admit okay Isis maybe involve
Newsweek has an article
Remember we said that sources
Didn't say maybe maybe it was the IRA as well from his sources on day one.
Neuseway Kelly X Usual Suspects
Las Vegas
Security guard
A full 6 minutes
Concertgoers police review
What we've been telling you what a Witnesses said
Not specific things that Alex has ever said
And
The shooting of the security guard
Was in The Narrative from the beginning
Like in the news
I read about that
The day of
Yeah but what has he been telling you
Telling me
Subtly that he doesn't read anything
I like that still have that phrase
He's phrases that as a question he still has the upward inflection at the end of it
Wait what happened
I don't even remember I am
Lost I have said a lot of s*** I'm lost in my own spider web
New Theory I don't exist
It could be good but you're the liar liar I'll tell you that much bong
Almost
So I tell I wish I could fire you up
I checked out that story in Newsweek and the title of the story is Alex's
Just reading
Las Vegas shooting
There could be a potentially terrifying reason
That they refused
To prove it
If I did it
Exactly well that's a bad analogy cuz he did it
This article in Newsweek
In this article they're not specifically say
That every law enforcement
Source everybody
Says that there is no discernible connection between Isis or any other terrorist group
And Paddock
The shooter in Las
Play make it
No Nevada
They make abundantly clear that's not
The appointed the article but
Dive into the possibilities
Since they keep taking responsibility for it what could their motivation possibly be and the article is about
The desire
Of course
To create distrust with immediate distrust with authority figures
You did it
You are way
Right
My friend as if they did it
They would have some proof that it was
If they were involved
Friday would wait for the media to say
There was no involvement
And then they be like haha your media lies to you look
There isn't like he wasn't anything like that
There is no evidence that he is
No one is
I'm pretty comfortable with that I don't even need any Isis
Showed up and they were like
He left the
He's an old white dude from Nevada who f****** shot a bunch of people because he's a f****** Luna
Does a slightly scarier version
About what's going on and we'll get to that here in a little bit
Slightly yes even scarier an embolism
It can happen at any time
Anywhere to
Was that mean
He's not involved
He's just a random ass f****** dude
And that's why gun control is so important
Is because this
This is just a random dude
Yeah
And could actually murder
58 people
59 people and injured hundreds more
And nobody really knows why other than he's insane
Terrifying
I prefer
Furret if it was an organized military Oregon
You know we could be like here's where they might
Could have
Yeah
Someday you might be walking out of
Concert and then you're dead
Bummer
Yeah thanks America
You know I want to double down on this point really quick
If it does come out
Is involved with Isis I'll be like that's a humdinger
But if
But if he's not then I'll continue to be like if there's no proof
That is
Will believe that once there is proof of it now it's does not have proof to believe otherwise
Right it's to believe Rogue thing
Resources
But hate these sources
They're real
Realsource
Absolutely
Ballistics
Ballistics expert was National TV shows
Just real quick
Every time that song
He's like you cannot say what Seal Team I'm apart of
And every time he's not there
And at the same time he's like
She says like 20 times on this episode
You know it's raining outside is one of his sources
Adjust the source of the stuff
But he says on air
That's one thing
Alex is kind of implying that he's telling another things behind the scenes
The problem for everyone
Members are the ones with all the intelligence I prefer Seal Team 3
Snob Avengers 2
Yeah it's this point
Is Alex
Has real sources
And it was not questioning
And he knows I know for a fact
Does Las Vegas shooting
You might wonder
Why is Donald Trump
That's a really good question
Why is he resistant
Alex has an answer
1011 days ago
October 1st
Cool music
Dial by Monday
White House sources
Social Security
Because
Isis
With codes
Sleeper Cell attacks across United States
Verizon
That are
And also
Complicated
I don't
Woods built in
What are the codes
Seal Team 6
Trump wouldn't have to say those numbers
What's the
Will it rain
So if Trump
It was Isis publicly
What's going on
Okay well we can just say that about every
Find the nicest
As we all know
Trump
Very careful with what
He says
Because what if it
It was the code
Right
Visit hamdingers it's the code on Mystery Science Theater okay
The Box
Humdingers
Who cares anyway
I think that Alex is narrative here is to
And I will leave it there
So we can move along
Alex talks about how the Las Vegas attack is a cover-up
There is a cover-up going on and
Attack or the tech
Self is a cover-up covering up the details of the attack that Alex
Has been trying to get his info Warriors
To know at the end
He lets slip where he gets a lot of
Cover this up
He said that last Thursday
Itz'ana is he didn't say that he didn't act alone is like
It's unimaginable that he acted alone
Inasmuch as saying it's
Crazy that you think he acted alone
Which isn't saying that they have evidence
That he didn't
Barbie videos
We can talk about the evidence yet
He did say that they were considering radicalization in response to a question
From someone who's in the audience one of the oppressed people at that press conference
Looks like some people help
Stop
So
Oh absolutely let's take a second to enjoy that he just said we don't know
What happened
We know that their stories collapse
About the very little
Highlights everywhere we were right
We told you my girlfriend went there first
We told you
That there were hotel receipts first
These are all are hotel receipts you got room service
These are also inconsequential it was like a receipt for room service for tooth
Days before
It doesn't mean anything
You could have had someone over like I made this point I think on episode I did a loan it could have been oppressed
For all anybody knows
You're going to go through
Not awfully always say
I do all of this stuff is like Alex
It's like saying that
Oh I told you I told you
That there would be an empty bag of chips laying next to the dead body at a murder
But yes
Right
Stealth brilliant about this
What are we talking
We're talking about all of his dumb narrative
Talking about the fact
One dude
Can get
A billion guns
Take them into a f****** hotel
And just starts
Sure no one can stop
And no one cares
Before he knows what's going on
Jobs from getting all of these guns
Explain to me why anybody
15 guns
If you want your argument to be like self-defense
Protecting the home you're not you're not f******
Protecting it from
Cadre of Invaders
Unless you think it is
Home Alone
Could be home
Enm and Alex.
These arnouts jump
We told you that
She was there
Who cares
All of it
And you got it from f******
Unfortunate
A lot of illegal pornography
A lot of people bullying folks into trying to kill themselves
Especially on the pole
He makes it clear on this episode that he gets a lot of his information
4chan
Reddit
The Donald
Who's like okay you don't have sources
Bananas
How important
Like we had like four Chan turn into anonymous
Point kind of behind Anonymous for a while and then anonymous
And then Fortune was like Hey what if we were Nazis
Another
What if we just stop jerking off to h*****
And started oppressing other people
I think some of anonymous is still okay right I think they're still
Yeah
But anyway
Alex
Steve pieczenik
Rescuer footage
It's real
Israel
Wild hogs dear
Nonc
Blow the whole side of the head
I shot one of those giant African antelopes
Big Pieces of Me
Nose ballistics do different things
I think is a little off track there but
Is gone hunting
And he's just completely started about Steve
Yeah might as well have ended with him being
And you go tell your mom right
Damn
Jesus it's crazy I mean he's not wrestling at all with the factor like
If this is Elijah told
Has he told on my show
I wish you would I wish you take that step
But he can't
I would also like to know what else is
That doesn't make me feel good at all
Junior explode through a f****** head I'm sure he's fine
And then he went in for another shot
Amox-clav to make the aftermath of Las Vegas shooting kind of about him
We know that's his specialty
Used to say nobody.
And it really upset on television
Explain
I'm not going along with it
I will not watch the footage
Good
Play on your chauffeur / aminda picture of the shooter
Allegedly a very graphic
Fixer so you're not really taking The High Ground there
The other thing is the only person
In the world
Who sang that it was fake
Is Steve pieczenik
So far he's the only one that I've seen and so the idea that someone
He's trying to set him up
It's Steve pieczenik was trying to set you up not the media
Do you think it's
Psych Warfare Steve pieczenik
Possible
That would be fun
Even more if you just
Was like
I'm bored
I'm an old man
Alex Jones is dumb let's see how far I can take this
Let's just say it's just to see if you can do you want to go to the Moon
Cuz it's
There.
All that lack of gravity
Think of the position
He could go down those are the two I know
I just got a great idea
If we get a hold of wheelbarrow if we get ahold of Larry
We got to ask him for pieczenik
I don't know if they know each other it's like
Well if you're sick you have to call those guy I feel like it's there's a there's an outside
We're like a Larry Steve will stop calling you will leave you alone
Iraq
So it becomes clear that Alex does not know what direction
Action is up
In terms of Las Vegas
Is narrative is all over
He has no control of what's going on
He's he's just spiraling
To the point where later is a guy named John Wesley Rawles on
Survivalblog.com
I bet he's a hero that they can't get him on Skype because he lives in the woods who taught him how to hide his guns
Broadcast
This shooting is suspicious to
Is the guy the pilot
He should have just
Flown into the crowd
Like okay Craig's I mean
Rake
Good point
Let me explain
The road along that way
Do you have to file a flight
ETA from it actually post 9/11
Especially when you're in crowded Urban centers
Yeah
Also
It's very suspicious he probably wouldn't have heard as many
I don't know
Depends on the plane
That's how
Because there were those gas tanks apparently
Nearby
I don't know nobody
Let me let me just ask John Wesley Rawles
Not as efficient as it could have been
But that's literally what this
Unabomber
I think a tree is breaking out in the chat room everyone's Calling lyrics
Spiraling out of control
And that's because they know they're not going to be able to cover it up
Because law enforcement music going along with it
And when it comes out
Criticism of trump now
The constellations brought Trump win
The populist resistance
Before we get into this part I just don't like the idea that he saying
Like a worldwide populist uprising
Another apart of
Because that ties
People across
The global influence
In the United
States with cool guys
These people are just
Connect
They all have their own nationalist populist
Uprising
Perfect sets
He was saying that earlier as if it was what he believed now he's like I don't believe that
No idea what's going on
No control over his own like
The way Fraser
Cuz it makes it seem like
I'm willing to believe that it
Beginning of the show
Didn't mean to say that like there is a code like Isis code in history
This is this is what sources are telling us this is what we this is what we're putting out his news now I don't believe that.
That's the global @fbi
I'm coming out
Blocking
Holyfuck
Document
Now they blame Trump
No but Alex's narrative is completely made up the idea of the trumpster teamsters went on strike
In order to
Stop
The goods out
Tomato
Believably affair
This is very much though especially because the energy from include the people in the Union
Teamsters a local Puerto Rico
We are not going on strike
This argument mean
He has to know that he's saying the absolute
Opposite of the truth
In Puerto Rico
Are doing everything they f******
Because so many people still don't have water
Still don't have power
Can't I can are starving
Are starving
Families are starving and people who are there who are are all really really trying to help
And there's only one
Small group of people
And that's Trump and his f****** monster
So how
I hate how dare you
Monster
What song is this
Launching there
Communist uprising
This is the final countdown
How many days are we out now
And we're ready
Yeah
Smash cut to November 5th
No communist upright remember remember
7th of November
When we've actually
My friend
I'm going to start an uprising it's going to be
Arrhythmic
What Alex believes that everything is based on movies and I know the Guy Fawkes was real
He thinks the beaver Vendetta is the
What is the true story
Through V for Vendetta
Years ago predicted program plan out there for 2017
I don't f****** know that's a stranger to choose knowing nothing about these
Hozier the Bolsheviks
Here in America
If
8 Bolsheviks that I know nothing about versus Alex Jones
Imma go ahead with their Revolution
You guys do you I mean
That
Chat room
I need you to be very serious right now are you guys f****** around about Larry asking for a call
They are saying he called them back
But I think they're f******
I'm not entirely sure
I'm getting a 100% true message from that actually happened is they called me
Never call me again and now you're calling into a trap remember
I will
Larry how are you today
I'm sorry what
I'm sorry to hear that
Just so you know this
We are alive
Streaming on Twitch right now
Let you know we got a couple of questions for you if you're willing to
Alrighty
First off of course
Did you do actually have information that you are willing to
Used to take down the GOP
Would you
Not yet
Would you mind sharing
Just a little bit with us
Blackmail
Okay
Well
My my co-host
Pointed out that
That could be.
Describe this black
Mail
In a court of law
It could be
I think you're the one who has me in
Don't have spam
Cygnet Court
So are you are you actually threatening
Blackmail
If they do what you want them to do
No problem
If you'd like
Would you like to
No I understand
Would you like to text me or
Have me give you a call later
Okay
Sounds like a plan hope you feel better
Alright
Have a good night
Good boy
We can take from that
How how did it look when we doing with our lives
Well I'm just saying and I have information that I will use
If they don't do what I want them to do
Black male that's just me saying that I will tell the truth but I won't tell the truth
If they do what I want them to do
So I think that's more proof that he threatening to Blackmail Congress although his answer would be we are not threatening.
Blackmail Congress
I would love to take him to court for that but I'm not Congress I don't have standing to take him to court
Is get you elected as the representative work
Call our representative
I feel terrible like he really
And I want to get an interview with him tomorrow
Here was the only problem with that
For some reason
Even though I knew we were going to call him tonight I have no point planned any questions
Well that's the big question question but what's up with some softballs
And then maybe he would have been trusting anybody
I just jumped you knew he was going to get off the phone sooner than later
He sounds terrible I don't mean that judgmental
Central Arkansas
Would be central time probably a 70-something year old dude
Wow
We got him basically to admit that he is blackmailing Congress but not black
Cigarette after that yeah
I'm a little bit already check there's blood cell
Harvey Weinstein situation in our position
Harvey Weinstein go f*** himself
And
Alex is Takis
Super convoluted
And touches on victim-blaming in a way that I'm not surprised by but I'm at
I'm still uncomfortable
Minimize it
About
Simply hitting on women
And cheating on his wife
We are angry about
Women saying
That's pretty clear
Make it all about you
Pervert
And then forcing yourself on
It's
Not really doesn't matter anymore
Scary stories
Here's the deal
Whether it's true or not
It's all part of the same slime
There's some truth to what you're getting into when you go to Hollywood
Special
Some of the young
Girls watch TV all day
Continue California
No chicken the bees a crack w****
Snuff film
He probably read that unfortunate
What the f*** is this on Reddit / of a Donald
Bill is a rapist
If our show were bigger you get $2,500 for saying that
Are you know what I did to something that I really really thought about after this
Harvey Weinstein
Is that
Everybody's like why are you talking about how Trump is a racist do you know we're only condemning racist when I
Whenever they're on the the wrong side
There is some truth to that
Is the f****** rapist
But you're right there is more than needs to be addressed about that
Write like all of these most likely this is and this is the this is nothing like
Now I remember how
Small a deal
Like relatively speaking
Speaking people made of that when Clinton was President
Sure
Ended up being
Stuff ended up not being true
Stop Larry Nichols
To the Forefront
Liza Larry Nichols brought up muddy the issue of what Clinton actually did get a lot of terrible things
Polishing it
It made a lot of people tune out there is a friend on the phone Larry Nichols is responsible for some of that
1 things that I think is super inch
Interesting is on yesterday show Mike cernovich was on
And he was trying to make the point that he's like
Oh this is like
I want to say that it's really cool that there are Democrats
Who are
I'm sending back money that you donated and donating it and
Stuff like that you know I always expect
If you don't expect them to defend him
It's really cool to see that they're you know they denounce
Going to get really mad
About Republicans but they're getting really mad about this and I was like
You see like Mike cernovich
Try and reduce that talking point into Infowars
And it just beat like
There's a
Super weird
Send.
Like he's saying all this
Stop
You know hitting on ladies and cheating on your wife as opposed to the reality what it is
We are defending him accidentally
Defend rapist cuz I
Arepas but I'm saying if anybody is a rapist
That I don't know is a rapist
About that
Look here's the here's the thing that I really can't
Here's the thing that I really thought about a lot
With this Harvey Weinstein
It is
Something that
Because I don't have to
To personally deal with
I have
Absolutely not giving enough at
In my life
Absolute
Sure
It's
It's mind-boggling to me
That I haven't
Like for all of my
You know
B*******
Liberal Progressive righteousness
What are the other is at the other side like all I can do is scream about how this s*** is is awful
We know comedians in Chicago
Who have absolutely committed similar things
I can't
I want to speak out about this
That's right but the people that we've talked to the victims of this b******* have universally said
Don't say anything
Yeah and I don't know I don't know what to do about that
Certainly not on the show
Certainly not
Calling Larry Nichols is dicey enough territory I don't know I don't know what the right answer
Incredibly complicated I don't know
But it's something to wrestle with something
To listen to people and try and figure out what the right answers I'm not sure
Will you you know you read all of this all of this s***
A lot of it comes down to like
Hey this should just be women who have to speak out about
This should be men speaking out about it too
I really do
But I don't know how to name names
Without the victim's approval
Other than to say snot other than to say this guy is a f******
Sexual harasser he's a Serial sexual assault
I have no proof because nobody wants to come
Admitted
I don't know I don't know what the f***.
To do because I want to do something
Something mean
Well with respecting the wishes of the 1st
I just it's not
I'm I'm I'm I'm worried
On a certain level
It varies it there's a piece that you're
Complaining about your position in this
But you're a tertiary character actual
Bright
Calm down
Okay I'm not good at listen to people and be empathic that's the best thing we can do
Where Alex pretend moving actually about Trump
Restaurants
Girlfriend everyday is what this is all about
Of course they're going after him
To make it about a men's war on women
So real quick real quick
Here is what he's talking about
And then they're going to roll women out there
MLB
Crystallize this morning
I'm looking at it
She's going to happen
Alex is a gene
It happened
I believe it's August 8th people come outside they've been assaulted by truck
Yeah
The people who cared about it
Maybe didn't care about it for the right
Supposedly care about it now that
Tina Scott doing
Voted for
Yeah it's it's it's
85% of our presidents have committed sexual assault in some form another
Probably America's filled with white racist
Intrinsic problem with how our culture has treated male power
It is unfortunate
It's accepted
Yeah
That's why it's everywhere
Let's move along
Next clip
Where Alex Jones talks
About 40 per-cent of men
Let's just
Mobile number
If you take a hundred percent
And you minus that 40%
You get 60
That number is relevant
This clip
Bad transition
Transition transmission
Checkpoint the last 2 weeks
Rental Truck
Closer to 60%
Facebook
So please do hold on to the let's explain something cuz it actually goes to a really f****** funny play
The research came here
Because I have pulled up Trump's approval rating
Currently an aggregate of all of the
Currently at 8:50
6.7 disapproval rating
Any 37.5 approval rating
If you weren't even add Alex's very generous 15
Points to the 37th
.5 still
Still a bit south of it's 60 prediction
But there's just absolutely no way that works misinterpreting house 22
It's work in terms of
Not under
Stuff like that
Allow you to move
I'm sorry for interrupting
I don't
About the approval ratings polls
Because
Those people would vote for him again
If we did the election
Tomorrow
It doesn't matter what his approval rating
Are they would still vote that weird 37% every single
Maybe not everyone but
Most of those GOP identified voters
Would do it over again
I don't give a f*** what they think about their shity president that they elected if they would vote for the GOP again
Because Trump is not
It's not
An outlier in the
GOP
I was doing everything that the GOP is always
Wanted to do
REI
Right
There's an article in Business Insider that came out this afternoon the track
The change in Trump's net approval rating
And if you look at this it down in literally every
Tri-State
Every state
Since the election Trump has gone down
At least
Net point
In terms of his approval would be the
The
Approval - disapprove
Alex Jones has a strong bed
Good whatever he's at
14 points down
In terms of the net approval rating
Illinois-chicago baby down 30.6
Terms of net approval
Reflecting higher
0%
What's the most
Conservative State you can think of like Wyoming
14.1 points
I think isn't it like
West North
Dakota that
North Dakota down 15.7%
Right so
I don't know if I mean it's just the idea that he's up at all in the polls are they any good
He's completely
Rosati
Maybe the better question
Rather than his
Approval Ardis
AR
Would you
Knowing what you know now
Would you about it for him
Because the answer wood
Who gives a f*** about us
Approval-disapproval rating
Is the president until our
Bulshit
Chevy oligarchs have the balls to pressure
There
Bought Congressman to actually do some
He's going to prove or disapprove
It's too late
Probably so here is the end of that clip again
I got it
He's going to explain
Is
Somewhere we trying to buy a vacation
You got to reset
Your cookies
Cuz if you don't reset your cookies they're going to charge you a higher price
Makes perfect sense up on that s***
Answer that leads into this
This is Maybe
A minute and a half later
Weird
That's good advice
Reasonable Drive
I'll tell my wife
Watch this
And every
The product
AR Lower
Price of magic
Talkabouttd
Covering about face
Brought up.com
It's the same price you see
Do stuff
Wow
So good smooth silky smooth
From Alex Jones
To do not buy any valak goes on 6 minutes
It's painfully long
Keep talking about Las Vegas
Now he's got to talk about air filters
So he doesn't 6-minute add goes to Commercial and then comes back
It gets into something else that's stuck in his
Scroll
If anybody knows what music playing behind him
Uno
Easter break
Inception
A big old fat
Music
That's code isn't the opposite
NFL giving into Trump
Waving the white flag
I still think it's a little bit of a
A little bit of
Little doggie whistle
What the white flag was really hard
Let's
Yeah
I don't know it just struck my ears
50% in viewership
But he says
Juicy
Gross
Disgusting can make describing numbers gross
I thought I don't know I don't like him calling anything
Juicy
And then I'm going to dive into my investigation
I hope we have more than those four beers
I was going to say we're already about an hour and now getting to the
Of the episode Special Report
Actually let me rephrase
And I have kept you from diving into the meat of the episode for this long
Making good time
I'm going to be screaming at you
Yeah you're the last little clip
Alex just saying weird stuff that I
Just coded line
Ghost of the Old Republic
Burning in the heart
Ears
I would love that to be my intro coming up on stage
Verizon
Here's that
He introduces Bannon talking about how they're going to primary all these Republicans who don't go along with
The Trump agenda never going to take down establishment Republicans
Alright you guys you guys f******
Okay have a war within your rank
Negative
What's going to come out of that war obviously
Other people are what they don't realize is that they created
The dumb people that are going to destroy them
Looks like aloe vera always Republican did the GOP
Capable of controlling this monster and then
I'm talking about
For us
Is it negative if they're going to destroy
The GOP establishment because what comes out of it is so much worse
Ladies Alex Jones School
Liberty Movement
Because at least
I mean
Sable
Politicians are great well it's not as close to Sovereign citizen
That's my position you want to be as far away from Sovereign citizens in general is pasa
I do think that there is an
A legitimate parallel now
Between
The progressive
Wing of
The left
Looney's
And there's only one connection that they have
Which is that
Growing number of people
Are realizing that the system we have
Is f****** up and it's killing
And
The Republican lunatics who are trying to destroy the GOP establishment want to kill for
They're doing it they understand the reality that she actually has
2 Chainz
Really fat
We can't we can't allow it to to do this
Yeah
That is something that I do have in common with them in that I do also realize
That
Neoliberalism and neoconservatism
Which are
Essentially
With slightly different cultural value
Brave
Leading to the end of the world
Agree
I was trying to make is that the idea of wrestling
Against
A
More robust
Bigger Liberty Movement
Is a scary Prospect
You like trying to
Waiting again
Dumbass
All right I think I disagree
Well there's about
A couple million people with
5 million gun
The take that up with you
They are when you reveal
How
White supremacist
Does the GOP Act
Phileas
The people who are theoretically in the
Center
Are going to rely are going to lean back towards
Oh
Nazis are bad
Like all this is doing again is revealing
How about early f***** up and racism
The GOP has been
Always
Yeah it is not a new
This is what people believe
Look
Lynchings didn't stop
Big Dipper
You know maybe maybe that
It's they just changed for
It's the same ship and twenty years ago
Even though we theoretically had a more reasonable GOP
It was still going on
We just didn't talk
I'm so now they're just revealing that their months
I'm not disagreeing with you at all I'm just trying to figure out how to pay resident
This investigation know if you've ever listened to anything I've ever said
Thinking of like what's the best transition
What's the word I'm going to use the only time he was after that 40 to 60
Good speaking of something that's good
I love you Dad
Today on the October 10th show
We have.
From one of the lamest
Obscure members of the Infowars
Would you like to make a guess
Securities
Lamest
Rainbows
Whatever happened to your girl
Millie
A barrier
She's gone Into Obscurity though I haven't heard
Not yet
In Florida for a bit with a grandma
Oh I don't know
Hope she's alright
We're getting we're getting a guest
Jakari Jackson that is not correct he's never comes out as I go back
Is John bowne
Oh that's right I remember that
John bowne
Make
The worst
Most
Special Report
And I'm going to clinicals
Critically deconstruct it
Buy f****** piece until there is no bone but no already left on these bones do you want me to
Put Cthulhu here while you do that and then I'll just I'll just come back whenever you like of user feedback
So here's how the the report starts out
Has to do with this supposed Bolshevik Revolution that's coming up
As we face
The violence that
Voice over
It's important
The Cedars Selinsky
Tactics
Coming up
Title rules
We can clearly see how the Whiskey's rules
Are being applied
So have you got the premise
The Bolshevik Revolution
Making their move in November is Alex's pitch to everybody
Pikachu remix
Hydrilla
Bun you scream icing fun phones
So
John Bonham
Did he is it stalled Alyssa
Yeah and then he shortened it
Crystalline
Yes
I am not a fan of
Saul Alinsky is one of these guys who was like George Soros in terms of universal Boogeyman of the Liberty Movement
The book called Rules for Radicals
This johnbowne fella
He thinks
He's cracked
The code about what's going to be happening at Isis Isis 6969
Hugo's through the rules
Radicals
He provides examples of a bunch of them
That view Liberals are doing
And I
Would like to propose
Versions that Infowars is actually doing
In a more real way so you're the first rule
Power is not what you have
Enter anyone in the government
Free speech
Historically
So that is a teacher at Dartmouth
He goes in
The gives a media appearances about an
How's that clip demonstrate
Power is in perception
I don't believe you
18 no point during that clip did he
He claimed to have more power than he
Kind of what Alex does
All the nearest clip from last week
This is from a law-enforcement source
Information
FBI HRT
And I found
Information in the room
So he did not kill himself the FBI hostage rescue team killing
Delete this information
All I'm saying is
So
Clip last week basically rolls his eyes
Perception
You just want your enemies to pick that you have that information
Do you are using
Larry Nichols
Can you really blackmail the GOP
No
Number to never go out
Outside
Quiz horse
Racist Trump supporter
Horse
The police
Administration have been increasingly intolerant
So I don't understand how that works either for his example
So if they were just
Is stay within your expertise
Fair
Alex
Just constantly talks about the globalist and Things That No One Else really
Nose is real or bruising
He insisted that
He is
More knowledgeable than
Many experts and climate change
Even people who make Max
Right who else
Speak like three languages also like like he just has his own
He has his own world did he lose them
Inside
All of the narrative
Whenever their guests are on who are like
You don't get along with him
He doesn't
Drift too far outside of whatever is singing
Racine open interviews haven't gone well he doesn't engage with me
Things that are necessarily outside of it
Number three
We have real
So I
No that's just as I was accidentally
Year is
Air assault
U.s. code
So
Alright Eddie Bravo people are going to know what that is
Other people
Hellfire club
And stuff like that if you don't know what he's talking about you're not going to be able to engage with it
Globalist narratives are exactly Express
Rule number three
Rule Number Four
Number for
He does that all the time I have solutely
I even when it's not too here's where I ran out of time before the show and I don't have clip to demonstrate all of these
But you are watching the show
Yeah they use real five
Number 5
Ridicule is man's most potent
So I don't
That was Kennedy former MTV VJ Kennedy interviewing the guy who's on the left I guess
I don't understand I mean like I don't know if that's
Ridicule are they Immortal might just be a snippy,
Is Shiva
No the guy is the liberal
Indulgence
Archetypical c*********
He does voices to be Isaac
BBC Alba to all the time
He does nothing but ridicule people because he has no
Did he can really stay in
Here's rule sticks
A good
Is 1 Europe
People enjoy
Urgent
Dear friends
What is 13130 fastest USA
Example
Before
Call Jeff's if we got to get him
Lincoln the movie
Pain in your audience
Bill Clinton is a rapist on TV
Indicative of
You know
Making your tactics
Appealing pierotti your tactics better
Picking out people who break these rules seeing as how he has a lot of experience breaking
He's made his tactics essentially just bullying anybody with
Progressive
And that's very appealing to his audience
What are you doing
Okay so when you chose those clips
Did he
Did he not
Clips
Because look
I'm sure you could find some
Google some clips of people saying dumb s*** like that
Like it wouldn't even be that much better much better versions of liberals ridiculing people
Pickard
Just do anything that I do a rule 7
Number 7
A tactic that drags on too long
Don't be
In the last week Alex Jones is
Open pitching conspiracy theories about the Las Vegas
I stopped but when it started to get boring you switched up into the LA
He switched over in Tulsa
Absolutely
We talked about this all the f****** time like right but we do follow the next
Keep the pressure on
I would
I would also like to suggest because he's still complaining about Hillary Clinton all the flying time
So you
These working with this rule
So it was real nice
Every time
They
Do you want to Saul Alinsky
Everybody has to drink all right
Number nine
The threat is usually more terrifying than the thing itself
I would argue that Larry Nichols threatening to Blackmail Congress
Is on hundred percent that Alex Jones also threatened
Like all sorts of secret information all this stuff
So number 10
Is the development of operation
Is that will maintain a constant pressure
Opposition
I don't think John Brown knows what that means
Alarm
Nothing
So I
Number 11
If you push the negative hard enough it will push through and become a positive
The Publix sympathizes with the underdog
I would argue that
You would say
Vivid
Antifa getting sympathy
You could make easily the same argument
Your
Yeah beat up all the time
You know what I mean
Okay now you're a Nazi until proven otherwise if you're on the
I was already there
UK it's a two-way street
It goes both ways my friend up with this special report
So here's a real 12
Number 12
The price of a
Is a constructive alternative
Because you're caught
Without a solution to the problem
I would argue that they're not great at that
Let's clean that sort of stuff
They have a fake version
But anything you would have a solution for it wouldn't be true
Number 13
Guitar
Personalizing
White people
I would argue that
Most of the time Alex Jones assaying the globalist
How to kill your family
Break your kids and take them out of your backyard I think that's personalizing
Greco's commercial
Maybe we should just go through the psychopath test and
Just be like
Millions of dollars make a better Special Report anyone who's thinking
Just be right through that
That
One of the rules
Like it isn't that
One of the rules is
Ridiculing your enemy strength
So pulling up
Rarity
But isn't that exactly what that is
Like leaning directly into it because that's the same bulshit that we've been dealing with all along
Alex is like
Whatever it is they say we're doing is what they're doing
I told of course you go right into the s*** that you like all they really need
To do
Is
Go through
What would like a list of the ship that they do
And just claim that the other side is doing it
The other thing I would like to say is that the argument that I intended to
To weave this kid kids should not watch the ship
Gloria
The argument that I had hoped to sort of transition this to is
Does ask you a question
What do you think the enemy
Alex is using
Cuz I would posit
It's his audience
If not the globalist
Look at the roof
Right but look at the rules
Power is not what you have it's what you appear to have
He only appears
To have this sort of
Fake
Secretive information
Who is audience who is bought into all of it
Globalist
Or the people in power don't actually believe Alex Jones
The only time he shows up in
The news
Making of Fame
Claymore
Play some gumball shadow
You know all of that stuff
Stay inside your expertise exactly
He does with his audience
Call him on it like what the
Sandy Hook bulshit
You just go outside of their expert
Using text well look
That whole thing
Make the enemy lives up to its own rules
If you believe in Liberty
We're the only ones who were fighting for your money
Ridiculing I think it's a little more subtle I think they're making fun of Their audience
Just buy
Impaired vision
Make a Rattata tactics
Appeal to your audience really never let
Threats work without follow-through he always teases. That never comes up
Image entire episode
Listen I'm going to get through
All of these articles
I've got 100
Sheets of paper
We're going to get through everything
Create constant pressure he does that all the time
A negative getting beat up is actually a positive right
YouTube censorship
And oppression women
She is there on air
Affected all the time anyway
Though he says important things that allows Larry Nichols
To commit a felony on the air
Push back on it
Well we kind of made him we were more asking him if that's what he was actually doing
You know all of these right now
And then he makes a purse
Haha
His audience is his enemy
He's using the whatever these Saul Alinsky
Tactics are
Against
Thank you
Write solinsky eye
Dammit
So
Here we go
We're done with the John bowne
And I apologize for making people listen to his terrible voice
Garbage but it is extra
He gets into some trouble news and it's incredibly scary outside of Infowars
Emporia's f****** scary
What is a stripe
Posture here
Also criticizing Trump
This is about the compass fermentation
Military post
Hey I just made it
The idea that
Days ago he is saying this is the Calm before the
The storm
Indicates
He's going to do something
Going to see a nuclear weapon
I only think it's possible if we do it
Exactly
I think that
Very possible that Trump is
Nuclear warhead
I think it's more likely that I want it
But the others are asking
Like you'll find out is
Is Bucking
That's a threat that's right like that's not a
Yeah that's f***** up
That really terrifies me anyways I'm
Incredibly
Uncomfortable
So remember earlier
Not sexy
Really boring
. sex
Alex gets deeper into that about
But then Alex makes
Startling admission
Pretty sure it makes him.
But we already knew
Show
Infowars
About delivering
Myself
6 months ago
His plan got Pitch
Through
Gino's
Horsey first put out planet
About the funding
And Anna
He's talked about Obamacare we went over this in detail and up episode like
Six months ago or so
Freddy
True there's money that came from
As if I got it money in the government
Jerome corsi
Apparently
Is lobbying in
In Washington
That's
Not
Good
That's not yet don't you want your news Outlet
Also lobbying for you
No
Celavi for you
No cuz they have your best interest at heart
That doesn't sound like human nature at all I don't know they're all altruistic
Especially whenever it's a corporation
If Alex Jones was trying to successfully lobbying the government
And he got his way
They would have liked
The school lunch program will be gone
It'll be replaced with super male Vitality Licor caveman the caveman for all the kids
Oh by the way I can't get audio of this commercial cuz it only plays during the live things commercial to cut out
From what I end up taking eclipse from straight-up commercial for caveman
Where he blamed caveman or give credit
Free son going through puberty
Well don't you want that in our elementary schools
So I guess
I'm up earlier than humans
Is that what we want to be again
I guess those
Classic mailbox
It's showing how
Because the president
Tomorrow
Article
Vicodin
Paul healthcare plan
And it's got the whole plan
Even if I don't get rid of the whole building
Itself
Quality Care
So I can do any of that
This is sad
This we're back back again
Does he really believe that
I don't know
That one
That one is one that he really believes
Mainly because I don't
Understand how that way
First off
He doesn't understand that the insurance
Industry
Is ultimately socialized
Like he doesn't get that the entirety of it is
You pay
Even though you're not sick
Because people who are sick will use that money
And if you get sick
The people who aren't sick are going to
Give that money to you in order for you but there's just a corporation skimming off the top
Yeah right there
If you get rid of
Those
Directions
Then
The corporation won't skip
The money off the top
But what he doesn't understand is that it's the reverse
Where's Camelot more
He's dumb
They are stupid versus evil
Continue in the dump
But also
I don't think I think he's a sociopath so he doesn't know how to laugh
I think the most likely thing is that he is dumb
Do the alignment is naturally evil has a baseline of evil even when he's being dumb
I think that's possible
Anyway it is next cliff
Yeah in your in your Dungeons and Dragons like nine things right there
It's not lawful evil or chaotic evil or neutral evil
University of New Brunswick
Saint Valentine
What's happening is they're less sexually active now on
And so
I see all this online that's what a relationship is
Just read about that
Psychological studies
Let's continue
Play buried boy
I think this is a new a new addition to the drinking game room is Alex Jones
Done something sexual
That's
What are you talkin about
Get the f*** out of here with that
A lot of fun I enjoy enjoy that clips
But that's a good example of what
Trying to get through the news
No
Analysis style is
But actually being with him in Broad
Terrible forklift last
And we get into a fight
Search somebody
Statistics came out today about crime
Extra read all of them
Who's presenting on this
Solve this crime as black people
I haven't looked at it but my gut tells me he's not being accurate
That's just my feeling
Percentage-wise
If I was a betting man right
I bet on you I'm fine not knowing entirely at this point
Because
This is going to come back up on a future show
I'll get some research by then so for now
Tentatively
Strongly disagree without
But this place was worth keeping in just because I even
Even without knowing anything about with us
He's talking about
Greenfield
Use white people
Because they hype up
The few questionable
As if it's the end of the world
Blooded
Call Sugar Mama
Caveman with the bone broth
With the tumeric the chaga mushroom or the other concentrated things like
What a piece of s***
What are
Piece of garbage
Have you even heard
From the New Black
No
And also
Look
Neither of those two are advocating for killing White
I am
Alex goes along with his narrative
Freaked out white people who are doing it
Well I mean yeah that's me
I will be fine if you picked me as a boogeyman
11th grade
Like you called him left a message that multiple people called him and told him to call you
That's weird
The house phone number from before
The guy who called me about Alex that one time up
Seriously
Cuz it is if you wants to talk again tomorrow then I want to make sure that we actually do have
I can wing it cuz I got a lot to ask
Okay tell me more about Linda bloodworth-thomason
He can't hear you
No
No you have to talk
I need to go buy a new cord
Right
So today Alex is stupid
He's convoluting this that Las Vegas narrative
The point where you can't even keep track what's going on
Do you have
Totally real sources
John bowne sucks at doing his job
I mean
You know what
Sitting there at work today
John Boehner
Amazing
His job is he's a Sleeper Cell
Voice over
The other side is doing
Crushed it
It makes it obvious
The thing that I came to when I was listening
Today was just like
This show is bad
I know if it's like
10 months into like a tent
Studying for one of the first times
Man I would like to get them in shape
Take me to manager
Yeah you know he's not going to fly right
Do you think this report
Is good enough
Alex
Come on
You got to make these less transparent moves
Your main problem with the show today
Is it wasn't slick enough know really any other problem it was a
One of the first times that really got my head does like they need a program
Thought process was like
Look
This dude is good at what he does
I think he's bad I think he's evil I stand behind a lot of that not today no way man
What he does in terms of like
Being slippery of yelling on a bike
But I don't think he's good at what he does in terms of running the entire operation
How much Buckley is doing
Behind the scenes
More people better behind the scenes
The inevitable
Issue with that right and it's
The same thing with Trump
He is except like what Trump is a horrible evil psychopath is going to get us all killed
As far as
That guy getting elected
He has to be good at f******
Can something right
He's very playful
If you're not an
Idiot you know you don't want to work with
The only people that will work with him
A bright-eyed
Young
Competent
Program director
Secret
Outlet
I mean
If I were trouble I would be
Kind of ashamed
The sloppiness of it
And here's
I accidentally watched a little bit of the real news with David Knight
And he boring is s***
He doesn't have the skills that Alex has
But the show is
Much better produce
Haha David Knight doesn't freak out and lose his place and thing
Whatever he does the ads
They're very
Kemp's ice cream
They're a little more classy in terms of how he gets into them
He always knows
Commercials are coming up he's never caught off guard
You never the middle of screaming before commercial
He's a boring
But competent broadcast
At least in terms of like what is
Acceptable brought
He's a game manager
Right
General Star pro wrestling fans out there
But like are you at the same time I understand
Alex Jones
Alex Jones would not be what
He is
If you was
Bad
Corso is it is this it's this classic
Paradox
The crazy man theory of foreign policy though
Is that a
An unhinged Act
Is somebody that is far more threat
If you have a Nixon in there it's like
I'm more afraid of America cuz I have no f******
Conclude with that guys go
Going to do
That kind of next year I will be working at Infowars and you will have a
Gun
And then you wouldn't grab
Listen
I would pass a background check but I can't have a gun because I have a history of mental illness and
My medication
Is working perfectly
Perfectly right now but I can't have one history issue
I want
On my on my
Because it's too it's too terrifying
Cuz it's a button
It's a button
It's a big thing that has kept me
From killing myself in the past has always been that it would be a lot of
Lack of access
Hassle
Great great way to put it for a national Mental Health Group
A lot of the time one of the big like you would have to take a
Depart my Razor to get the razor blades out
Be a lot of work and you can't
Something
So I did
Mental Health Awareness Day
I did
Attempt
To jump
And that did not go well
My railing
Every some reason either
Jump to it
The context of in front of
Karura
Which in retrospect is like
Come on man that's not going to work
National
Mental Health
Having these sorts of things in your pasta is okay it doesn't mean you're broken you can't get better there
Please help absolutely
And
I don't know why
I just think that they big
Sing is
Keep trying
I just because I've gone through a bunch
Keep On Keepin On
Time I would never have actually
I got onto the meds that I'm on now and they work perfect
Any
Failure or setback
In terms of progress
Does evidence that progress
Isn't going to happen always impossible
You're setting yourself up for math
You know
It's very attractive to do that but
Weird way to end
Weird weather at
You know someone who I wish would stop price
Floor balcony
Himself
He has right before the number of it
Alex
In color