Thanks for holding
Alexandra Thurston color
Alex Jones
Dan
Is there a bear is a couple twists
I know a lot of
And I forgotten most of Arizona prescription energy is our sponsor for the day
Going over the October 11th episode
Put it out on Twitter so I guess he denied that there was anything going on
Could not have
I come in like f*** y'all
Going on
Earlier today and
Guys we're going to call Larry Nichols he's agreed to at most an hour
Screaming at his face
That lot over the phone yet but yes earlier today we had a very
Congenial conversation
Complicated
It's not alright
And then if they're like
Do that the Senate votes it's very simple but it's complicated
If it does happen they're going to be like
No no no
And it won't happen because the Republicans are f****** coward
Even he fuc
He knows because Haler
We talked about yesterday November 4th is worse than
Alinskyite evereve
Larry Nichols like you said he agreed to talk to us for an hour
He also said I think your offer was half an hour I also predict is going to hang up with
Pretty quick is he is going to try and worm his way out of
Literally every
Well
And here is Larry Nichols right now guys
Larry how are you today
Just to let you know we are live on the air right now we are recording
You are right on time I friend
Real quick before we even get into this there's one thing that I do want
Tucanos
Upfront
Which is questions about your past with the clintons and a lot of the
Claims that you've made
You've said a lot of things that are
Andrew
So what we'd like to do is
Just have a conversation where you feel comfortable telling us what it what really happened
And all of those things is that okay with you
Excellent
What work did you do for for Bill Clinton
The largest
Gotcha
I was thinking I was thinking Doogie Howser but that's fine
Started working for Bill what year was that
Okay and then how did that turn into your jobs for Bill
Call Neva
Little Rock
Sorry Justin Bieber
And what was that
It was a 70
It was the 70s
So in the very first meeting you had with Bill Clinton
Bill told you
That he likes to screw around basically
So why did you why did you start working for him then if that was that
Money
Yeah so are we working
Political world lyrics
This is killing me
So did you function as his campaign managers in
And this was during the first time he was governor of Arkansas
He did not become
Governor contiguous leash
He lost the second time and then became Governor again
In 83
Nat1
Whatever you're that watches
Song b**** Don't listen
Who are who are the
People from Vietnam
Okay so you went to work
4 bill
Then you went to work for Frank White
And then you went back to work for Bill
Okay
La Thoma
To build build sold out
So Bills sold out basically in 82
Okay
Okay so then you stopped working for Bill in 1988 why did that have
When you're when you were working in the marketing department of the Arkansas Finance Development Authority
Where's the Nicaragua
Resistance
Haha
El Rancho
What what
Racket
So did you actually go to Vietnam
Doing crazy stuff in the jungles Nicaragua Nicaragua
Okay could you could you tell us a little bit of that crazy stuff
How did how did Reagan put you down in Nicaragua
You didn't you didn't stop working for Bill until 1988
New York whatever
Okay so if I understand this correctly
You had a jingle business
And then
Directly from there you were recruited into extrajudicial Nicaraguan operation
That's wild
But how in God's name
Did the Stephen
The did the Stephens Brothers have something to do with that
I need one of their guys
Truth or dare
You got understand
Okay so here's the here's the problem I have with that
Is that
Is there interest make sense or whatever that's fine but the ideas
Like they would have you take care of all of their interests based on
A slight bit of advertising work seems very strange
Yeah that's like if Obama had the guys from the Sonic commercials kill run I ran for awhile
Wild
Is just a job
Alright
So so because of that
24/7 once he got elected
All right that that sounds a little bit far-fetched
I mean it's okay
So
Alright alright let's
I mean
That bananas
If it's true that is one of the most implausible realities I think I can imagine
Fair enough fair enough
The public version in all the information
Verifiable through Source reports
I wear that you work there at the Arkansas
Financial Development Authority
And that you made a bunch
Long distance calls to Nicaragua and that's why bill
Ask you to resign
So
How is it how is it that
All of this reporting corroborates one side of the story and only you is supporting yours
Today
Fox News
There is
We're all the adults do you got to take everything with a grain of
Adults
The only world I have to deal with
Nicaragua
Well yeah but
Arkansas
Washington
What should I say
You went on a radio show in claims you kill people for the Clinton
What's that
You were drugged up
So
Ashoka
Children
Okay The Killing was metaphorical
OK Google
Saying that you made stuff up then
I mean
That kind of makes it hard to believe what you're saying right do you see the DCd
That's fair
I truly believe that yes
I barely really care what I believe
We're not trying to come down we're not
So if
If you admit to having made up
Whenever there wasn't any information
Would you say that when you said that Barack Obama is a secret Muslim you made that up to
What I did
Okay so when did you stop
When your family told you that you were getting too old
Call mrs. at Triad
Right
Sure sure sure
Dish
Crazy
Well it's also I mean all this stuff is great
Airstrip
Trump from where I'm from where I'm sitting Larry just seems very convenient that you're bringing that into all of this
When you admit that you were involved in Nicaragua
You know it seems like you're
Maybe
Right
Now here's here's my here's my question to you real quick before you keep going any further
Now when you are
Describing this story
This is happening at the same time that you are convicted of fraud
And it was
By deception they were facing charges all around Arkansas
And
That was before that this was that in the lead-up to when you were
Alright
Beaver Lake
That's that's fine that's fine Clinton as some sort of all all night
Towing power that can just black people at at will
Don't you don't you see how this kind of
Conspiracy just doesn't hold up
Especially because you're also saying that it's Brothers
Okay well then we'll then let me
Let's switch gears then
So
Just recently in 2015
You told Alex Jones that Obama was the last
Because if you're the last president
Yes
Why do you think that's true
Washington last 25-30 years
Into a state
When the president
Santa Clara
That's demonstrable be untrue
I don't know I don't know
Yeah I live in Chicago
No yours in Washington
Show me show me
State congressman
I've read a lot of these
FEMA camp in the FEMA documents
I've read a lot of those all of all of those FEMA documents are public information
So you're saying that there's a secret documents that we don't know about
Additional
Government
Temperature
Is there people that run around and they say they know
I think we're just basing this on
Things we've read
Things that we understand that the president becomes king and all the Congress people become do
It's just very fanciful it doesn't
That's not how the world works
Roughly 250,000 dollars
Well yeah all they want is tax cuts for the rich
Kimani that's not in their salary
Considering parachute they're taking on consulting jobs later on
Some sort of
Feudal society that they're trying to build
I bet
That's a good point
I think everybody's pretty aware
Well we're going to talk about the cost of things
Would you
Would you say that right now part of your income if not a lot of it
Comes down to
You know people
Believing what you're saying
Also
You know we have job
We have nine-to-five jobs in a couple of jack off to pick were funny
Larry
Right
Well then here's my question
Okay if you are afraid of Obama trying to become the last president
And they're becoming King
Essentially are you not worried about Trump doing that
Okay
So would you say that Trump is
So here's the thing I want to know
Knowing what we know about Trump and his actions currently
It seems far more likely that
Trump is
Going to try and pull that off it is if it is real
Then Obama ever was
Right because he's not a secret movie
Oheka Castle
If it's becoming King is part of the FEMA provisional powers
It's the reason babe
FEMA as it is right now after these hurricanes we've seen that they don't do the best job necessarily
They're not necessarily the most effective organization that we have within our government
It seems like installing a kingship
Might be difficult when they can't
Get supplies where they need to be
And then you need the support of the military
They would have to turn against the entire concept of democracy
Wow
Washington
Any goddamn money
Believe me when I say if there really were a rainy day fund
He would have
A long way away from having a FEMA provisional
Government very very different
Very close to being a
Percent of the people in this country
I'm sure of that
I believe that a hundred percent
You can you can if you'd like to we say f*** all the time
Alright
Now we're on board
So here's here's another
Here's another question
For you all right
When you when you go on Alex's
You willingly go along with the the whole globalist idea how much of that do you actually believe
Roaches
It's good you lucked out on that one
What would you do talk about one time was that you believe
Hillary Clinton practice black magic
Which was
Isn't that troopergate
Whatever
Designing Women
Lovett great show
Quick follow-up
Can a Witness church quick follow-up
Linda bloodworth-thomason from Designing Women was there
Did Delta Burke ever go or Meshach Taylor
I'm curious I like that show and I was a kid
Yeah
I was just asking if Meshach Taylor ever went to the woods Church
With Hillary
You there
I'm sorry about that a little bit of issue it's just
Really really quick
I mean
Here's here's my last question to you
Yes
Call Cuzzo just
So just cause more attention to come your way that's not a good argument
I think you're I think that's probably save might have better use of their time in the same way
You did threaten to Blackmail Congress recently
And no one's going to sue you for that
Congress people have a much better use of their time
Been hunting down these sort of
Lawsuits that probably could be one based on
It being very
Sure
Oh
Right information that you would otherwise use to Blackmail them would then become public
Yes it would
Larry Larry
If that argument work no one would ever get charged with blackmail
Here's something you can do
Okay
Futures Granger
Blackmail him
Biker witches
Maybe whatever
Alright
I think you're I think we have a misunderstanding of what our goals are and
Isaac thank you for talking to us I think we got to get a move on
You're just fine
All right you have a good night
Alright
Post call
Outlook
Well here's a really believes all of that b*******
Yeah the issue and the issue becomes too like
So much stuff is is completely undisprovable
And that whole idea of you had to be there at the wild 70th and Arkansas switch
It's like in the 70s people or blackmailed people do cocaine in the south
There's all that sort of stuff and it's like alright fine that's the narrative obviously wasn't in the 70s
Arkansas it's very difficult to get around the
You were a functionary low-level adman and then you got put in charge
Of drug running and gun-running operations in Nicaragua
And the youngest president ever is Handler like it's just all
Lake and his rebuttal to that is just
Well
Okay
So
Do you know what's crazy
Guy who wrote badabababa
North Korean spy operation
Booking
The chat room
Please don't ever ask us to call him again
It's really difficult for me to handle two because
AR phone
I was working you know it's just
I difficult for me to get involved and Larry just loves to f****** talk
Yeah I know but I couldn't really get anything and there's there's like follow-ups and rebuttals I would have liked to make end
It's just incredibly difficult timeline works out
But I know he was doing after he got fired from the Clinton campaign
There's literally no way any of that stuff matches up
You started working with a guy named Larry case
Been trying to sell stories about these women
To tabloid papers
Larry case recorded all of his conversations and gave them to the Press
After he and Larry Nichols had a huge falling out
I will put a link up later to Salon article about this
It's it's fascinating like
You're never going to get what you want out of a phone call like that my biggest issue there is
Why don't we just we just let him ramble and that might not be the best thing ever but I got a little bit of a cold
I was I was really hoping that if we
Like
I was hoping that it sooner or later he would drop
The facade
Because why
Because they can't f****** keep doing that
We know it's not true
He genuinely believes that though so I guess I guess of course there's no point in
And doing that s*** piece of s*** clearly killed people in Nicaragua
Or whatever the f*** you want
What's a belief if you have lights
30 years of follow-up or 30 years of building in
You know this narrative that it's going to be very difficult for you to
To give it up
I think I think that you just lived inside that now and I don't want to
You know it's crazy it's not my interest
I don't I don't
I obviously don't believe
Most of that and now your name is just
Apparently in the chat room
Yeah
Now that we have a thoroughly unsatisfying interview with that piece of s***
Glad we did it and I wish we were pushed a little bit
It's always going to be different
You know I having a conversation with
Someone who is
You know pretty well-versed in marketing and propaganda has a lot of experience in it
And you know could you see the way he kept trying to butter us up the same way that
I love you guys
And you can believe what you want to ignorance is always not very
Cuz like
Time-in out is what it is
Jingle business
To a huge player in Nicaragua
Is f****** banana
A bit more detail that's been less
Which is
My guess is
That is something that he heard or read one time and a mystery novel
Hangout with Hangouts VFW Hall
Yeah exactly the first clip from Today Show
Episode
It was a boring show
Alex's just out on a whole big
Hey I've been totally right about everything responsibility
Being right about everything
I'm going to turns out to the Mandalay Bay Hotel
Timeline
That the police are suggesting now is not maybe you accurate
Spokespeople come out
Just the timeline that says that the guys shot at
Security guard
6 minutes before you open
Bonfire B not be accurate
Bright and the reason that they might be saying that is because that's the shooting
Their company is
Brialee imploding
And one of the reasons is because
Seems unsafe
And the idea that the shot a security guard in six minutes elapsed and then he starts shooting everybody only
Feeds into that collapsed spiral that the business is going
I don't agree with a narrative
Even if they have no evidence
That's the case right
PR move
Alex
Anyway here's a clip where we're going to start about
Guaranteed
But that's what they're all like in Hollywood it's not a crystal ball
Directions
Phrenology
In there
Not criminals LifeLight
15 different types
You just learn the group's
How wild hog acts have a whitetail deer racks
How Puma axe
Relax gif
Palafox at
The way you are out
I want to give Millie a children and innocent
Young beautiful women
Using the bathroom on the floor
All you want that song
Call me God
Get on the ground
Call Dad.
Weinstein
What I do on the ground you understand
Really enjoying that too much
I mean Harvey Weinstein
Falafel stop
He's like hey it is bad whenever women are more like
It's only bad whenever Hollywood
Glitches be like it's not about putting them on a pedestal
It's almost as if he believes like you just make him calm everything will be fine
That's like version of misogyny
Read them that poorly
So long as you're like
Worshipping them at the same time at all
Talking about worshiping poop and what-have-you which makes me real thrilled to learn we learn in this next clip
About to
Everyone hates Trump
Message my oldest daughter yesterday so I should thirteen-year-old sweetheart
Watch
Have you watch any of that
What do you watch
She goes
Will you
Oh no
Sure
Across the street the high schoolers
Paparazzi
Cameras
I can literally go out in Austin
Watching Angelina Jolie or Morgan Freeman
Angelina Jolie
Morgan Friedman
I'm not bragging it's probably mean
I feel self-conscious about how hard I'm bragging
Look I'm not going to get a camera and prove the kids mob me everywhere I go
Harvey Weinstein shooting on the floor and then making snuff films with ladies
You should not have twelve-year-old listening to that
Even
Critiquing in breaking down what he talked about I don't want twelve-year-old Livengood
I'd be horrified if I went to school ever
No
We got it we got to teach them young no turning power how else do we get the win them off the scat play
They have the internet now we got to we got to explain that it's bad
Someone took
Vetta it's shocking
But he can still talk to his kids at this point
Allowed to use clips of the show and the trial
It's court ordered that I go to
Psychology meetings every two weeks
With my
Daughters
Your f****** your kids like that don't do that
I don't have to go
I perfect
There's nothing wrong with me
Narcissism the horrible things that I put everyone around me through
What happened
Walking to psychology places
Psychology
Walking out
Young daughter and a son
Another day love David
Already. What is that why they're in the psychology place they like
Love that night is when he says which is which is the dead ringer
No one brings that up in public
Appreciate
I go sit down
My daughters are inside for an hour
15 year old girl comes and sits down
Researching
No option
And she looks at me
How much do Noah Troyer right now on this app
Not true
That is the Nicaragua of
I didn't talk to the fifteen-year-old girl cuz she was on a company's like that
Predator
Nah
Leave people alone in public is leaving her alone is worth
It's time to play
It's weird if you talk to someone in public if they're not alone
Then I think I think that
Definitely true
It's it's weird not true story
But it is it's not I don't think it's wrong
It's just
Strange part of your fantasy life Alex
Incredible
It's amazing
Where the future are where are we
The point is
They are the past they know they've delap
He's basically saying that he's the future while saying I don't know where the future
I'm just saying everybody else is in the past
Do you think his kids listen to the show
The show
Tell me how much they loved Infowars
Keeps going
I and I
There's even more
Give three examples
Almost
But the statistics show what I just told you
Show my children go to school so they wash it was in there
I also don't forget that like the school from Fame but for Infowars they're all dancing down the street and then the
Is it all the kids at my kids school listen to the show
He's dumb
To the first rebuttal he could come up with all my kids go there so they must watch it all at school
Jim the classes because
Not a chance
Also if you were if you were Alex Jones kids
There is no way that you would want
People at your school to know you were Alex Jones if it was bad enough being me
In high school the computer teacher at my elementary school
Roodle music Jeremiah Elementary School
Terrified.
The light in person or it's a tragedy everywhere I don't know what the reality is
Young people and they see me at the mall River
Literally the living me
Home Depot
Park Slope
Hispanic
Executive class in Spanish
Girls
We've even got business classics
Let me tell you something
None of that priority boarding
The mall slack-jawed at their senior living me
It's really pretty hard
Quite a bit about
Which is a little bit too long for me to have been an out-of-context drop but I wish it would have been
Because this is f****** this is delightful
Domination
I'm control
Lyndon Baines Johnson is it on record
What hold cabinet
He took extended
Incredibly stanchfield
Dumps
Passed the Civil Rights act as well as Medicare and
Subtle differences to holding cabinet
Forcing women to do today
Our presidents have been almost universally
Course
It takes one help towards you deserve power
It seems like
Much smarter people than me have said this
It should be a picture
Anybody who wants to
It's indicative but there's something wrong with you
I'm so
This is a little bit more about Lyndon Baines Johnson
Then we've got to get to a failed prediction that I made last night
Hollywoodism
Aldi superintendent
Eminem
Just some pathetic corporate shill and LeBron James
So I texted I think this morning and I predicted that the show would be about Eminem
And how he's a race traitor
Willie's word that Eminem rap battle
I was hoping you'd bring up Eminem cuz I wanted to talk about in a little bit
First of all I think Eminem is pretty great especially in the context of d1212 is amazing
Set out intentionally to freak out white people
Isaiah is a part of the job I love it
Descendant of that I didn't like that as much but yeah
I do respect a lot of Eminem's worth
I don't disagree
But be that as it may
That video that Eminem dropped
I got to say
Is that great
I appreciate
The context in the subject matter
I think that's great I think he's saying something that he's being like
You cannot possibly support what I'm into that's great but Manny was weak on the bars
Him pacing around it's very produced and then everyone like all these dumbasses on Twitter posting like
Oh my God that freestyle was sick and I can sell it
Crazy before
If he was doing it he was actually
Off the Dome as they say
It would have been so much better
It would have been amazing
But that was very very rehearsed and first to make it seem extemporaneous
Because I was like I don't want to
I don't want to a be a part of this and be the guy who's like
Like I don't want any part of it last night
I spell supportive
I just think it was week in terms of actual rapping
Yeah I just need that to be clear
Dumb zombies
Schmucks
They do spend money on that
It's not the young people anymore
They're like Dad
I don't want to
Go see Harrison Ford movie your life
Harrison Ford movies
I don't want to go see Hollywood mode
Oh you don't want to go see the 2 hour and 40 minutes if you want to watch
Hollywood
I've never
He's a correspondent on Infowars sometimes
Good online
Today on the show Alex Jones does it takes a lot of calls
Comparatively it's still not many calls right
His normal rigmarole
Quite a few called one of them is a trying to lure him into talking s*** on the Jews
Advising the are the globalist actually the Kazarian
Evil Georgia
But he does fine but the best call is a guy
Mix Alex remember
A long time ago said he was going to make a music show
That was brought up again yeah because we know that
Properties
Basically
Infowars or Patriot music
What way does that mean what's Infowars music
Muslims in public freak out
The last four years I work with a friend of mine it's Nashville staff writer
Here in Omaha
And that's basically the feedback that I got from him is
I would
Music sucks
If that's possible
It's just part of being a conservative
Because you don't have the
Potential
Facebook in your opportunity to be able to promote your music personally there no
Cabal on our back brother
Once were awake and we know that they're on our back
Just like a bucking bronco or bull
Turn on frosty on our back forever and hold on for dear life but they're never going to
8 Seconds
Independent new music
This guy does not have a producer
Hollywood
Just gets a little weird
And so that's why
I'm sure you're great
Music online
It just doesn't get Hollywood recognition
Play 100 people about truth
Supporting the media
50% off
Right now on a great brain pill
That's amazing
Two more clips
In manipulating his audience pretty hard
One last clip that
Delightful
It's really important
Through
I'm Alex's journey in 2015 where he comes to identify with Trump
Becomes like interlocked with his goal is
You can see in 2017
He's really desperately trying
To do that to his audience
In this clip
And remember when they say Donald Trump
Trying to get me to identify
When I see Trump
They think
Average American black wise Fantasia
That's that's
Manipulative nonsense
Fake billionaire liar who is a sociopath who's trying to get us all killed
Gun owner mass shooting
It is making those more likely
Absolutely what makes them more money than mass shootings
Yeah like that's the reality of it of course the NRA wants mass shootings
Continue happened they make a s*** ton of money when they do
Amy and the Bee
Gets even worse
One Bastion halfway left
The globalist minded Hollywood minded
The Midwest City
Oh boy
Whitening strips
Oh or what didn't things mean to him
But you got to look at it in the rivers Christian mean wife and white means Christian Middle America means white Christian normal
Trump means white Christian
We have plenty of but we have evidence that there is at least one black white person completely f***** up
What there was a clip I meant to pull and I didn't get it sucked
He there was one caller this lady called in
Straight up
She said
Hey you don't want Obama
Bring the country together why didn't they play up more that he was half white
Lady
Her idea is that
By his being biracial
That's how he could have done it
If a plate up he is both black
Michael Jackson videos
One of you white people trust me I'm halfway
There's definitely no historical precedent for mixed-race person
Horribly as someone who is otherwise
Entirely black
Exposed
From the Rogan podcast
You're really smart you're on top of it
It's f****** Christ that makes it very clear look at this last clip in here
Nichols interview f****** exhausted me
But
Alex talks about that something I don't know I don't know I spent a lot of time in my youth
Contextualizing
Support the good little church the song the truth
All these big mega-churches are swinger clubs
Just like that.
I did not know that
Everybody that goes to him knows that
Ice weather stupid
Good riddles
I like I love that everyone knows that
Or they're stupid
I didn't know if I wanted wanted to swing could just go to a megachurch I went to a megachurch
And I will tell you it was not
Swingers club
Finger-bang
If you're not finger banging
I was throwing up
I don't feel like I got what I wanted but
I also expect
I suppose with all I was really hoping for was to get him to drop that b******* for justice
Just one second of just like
I'm just him stopping and looking for a moment
But he's still good
Just f****** rolling with it if you don't believe me that's
And you don't believe me that's on you I don't need to follow up with
Anything
You know there's just so many little points
There's a
There's a whole celestial sphere made up of these
Little names and little details
Snowpiercer
I did like finding out that he actually thinks he was
The leader of a Nicaraguan drug running
That's fun
Did not want to do that no
You can't come at me
Please stop telling us to call Larry Nichols
Trying to find other people's phone numbers
Yeah
Not fun
2 / 40
Thank you all and we appreciate it very much you guys joining as long here on the
Also everybody was listening to this later
Twitter it's correct
What was the other thing that we do we are
You can download it you can subscribe you can leave a review generally Monday through Thursday
At 8 p.m. central
But this Thursday tomorrow we will not be
Cuz I'm going to Friend of the show
Congratulations by congratulations next week
I will try
Since phone number
I know I don't really want to talk to Alex either because
Example
Alex
I don't give two Hoots of a rat's balls Alex
Alex will be all this podcast by the time I'm a duck
Going to have wings
Nichols 4
Son of a b**** you won't give us a call
Howard
Higher
I got a little cold that's why I'll never hang it up
Do you know who I really think is at fault
For this whole thing right here this whole interview with Larry Nichols
Larry Nichols after I talked to him earlier in the day he gave he gave this guy a call
He was like
What do I say
This guy was like
You just lie your balls off keep talking keep on lying to him
I have one thing to say
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work