Holding
Alexandra Thurston color
We are like sit around and talk a little bit about Alex
That is some sort of
People to listen there is a
I am drinking a cappuccino beverage
Have you are drinking
Alcoholic beverage in Golden Road
Wolf pups
Call Greg
Revolution Brewery please sponsor I was just thinking how is this insulting the beer going to help us get a sponsor
Revolution
Smart I appreciate it I respect the game
What's wrong with my headphones
They probably
Anyway
We are going to be going over a lot of stuff today we're going to have a number of days
We're going to be covering today because we were off for a little bit
Issues but first-year is an out-of-context drop from Alex Jones
Oh boy
So then they must be the most profitable company in the history of the world I think I've never had a bad day I think he
Mentis in reverse
You are always plug
ABP
Cappuccino beverages airport closures
We just dropped on Monday we dropped our episode
Larry Nichols
Us had a conversation
About 40 minutes
I want to just do a little bit of a post-mortem on that now that we're back
Together here sitting down
All the peeps of been able to listen to it
And just not super Plaza
Address that in the
Gametime but
Listen
Like we could do an entire episode breaking down or why the FEMA provisional government isn't real
It's not real but that's all we do
We just save that have a good night before I feel like we covered
The FEMA provisional
I've done a bunch of looking into it all it is is just
The same continuity-of-government
Fears that Alex hatch
And most of it is based on the fact that FEMA was created by executive orders
Rover belong
President
Yeah I never actually formalized
Into an actual government organization
Until fairly recent
This is executive control and
It's not real
And it's only popping up now because
Lovely remix
Call Larry Nichols bring backup
If you Google it it's all it all goes back
Wow this is all just him
He was he was peddling s*** like this in the nineties yeah
Are we boring actually being run
Like Iwo Jima provisional government
Behind the wheel
In terms of like what we've gone through mind-bogglingly stupid 9/11 happened
The plans had to be kicked in
No but members of the government had to go to Safeway locations and stuff like that to the continuity
Bush did 9/11
It happens whenever they're disasters that's just that's just a
The piece of
It's it's
Let's all that nonsense paranoid fear and it mostly comes out of like weird
Militia type
Turns out I think Larry is
And that's it
Cadre
Either that or he's exploiting that Cadre of idiots
Involved
Dinner on contra
Does does not make
To Nicaragua
None of it but I want I don't want to dwell on it too much I want to get it out get it out of their shake it off as they say
Dust off our shoulders and what have you and move on to greener pastures
I love it when you when you do a
Play my distant shoulder from the camera
Yeah so
I want to tell everybody who's listening live
Appreciate it and that everyone is listening later
I want
Abundantly clear my job and at the end of the month I will not have a job
And I want to do this
In a much more serious way
How much more in-depth weigh
And in order to do that I need your help
And generally we put some sort of a lackadaisical plug at the end of the show
What is become a policy wonk
I want to be much more clear
If you are in any way inclined to donate to our show
If you like what we do
Please help
We need to help
I don't
Soros is going to come through
No I'm starting to think that all of Alex's imagined enemies are real
Yeah man they would love us millionaire
Totally
If it got wet
You can go to patreon.com
Knowledge fight, the button that says support the show
And we really could use your help in order to make
This real
I make this work in the way that I wanted to as a
A radio show as a much more in-depth
Investigation
I will set up a phone line so people can call in
And episodes were cthulhu's co-hosting with me
We can have weirdo collars
I better much
The sound a lot better than
Larry Nichols of dumbass
Other people
I will I will hunt down other Infowars adjacent people
And I asked them to the difficult questions
Yeah
I will do that
If I can make this my job
Cassidy I will talk to Carrie cast we got to get
Twitter
Is your dad still alive so I can get on one knee and ask
Asking for permission to marry his daughter
She can't really be that
Connecticut
Anyway that's more than I wanted to be but please if you would like to help we could
View the help in order to
To survive
If I get a job
It's going to cut in today
It's weird it's weird
You're not going to be a mess or job where I can't listen to Alex Jones
As well and I got a new room
Stand up
3 times as much as I was before
If you could avoid the gig economy and axle
Just do something like
How do you how do we avoid calling this valuable cuz I don't I will I will I will validate
I feel like it is broken out in the
And my cat
Some good
I'm doing I'm getting killed a lot
Is the winner of all across the board
You don't want to call this import
I'm going to make the argument that what we're doing is important
Play clips
Demonstrative
Very difficult problem
That we have a thread on that I don't think most people are paying
This first clip comes from Sunday
September at October 8th
And I heard of this clip
And I forgot
And I'm glad I did
Because it comes in much more relevant now
This is from a conversation
With Rodger Stone
On the Sunday show
It's clear that Alex is drunk
Dear David
Body Rogers somebody somebody
Do you not see the trailer
When we simply try to express
Dinner with our fellow revolutionaries
The Weeknd
Americana dauntless
So
That's a drunk man
There's a couple things
Enough
No but it is a very specific boat from Star Trek Voyager or a spaceship
Star Trek Voyager
That was designed to look like a voyager ship
People who came aboard what looks like a human ship
It's also
It's also a generic name for like a pleasure but that's not the important point
Is Rodger stone is straight-up saying In that clip
South to meet up with
The Arkham Patriot
Our fellow revolutionary Milo
Now why this interview happened
Long after that BuzzFeed article came out
Wherein we learn
Fitone of Milo's primary objectives
Was to whitewash and make more palatable
White supremacist
And neo-nazis
Talking point
Into mainstream discourse
We found out that one of his email passwords with kristallnacht
Another one was night of the Long Knives
There is undeniable that you have leaning towards
Leaning towards neo-Nazi
Absolutely alright alright means.
We're done we're done with alt-lite
The fact that all of this has come out and Rodger stone is still calling him a fellow revolutionaries
And they're working together
Meme
He doesn't give a s***
Come on
What is what is Rodger Stone but Milo as you know 40 years later
What time was the
Do you work with Nixon
You clearly had
What
The argument that I'm trying
To make that I'm trying to come to here is that
We have a group of dudes
Who are clearly working on a operation
They're working on an operation
That is
White supremacist
Neo-Nazi in nature
Is it like
Pride of lions
Is that what we're going to call the Nazis
Yeah yeah
But here's the here's the other clip that is from the October
16th show
Home
Why they're doing
And it's the way they present it
And it's not
Not good
Politician
So they present this as a global populist uprising
That's happening
When in reality is not what happen
That is not what's happening in the world
They are on
Besides it's fighting against
Vun
That would be
If you said those things 50 years ago they be taking their proper
I mean
There is a global populist Uprising it's just being
Co-opted by the people that they are supposed to be uprising
Like if true or using
But like all they're really doing is using the Nazi white supremacy ideology
As a way to shoehorn in people towards
Giving billionaires
Like all is all
Berkeley manipulate
Milo is owned by the Mercer
Indebted to all of these billionaires
People's Banner
About how the body politic
People who've been bought by the same billionaires
Like it's a controlled opposition because it's not even that it's just
Mind control
And now take another step back
So we have
Rodger stone is clearly still in League with Milo still in League with
This
World it's only
Daily Stormer
Only this far away from outright
5 knots
Then we have Larry nickel
Who is so gracious enough to have a long conversation
She brought up
Troopergate
Yeah in the conversation that we had and if you think about troopergate
What was going on was Larry was convincing these
Troopers
And paying them
To tell fake stories
About let's say Vince Foster s***
All sorts of salacious
Just up against
The clintons yeah you know who was funding
It came out that it was a guy named Peter W Smith
Who are the Chicago breaker killed himself
Last year at the age of 81
One week after talking to the Wall Street Journal about how he was working with Russian hackers
To try and find Hillary Clinton's emails
On the request of Mike Flynn I don't know
This f****** stuff
It's such a mess
Such a mess
I weld
Do you know what's crazy
People are so like
I don't I don't want to get
Log into like a
Like this is a conspiracy me all this stuff
TV named after
Look at all these other
Public
Look it's very clear what they're doing
The only question is always
Who is conspiring with who
With who
Do they even know what it is
Is that there actually were
To have some awareness
Acting well within the Mercers
You f****** stupid not
To know that
Of course probably has the idea that there bankroll
Yeah as opposed to
Utilizing him as a propaganda tool to get their gate right your ego probably doesn't let you take Xanax
Exactly
So all of these guys are
Inspiring imagine
Or at least
I don't know convincing themselves that it's towards their own games and they have no idea that they are not even playing
Right like that's what it seems like
So
I agree
The point
That that folds into
Is that all of this is going on
And we have a thread on all these f****** a******
The picture starts to come into focus a little bit
And I think the easiest attackable point and the easiest exposable point
We could do it very easily
Is Alex Jones the assholes
These number one Castle keep his mouth shut
Blazing
Over and over again if people would just pay attention
Right so now here's the other part of my thing
If Alex Jones were to go down
If you were to disappear
I'm a hundred percent convinced
It would leave a massive hole
And here's how I know that
Okay
David Knight is boring as s***
Agree
He gave him 3 hours
On his Network
Wonderful
The other person
When he gave three hours on his Network
Is Owen Shroyer
Hilarious
The the War Room
After Alex Jones Show
I'm still going to call that's fine
On the 20 on the 16th
On October 16th
Alex leave the show early
And Owen Shroyer takes over
And I have some
Clips
Demonstrate
Shroyer
Can't hang
He can't do it
We if we're able to
Like expose Alex
I know we're capable of
What are you left with
Boring-ass David Knight
He's over getting inflamed the neo-nazis to action
Absolutely not
Specifically
From the 60s
Owen Shroyer
Justin. Doing the job
Here in this first clip we used to be
One of Alex Jones has big tricks
Is he gets people really excited screaming out to break
Owen Shroyer can't do it right
Daniel de Jesus
During a violent crime in connection with the death of an eighteen-year-old Diana Martinez Gonzalez
Murder victim that he probably would have
And yes
This individual was protected from deportation because of the DACA program
Man is that bad that's not like I get it
I don't know if the sound mixing was bad or whatever
You can't do it he doesn't have that like Alex will be going every second until the cutoff
They just can't you can't do it
There's a murderer
Terrible zen12 scream about and complain about the
PC culture run amok
How can I watch Warrior can't do that either listen to how he f**** this up
This is from the college fix
Halloween universities Nationwide tell students not
Tell students What Not to Wear
So Alex has been telling you about this extreme now
We are a culture
Not a costume
Who are these people
Who are these people that are so indoctrinated into identity politics
They can't even
Enjoy Halloween
It's insensitive it's insane
You can't wear on Halloween
Blackface
Identity politics
They don't even love algae
Adreno over Gavin McInnes
Bushwacker
I get it you're not supposed to say the party
I'm a culture not a costume
Because that makes too much
Does article you're not supposed to save a thing
That most people thinking we are
Definitely not supposed to do this
Because of cultural appropriation
Unacceptable costumes
Native American headdress
Dressing up as Mexican by wearing a sombrero
Dressing as a geisha or any form of blackface
I don't know about blackface
A Native Americans Indians and Mexicans
I remember
And it was
Offended
Right
I imagine
I don't know what kind of people Owen Shroyer hangs around
I'm guessing none of them are first
I'm going to guess not I'm going to guess
White was telling this story
What else would be doing it as opposed to putting himself in the hopper
I'm the guy who dress up like bear claw
And they said you know I don't even understand why it is that people aren't allowed
All the sudden there are imaginary people on his
Another
Hippie Halloween story all over again even when he was trying to be like
Ridiculing and his tone of voice when he's reading the list right he can't pull it off so just like you can't dress like a native
American you can't just like he looks like
Yeah
Him on how to be a better shity propagandist
Well I'm just saying
The other thing too is like if you're going to be like I have a contest
Costco hours
Q-tip everyone called me back
Tim McGraw
Call
Casablanca line
New new pitch
No instead
We get hired by Infowars goddamn train his
To get into shape seriously Alex Jones
People better than this is not a bad plan
Infowars
You don't make sense what you do but apparently work
Last clip of Owen Shroyer officially free-agent mercenaries will train any
Propaganda
You could ever have
This is him
He's trying to talk about
The situation with Colin Kaepernick
But it's terrible
Colin Kaepernick support is dwindling
NFL ratings are dwindling
NFL attendance is dwindling
And it all started
Yeah okay you can say was yes please
But
Become the story
You're kneeling during the national anthem that's never going to win
Alex
Would never
Optics become of the story
Because you know what that means
We lie
Know what the real story is
Parents
In order to make racist
Angry
Clearly he's just
He's just telling the truth man
He has no idea that he's giving up
About police brutality
We making our point for us
To that was
Was like
I know you're right
He started all this and now he doesn't have a job
So
What is collusion
Obviously it seems like it's indicative
To you just clearly made the point that if yes it was about cops killing black
People you know it damn well
Buttocks
Kaepernick advice
We're charges for Alex Jones
Kaepernick advice on how to do it right like Colin call the baby
The right light bright
Become the story is kind of like
Kind of
Anyway
Which means we can lie about whatever it is you're looking
I think we've made our point
There's no way
There's no one competent to take over
What's that
KIPP can't hang
There's no adults there other than him come out from behind the camera and host
Who's going to do it seems as though Alex is the only one who like they all are probably believe
Libras like
What
Is that they're all actual belief
No
No no
You don't think so f****** think someone has said anything
This is why I'm going to go the opposite direction
Exact
Because he thinks
This is a new show
I don't think so I think he thinks
Alex Jones is the only one
The program understand
Listen to his f****** voice
How
Seldom people stick around
Of all the people
They're not around
In terms of
Ashley Beckford
She's gone
Never meet your
Jakari Jackson
The only people who stuck around to Rob do David night Owen Shroyer hasn't even been there that long right
Videos
Mimi's
Maybe Alex's
The real problem
Maybe it's hiring practice
I don't think that this is much
To a lot of people this or 2gig whether it's news or not
Let's get to let's get the bulk of
Today
We're going to be Friday
Friday the 13th
Watch over episode
Big eyes
Let me say this
There's a lot of people have a lot of different favorite Alex
Like what's your favorite
What's your favorite version of Alice
Like what the mood
But he gets into is your favor
Probably the least an Oculus of all which is the
Fake angry
Okay so the very obvious screaming
That is the least harmful baby cuz
At least most of his products
Can actually do anything unless
Use them beyond all to take them everyday
Alex from the chat room
Of course
A favorite of everyone getting a dead Alex
Survive from my friend Brian
You got but I'm right there with you
I like Alex
Quite a bit
Like there is a version of Alex that is kind of rare
That is Alex surprises himself on air
Advanced something happens that like
He punches himself
Right into another punch that comes from another Direction
Evan Hughes lost without a map on air
It has to fill time
And he is like
Dave
And that always leads to esoterica
That might be your right whenever he just randomly starts getting existential
The Hollies
You got the right Alex riddle teller Alex is my favorite allies
Are all day February
Alex
Get
Stupid esoteric
Okay but there's a narrative to why it happens
That I think is a
Really interesting path
Okay in this first clip
To the beginning of the episode he's not super interest back Tavor super
He's reserved
Then
He accidentally talks about wine
And he accidentally
Brings this up
Show I've been on a lot of TV shows
Comedy shows
I can't imagine that
Hollywood was so one-dimensional
That must mean you're a liberal
Until they find out your real political views it's just crazier
And instill they like you because you're criticizing Bush they don't don't like bush
That was
20 years ago
15 years ago
67 years
So he's
Debbie's 44 now
To that point and I'll keep that in mind
I don't think anyone's ready
Here but at the same time
I'm not judging him
I'm going to enter this the end of this clip
With a lot of empathy in my heart and
Five Northern California Love Central areas Lubbock
Los Angeles
If Satan lives on the planet that's where you live
The energy
Going into meetings with Hollywood producers
People that ball want to put your film outer make a film with you these are big big things
Not as big as Weinstein is he's just ubiquitous that name but
Grocery wise as big
Lawyers for some of the top people
The owners of
Capital actors
Hollywood
Itzy popularity for other people
Okay I play football
And I never took it as if it was done that
Homosexual way
It was done as domination
What the hell's going on
If you just said
Binoculars
What I wanted and they would be completely scared
So
Okay
He goes on a bit about this
Back into bravado
He just revealed that
We assaulted yeah
And he gets
Exactly what that is
It's not
Yeah
Where I'm sitting
It's in that in that situation
That is not something that I would ever come down on him
M4
But I do not think you meant to bring this out on the air
Necessarily
I don't think he realizes how big
Like how
You know that's
That's better
Something to bring out into the public Alex
You never give me you've joined Terry Crews
Yeah
In the funeral hey it happens to us well kind of
That blindsided
But the other thing is
He can't handle the fact that I think that there's a little bit of vulnerability that
Comes out in that moment
That was that was honest
And he
He was telling the truth
Eddie talked about it a whole bunch more and I didn't believe in anymore cuz it's not like
Into more details you disorder reiterate
Stop
He's ended up having like a little bit of like he gets in a weird mood and he goes to a special report
She throws it to a special report from Mark Dice
I don't I don't know
Okay we're getting to why I played that song before the show
This is bananas
Suggested he knows
Jessica Mendoza
Exactly what sexual assault really is
It's really about
Yes and
Or I guess he has
To divorce that part
He's tried
To kill that part of
Himself so much that he's gone so far the APA
Opposite direction
Exactly
Feel bad about us like covering this and I still hate him
But at the same time this is why
The recipient of being broke
So he goes with Special Report
Been up to
Add from Mark Dice
Yeah
Left the entire thing in but here is Mark.
Very iffy take
Auntie
Situation
In Hollywood
Who face homosexual
So there is an issue
It's not
It's not great to be like it's so much harder for men
It's not great
It isn't lying with Infowars sort of brand certainly but
No
I mean
There's so much
In those very few sentences
There's human
History and those three
Is right there
Absolutely
Of course there is
That fear of
It's at the worst possible thing that could
Rights of Man being sexually assault
Because how much worse is it that the man who's supposed
To be dominant rape is
Dominate
How much does a play into Alex's
Kind of
Is it does get better
Idea of like
Abusers have been abused
Abusers because of that abuse
You
You know there's no like short psychological
Through-line 2nd of
Amount of like
Alex was
Dominated and he never wants to feel like that at
And so you does that to everybody that he can't use victimizer is everywhere.
Someone who wants to kill all of us
Everybody's trying to
I don't like 50 describing it
But when you
When you start to see that abusers have been abused
Through-line
Hit through so many different areas
Brave
Who is
Like that
Like he has no idea what
No use in trying to get click
What it is
He's accidentally revealing about
Himself
Infowars in everybody that they're talking
Yeah yeah yeah
Because even worse has the tacit admission
But this is a horrifying thing that can happen
Minimizing maximizing
Sentiment
Still discussing that this is the thing right
It's not
This is like you know I don't
But I don't think it's
Productive for us not to treat Alex Jones like a human you know like I don't think that necessarily like I don't think
I don't I don't think
To look at
Someone that you even to someone you hate
And take as a huge problem in the world
To look at them outside of the context
Like I have things happened you live your life
Are you baby
Are are in town
Killer books
And you see
Very similar
Types of story
Emerge over and over and over
Like there's this book called The Road out of hell
Where it's like
Was a true
Monster this is
The psychopath who had murdered
People who committed all of these horrible Acts
But
If you go back to
To before
Here. All that's
His childhood
There's no way that you
You can't feel some empathy
For that child
While at the same time thinking that that adult
Should be murdered in the street
You know
Skip out
Yes please on this right now
What sets off Alex into the strangest mood possible on this Friday the 13th
He spends
Talking about
Trump
And how he knows about how Trump dates
In this next clip which is just
He's delivered
Between
Not just from Rodger Stone and people become a lot of other folks and
Electronic
Quartz women
I won't jump in bed with anybody and he's
That's what no one knows
When it comes to relationships everything
Woman
That woman
Yes money
Until they're not
Donald Trump
Boss and the guys talking about women and goes yeah it's incredible
Here is the section where you misinterpret
Billy bush
Something weird
I want to climbing up on you on you
And then it's a ritual
The wrestler
Alex their hips
Kissing this isn't
Whippoorwills have their songs in
Creatures mate
Different whale species have their stuff it's not that
A woman jumps on you
Throwing your panties at you
What do you think that means it means we want to make with you
Years ago
Most men are hypocrites if you
Haven't been in a locker room
And made comments about your girlfriend or wife and they're not bad ones
Call about my wife she's not street legal
10000 horsepower car
If you want
Horsepower what are you doing with that out here on the street
Complement
Okay
The sixties in a
Room
Spiraling
Should drop of that locker room
Maybe not as 12 years ago
Let me talk about how my wife is too much
Horsepower
Ownership
A little
Like is like
Give you gas and all this stuff and then the moment you push back here
He's gone right
Like it.
My wife isn't street legal like a car you owe
Yeah there's something I don't says that most men are hypocrites
Sure I agree with that
I don't agree with anything else
Are corrected not street legal
If true
Interstitial thing we had here
We had this weird Revelation about
Meeting with Executives at
The top
That was the punch that Alex
Himself that knocked him in this direction
Adhere
Is the punch that I think
Comes to him from the other direction
He wasn't expecting
Trump had a press conference
On
Yes and I think Alex thought it was going to
To talk tough about North Korea
Not have allowed that I've been building
This is Vanessa
Now Ron Paul thinks I'm a neocon cuz I support Trump
This is important
He starts just saying all
About how evil ouranos
And Alex has this moment
What is something going to war
So control The Narrative of how this is going to go he is not in real time
Making a justification
Absolute until Alex is like oh s***
I think we have in that moment that you hear the
Like I sound like
When he goes to break
I'm guessing
I was like
The propaganda
Neocon
Is that what's going on you wants to attack around clearly
What is going on
Follow the rules according to the investigators
It's so Alex
Realizes that he has only a couple options on the table
And that is
Pretend it didn't happen
You got to kill another hour-and-a-half of the ship
He can't have Owen Shroyer feelings we see what he does
So
Trump is definitely lying about the Iran agreement clearly they've been following the rules
Manipulate
In this
We get to where Alex
Just trying to get
Any kind of a toe-hold
And it's not really working out
It starts with him sort of making peace with war
That's not great
That's the compromising of a lot of the things he stands for
This is 7 minutes long you can tell me whenever you want me to pause it
It's a miracle we been here this long
What
Long Pond
Latta Long Pond
I just look at
I know what trumps doing
Where we been maneuvered by the whole Hollywood globalist
Hollywood stars
Token economy and then
Made themselves Richard and God basically but then cut off the economy to make people poor
The terms of their surrender so they can cut Christians
And people that are so good
Weird stuff
Hollywood into a bathroom with him
Long as you belong. But hey
Follow this societal comportment
Destroy your life
This is about Iran
Biggest weakness
As decent Christian people we have a moral compass we have
Conscience
Take care of your children and not lying
You lie all the time
Replaced it
Where do you got to teach 5 year olds
What
That's your new religion
Extremes of Christianity and cults
Using the Christian faith to control people
Churches in Mumbai
And follow it and get it all this self-loathing and
All this guilt
Okay
You can pause it right
Luckily we have a lot of long pauses in order to I'm worried
I think I agree with 80% of what he saying right now
And that concerns me
You might be because I understand exactly how I'm
Feeling about that speaking so vaguely is like
He's at he's at that
Like
Is that a turning point really
There's that moment where you can see him crescendoing up till like
This could be and then come here and then they teach your kids and
And then it gets right back up there and he's like all the banks are doing
Purple Penguin chair
Liberal Alex who would scream about
That's never going to happen
Liberal
It was never going to happen
Is it Direction instead holyshit
Before you
Actually
TripAdvisor
That's awesome
And those of us that have consciences
Become the slaves of people that don't
Ibanez riding line you're describing you
I love God because
I know God is real
Churches
Spirit
That's concerning
Christ why you hang around these prostitutes
Because they don't claim they're good
Little planet already got it all figured out
And do around it
Correct people on Shake people down and you'll have the tax collector do it
Tax collector actually goes out does
I'm lost
You were going somewhere you're going over there like
Text collectors back then actually go around I like what what are you talkin about
I don't know but hold on Jesus wasn't about like that
Robert's Rules of Order on that front but what about
Realize we let Congress do that Congress did that
Cristiano Ronaldo
Turn around and in all honesty to blame the TSA people
Stopping hypocrite I grew up
I let Congress do you like
I'm not going to sit there
Working TSA
He's going to
I'm not a hypocrite I grew up I don't blame the TSA but it is a terrible organization we should get rid of it
Okay so here's his other suggestion
The public
NFL watching wannabe tough guys that run their mouths are
Hawaii as fast as they could
Okay
There's different I'm not running
I'm scared I'm scared of running
My leg hurts
Find feel good.
Ankle
That's why they're so much as they know they can't scare us
I'm already sure separation from God
I've already
That energy
I've already dialed into an it's so good
Don Ashley ask Alex
Rangoli introspective
Good or bad
There's there's a glimmer of Soul that's left like that's why in his list of like
What
Includes
Not lying
Yeah
Simon Says
Is like
I'm so good you like
You're doing the opposite of both of those things
Absolutely
Let's finish this.
Cuz he's going to take this all the way to a break
I should worry about myself my family
It's not some
Or some negligence
Parricide
Also
I just want to be clear
You're not ready for it
Not ready for that you're not ready for the going to break music
Divorce match
If he goes into a sales pitch from here is my friend
But the going to break music
Family and I used
Filters for that air filters
The shadows and Echoes of that
But I'm all and everything
My family might need my treasure my blood I'm ready it's all in
Making that decision
Spiritual level
Is like coming out of Egypt's like coming out of that one
Decide
To be all in
Is a minute you start level
And then you start knowing
You don't want to commit suicide you don't want to die but you're not afraid anymore and
Or at least
He at least has had some dark moments
Before Trump
Oh yeah
Maybe he works out like so stagnant
And nice maybe that's what drove him after all
Maybe was being a lot but you also was it like
Just like a depression
Maybe Trump never was bulworth movie Alex was bulworth
Oh boy
Pennywise
What a tangled web
Will Shakespeare
Your family
Wait for the f****** music
Chicken
But you want to be with God
Montana matters in this universe
You get buried six feet under your car
God
Free will
No
God
I'll be there if you don't want to be
Friends
What separates
Is a choice
People that are so insecure
Sphere
Get into the spirit
Deodorant easier
Is it rolled over to
Simcom
I have to I have to pull it I have to pull it from the 90s
Liquid
A sad
Support the show is not what I was expecting
Elizabeth Police throw to break
Sphere get into this spirit
On my flash
Choke on my flush
Infowars.com
What are you talkin about where the wolf cubs her baby
Toca by fly
No idea
Okay
Chat room
Get on this I want all of Alexandra
Speeches
To be sent to different Chemical Brothers
You're in no shape to be on air
Forever
You have uncovered
That's Alex Jones the Hillary for prison
T-shirt from a bumper
Sticker
Which album
From The Chemical Brothers
I'm not sure I don't think it's going to be a little more mellow
Music videos behind them that would be amazing
I'm Massachusetts
Chucky 1776
British guy came up to him and said that
And Alex wasn't like
Where the f*** are you from
The guy up
He was like the former top
Autonomous
The British government
Multiple prime ministers
So he's
Is bigger drums and I was the point lies inside
No there's no need for that
To do it
So you drunk than him
He's a bigger drunk than I was the point was that
It's just
50 cool people man
That's a person everything
Spirit
So-so
Stealing what he said
Do you not then prove that you are one of those people without a spirit
You don't want to kill yourself
Together dirt bike
You know I was hanging out with this British guy is a drunk what a good guy but
You still in there
When the wolf fenrir comes to e2000 Jesus
Coming out of a commercial I was like oh no no no
No
Hollywood and all these people
If you want to know why they fear the dog
Social President Trump
What we're doing
Don't know how to defeat them
What is it
That's why
By what other people think about you
So real quick
Hold on to those thoughts
About genuine being genuine
And then having an inner compass
Those sorts of things
Well in your mind
Because they're going to come back
Show
Google and Facebook and Twitter
Really curtailing ice really walking us really
Putting the screws everything I mean
Newswars.com and prisonplanet.com it on right to horse.com it's why we
Watch radio syndication in TV syndication in Wyoming
Try all the things we've done had some success because of you
You are
The oxygen
Listeners
Do you know that
Alex Jones is up here
Alex Jones
No
You're at your man
I'm with you right now you're with me
We don't like the files we don't like
Handicap kids
Call Blacksburg
Fat people
Controls we don't become down
Okay
Jack come out
Who You Are
Aunt
You already got so much strength
Frisbee.
You're smart
Problem
And gosh darn it do you have that strength
Don't like it
If you don't have the office
Even if you aren't in the power structure
You're talking to yourself might call your skinny as of your hearts pointed towards God
You have the birthright
Enemy
Everfield
Tammy falling in the enemy says if I could just have control
Whenever you had discernment
You're built to be a
Receiver
Shub Creator God sister
You're a spark from God you are not God
You are the space time continuum
Of the progeneration
Incomplete
God
But the attempt
That would come out
The mouth of the river is the river is a lie
Like a tree that grew by the side of the river
Gold fell over into the river
Those that choose to be cut off from God achieved Oblivion
I don't know what that has to do with the river
I've kept in the last 10 seconds of Silence
That is such a god
That's our biggest number 14 why none of those fuckfaces
Is could ever
Cover for Alex
Because Daddy
Your Evangelical pastor
That has all of that
Cadence that Rhythm is a point where if you're not paying attention
Sounds really comforted if you're not paying enough attention it sounds like you miss
Something stupid s*** that you're like
I guess he knows what he's talking about the parable
It's not a river in Utah
Calboy
I've been to so many churches
That have that guy
Until you actually listen and then you're like oh no this is all dumb and ran into a crazy
You did the thing and then
Freddy jumps into clip from the day before show about
Hello is Project Veritas a town
That's how he kicks out of this downward spiral
The show is whatever it is
Takes over the fourth hour but I wanted to go on with that
We had a conversation
If he says
Let the wolf die choking on my flash
I'm not going to
Big fan of that thing I like
If I were Buckley
I would have a button
If someone would tackle
We talked about that
Buckley has the balls
To come up to Alex and be like hey
Maybe not so much with the wolf
Journey through Alex Jones
Wherein he makes an accidental confession
Something that we all
Should feel sympathetic
About
Evan
Learn
The guy you've been
Stumping for is probably more militaristic than he's been pretending
Is an insect
Psychopath who doesn't believe anything
Despite the fact that he is an intake
Psychopaths actually does believe things in
He's coming up against the idea
Like if we if we think about it like
Steve pieczenik is just falling out of Grey
Right he also lost Robert David Steele as a as a source for something within the last couple
Losing a lot of these.
Answered right after that
He's finally coming to grips
What's with the Lost
Could be
In the context of all the other tragedy plus time equals that
Burnout
So there's probably a
A bit of like Alex
I mean if he's it's never going to become going to get more than they
I don't think but he's struggling
Hey Miss episode Italy
Friday the 13th full moon
He's struggling super hard with the dissolution of
It's probably cathartic
For him to just ramble and say nonsense on air
You can never really be on television Alex
That
You wonder why people use
If he was on Taylor
Someone would say
I have that book
Cuz then Infowars would just be Alex Jones
Whoever Buckley said that I'm not against it
Libertarian
I'm into it
Oh my God
Lyrics to fix your f****** show and get you on Spike button
All that would do that with Jenna gray tarp
With millennials
We would get you so many viewers
So I told you to keep track of genuineness
I'm having a memorial Center
These ideas videos about your
Your Center
One is from the Sunday
October 8th
Show
Zahir is Alex Jones Rodger Stone having a little conversation about Rex Tillerson
This is right around the time that Rex Tillerson
Inside the Trump is a f****** moron
Cuz he is so so
You're saying from your Intel
Also Alex
This is drunk on this
Before the storm
That that that we are getting ready to hit North Korea
That's my very best Intelligence coming out of both my another.
That's why I think the president was
Ruskin putting down
Rex Tillerson
He's talking about coming exit
Because I think he's going by December
He wasn't a white
You promise exactly
Not enough Rodger Stone
Used later this day going to meet
With the my love
Download the mainstream media
Directions
Open
He is really bad about the present he said a lot but other telling Rex Tillerson resign shouldn't before that
Well you know what the problem is it when the president exercise Authority
Do a lack of stability
What is very cool
So okay so
The mainstream media is going to use it
To show a lack of
Stability in a very tumultuous
Court
They will use it as evidence
The thing that is
Alex
You realize Rodger stone is lying to your face
Right now means what it means with Rodger
Let's flash forward to the 16th a little
About Trump
What was the system of appeasement
North Korea
Still didn't have that
He's insane
Play bad cop
Turn on inside the Trump
So
Estimating that
Like what's the point
Every profile on Tillerson
Fascinates me
Because
It's always like
He didn't want the job
Doesn't want the job
But now
Literally the only reason that he is still Secretary of State
Is because he's worried
If it's not
Trump will nuke
The world
That's fascinating
Hilarious imagine there's some truth to that narrative but at the same time it's probably not
Probably subtilty trying to save face
Tillerson is a PR for tillers
Is a
Horrific monster who shoot
Immediately
But
I do think that he is he's the Exxon executive
Who has
Turn his
Big Fortune into an insanely big Fortune
Fair
Coming to
He has to know that
He doesn't need this s***
He doesn't need this
No problem.
And now
He's not getting what he wanted out of it
This is a pain
Compton
In your mouth situation
Is ever good no ever
So the only reason he's there is because he's worried that if he's not
Trouble Burger everyone that's all good that's hilarious that's all good
Is the difference between those 8 days
The first one
Kinder's not there not coordinated
Good cop
There's their strategies going on simultaneously
It's just good it's just
Rogers moved me out
Updated my programming
You threatened to me about something on Friday
Come back on Monday and do better
It's just so stupid I don't think that
I don't know
It's too much speculation
I do know that it
Like something I do happen to make him
Completely change his narrative about what's going on with Taylor so
Driving
Different mood swings
Probably
I think that's more likely than Rodger when he's drunk
I think Stone just
Loves watching chaos
Probably
Stone is loving it whenever he's like stones just smiling at the back of his head like
Look at this monkey I can make that amazingly powerful feelings
Alex Harris I want to feel that way
The bigwigs popcorner propaganda show
You got it succeed make a star out of rhabdo
Can't do that
Make a star out of man
Alex even trying for a decade
So anyway
Go to our website
Make a star out of yourself
Free websites call David stripe.com
Ross on Twitter
I'm no longer on Twitter
Done
I'm barely there except for on our account
Absolutely you can follow us on iTunes look up Lucas up in the review section
I like you
You guys
Mention George Soros at any opportunity
Pittsburgh marketing gets to him
That be hilarious do that that knowledge fight.com is button to sport
Not belabor it
Every Monday through Thursday I believe you will not be here tomorrow
But you'll be back eventually
8 p.m. central
How to break down all this b*******
Jordan
Love you then
Love you too
That was great
Even old guy
You worked into the B Sowell
Let me tell you about this guy okay
Is there a bit
This f****** guy
You do what you do that one thing I'd like to say about this guy
Flash
Alexandra Thurston color