Controlling
Alexandra Thurston color
Do you know what you're not wrong
For today
Is all hands on deck we got some
Serious business
Before the show
Almost nothing
I did from a listener apologize
We're almost a year into this
You don't know almost nothing about Alex Jones
And that's an unfair way for us to open the shows kind of b*******
Highly overestimated my ability to remember anything that you tell me okay baby
And you have forgotten a lot of things maybe that's a more accurate way for us to start show
I think I really just talk
Unfair
Rude I don't appreciate it
On Monday we put out an episode
I hate it it's frustrating it's the conversationally difficult I do I had to do
The 2015 investigation into
Team Trump
We know pretty much for a fact that he joined up because
Rodger stone is lying to him
On a massive scale Russia
It was where we left off
Mother
I was going to heavily into this episode actually
Realize I did something
I thought about it but I realized
Capricious
In ending the investigation or in declaring case closed
Absolutely
And one thing triggered that
In my mind
Something that happened the other day
On Alex's show
Episode wow we were alone I was alone you weren't on the show
For that
There was a something I'm sorry I had to go grab the clips
Cuz I forgot to load it up
This triggered something in my brain
Realize
We need to double back
You know sitting and thinking and having
Something triggering your brain
That's how God,
Buddhism
To really crack
No time until God
, rather than Hitler because that would solve the real
Oh sure yeah
Great great I don't stand behind that but I do want to play this clip for you because I'm not sure
Who's even listen to the episode
Question of it
Prove it I don't remember it goddamn well good cuz this is going to be
Fresh for you and maybe repetition
For people who let the
But it's still I will set the stage for we're going to be going on
Call Brenda Georgia
And talk to Paul
Thanks for calling around here worldwide
That came on yesterday on
David Knight show
Las Vegas
Information campaign is he still working for the CIA
Anybody disagrees with Alex
That person is now a federal agent
Jump in bed with psych Warfare people
Don't do it
So I heard that
Blue my mind
Because
First of all that was news to me that's doesn't believe the Las Vegas shooting happen
It's crazy
But he does believe it happened
No Doubt
Tap so I heard that clip
I was like I need to think about
Pieczenik a little
I need to explore
Him
Like Buddha
She was
In the game
At the end of 25
Okay
Did that I never listen to David Knight show
What am I go back and listen
Actually saved Las Vegas
Here are a couple clips
From the October 4th 2017
Where Steve pieczenik comes on
And says with Las Vegas attack did not happen
Go straight to the shooting in Vegas
Number one why I
Can't get on the internet the reason is very simple I'm being hacked
The reason why you're hearing me now it's another person bumps
But why back 911
Anything you said David
The same thing I said within 24 hours of 9/11
My CIA operatives admitted that they did it I had the names of the people in
If you ever f****** names it's a continuation of 9/11
He says he has the names of all these people then I implore you sir
Let's get let's get on with it
Let's get on with it because we need
I believe that the entire world security is contingent on you producing these f****** names
Steve
Painting
Troodon
Giuliani
The Mossad operatives blew up the building and
And County and as well as cooling down
What's happening now
Anyways Sandy Hook false flag
San Bernardino false flag
Yesterday in
Complete
Set up as we had in Sandy Hook
Narrative is so predictable that no one was killed there was no shooting
In fact what happened in the giveaway what's this was the greatest
Chilling and all kind of America that's distinctive Trump
He has to have the most in the bed
Parties that Trump Bell Angeles
Co-opted by the Department of Health
CIA and FBI what we need to do an Americanized Amman
Indictment of President indictment of officials
I don't know if it'll happen but this is enough
Reasons to start a revolution
That's crazy
He is
The most
Right ever for the
Bronx reason in the history of the world
F****** it starts with
What Reagan in the Iran-Contra
Scenario president since then
Should have been put in
But f***
Christ
Is he right
Dally around with the idea that he's right because the part that he's wrong about more important
Put
The part of me that was
Find a figure out a way
There is not
Stupid it seems
Prohibitive
In terms of difficulty there's no doubt but it is fast
Fascinating his line on it is
Trump has gone South
He started doing.
Revolution against Trump
Because he
Fake the Las Vegas shooting
In order to have the largest
Fakes
At what point because that is the craziest I've ever heard like
Keep in my head sort of the power ranking of my favorite crazy on Alex's show
I know that photo up top where we're going to meet number to honor next episode
I went to go do a deep dive into this next crazy but
No he is just
Until we get through all this
Do you think
I like it deliberately like
Yes okay
I think this is like Warfare
Kirk Franklin
I also think he's a little bit crazy
There's no doubt about that
Yeah
You heard him
Still in 2017
Sandy Hook was fake
And Alex
By virtue of
He's allowing this to be broadcast
Operator
0 + 4
Okay
All right and I wanted
Get this out up front
That way the rest of the episode can prove me wrong but I had a good time
I think
That when Steve pieczenik live through a hurricane
Okay
Realize climate changes
And when
It broke his
Because he spent all of his time denying and now for the first time he's
He's confronted with reality
And his entire worldview breaks down so there's two ways to go
You can either change everything you think
Double down on your conspiracy
A continuation of your theory but if I leave
Climate change is real
You've got to do his part
To get Trump out of there so someone responsible with knows that the only place he
He has influence with be able to effect by making an
Even more insane Theory all right for them to get on board with and that is okay
Unfortunately it backfires cuz it says he's still working for the CIA
Here's Steve talking more about how it was
Still alive from goodnight
There was no death
No killings no shooter
Absolutely nothing
Nothing
It was basically a total
A false flag it was a total Sandy Hook
I do not like the operation things
The expression it was a total Sandy Hook
That's grim
World now that is so beyond insane that I can't help but laugh
Lunatic
Blake Anderson
Look if I did that on stage is a bit
The most ridiculous thing that you can possibly say
Press
He said okay
David Knight the last clip
Yeah I want to be clear because I'm I'm saying goodnight
Steve pieczenik say the Sandy Hook didn't happen as evidence
Also doesn't believe Sandy Hook happen
I mean look they intimidated Alex Jones and thinking that people really died in Sandy Hook
Explain how that happened
Yeah I understand imitate it
I wouldn't disagree with you on
Even more insane
Look
If you believe
Both were fake
Certainly
Thursday
Series
Because then at least his sort of mental illness schizophrenic
Break that he's having
Have clearly delineated line
Everything is fake
Because he's been so I don't think we can use this one
I think that if we say this is fake we're going to look real bad
People have started to pay attention to us
Under the radar and just make him scared
People
Late night shows make fun of us I don't want the world to find out who I am
People realize Owen Shroyer exist when he got
Made fun of by a little girl
Finally saw his name
Imprint lawyer
It is
Shroyer is dangerously close to people knowing who he is
Girl everyone just
They'll realize like
Is an integral part of Alex Jones is operation
And he's also a monster
Skip to the end of this clip
Determine exactly what happened
But I certainly
I believe that Sandy Hook was a full-blown false flag but I believe the people died here based on what I've seen
Witnesses to this event
So you just shut it down
Sandy Hook
False flag
There were a lot of witnesses who saw this
A God damn
Lick of sense
It's not good how many witnesses is enough Whitney
Fact Witnesses
Blinds drawn
Can I listen to this
I was like
Is crazy
Between which one it is
I think this is a more stringent we also reservation
Out there traffic is a really important part of Alex Jones is worldview and
Is support for Trump
We know that
Good enough job of
It's time
Text Alex
Wrestling with that
Cuz running Edition
Information campaign would be at everyone's best
Centrist
Explore the last two appearances
Steve pieczenik
In December of 2015
May the train
Now on our last episode
To become
Fully convinced
Had to go with Trump
By the the last Republican
On December 5th
Right
I picked it we're at our date off a tiny bit I think it was already fairly onboard
By then but
Now I have no reservations
A day that will live in infamy
December 7th
The anniversary
Pearl Harbor
Which is very fitting
They make an appearance on the December 7th
2015 show
It
This is
This is like the kind of stuff
That Alex
You get to watch him
Throughout the rest of this episode
In real time
What's up
Oh my God
Flags
Still have
Right like the term comes from
That would put different flags on
To make the people who where you were going with someone else they would kill every
Privateers
Yeah back whenever it was
Yeah
It like if 9/11 was a false flag
The tower still did go down
Didn't all get f****** mr. like
Mesmerised
You're not putting a giant
Okay is Men in Black 2
Argument
Rockstarz Buffalo
One of the things he's saying is
The target is the Moto
That's something
He keeps repeating over and over again
Christian conservatives
Scooby stereotype in country music
They are the ones who wear the target obviously
The motive was wanted to kill white Christian
A conservative type
Okay
And he's making the argument that must mean that it's liberals
Door behind
You're the antifa
They would want to kill Conservative Christian
And to that end I would make the argument
If you had a crazy conservative
Type and I'm not saying that this is
Crazy guy
Maybe someone who listens to Alex Jones and loves the idea false flags and understand
Blamed for certain thing
Wouldn't it make sense for that person then to target Veron
People
He says that the Democrats are going to do that
To gain sympathy
He says that the Democrats are going to start false flagging each other in order to blame the Patriots
2 using that same logic
Doesn't it make sense that he should consider the possibility that some unhinged militia person attack
That would appear to be white Christian conservative
In order to
Jamie Dornan
I'm not using Alex Jones
That makes as much sense as anything he's saying
Right
Problem
It's crazy
Batshit
Also
We live in a comic book now
So that might as well
In the world that we live in
I'm at a place where it's like
A year ago
That's f****** crazy dad now it's like 30 12% possibility that did happen
Actually the way you described that I think it's Alex is like
You know he
Describes all sorts of Nefarious motives to one side and then doesn't think that people listening to me
Might think
That's a good idea
I meant go do it
So the reason that
Again I'm not saying that's what happened like this
Is obviously the true
If we just start going
Conspiracy theory Beyond Alex Jones
Sure
I was starting to flirt with the idea of pretending
For his dissertation doctorate
When I was growing up and I was super young we lived in Cambridge in Boston
Is doctorate in religious studies
Alternative fake
Reality we're actually there because
They were doing tests on me in order
Jesus I was thinking about trying to do something like that and the idea of you say we should go crazy
What's an idea
Exceed
No
You're you're discounting the fact that if Alex didn't
That that's what
Could have happened
And would have
Then his job then
Pretend
That
And it couldn't be what
See what's going on then do I know
It's impossible to get
Nothing with with that is
True
We only make Alex smarter and
Smarter and smarter
We should be going the exact opposite
Get directions
I'll bet the first thing that I want to do is I want to play
2015 show
Always talks about
Come out
Veterans United States funds
Who's Isis
Realize
Exactly where he was getting this from any Mexico here in this clip
No problem
Blown up
I don't think the establishment
Television
Consciously
It's a horrible idea I don't know what
Do you know who that is
Michael Flynn
Of course
You know what
By the way I listen to that interview
Unwise
Vet Mike Flynn
The guy who got
Fired
From the Director of National Intelligence position
Not good
Currently working
Forever 21 at that point you making these claims
He's actively an agent for a foreign power
Cool dictatorship
I don't necessarily think that discount
Interesting
Okay
So it is not beyond the realm of possibility to imagine that
We funded ice
Entirely
Well before they were the Islamic State
Right before they were an entity that was International
Probably most likely
Different generation
It's a different time it's it's not like
It's not like we funded al-Qaeda in Uno 99
They were fighting the Russian
Again it doesn't necessarily
Discount what he
Right
With that
But Alex says he's
Right
And then there's also the fact that
We are
Constantly making ice
Simply by having our dumbass
They are recruiting entirely baseball
At least it's not like they needed it Obama drone strike the hell out of enough
Recruitment plan
In effect
End up helping Isis
But that does not mean that we created Isis
Channel 8
In the same way that like
Car or even a pill to some extent
There's a negative side effects
Just found out that's going
To call
X amount of
Right I could either recall it or pay people off
Businesses
Right they just decide that hey we're going to bite the bullet on this and just gets as opposed to settle out of court
2 Chainz
Probably foreign policy equivalent
We're going to kill a bunch of terrorists
Amor
I think it's I think there's probably an equation the people do and I disagree with her math probably but
Nothing makes
The gun companies
More money than whenever a mass shooting
Bright socks got sold out immediately
Nothing makes military contractor
There's more money than
Yeah and nothing makes our GOP Congressman more electable than
Pretending that there
Fighting against terrorists
Yeah they have to create
America
Create its own anime
But being f******
That is a big part of
That's what we are so ugh
I don't necessarily discount what Mike
Michael Flynn
In that regard because
First off
Who gives a s*** going to jail
Probably
Have to know that at this point
Seems about his goal is either.
Parked
To f******
Go all-out right
So why not
And this isn't December 2015
We got to remember that we're back in
The past has been named
Trump
Nationals
Security guy or anything like that
Connections that have already been forming
Right now
And I am not doing a good job covering it
You're like I should be in prison
International frogs
Let's put a pin in all that I get what you're saying
I don't just I don't disagree but I don't hold
Agree either
But it's immaterial to need to get through today
Chinaq
He comes in this December 7th
2015 episode
Obama
Repeatedly our intelligence Community to stand up
Stop the president of the United States
Trainee Clinton
Or Obama
Obama has been a disaster from day one
History has been nothing but a contrived
30 how about a CIA operative
Born of a CIA grandmother and mother
Grandfather who had no background
No experience whatsoever
Was voted in without any letting by the Secret Service
Napa security or any organization in the United States
You and I could not
I'm president of the United States the way Obama did
What did he do when he would have to be elected with you killing of a
Sama Bin Laden which never occurred
So literally everything she does not believe anything
Annihilus
We Believe
I may or just like a solid
He
In 2015
He has to know that
Full of come
Complete bulshit
On that one
Like there's no way that he
He could even pull up any evidence
To support those dumbbells
Obama wasn't his nonsense
Complete not that he was already
He's been in government
Look Obama a good president
He was a
Absolutely
It's all yours up there without the r
You could make a very compelling argument that his
His response and his
So many things
Is the reason that we have
He was a
Huge proponent proponent of neoliberalism which has
Destroyed the world
So
CIA operative
And pathetic wants are in
Teligence community
To have more
I think so
You're a genius
They Don't Really unpack that idea that these
Deep state
People
Should have control over that
The idea that we want our intelligence community
Is very scary
Consider how utterly incompetent
Stupid they all are
If you think about
We
Should have probably killed Fidel Castro 60 time
And they failed every single
Like with
With cartoonish
Bonvillain plant poisoning
Intelligent
It's more fun
Look all I'm saying is if Putin can kill people in the UK
Easily
Intelligence community
I don't have it I don't ever bottle to that I was just thinking it's probably easier
You to kill anybody anywhere
There better be idea that there
Big smash
There's a difference there's a difference between like a dissident who's
Country and a head of state
You mean an ambassador
Sure there's a difference between Ambassador and the president to whatever position
Fidel Castro
I mean if you're killing people
Security as say
Fidel Castro understand
I don't know I still think it could be they're trying to bring in the idea of Las Vegas
Not that hard to pull off
You were secret clandestine organization
Really well look I'm not saying that that was the case cuz I don't believe it was
You were
Some sort of secret organization that has
Unlimited funding
The idea of
The lone wolf killing
Type of thing
Don't seem like it would be too hard to pull off
No
Back it was Bush and to the left
Who killed JFK
Conspiracy theory
Become vice president
CIA
That's true
Pennywise
Steve pieczenik doesn't believe
He probably could have pulled it off
Maybe he was in Copper
You're so frustrated with me
I like her I like a balance
I like having you here do you know to have conversation with but I don't f****** like every single thing
Pick any edgewise word you want but when I say in this next
Generally they say something
Cuernavaca
I'm 35 minutes already
Alright I apologize
Next clip
We found out earlier that Steve pieczenik does not believe the Sandy Hook happen
Crazy nice States
Create it
Don only in Benghazi
Not only
And downtown oven on
Button Sandy Hook
I'm a Bin Laden kind of like a political John dumelo
Anyway
Sandy Hook was par excellence
Description of a non-existent
Killing
Show called Asperger's individual
Supposedly killed 22 kids
Federal adult
A lot of Machinery in a lot of heavy equipment it was nonsense
Moving along
Another one
Is because it becomes abundantly clear when you listen to this December 7th appearance
Listen to the December 20th
Appearance
You really start
To get the
All the pieces coming to play about Steve
Manipulating Alex
And there's a couple moments where Alex
I think he's
He's been through it a little bit
Squashes those
Beers or like
Belfor
Pretended to go full-on with Sandy Hook
He's manipulating Alex
That's all you
He's just sowing chaos
Horsemen of the Apocalypse
I think the populations are much easier to control when they're scared and when they are
Distrustful of authority and that sort of thing
Ain't So if you want
Mccreight book
And stuff like that
30 styles
I'm sure there's some
Interesting that but that also
Just pushing through
You know what I don't know
Purely Financial motive
It doesn't
Seem like
It's not clear he has a vested interest
Trump getting
He doesn't seem like
He's not as much of a bigot is a lot of Alex's other cronies
What is he getting now that he would have gotten
Stolen Valor
A little bit so this is just him wanting to get a
Handjob mean if you're going to make the argument that you think he's crazy
He's crazy enough to just want everyone to think that he's changed the world
That could it could be just ego as it is about people like
Larry Nichols
Basically that's
The primary motivation
Noelle is not boring in terms of the Witch
Stuff but then there's other people who it's clear that like because it will
Ada rollback of civil rights
It will Aid a rollback
Of taxes on the rich
And stuff like that
Divas
It's not it's clear I think you playing a really interesting
Game
But yeah I don't know why
Why is not clear maybe maybe
Regardless of
He's going to get
Some
The more he appears on these shows
Is it really just he wants
Detention
Is he just another just another narcissistic
It's possible but I think also he might also be
Being manipulated
In some ways
As manipulated
Text but over the course of
I think you'll start to see little indication
Possible
That other characters we know are working
We talked about
Manipulate
Rodger Stone
Now we're giving Rogers
Let's listen to a few more clips and see where we land that it's very difficult to say
Exactly what
The motivation of the endgame is
I think it might be possible that we could sum it up as a drastic
Change in US foreign policy
Okay and I think that you might have some
Softness towards Russia
You might be a pro-russia guy
It's entirely possible.
Piece of it I don't know let's play some of these parts
See if it develops
Alright
And his next clip
Receive Justice
Classic
Textile flattery
Indicative
Forget Alex
Into a narrative
You need to listen
Security with this
Athleta
The American public you are important
Because basically you have been the game changer
The entire business is immediately
The New York Times
The Wall Street Journal
Ratings
And to get money for whatever,
Your job what time is it
And thanks to your own intuitive
Knowledge
Sense of righteousness he went on to say okay let me hear with your kind of guitar
And
Used tenured with it and in that sense to me
You represented the American public the public
People who worked hard
People who wanted jobs on a daily basis not
Politicians like Hillary
Are you saying that you have change
Change the game
You are responsible for a change in the game
Because you're not like these assholes
You're the voice of the under
You are the voice of
Truamerica
Exactly what Alex wants
Exactly the sort of thing
He's a patriot
So you're taking some notes already got
I just like
Beauty in a certain sense
Actually
Unfortunately
Drudge and all of those guys and of course after the BuzzFeed article that
Once again proved
Milo yiannopoulos
Which f******
Yeah we got some
Real blowback
Wonderly
3 what I say
Jordan one of Milo yiannopoulos has email passwords with kristallnacht
Or the other one was night of Long Knives 1920
Yeah I bet I bet
That's a long password
If we are going to direct
Don't understand
Absolutely
Tell him that everybody else is looking
To tell him that
Because Alex
To believe that he is
Getting this money under duress
It always has
Have to be to keep the doors open
Right can't be because Alex is a multi
Play millionaire
It can't be because of that it has to be because he's a
Cuz that will fulfill his narrative
Pieczenik is doing that
On purpose
As opposed to
The net
Daddy says
Has to be f****** insane
Okay
And what happened is you allowed to Trump
To come in
Thanks to Mr Rodger Stone
I've known it bad since the Reagan Administration
And he was brilliant enough to say you know what
Wiccan illegitimate
People who've been out
Call the Troopers in the wackos
20 million of us
Basically are saying
Plush
Change
Drawing your criminal
How much
He's really really great
Did you notice where he's like
I didn't know that you knew Stone
Steve is like
Now I don't know him personally
Since the Reagan Administration
And that record starting
2 in this clip you starting to realize that Alex is starting
Some pieces together and he needs
What's the distance himself from Rodger Stone
Because
The two of them
Are playing Alex
From different angles
That's clearly what's happening
Okay
Working in concert
Suspect that
If he does
Then he'll realize that they're f****** with
Okay I know that to be admitted it since then
Yeah but that was
Real
It's a thing that Rodger Stone and Steve pieczenik
Who knows what other people
Auto part of strategize
So obviously Rodger Stone
Steve pieczenik
Do know each other at this point if that's possible that's not the case
I'm making
Summer sershon that are based on some of the later Clips to
Right. Don't like
You don't push back too hard but at the same time
I understand your critiques
And their Fair
Will you know I'm always going to come from the Occam's razor
Simpler explanation of them know each other
More about the coordinator
Waverly let's finish this club
And stone was basically
None of them would ever perfect
Realize
If we don't turn things around and stop
Select
I agree with you
Took
Where we get the word of that you're just like
No the only the only thing you concerned about cuz immediately what he says after that is
Did that he's concerned about is
Fat pushing back against that
Cuz what you heard they're at the end of that clip
Alex talking
Is something you will revisit later
And it is a realization
Did Rodger Stone behind the scenes
Has been telling him
Verbatim
The same stuff Steve pieczenik
Telling him
Indicate
Coordination
Set
Compelling
We just saw it right there
Is
The temperature
He's been a long time
Rodger Stone his not
Rodger Stone was a part of the Trump campaign
August 20th
In order to
A Groundswell
Supposedly not connected
Did the Trump media attention
Yeah I mean
Heart attack
So what does
Have connection
With Steve pieczenik
I need to work together if we're going to flip
Alex Jones
Right we're going to get him on board
Months before this
This December
Episode he came on and said that me and some other people
Have convinced
Trump to run for president
Because he is the one who can save the country
A couple months ago
In Alex's house
Because
Interactions that he's had with Rodger Stone
The people that he's talking to behind the scene
Rodger Stone
And ostensibly other people who are members of this 45 group
That is my belief
Ozon
And I imagine
You know Steve pieczenik is spitting the narratives that Rodger Stone will
End up staying
What's he shows up Rodger Stone shows up
Exact same things that trusted
Pertronix
Be true
You guys can't be connected you say you don't know each other when in the meantime
It's just a perfectly elaborate
Perfectly laid out charade
Loudoun 2017
Has collapsed
Because Steve pieczenik
I said that
Las Vegas shooting
Because or they're not
I suppose it's just
I see these two guys as
Is being
Stupid
Can successfully pull off
This scam
What's stupid about
Stupid about the
Listen to what they say
No cuz there's intent behind the things
It sounds stupid
That's the thing that says
To be taking it again
Consideration
Like if you are I said it or if you walk down the street and you saw some guy in like a
The information is not stupid they're doing it for a reason
Propaganda
And conspiracy theorist
Very rarely
Exist in a vacuum
No they're not they're not espousing to dumb theories that they espoused
For no reason there's something behind all of this
Kahneman
So April like are they and cummings motivation
Doing this for some sort of
America
Right
So you always presented as I care about the country yet
Do they want Power do they want influence do they want money
Probably do they look like and how does this
Help them
This is what I don't understand
No I think school is for people to look at him
And say look at
He got a tattoo
Nixon
I think that's a big part of it but you have to
Consider that
You know he's been in business with Paul manafort is Broderick
Slips in there he's been involved in third world country election
He has
That are not abundant
Clear without digging too deep into that
I think that
Probably they all stand to gain
An amazing amount of money
Wicker Trump being president
They all know that they can use it
Convoluted
Rube Goldberg machine of making money
Well maybe some of them had their backs
The wall
Maybe there was no other option
People like Mike Flynn probably didn't have another option
Right people like Paul manafort
In over his head
Probably didn't have another option
I don't I don't
There's so many other options
They already have
Influence
Name recognition of billions of dollars to a foreign powers
That wants their money back
What do you do
You can influence trade in order to get your debt
Forgiven before does
There was an article that came out recently about how
Did the
The prevailing theory is because
Money
Aubrey was involved with that.
Director
Guy I can remember how to say that Russia
The emails showed that he was offering
Private briefing
And the prevailing theory was that money is super easy to
You traced
And so he was offering these
These things in exchange for debt forgiveness
Because that would be
Impossible to trace
Situations like that
Status
Steve pieczenik I don't know what he has his fingers in
But you have to assume with a lot of these
These people
That is what's going on
They're desperate
Hard for me to jump
Full force into this because again it's
It sounds like a f******
Comic book
Like this does not sound like it would happen in reality
Trump is
Who knows what could happen
It's it seems just so insane
Actually happened in real life
Just because
At the same time
Guy seems so
They're amazing or they're terrible
There's no there's no middle ground with
He's f****** idiot
Bright
So here's the article about Paul manafort
We now know more about why manafort offered private briefings to Russian oligarch
Paul manafort offered private briefings to Russian oligarch
Resolving a business
Dispute a new report says
The dispute erupted as a result of a failed 2008 business
Manafort representative City offer private briefings never materialized which is irrelevant
Former Trump campaign chairman Paul manafort offered private briefings
About the campaign for Russian oligarch
Deripaska
In hopes of resolving a years-long business
Sources told Bloomberg on Wednesday
Failed business deal in 2008 involving
Ukrainian TV company
Call Black
C cable
According to Bloomberg
Legal complaints filed by deripaska representative
In the Cayman Islands
18 billion dollars
Invest in the company but
Project fell through
Amana Fort all but
Appear without paying back deripaska
And pledging to recover the money from him as recently as early 2006
According to the Associated Press
But they reportedly backed off on accusations
Shortly after manafort's
Campaign display
Do you have situations like this pretty open-and-shut.
Or at least it
F******
You need a good excuse if it's not
Obviously
Write any other conclusion is outside
It would be baffling another conclusion we have these things that are starting
To come up
Who knows
I'd like I said
No.
Game in it
I don't know exactly what Rodger Stone
Right but there are
Sleep the lifting of sanctions
Billions of dollars
End
They couldn't
Piece of that
Possible
Or just
I mean
Pretty clear to me based on Steve pieczenik
Things that you said
He has a soft spot for Russia and like
Makes them being able to work with them more
What is not being illegal
I don't know but can we stop on board with a global
Whenever were fighting against a global conspiracy
I don't think it's probably for European very localized
Very localized
Open is just part of another larger
Like if you're going to say if you're going to say that
Are both
Manipulating Alex
In coordination with each other
Then you have to get into the large
Do they all know about
45 members
Alright
The Crazy 88
So then you have to say that well that entire group is probably
At the very least had a
Conversation about
Or they purported are probably in there too
So now you have phlegm also with multiple different
Commence
Dealing with global conspiracy you're not
Successful
Globalist
Conspiracy that Alex
Because involved
You know like poisoning the water
And this is just making a motivation is very
Clearly just
Selfishness and self
Empowerment yeah
Is a global conspiracy
Is based entirely on that makes
More sense than otherwise
Is it really that easy
What it's very frustrating
Is that what you can do
If you get enough to do if you get enough connections is it all the sudden like
Hey let's make a billion dollars off
Sanctions
Lifting by electing the worst president in the history of the world
We couldn't possibly have done
Barely happened in the first place and a couple of other flaming bigots
So we'll just distract everybody with all sorts of birth-control and out lawn
520 week abortion
S*** like that
We'll get everyone hot and bothered and distracted with that well we
Rake in millions
And then the door have our Millions
Forgiven in death
That motive in there it has to
Movie desperation
Tattoo of Ben askren
Imagine if our media actually function even slightly
But that's part of your calculation
Right
A little bit
If they've given the if they've given Trump
Billion in free advertising instead of 2 billion in free advertise
Would we still be in the same play
I don't know I probably
I think so
Do you think it was inevitable
Unexso probably
From
It was inevitable
Maybe
I think we'll know more as time goes on
Yeah I mean in terms of
Cambridge analytica
In terms of the micro-targeting of people with ads
Yeah her movies Russian companies buying
Weird ads
Have to do with art
Domestic issues who Woulda guessed trying to
You got caught people to be racist
Ford strop
Howard to get them towards drop by and slamming it
I think it's a lot of those things make it much more inevitable
Certainly wasn't
People could have fought back against it more effect
Actively fight
Yeah I just don't like
I don't like that narrative
Because that is
That is the
The people with information
Defeating the people
Without it
Is the people
Insanely rich
Effective
Target propaganda campaign that I just don't want to believe that
People are good at some
Rodger stone is one of the sleaziest
Players in the game B's the Ric Flair
He is dirty as hell and
What why would you not sink
That would be his modus operandi
Pulling off something really f***** up
And sleazy
Is exactly what he's all about
Like I know that he and Trump have been friends for a long time and all that and plain sort of his
Proximity
But his involvement
Is actively involved
Dolphin
If I'm if I'm going to do a an autopsy
My first
First
Kill
I mean my first like suspect
The prime mover
So to speak
Is
Mercer
I think this will go down and
First time
That artist
Social intelligence
BBQ man
Blue
Artificial intelligence improvised in that regard but I do I do think that
Cambridge analytica is the
Secret
One of the biggest
Pieces on the map
Behind all sorts
Yeah
Like this but at the same time
I wouldn't
I would not put it past
The
Do you have that the 45 group might even be affiliated with him
Robert Mercer
Mercer is
Behind everything out
I do have the inklings of an episode of Doctor Who
Mercer
Is actually just a robot
Who is being controlled by the silo
BuzzFeed article about
The emails
Leaks from Breitbart
Milo yiannopoulos
His connection
Supremacist sources
Tent
And a handsome
Campaign put those two together and realize that they're the same people
Consider that they are working
Allegiance
Edit concert without
Infowars
It's just
Slightly disconnected
Because I mean look at it
Milo's come on out
What's the show that they're friends
He loves Bannon
The genius
On a recent episode he's talking about how the fourth turn is coming that's a big piece of
All of this is connected with the whole like Global conspiracies are dumb and now I'm right in the play
All of these all of these Outlets
All of these
Media Outlets
Connected
In creating this Loop
And they're all funded by
Rich old white billion
And Betsy DeVos
Sure I hope she dies
I really hope
Delete
We lost track of that was really important is that
Technos that Alex Jones
Got information from
Rodger Stone and Rodger and Rodger Stone
Him
There's no indication that he should know that
Alex's never said that on air
Nobody knows
Suggest that Rodger has told so little
So now we are up Alex
Decided by you
Flattered
He does something very
Tensional and I will talk about
This cannot continue if we do not have a Congress and President
For a military and intelligence
Viable
I'm concerned about a national security
And that's where America has to have the American Revolution
In a way that's
Struct
Why you are important
And why Trump was important
If you want the game-changer you are the expression that American Revolution
21st century
Allow the truth to come out
Saint Augustine said don't worry about the truth
Let it do what it does best to destroy those
What's the truth
It's important than Trump was import
Using the past tense
The other thing is
Inexorably
Ty's Alex
And Trump together
Lesbian
The forces of this new Revolution
So at this point Alex is still not really
Ricky hasn't come out gung-ho for truck
Right
It's putting the two of them
Together as being
Proponents of this
American
Put into Alex
We are of the same
Yeah yeah
I mean like December 1st to 2050
Trump came on his show
7 days
Before
December 2nd
Auntie came on
December 1st
On the show he's talking about tomorrow
The 3rd
He goes so far as
Still say that you love
And Paul is fourth ramp
But that Trump is okay
4 days before this
He's still saying
Could been on
He didn't go full-on
Steve is needing to connect them even further in order for this to really exist
Get home
And that's that's the job he's doing on this
Episode
He's tying them together your Fates are entwined
You are the game changer that will help bring the American Revolution
That's f***** up
It really hard to
Like
Hard to hear that and be like
Can't do it what's really interesting to me about that
Is it seems as though everybody
Everybody fights
Everybody who's trying to
To influence things and everybody who is looking things
From a
You know
I don't know if you want to save it
Pieczenik is ration
He is making the same point
That I would be making
From a different
Perspective but
The system is utterly and completely broke
Yes it is destroying every
So his his point is
We need to destroy the system in rebuild
His motive
Then the only the only
Prince between he and I
Is
Spectrum
I think the system needs to be broken down and rebuilt
In order to
Benefits
The poorest
And he disagrees
He thinks it needs to be broken down and rebuild
Benefit
Only
So
Those people
Is that it is already
So what is it that he wants to how is it that you can break down and rebuild the system
To benefit the rich even more other than
Creating a new feudal society
I think.
We all know Larry Nichols
Become a Duke he was actually bluffing
Sofia Richie
You become a Duke
He wants to become a vassal
Right
I don't know
Except to say
His next court the last one we got from December 7th
Again the day that will live in infamy
Alex almost
Realize that he's being f*****
The almost realizes
See if you can give me the high sign if you can tell where Alex
Almost to get
And then
Response
He said
Stories
Ouch
Because
This particular
The fishing rod
Was somewhat successful successful
Good to let them know that
Okay
I'm just your common sense
The world's greatest dirty Trickster
Credibility
Beyond The Pale of reality like legitimately Steve pieczenik ends up saying
Donald Trump
Just
How to become president to straighten things out
Adventures going to disappear
President
Loki and the Oracle are together
Complete b******* right there Alex's like
Come on better to right there
Music making app
You processing it right
Finish the job like
On the show
I'm at if if
At that moment
Stingrays operation in quotes
Like at this point
Pieczenik might as well say that Las Vegas
I've never been there I can't prove it's real could have been
Could have been race memory
They could have built it just so when I showed up there like a lot of people
December 20th
Where's Steve pieczenik
He's back
There's going to be two things
The 29th
Already
We missed
Some things
Christmas
Certainly it's coming up
Or just happened
Whoops
What happened
Christmas
Course
The war on Chris
Christmas episode
I don't think so. Eve episode which were going to come over later
Anything
Hear them
Try and
What about
I'm right now
The Muppets Christmas album but replace John Denver with Alex
That would be amazing
To do a lively
I want them to do a live reading of A Christmas Carol
Just rewrite it as they see how that would work like
This motherfukers
Personal private property
Conservative Christmas Carol
Libertarian
Shotgun out be like Intruder and shoot the ghost in that would be the end
Episode
Sure
I just supposed to
And all is well
Constitution
University
Cowboys
Smelter 55
Safe and
The real liberal
Right is classical liberal
Classical
So let's get to it
Steve pieczenik comes back on
29th episode
At this point
Transform
Music
Yeah those we saw on December 5th
Absolutely
I tracked it down
Okay so now it's watching Alex
And not realize
How hard you getting played
You'll see it all
You'll see the moment
This is sad
Is really f****** sad
We have had a military-to-military relationship with the Russian
It has been outstanding
It's 91
Anil Kant contrary the narratives of
Billions would like
To say they bombed the Russian
What's a Russian
A conspiracy that's absolutely
Literally the best
So at this point in code is B
Knows damn well
Connections to Russia
Inoculate
Oh yeah of course they're going to be attacking Russia secretly because
2001 because of 911
You said 91
Advance that like
It's already inclined to believe
That just doesn't make any
What do you mean
I mean everything
Point-by-point
Are you saying that
Military
Cooperation
The Russian military in our military
Assad had a trilateral agreement with our military
You know where that comes from
Let's finish this quote
You'll see where it comes from
You have to understand I mean
When I work in government
My primary position was always as a military officer
When I went into intelligence
Random at MIT
That was a secondary position but I was proud to be an
Cours de Miami
Psychiatrist
My loyalty has always been to the Republic as as it has been for Martin Dempsey as
Expensive
General Flynn
And understood that our civilian leaders remember most of them have not been to war
So a lot of these ideas
For people like
Michael Flynn
So he went to the military officer
Right
Then he went to MIT and Harvard in
I guess so yeah
He's a psychiatrist
It does
Cointelpro G like what is going on
Community based on what we're getting from this
I don't I think you got to get recruited
You think so or it doesn't exist and you pretended
That's another good with specified.
F****** crazy
Free Wild
This would make a great
One day it will be
Tinker Tailor Soldier Spy except it's real and we won't let go
And one of the biggest mouse
Piece of it is often drunk on there
Evader toria's big it feel like to have the taste of whiskey so
Counter-coup narrative
Mentioned
2 is I guess Hillary
Taking
Empower
Or something like that and then the counter
Sakura's what's deep
Chaneques involve
Huge basically military
Civilian
Slot machines
Trying to conquer
Neocon
The authorization
Disturbing
Bottle
Let me put it this way
I would call this a we call this a soft coup
Coon meaning that we haven't overthrown the president we don't intend to overthrow the present
Violence involved
You're not going to be guns in the street
Bart Allen
The same way you changed
The Narrative of the media
What's happening now thanks for The Bravery these men who've been in our military and our Navy
The man who was fired in Benghazi
Stand-down in africom in the naval officer too involved
These people stood up and have their
Stay in court and continue to have that
Summer Harris Summer
Remember our democracy in our Republic
Military
Systemwide saying no to the tyranny
And what happened is because of your ability to articulate
Lady in our military willing to stand up
We're not bragging here basically saying because of that narrative
You have a man like Trump
Whatever he may or may not be
He is changing the entire Dynamics
Of the Republic and the way they getting elected
Excuse me
Steve
You can keep blowing me but don't stick your finger up my ass
He's not on air
Yeah
Essentially saying
Because of you and your
You have created Trump
Trump well God dammit
Right
Andy's images already jumped on board at this point
It's more
Aggrandizing Alex
Compromising
Flattery
What is a guy likes
Like I said
Day today
Nobody likes to I don't know you lived in Florida
Golf
I don't know
Is a retired dude I don't know what he does
Text
The f****** office just dreams upon dreams of possible like
This b*******
We are having any trouble as long as you keep being like you're the most important person in the world you're so amazing
He's never going to push too hard back on
Right
If a person like Steve
When this falling out about the Las Vegas thing happened it didn't even happen with Alex
Admiral David Knight
Alex's show I don't know
Right
Respond
I'm about it
Put in the hot
I don't know what
Urban light
Yeah probably commercial buttons
I don't know what you talked about
Whenever
Who was it that brought it up and they went immediately to commercial
Pull that s*** up and Alex Jones like
Volkswagen is really good at that
Geico commercial
So
Steve fakes
His phone being f***** with
Vicodin
Tradition on Infowars
I think that you
You can pretty well assume that Rogerstown
And Steve pieczenik are working to
I think it comes out
Don't the crooks
Because
You see I'm getting into filled with right now
Play Jammin me on this phone
Paranoid I just know it
To hear that
Or not real
This is an undisclosed number
Paraprofessional
Experience Obama is created
Developed and nurtured by the
DIA
Chinaman
Strategy
Simple man not a great thinker
The man has been told what to do
Pathologically in a way that absolutely
Like he wasn't the most
Honest man I've ever met
Obama has repeatedly lied about
Posite Pro pictures
Mr. stone with the Trump came
Crab
Timeout right there
Steve pieczenik
Response to that is
Correct
He's out of it slow
Steve pieczenik knows what's going on
Okay
Presupposes that
Stonehenge
He's basically running the campaign
That means a lot of other reasons
Alex knows the reason
I can be more effective outside than inside
Of course or whatever
Just b*******
Steve if you have some awareness
Instinctual response would not be
Respond
Factory response
Correct
Leave me to believe
Okay
I have
I have to
The worst
Stone
Entirely possible Stone left because Stone
Is the worst person to have affiliated
With your ass
And they wanted him
Possibly
Still a possibility
And it's entirely possible that I don't buy that although
Insist
He's still running
Because he's Rodger f******
Stone he has two at the very least
In the same way that somebody
Kicked out of it
The fifth Beatle is still like I'm big reason
In the Beatles were successful
Do you know that
Results
The same it doesn't matter you're acting like a little bit of nuance
Semantics
The end result of kicked out
Because he's too
Something like that or he left
Strategically in order to create a propaganda
Write the end result
You did create a propaganda machine in service of trump
Deathstroke so whatever the actual reason
For it is irrelevant
Succeed in doing that Obama wasn't a
Like
About Obama
Batman was
Ifucking thinker
I know but at the same time there's a lot of people coming out to show who like say stuff like that
Brave
President
Diva dresses bear
Christ
Blessing the next Pueblo
Crab
Respect
But
You laid out everything he said word for word
What he told
Fisher in the system
Trump knows that music
It's just very very
Well the truth of the matter is
There are those who believe in
Truth truth or can I take it as an insult but as a point of Pride and I think your entire audience
There people that know the truth
Mainly because
All we believe in is
F****** Maps it out perfect
You told me what Rodger Stone already told
And you knew that he had already told me
Supposed to not be what it working this out
U82 like
Have you ever seen
A video of a dog falling off a dock
Like
Tara videos you can find a seat at once in awhile in my life where it's a dog who's hanging off a dog
And it's scrambling with its paws trying to stay on the dock with a lower half is falling off
Trying so hard
That's what it's like to be to watch Alex Jones be lied to by Steve almost
There's this moment there is like
You're telling me the same things Rodger Stone told me and
You can do this
Told
Me
And like you're not going to get there you're falling off that dog is a cat
I think it's one of those videos of
The cat where it's like
I know
I can get the top of that
I'm about to go it's like slippery
There similarities
It's just sad to me it's really sad
You see the like sort of jump off
Point of like where life could have been entirely
The world could be dead
Trump I don't
Thank you would have won
And that's not to say that Alex
Is the reason the tripod
I know it's enough
Overpopulation
If you had just like
Either been neutral like he was in the Obama McCain election
He had been against
Trump because hey they tried to run up on me or something like that
Would it maybe huge difference
And quite frankly I think Alex Jones is going crazy
Is entire operation is
Descended into
Bigot filled Madness sent 2015
Neville is so much iron
Is so dangerous
They're like
I think we could have saved everybody a lot of trouble if that dog would have got on that.
Like if he would have realized
Fox TV
Rodger Stone
Clearly
Why are they pretending not to know each other
Yet they say
Word for word
Verbatim the same stop
Is it together
Could have saved the world
Well if we're working under the operating position of
Neoliberalism
Perhaps the root cause of all
Eyeglass
Oh yeah
But which is which
Good neoliberalism is
Bilderberg
So I mean Hillary Hillary is President would have had the same result as Obama's president
We're just pushing me people into
Two more and more of
Trump is the inevitability
Of a broken
Democratize Republican
Capitalist
What
Yeah I mean
Kleptocratic
Maybe
We're going to look at this from history
Really have to
Because if you
Driving to the day-to-day this is all unreal
Unreal
F****** gladiatorial combat in the Colosseum
Emperor
Put the thumb up and down on
But like this is f****** insane so look at it
And you see all of these little
Pieces coming
Together
Which perhaps made what is
Really going on and inevitability
And instead of saying Mercer it's all of these things
You can really point to all of these
Historical inertia factors
Better just pushing us ever closer
To complete
Can I can I poke holes in your intellectualizing
Could I please
I don't think it matters
It is it is interesting to think twenty years from now that's a
Fun conversations
Whatever happened
Weather weather Trump
You know like you described
Kleptocratic
Unhinged
Unhinged meaning
Tether to ideology
It's not be easier if you was just
Because I supposed to like
I'm going to
Advantage of
Some of these I mean I have
Leanings towards white supremacy, take advantage of that block is best
Video
Heather ideological
I'd steal everything
IGN up and really excited
He's dangerous
Conservative
Miller militia types
Whether that's inevitable
Don't matter
Customer service did do this
Right
Is the person
I am though
And the 45 Club isn't play
If Barbara tuchman wasn't like in her seventies goddamnit she would write the greatest
I will donate not have to have a job
I have a lot of thoughts
Anyway
Of Steve pieczenik before we get into something that I think is
Fun
Is the last clip of Steve pieczenik
Do not
Get the picture
But he's being played
Whoever Trump is he is a force
Contend with
And he will not tolerate
Testosterone
They lost all credibility
Also just fun to remember that on 911
Trump's response
Was now my building
What's bigger he said that on
News interview.
Now I have the tallest building in
Yeah actually say
I don't know if it's barely is
How f****** fun would have been
Fantasy scenario that Rodger Stone
So Trump
That would be amazing I would have voted for Trump
Patriots
And real
Real statement
Trump believes that are real
It trumps all these other fake people we've got a bet on it
Fremont
Because it was the truth
I'm so fortunate as America
You are to have Trump
Spanish time
You don't need to do this
Smart individual
Incredibly true
He understood what happened in 911 because he knows Silverstein
He knows the World Trade Center better than anybody
Because
Why would he know the world
Anyone
Other than
Abject
Almost got it
Dog dog just fell off the dock see this thing is he was
Told
Trump is going to go after 9/11
Trump is going to go after the rape
Paint old house Rodger
The only person I think that's the only person that he had access to it
Yeah you've sold me on the two of them working together
It's at the top of the show
Believe that people are successful I would like an hour and 20 minutes ago I said a lot of
This is about
Months ago you have to know that I have a plan
I'm not going to make a Bulbasaur
Is why we
We have the open
Of you know a lot about Alex
Fair enough
So
In terms of Rodger Stone and Steve pieczenik
Together pretty early on
Is there anyway that we can
Can prove that
Without hacking your emails no
That's the thing be
Because if we
Actually have concrete proof of that the whole different story
The problem is it is
Alex
Amazing circumstantial proof
Obviously working together but we can't pull up
Look
Re-up
No judge obviously Alex Jones Show is a perfect
As like a
Judge Judy
No it's B is suing in small claims
Anyway I think we would be the defendant
I think once he realizes that
Conceivably we are the people who are doing
The most
Dangerous work about it
His credibility
I do think he might sue us for playing Clips ourselves
Temperature
I do not recognize the authority of the store
I am showing up here as a child
I will be writing my name
Thank you very much
Anyway
This is the 2015
Investigation
Think this is actually where we'll put it
Yeah I think you're right Steve pieczenik Rodger Stone
In League with the mysterious 45 Club
45 group
You got Sean Connery
Watermelon
The guy from
20000 Leagues Under the Sea
Right
Really who's the Indian dude
I don't know
Where's the graphic novel
Alright
Anyway
We have a little bit of a
A bone cruise from The Mummy
Here at the end we have. We're done with her 2015 investigation aspect of
This episode
But
I'm going back through Arie listen to
To the December 29th episode
I realized that I
It off too early
Because
Alex Jones has his friend Kevin Booth
Song
Who is the guy who was
Bill Hicks
Right absolutely
So the two are on because Kevin Booth
Have a guess
A friend
Film that he
He's doing this guy was
The gentleman
By the name of doctor Gala
He had done a lot of work
In terms of
Interviewing people who defected from Ice
Okay we have his bio
I pulled up here
Dr. yalies research
Mainly focus on terrorism radicalization and countering violent
Extremism
Co-op and several articles
Books on the subject of terrorism and violence
Gluten First Responders guide
Professionally interact
With Muslim Community
Law enforcement
Emergency in firefighters understanding and respond
Terrorism
A complete model to deal with terrorism and
Understanding and
Responding to terrorism
Doctor Gala over the years I've interviewed cadres representing a terrorist organization
The Isis Defector interviews of late are unique
Then the world as he was one of the first researchers who managed to reach Isis defectors
And persuade them to talk about their stories open
Editorially and parentheses I'm going to add this
Without torture
Most of those were also video recorded for future doctor
Documentary
PhD
A real degree
He formerly served as perfect
He formerly served as professor and the chair of Sociology Department
Tehran University in Turkey
Dr. Gala in both his master's and PhD degrees in
In criminal justice
University of North Texas
Dr. Galas
Counterterrorism and Operations Division
The Turkish National
He's written multiple books
Is in hiding
For the most part
Because of
The incredibly dangerous work
Because
Cultural revolution
He's.
Longview lawn
Because he has talked
People who
Confirm Isis right here knows who those people are
Information from them
But they do not want to be out
Kevin Booth
It was on with Alex that I didn't
To this interview
Is because I have like
They have terrible Tech difficulties
Kevin Federline
I made a big mistake
You're not covering this interview and I'm going to rectify that now
This interview is damaged
In many ways
And I'm
Started
With Alex Jones
Introducing
The gas doctor
He allows the guest
Weights
Dr. Gala goes on Alex Jones
Because of his relationship with Kevin Boothe
Documentary
The turkey
It seems so far away is somebody who knows what the f*** is
Let's see what happens when an actual Scholars shows up accidentally on Infowars
Accidental
Situation
I don't think so
But also
Here's how Alex Jones sets it up
It's important to take note of it
Because I think he would redo this
Afterwards
Pizza Hut
Dangerous areas Doug's Cadillac
HBO show me other channel
War won the belt
Fredericksburg
An exposed at the west of the Turkish government now there's our funding up
So
Alex Jones as suggest
And presented this
He knows
Who this guy is
Exposing that
The US
People that
As opposed to
I don't believe that he's getting people
I don't know I can
Speak to that but I don't know if that's the case
What causes
They play the super
That's really interesting ideas about like what are the biggest
Identifiers
For what puts someone at risk
Of being a member who has been killed
Us drone strike
Poverty
Basically a lot of
Motivation
The way we reacted after World War 1 caused World War
The way we are reacting after 9/11
Desert Storm
Further
Hoover Dam
Are chicken eggs
Tricom anyways
What is presenting it as this guy is a
Exposing
Is funding Isis
He does not know that that is not what it's going to be exposed in the
I have two clips
They're a little long
But they're necessary
The first one I lived
Just labeled
Is not a name for warrior
The facts
Syria
What's a geopolitical
Behind Isis shirt
I have a question
Most of the time
Saudi Arabia
14 factors
DTC
Great
Connection
Angel
Calendar
And right now
Make it the critical
Decision
On the battlefield
Russia
So
He's he's
Cuz it's kind of a little bit thick
Red
There are 40 to 45 year old
Retired military personnel director
Well some parts group message Battlefield they are making
Battlefield decision Hughes sayings
From
Whether or not you want
To deem him
Incredible or not
Decision that you have to make
Information
Is giving her
He is
I've looked into it a little bit
Credible track record history of interviewing
Plus I ran
Russia
And it is
Turkey and Saudi Arabia Qatar in Turkey
Those those those
Consistently given by ISIS
60 factors
So you can
You can either
Except that as
Each one of them
Is getting different information
As opposed to a unified
Bright
Would love me to make us analogy but
Isis isn't a group where they have like
The heads of all the local meat together
Very likely a piece
All that that is
Very likely there is a piece that
Swayed by a Ron
Interesting
Yeah
Talking about
If that is
Possible
It is possible
That all
It's entirely possible that what
Really going on with
Isis
Is that it is a loosely
Connect
Responsibility for so many different
Terrorist attack
Because they are direct
End up fighting with each other
BMW
It was pretty like you remember when it was like one big group
Ymn the Luchador World Order
I got you
Like maybe there was a central
Idea to Isis at one point and then became fractured
There's a whole lot of possibilities and I don't know
Different groups of
People
Looking for funding and different people
Responsible
With money
And they don't necessarily
They don't have a centralized
Tax plan or whatever it is
Do you want to go to
To find a way to get that
If they're gold temporarily aligned with Russia they get Russian
Mercenaries less than
To get a caliphate
Will kill time to people for you if you want it
Through in my mind
And I'm excluded from my mom
What is misrepresenting
Agreed
So that he is telling the truth
You to remember that I think might have slipped your mind
Just want this first one probably not and that is that Alex set it up
America
The second you almost certainly a forgotten
If we covered this on the last 20
15 episode
It begins with Alex Jones
Pretending the Infowars being
Being hacked by the
He believes that it is by the Turkish
And what have you I need you to keep that in your mind for what is going to
To happen to clips from now
In your mind
Cuz I have
Very strong theory about what is actually happening
I think you might have actually been hacked
Yeah
I think you might actually
Oh my God is looking for
No
Aspect is wrong
Identity very specifically said he asked
These people if they were chechens of nevermind.
Eyeballs work
Countering Isaac
I don't say
Well now let's
You listed a total of like
Russia
The only one that has not he doesn't even really necessarily
Syria right
Guitar Arabia obviously
Vandoren probably is not worth fighting about
And I like interview
Time
In his busy schedule
To argue that there's no way Russia
There's no way
Because that's his that's already his argument is that
Syria is
Dr. Gala
Pretty much lays out a very concrete case
Haha
Assad
Working together based on his
And you know what's awesome
About
Somebody who knows what they're f******
Talking about
When asked
The direct question
My proof is the people that I've talked to
He does not say
I know this is true
Right he is still
You stopping to the idea like I'm just reporting what I saw
It's entirely possible
Aggies flummoxed
Is there the entire time and he knows to shut the fuk up
Chaotic elements into Alex's life
Kevin
Imagine
That last clip was over Skype
I've been Skype
Attacked
Until they have to do this next
When they come back from
Commercial
Their Skype isn't working
And they have to use
And so it sounds a little different but also its
How is he
He's in the United States
I'm not competent of anything at this point
WeedMaps
I am still
Energy drink
Monster Energy drink it is on Dance Floor
And leg
In the United States in so much as I don't really care to wrestle with it
I want to argue
If if we're talking about this
If you were saying that the Skype one
Because
He's in some sort of
Remote area where in
The signal just may have dropped
It's possible I don't have I don't have a concrete answer on this
Basically dropped but I I want
Bring that up most can really variable
That's alright
In this next
Dr. Gala
Second ago
Lays out a really convincing
For why
Asada
Isis are working
Together
Very negative reaction
Yalla
ICS Orgrimmar on the side bivol.
Yeah you know me
You will have anyone
Usher runs me
AAA
Just basically theorizing with a person is clear
Yeah
100 time
My friend over there is that is chaos that is very complicated in that
You have a lot of people with a lot of agenda trying to get money trying to dominate trying to create their own things and it's
It's a very chaotic situation
What
I'm not fighting each other
Calendar
To get to the
Just real quick what are you saying is that
But he runs into
Interrogate
Interviewing
Is Isis defectors
Is why
Are we
Just never fighting
Mossad
Which is an interesting question
Is that the rebels are not
Isis
And so if
If Isis is in Syria
American and Russian governments both
Can say that they are fighting
Against
When in reality what they're doing is fighting a
Rebels
Who are fighting against
Listen there's a very pro-assad
Position about the United
States and Russia.
In order to maintain some sort of
Stability there where is it
Then
Siri is up
For grabs at that point and we all know that side in Russian
Absolutely but very concrete
Example
But Alex that makes him
Freak out
Right
Indiana history
Misha
David
Angela Fraser broken
80s playlist
Taylor Schilling
And then
That's a question
Eurasian
Indian history
Lincoln truck
Close of Bayshore regime
Thursday
Play Sunday Charlotte sold weapons and ammunition
Question
It's clearly
Understandable
Michael Flynn
A few months ago
The US government
Basically funded Health Isis
That was a direct order of Obama
I don't think so or I have never heard of
I want that
Man Alex wanted a different outcome position or two
So so very thing that he presented at the top of the interview
The closing do you know ask somebody
Never heard that
Crazy
So the doctors
Point is that
When Isis
Took Libyan oil refinery
Bisharp
Sent
Syrian Engineers to
Build-A-Bear to rebuild does it refinery
The moment that happened
They started selling oil
Bashar the people who defected we're like
What the f***
That's probably a big reason why they detected
Killing the people that made me want to join Isis
Because they were
Right
And that's something that he's gotten first-hand
Provable
And it's something that's obvious
Okay
That's not a good sign for Alex Alex
Alright let's f****** just asked
The question
Mike Flynn
Didn't quit he got fired
He presented equip
And he's come out and said that you asked
Creative and fun
Right
I don't know I don't know that to be true
Save-A-Lot
Anger that's f******
Commercial immediately
Course
Here is
Is take on
The interview that he
Bridget a doctor
I'm at s
Film
No one else to say
Reportedly
Set the West did that using Al-Qaeda
It's on record
What would you like to remind people
Al-Qaeda is fighting Isis
In most parts of the world
For obvious
Obvious reasons are to some people might not
Understand that
Specifically born out of Afghanistan
He specifically born out of Iraq
Is this situation that Isis
Is capitalized
To facilitate
Really want which is the end
The ultimate battle between the West
And the Middle East
Switch Bannon and clearly Alex Jones
Their ass
More of a
Freedom fighting or go
Innovation like that's
Really there gold brother got off track a little bit
But the point being is Al-Qaeda is
Far and Away
Interested in avoiding back kind
And a caliphate
Into something
Don't want
Involved in Afghan
Of all the things that I've going to stand
It is a country that truly believes
Being its own country
It does not want to be part of Saudi Arabia it does not want to be part of all of these
He's different places
It doesn't to be absorbed
But all of the wars that have been fought in Afghanistan
Heavenly f
Soic
Is another one of those
Take over Afghanistan
Al-Qaeda
Ideologically opposed to a dum dum it appears that there
Islam is all radical Islam as
As opposed to
Any number of sunni-shiite
Divisions between the between
I got a better fighter spider-verse I do better version of to school you all day
Identity evropa
You would like to tell you that all day but at the same time
Paint with one brush
All of Islam radical Islam
His argument is just that the globalist
Decided to change the name from Al-Qaeda to Isis
Confuse people
That's
Is indicate a lack of reading indicates a lack of global awareness
Anyway
Did you see that you see in that last course
Sects of Islam in
In the same way that Prada
Isn't products
F****** Lutheran
Goddamn
Quakers
Like it's all of those things everything was not Catholic
Has Dark Pulse
If you ever watch the order Temple
Is influx in concert
Play as well difference
Different f****** Lutheran's that are much closer to Catholics than 10.
Catholicism
U-Haul POS
Acceptance
Alex
As part of a wide swath of
Christian identities
Anyway for the idea that any Muslim is different
Laura Lou Marano couple weeks ago in 27 there is no moderate Islam
Piratical
F****** that sort of language
It's not going to ruin the world do what it going to do
Convince
Some people on The Fringe
Who are close to radical Islam
To go all the way
Not necessarily A
No it's not but what other purpose does it serve other than to make white people afraid
Those two purposes are the only real outcomes out of it
Get the specifics that you mean
Is no positive
Productive outcome
Comes out of
The single best
Parallel I have
For why
Christianity
Islam are both stupid
Their religion
Look at the way
They spread
And they
Destroy things
Whenever something like for instance
So many difference
Muslim sects in Indonesia
Far-forward
Very moderate
Very interested really in kind of
That kind of an Evangelical
Also tempered with Buddhist influences
In the past
Saudi Arabian
Islamic
Have been
Different
People in Indonesia
Turn them
Muslims and Christians
Murdered
Because he's religion
F****** horrific
Is in Islam is horrific
In the same way that everybody who believes
In Christianity is
Is it not horrific
What is 8
It is a
An ideology
Fundamental fundamental adherence to a structure
Capitalism
Appearances are outdated modes of being
Ever breed
Yeah I'll be altimate end of all of these religions
With
If your religion
There's always going to be a certain group of people who sang
Well it's my job
To bring it about
Because
It's a prophecy
Has been struggling with
It said I have
Do it because God tells
Right
F****** Fool by idiots like Alex will War like looking
You'll have
Hey weather
In a revolution Revelation is
Is coming through or it denotes just coincidence
This is biblical Antichrist
Trump is the Antichrist than George W bush
Like it's always
This guy is the epochal
Rhetoric is unnecessary to deal with the actual problems
Now it's the same time everyone accuses everyone of calling people Nazis
Sometimes they are
Yeah I do
The converse of that
No
People some people are not
And it turned out a lot of people are not
December 29th
It's more about Alex
Who confirms all his Michael Flynn
I will explain
Why I kind of think
He might have
Actually been getting hacked
Pink eye
Different
Successful successful
Infowars right now
With them posting
Good morning
Obama's personal
I don't want that.
At the traffic
We got our own traffic criminal
You're not involved
Because
This is what's going on real world
Earlier
He didn't say that either
Interview
So here's my thing
Okay
The Syrian electronic Army
Alex is asserting
Sia
Fire meet gasoline lyrics
Hair goes directly over there. Electronic Army
Is Russia rich
I don't think I don't think necessarily it is
But if it is
Situation
Let's possibility
If that is the case
I would posit
That Russia is
Is hacking Alex Jones Show
Because they're not idiots
And they know what this doctor knows
Now here's where it gets fanciful I don't really believe this okay because
I recall now that my
Maybe our
That he should not have.
Yes
The Hat covering her ass cuz I got the bed information put up a bath
And working collect credibility
To the idea that they have a Turkish person on to talk about Isis
Or they got
Some good
You think I'd want actually was at Air Force Base about how there was a
Plant
And everyone was hiding
Right right Frodo
Yeah
That's the other possibility is there
He figured out somebody gave him the plan
Any of these things are
Look like
Of course I think that they're fake
But
If it is real
Don't think it's turkey
I don't think it's some group trying to
Pretend
To be somebody I think it's
I think of course it's
There there it there at this point hacking everybody
This Is Our Land of 2015
True
Therein
A hack fever
Crazy with their parents
Throw it on the list like I got ahold they got ahold checklist
Their campaigns are going Buckwild to a certain extent
The idea that they would
Feel like
He's going to interview this guy who
Knows that
Some of our retired generals are running Isis cells
Why wouldn't they be trying to f*** with that
That's not proof of any
But if their idea is to shut down the sky
Like what you would want to do is
Attempts to shut down the site we run success
Infowars got to go to security apparently
It's all fake I was
Oh well
Anyway
Alex Jones accidentally
I just love I think that Alex Jones Greatest quote of all time
Dispenser
Volume
So much it's so clear
So full of s***
But the only thing about that is that sad
Suggest to me
That Alex does believe his b*******
At least in this
Stop to me
So you think he is
He's angry because
Tubi
I'm not
Good enough
Set this
To figure out how we
Spin-out
Like velcro that is frustrating as a propaganda
I've hit a brick wall
2 minutes away from
I see I thought this question was going to lead to
Him saying well I talked to said that the United States
Now what would I hear in that
Is
I am not getting what I believe to be true
Tubi
Confirmed
By this guy who I have already in
Interested
Is annex
Is super credible
Either I have the choice of
Entering
That's
I have the choice of being Alex Jones
And being a whiny little b**** about it
And kicking you off my show
Belief
Tell you one of those piece of information that
On the 29th
This interview that went really terrible happened before the interview with
Check
So
If he was going
The question thing
And be like
Russia is
You're saying
There are some Russian
Enforces better
Behind Isis
I better rethink everything
Then he's got a dovetail that in TuneIn
Interview with Steve
Right after that
I would posit that those moment
That's where he almost realizes
He's getting played
Are the aftermath
Of this interview
With Dr yayla not going well at all
Possibly of like
Is wrong
Belief
His belief has been shaken
Not his propaganda
All right there
No.
It's just such complicated bulshit
It's very difficult
Unpack exactly what
Is being Express
Austin what
I what
Bratz
Isaac
It's possible
This belief is being Shake
In a little bit
I'm Steve trying to come and gone a little
B of A booster shot
In some way that I'm getting out of this
Possible
I don't know
Bottom line is
Is that
I believe the December 2015
Was a month
Destroyed archon
But there was a chance
For Alex Jones to be
Becoming antihero
Are you f****** Blewett
You f****** blew it real hard
It was possible
I think even a
Even
Very dumb
Man who believes that the Civil War was about tariffs
Going going through our investigation
Has made me believe that he never had a chance
Maybe maybe that would be at every point
One of the top
Maybe we'd be in a different situation
Grandpa was
Who else was he going to go to
I'm crossing my arms right now very aggressive
For a couple of
The reasons that I'm doing that are like
There have been election
I swear he's just stayed out of
Even if he's not picture
Because you can't
Falls out
It doesn't necessarily mean that he would just
Have to choose somebody in the Lacs
He's done that
The past
Piecewise together chance
You haven't experienced what I've experienced
Nion
Hundreds of hours of Alex Jones
How are you trying to say
Asperger's and b*******
But the reason that I bring that up is that like
In my investigation
Can I listen to a bunch of
Old stuff
Stuff to
In addition to the 20
15 stuff cuz every now and again
I'm trying to find like stuff from 2008
That
And I would be a good episode
Right
And you see a different man then
You see if
Not
There's no doubt about that
Will you see a completely different person
Like there's an episode in 2008 I was listening to the other day where
He sings along to the Renegades of
The funk
As they come in from commercial
Actually enjoying himself and having a great time on that episode it's right when Jesse
Ventura gets his Conspiracy Theory show pilot
It's a Jesse Ventura as a guest on the show
And Alex is like
He's so
Excited and bubbly about the idea that friend is going to get a Conspiracy Theory TV show
Look I want to be weird but you should have me as a sidekick there's a bubbly like
Laughing like not fake laughing
Real there's a sincere enjoyment of being VSCO
And I don't feel that anymore
I don't feel that in 2015 I don't feel bad
June 27th
I feel like he's a
Broken
A disaster of a person
And I do think there is a chance for Redemption
In terms of
We see it
Very clearly in the stuff that we've got over on this episode
Bubbling point of all the stuff that we've seen
In the last
F*** 20 episodes of the investigation
There are there are forces that are trying to manipulate
Their forces there and I don't want to take his responsibilities out of it
But
He had a chance
2 speed that Steve pieczenik
And Rodger Stone
And who knows who else
Behind the scenes
We're lying to him in a concerted effort
To be their propaganda mouthpiece
Yeah
And if you turn Face on them
If you can hit the bad guy with a chair right there right there is that
Possibility
Botanica Goldstar
Maybe I watch too much wrestling watch too much wrestling and there is that idea that there is the Ville
Dylan's Redemption
Like all of these things are possible
From everything I can see
He had a chance
It was in December
Eddie f****** blue it
Okay with that argument and that's from a personal
That
My parents
I agree to see through
Fat Republican bulshit
They had a chance
Corso now
Corseted
I just don't think
Every person every person that has different like when it is in your personal
If your journey in your life
I think everybody has a moment where they can go
Superbad or super good parents probably only affect you
Like
I mean and some other people around them in their personal life and the rest of my
Sure that small-scale
See the propaganda put millions of listeners
He had he had the
If the difference between with your parents at
The Twig breaking
Scheme of things
With Alex
A glacier falling apart
I just don't think we ever had a
The moment the nominee was Hillary they never had a chance
Like Hillary but even if it was Bernie
If you eat
For him
He could stay out of an election
In between Bernie
Absolutely entire worldview is based on socialism leading to totalitarianism
To fight Bernie
He was a white
Bradley's Bernie was a
Have gone through
But almost certainly
100%
But yeah but
I think they never die think the Republicans never had a
Because of Hillary
Like they were they were primed for the con man
Because they were so blinded by their hate for Hillary
I think there are a lot of
People who are like that
Alex Jones
I hesitate to say exactly a large
Piece of it is a piece
Of his journey there
But that's that's
Is
Wildly simplest
The idea that most of what motivated
Anti-hillary
I think it was a part of
But I don't think
50 Whispers in the ear from Rodger Stone
We're like
I understand that is motivation
Partially
Is negative Hillary
But more of it
Pro Trump
Based on
You've been told about what Trump will do to
To be fake globalist
What he's going to do in the world stage
The idea that he's going to leave office like so long
It's nonsense
I don't think
Well I don't disagree
I think my I think my
My view on it is of course not
Simplistic
It's just that they hate
My view on it is that
Because of
Their hatred
As a linchpin
Of their beliefs as
For twenty years
Yeah
That they could not
Abandon
Without
Great person
So they were primed for the con man
Of the
Vicious weirdos the Rogues gallery that Alex Jones
Never
Is Larry nickel
Scores
All these other people like
Steve pieczenik is now on the out
Yep.
Documented the last like three appearance of the two of them
He's doing this Las Vegas
Probably not
You going to be
Hanging
In the near future I'm not entirely sure Ron Paul was on the other day had a f******
I don't know if
Ron Paul is like
Alex
And him are going to be tight
Anymore
Rodger Stones a different quantity e
Amorphous blob of whatever the f*** you want knows where his bread is buttered
Now at more than the other part of Trumps
Right though he
Sort of irrelevant
Oldies like old-time weirdos
Really the one who'd never
That is the problem
Is there a nickel
And ideas
I mean it
Like it's not to say that's the reason
Trying to get to is if it's the most attractive most universal
But I mean more of
Two cards of their beliefs
Which is not
And any little thing
You don't have the card
Now he kills dog
Yep
We cracked the case
It's like it's like a
Anti-hillary was
The Cornerstone
If you pull that
Then everything
So they didn't have
Chance
Because they
Could not post if you actually
Get those people to say
Will Hillary would be better than
That means
Hillary is better than
And they cannot believe
They can't abide by that
Cuz that would destroy their she is the worst human being ever
Suggest to them that maybe there is a career politician
Who's better than a non career politician
Any of these people for them to not vote
The people who hate Hillary
So f******
For them to not vote
Gangster
Is
Insane to them
That's pop
What's that's compelling
Which again is why he
Could not fit out the
This election now
He hasn't
Is is Associates have he gets
Distracted
Granted Hillary is Hillary
She's also a witch
Great
She and the Real Housewives of New Jersey
Nono's Linda bloodworth-thomason
They're all the same
F****** design
The only rebuttal I would make to that cuz I
Mostly grievers
Even if
Anti-hillary stop
Cornerstone
The other stones
Without them you don't have ability you don't have a building
Bright
You don't have a building without the other Stone even if there's one that holds everything up the other ones are necessary for the
Construction
And those other ones
AR
I mean they're all
Is but absolutely
It's fascinating to me
I mean I want to get back to the episode that we were just
This conversation is good and all but like
It's not as though it's as though nobody's ever had the autopsy of
People really hated Hitler right that's a little that's not a groundbreaking
Absolute
Don't discount that at all
I think there is a
Truth to that
But the other thing
Is that
What we what we've just witnessed
In this episode
Alex Jones
Bees very willing to be lied to
So opposed
To the idea of someone in
Impugning Russia
Like I want to bring that back
Here really quick
Yeah in the sense that that is the only thing
He really can't app
In
Dr. Galas
Tripped
Has it worked
Like he doesn't even Rabat necessarily the idea that
There were
Syrian oil fields
Is that Bashar al-assad
Set people to fix so they could sell oil
He doesn't even respond to that except
You say Michael in says that us is behind it
That's true
The only thing is like this is stupid
Is the idea that Russia is
Is involved to me that indicates
It's much more
Problematic
Goddamn thing about the other things that he said like
He doesn't know anything about turkey
He doesn't know anything about
These people Russia is the only thing that he
He does think he knows any
The only thing
He has big pun about claim
Absolutely
So he thinks
She has that piece of information
Witches
Fighting back at
Step on that point
F****** off the reservation
Siri on Siri
Franklin
He has no idea what
Bashar al-assad
Actually does
No
He thinks that he wants
Go back to Britain
Look at mean Workwear spiraling a lot
It's f***** up
It's so f***** up and it's not like
I mean we can come back to this 100 if
Sometimes but it's like
Okay
I get it
I'm going
Crazy
No I know
Penolak
I get I get the idea that people think
Like I have friends who are like what are you doing
I run into people I used to do stand-up with and they're like
What have you been doing
Just about everything else because I am an intensely
This is the thread
Really is
Now granted
That's red that's a loser is like
If we could hack Breitbart emails
Break BuzzFeed
If we could get
A data dump
Like
It would be so much easier going on context clues and his actual word
Yeah I legitimately think
This is the loosest
Thread unravels everything that's right I think that
From
Experience from listening to him
From understanding what he
He's talking about
A people even who
There are so many people who dis
Alex Jones
Crazy he's a crazy
0 people
Think that they know something about Alex Jones
VIP don't know who Steve pieczenik
Like it's right there
They don't know who
They don't know Rodger Stones influence
Like we talked about earlier to spell his name
You do a podcast about
I've always pronounced it
Troyer this cuz Vince
Minimates
There there
I'm I'm
Maybe going crazy
But the only reason is
I'm a hundred percent can
Zeze
Circumstantial
Pieces of evidence
Build up
A very compelling
And the compelling argument is
But there is a group
Call the 45 group
Rodger Stone
And Steve pieczenik
Have admitted to being a part of
On Alex Jones Show
In Russian interests
Then they are an American enter
Right and what they have done
Is concoct
Crazy bulshit narrative
That they have
Convince Alex Jones
Is true and they're using him because
Let me let's go back to our first f****** episode
One of the things I made very clear on the first episode is it
Alex Jones is incredibly Talent
Yes very good at this propaganda game that he plays
And I don't
I don't
I don't take that back at all
100 and something episodes into this
He's very good
And if they recognize that and are using him as a weapon
Now
Your point
That he had no shot
There's no chance
But things could have gone better
That is
A difference of opinion
If you might be right I might be right
Impossible
Take down your arms but either it's also a glass half full glass half empty
Course
Not is
If you were
To pull off a massive scam
If you were trying
Do something really f***** up
Alex Jones is amazing person to have on your side
Yeah
I mean
A white
Clear ultimate disagreement on this
Is
Nothing to do with
Any of the circumstantial evidence
It is that
I just
Have such a hard time accepting
But they actually pulled off this oceans11 scam
But that's that's where Cambridge analytica
That they would act
We be able to pull off
East of the century
Steal the president here's the thing
They didn't
Cambridge analytica in the Mercers dead
They did
The actual height
Alex Jones
Is dyspraxia
Alex Jones it was running the
Hey look over here and the reasons it right it gives away the bank robbery
Is because
He's so obvious about it
Yeah that is the point I'm trying to make I believe
Oceans 12
Movie is which
People who are actually cracking the safe
Cambridge analytica
Jared
These are the people who are actually the ones who
Involved
Alex Jones
What is f****** hon
Jimmy Caan son of course our analysis wind up being the brother of a famous person in the
Son of a favor
Exactly
Perfect
Considering the world we live in
We're looking at this
In terms of like
You know
A lot of really serious people only want to focus on what happened to
But the safe
Very valid
Point of Investigation
And quite frankly I think it's a part of investigation that I
Mueller well I wish
Probably not
I was looking at that well
Help with is
Review the tapes
Brunswick
Casino where there's people acting real weird
Interesting
Let's listen to what they were doing a couple months before
And all turns out they recorded all the things they were doing a couple months before and they're basically laying up
Everything that ends up have
Who is the guy with a backpack
Is that what's going on
The demolitions expert
Alright great job.
Look
I don't think we're spiraling way out of control but
I'm just
Unbelievably fascinated horrified by all the stuff that we
We talked about
Edit
It's such a
Elite
It's such a jump
I have to
To be skeptical otherwise
I feel like I'm
Start get into a place of magic
Thinking
Missouri health
Against this because
A compass
Scentsy
That I am
Unwilling to accept
If they were actually this
If people
It seems as though a lot more wood
Get done
But from my understanding so much of History
Century
You're welcome
But you're talking about
Capable of
Securing this
Years
Disinformation campaign against Alex
With without breaking
What
Thanks SNL sketch without breaking your misinterpreting
Okay alright
Steve pieczenik is involvement in the scam
It's probably much
More recent than his entire
History on Infowars
It's not like he was there years
Planted in advance
I'm still talking about the same people
Who was hit the nas
Righttime
Did just have to hit that booster
At just the right time as they did
That's the entire race
Even given
Inkling of like hey by the way I talked
Because stone is realize like this is a better gig
Stoners
Like you realize I think that's like Infowars dirty sleazy f****** dude
This is much better for me I make money
Be involved in politics
That's what it seems to me is what's going on is much lower Stakes
It's not going to get him in front of the house intelligence committee
Most likely
I think that Steve pieczenik is gone
Off the reservation he's going nuts with the like
He's doing his own game
Right Riemann him on the hurricane right now
Oh hey let's Double Down hook
You got intimidated out of
Pretty sure operation
Deteriorate
I don't think it matters anymore they did the job that needs to be done
Still fighting
Like a guy
Behind Enemy Lines doesn't know the war has ended
Yeah he's a guy who's drunk because
He's changed friends
And now his friends
Is Renzo D Mike cernovich
Was friends are jakpa sobiech
These people who
Like they aren't ideological
They're not smart they're not spur
Chicken the same way that Rodger
Rodger Stone
To some extent Larry Nichols
Alex is just
You even a new ocean
Inasmuch as
Yeah the same boat
Yeah and the boat is what
Rodger Stone
Gave him earlier
That metaphor fell apart
No problem
You had a good
Great great jump
You do
Perfectly in the belly flop
Amazing
I mean
It's just we have so many
We have such a
Cast of carrot
Who all seem
Pathetic
Whenever you reveal all of this stuff
And it
They are
But yeah they're not not no
Because because you put out
Compelling argument
You really do
Like I have no
I have no real life
Put a little hole in this here in a little hole in this air
That would
Deflate your balloon in
I think there are some places where maybe you've gone
Too far or not
But
That is part of the
Sure I just WWII memes
Just have a hard
Like a version
To accept
Set these Pokedex
Pull it off
Like probably
You're pretending
People could pull up a maybe maybe I'm just misreading so much
Harvey Weinstein
Yeah
A really powerful dude
Like it.
I mean it is a little bit reductive and
Insulting to call it a scam
But on some level
The serial sexual harassment of
Women who are
Your subordinates or you're in a power position
April
Personal stamp
But it is
The cover-up of it is another scam
All the time
I think the idea that these people
Did those people aren't really that smart
Harvey Weinstein isn't that smart in front of people
Smart it's smart doesn't matter right paying people who are good covering stuff up right and manipulating peep
Is what does the work
The people who are behind the scenes
Doing PR work are the people like Steve
Here is your simplest
When
Powerful people are insulated from
Any consequences of their action
Why the f*** would
Right
Like just like
Just like that's the thought that I had
If you are insulated like even now
His worst consequences
I retire with my billions of
Sprite like if your insulated from any actual count
Why the f*** not play this game
It's like gambling
Threatened that maybe
Explain some
Trump's motivation
Go into what we already talked about about man
And some people who are desperate to avoid
They're coming together
In a terrifying fashion
Really the ultimate
Of all of this is that
Whenever people are insulated
Consequences
Perhaps
Jordan's been fun
This is
Except
Hold on one second
Let me just put two Cthulhu right
In front of me and now the video episode
Now we can talk
Website.com
Absolutely you can also follow us on Twitter at
Go to iTunes leave a review
Baby Alive
Twitch
Appreciate it I would like to do our bit but
Be honest
That's really bad
There's this guy
Holding
Alex