Alex
Jordan we are two dudes like sit around drink novelty Beverages and talk a little bit about Alex Jones
Energy very American American flags
Soldier
I believe these are 99 Cents at most gas stations
Colin Kaepernick
I have Sonos
Very sugary
Super sugary and pedigree my dude
Let me tell you something
Taste delicious
I don't know anything about Alex
Jordan's good to be back together
Big business to go over today we got some interesting brakes
In the world
Alex
He made it very big f****** and I am going to lay out exactly what he did wrong
Alright so he made two really big f******
Much more important than the other
I would like to get your mind off the Cubs and how they're losing right now
Text Rob from Alex Jones
Coronavirus tips
Come on you got it
MMA long as positive a like
That's an excellent out of context from the top
Jesus Christ
Just for me
Alex today we're going over this episode over the October 19th episode
With a couple of pieces of evidence from other days
Comparison
Today is
Show I want to say one thing
He
He's really pushing really hard about his show for tomorrow for Friday
Guests who are exposing pedophiles in Hollywood
Documentary that has nothing to do with Samantha lawyer
But
The way Alex is ramp it up
Pretty sure he's about to get sued
He is working himself into a PR stunt lost
Like he's going to say something he shouldn't interview
Something like that is going to happen
Smell it the entire religion of Scientology
That be a wild turn of events
I hope you destroy each other
I hope the courtroom accidentally lights on fire tomorrow show
We don't really have any of that
In here
But we do have a repeat return appearance from rainbows naturacel Millie Weaver
Joe
Enough feedback on that where they like neither of us
Improv training papers were skaven
Hollywood Reporter did not give the opposite of Hamilton
Dispatch
No.
I'm so let's start off the show how Alex starts off
Nonsense
If the broadcast that I know are particularly historical and important
He's got enough
Victories
By the day
Against the globalist
Unless it's really happy
I got a really good feeling
Residential
Bob Lazar going to strike back and they're going to strike back hard
Crowded
Icebreaker
Yahoo doing through their lies
Donald John Trump
And I just love the fact that the global took over one of the most American cities
Pure Americana
Corrupt
Hollywood babble-on
Set Sodom Gomorrah
Who is the catalyst
Leveling the playing field
He's taking care of American workers are veterans
It's incredible
Do you mean
That's why he tries to get charity to give 25 to $50,000 to every veteran
Killed in combat
Every active-duty Soldier
You mean anywhere
Air Force
That's why he tries to personally visit them or give them mobile phone call him because that's one of his big strengths
First one to get money they make it as weakness
Chandeliers
Party mothers
See that's the problem
Soldier
How old is he goat
1 multiple wildly off you are not ready for the rest of this year
What the stories that is referencing
Caldwell
Promise the day
Promise 25,000 to them
Never paid
No those are his strike
What the f*** are you
Talkin about
Probably makes great deals and that's why people make fun of all the bad deal he's
Because he's made zero great deals
Denise tried to destroy every
What you don't understand is you got to you got to get into the headspace of an Alex Jones right about now
And that is
You ain't not be aware of this
Sean Hannity has been pimping real hard
Documents
And you've got a big scoop about Hillary
And it's mostly this uranium
It's mostly that there's a new twist in it
I bet it turns out that the FBI was doing
Investigation
Concurrently but not about Hillary
It was about a trucking firm
That have nope
Was getting no-bid contracts
And had been basic
Play compromise by Rush
Yeah
They were investigating that Alex is turning it into a thing where they're
Call Hillary
Yeah but
Bitter and Petty about the fact
That Sean Hannity's getting a lot of attention about it
Is like
He's in this place
He's like
No one
Tumi
Struggling
At the same time
Because of all this like
All of this stuff amounts to a hill
But you got it
Use it as a
Why
There are questions about Trump and Russia
Do you have to go
Use this as a way to
Deflect from the Russia investigation
About how much more
Real thing
Involved are present
The thing is what
Using this week s*** in order to deflect from the other ship its
Coming
He flips
The alai
To deflect from the truth
Of these attacks
You were screaming about drunk
Motor hard right now
He is
Straight up lying about this
To the point
You have to be like
You're lying
So you don't look over at all the s*** that he's not talking
I mean
I'm stupid
Yeah but it is it is
Tactically a smart idea
I will accept that is what we come down to over and over again
Is Ronnie's the
Red flag
Yeah
Distraction everything
He's f****** banana
Is he gets into the
The
Handy related Rochester
Pretty early so let's jump clip is about Mueller
The entienda basically accusing
That Robert Mueller had delivered uranium
In two thousand and
15 to the Russians
I knew that they have gotten hundreds of millions of dollars
Candy companies
Real quick just about that because some people may not know what the details of that
Situation were
Robert Mueller deliver to sample of Highly enriched uranium
Confiscated from
Smuggler's Inn
Country of Georgia
Russian
Authorities for forensic
Examination back in
The request of the Russian government and with the blessing of the American law enforcement
Alex
See what confused me with Alex said I knew about it
In 20
Bright
He did it
Yeah wasn't the directory
Mel
2009 it's nothing nothing
Spooky nothing nefarious
It's like you said WeChat week-tv
Nonsense
And that
Killer has work for
Call me was his menu
Basically still the head of the FBI degrading stand
And we had
The cfcm
All of that information
Flyers Larry Nichols
Hillary criminal investigation
Bi
Opera
New York with photos
I'm sitting around all the famous
Huge material
Infowars.com
I can't find it I don't know what he's talking about I tried to look for it
It's nowhere probably because
Just untrue for their state
But also legally action
Written
That is almost certainly something that you
You can sue for libel
I would I would assume so special if you somehow doctor briefcase
I don't know I have to reserve judgment until I can find this mysterious article
I did go to Infowars though I don't want to give you a little bit of a glimpse
Into what's a hot news over there today
Bar over on the side number one top stories
Saber-toothed cat
Mingled with modern humans
Big news
Do you think because it's okay
You think that means that their Jeeps respond that's exactly what I think is going on
So what they're saying is about
30000 years ago
Sabertooth
Tigers were just hanging out with National Geographic
And then in the top stories bar we have a total of 7 stories
Two of them are about things that
Newstead
Public statements
Does reinforcing up
Narratives about the world
If us develop new nuclear weapons Russia will too
And the other one is Putin
Hillary is behind Russia
Conclusion Hysteria
An elite
Disrespect
Trump voters
Maybe it's not that
Trump voters have zero respect
And we should not respect
They are deserving of no respect
Voters who don't like Alex
I'd be interested in meeting
I told you before the show that I think I
Stumbled
Something big
I was just I was just thinking about his his angle on this and apparently the new angle that the Jeep
He is going to go
Instead of ignoring the Russia
There's no story so we're not
Comment
They realize now that's not going to stop
So what they're going to do then
Is deflect
The Russian operative
What is
What's going on right now
Clearly everybody knows Trump
Committed
Nobody wants to deal with it because
That would
Be f******
What would a big Mastiff
We would have to first of all hang Trump
By the neck until dead
On the national Square from the Washington Monument
Somewhere
Right
For sure most likely
Taking those guys.
You're like that
One out it as being come on now don't you don't like that
That's a good thing as monsters person
Secretly gay just because you probably
A lot of the most
Maryland antique
Yeah well cuz I'm
Thrown around is like a negative
Sometimes
I know you weren't doing that but I was just
Be that as it may
Homophobe
Sex with men
While the same time taking away
Your own right
To do so hypothetically you lose a lot of like negative
So
Now we can get back
This
Is important
Their honor episode that we put out today on Thursday
We discussed
How
By looking back at December of 2015
We were able to
Fairly accurately
Depict
Determined
That
And Rodger Stone we're working together to manipulate Alex
The Joint team Trump
Concerted effort going on
At that point
They
Now I want to build on that
A little bit
In these next
Because I think Alex accidentally said something
Over the last three days
That he might regret
You might regret
Because I think he
F***** up the time
Cuz
Getting really jealous
About John Hannah
Right
And he's speaking a little bit to extemporaneously
He's being a little bit too loose as is as is his wont
Yes
So here's the first clip
This is from the Wednesday show
From the 17th
This week in 27
This is
Expressing a bit of
Pettiness
About the fact
They know he's not getting enough credit for the Russia stories
And what have you but keep in mind
Closely to some of the details
About timeline
Can hear because they are very
To the rest of the story
On russiagate
Clear
Understanding the media cover-up
And why
Hillary and others
Went after Trump for what
Themselves had done
Here's the article up on infowars.com
You story on Hillary Racha chat to drop
Tonight
Bombshell expose
Journalism
The president Nelson
Does a great job has a lot of Courage
I don't want to sit here and say this is not new news
Record show on cable
Protest with Rodger Stone
Hundreds of shows
Hundreds of articles
So
In clip
There's a
Nonsense
Trying to Cock out the audience size of an average
Alex
F***** up
He's saying
Then Hillary Clinton
And all of these people
Start accusing Trump
Of colluding with Russia
Because secretly they knew they were guilty of it
So they were trying to get ahead of it
He f***** up
Cuz you said
January or react in the next cookie says
At the beginning
Me and Rodger Stone started pushing this
Really hard
The idea of Hillary colluding
With Russia
What was happening in the world
At the beginning of 20
Dude
At this point I
I can't f****** handle the barrage of
I don't remember much in October 2015
In October 28th of 2015
Build
The Moscow
Trump Tower
Of 2050
At that point also
Phlegm
I'm just temper of 2015
Gave that speech
In Moscow at the RT convention
With Putin and Jill Stein
Also at that point he was working forward one
So
We get to January of 2000
Steam
When is and even
An advisor formerly
For trumpet this
Right manafort isn't
Even
His campaign manager
In January of
No one has it ain't
Until what
Like August
At least
Yeah
Paul manafort became the campaign manager in March
29th was announced
As the campaign
Convention manager
April 27th
Was when he gave that meeting at the Mayflower Hotel that speech
Met with all the people
Come out until much later
June 3rd is When Donald Trump jr. had that meeting with the Russian lawyer
They got setup
I'm sorry that was a little bit later in
Is window washing
Post reported that hackers gained access to
The DNC server
Even happened at that point
And Alex
Ian complaining about what he's
Accusing Hillary of
His giving away his own
Threat
Of course the other person
Doing the thing you were doing in order to
Heavily
Gino's
And Rodger Stone
Nose
That that's what they were doing
Because
Debriefed by Russian intelligence
November
Well whatever November December
It could have been years
Before
22nd 2016 is when Wikileaks released the DM
Right
When people started to get low
June 25th
Later that week
Is when the FBI confirmed that they were
Having an investigation
Trump tweeted
Vintage Oak in town is that Russia did it
That's when people started to be like
Herbalife
You give the press conference
Claims he's never spoken to Putin even though in
2013 even though we have a great relationship
Yeah so it goes on from there
August 8th
2016 is on Rodger Stone publicly admitted that he had communicated
Whether it's the Rebecca Channel or whatever with Julian Assange
A little bit later
August 21st is when Stone said trust me podesta
The time will soon be in the barrel
It will come soon
In October
Stone is pleadings at
On Wednesday Hillary is done
#Wiki Lee
Yeah like all this stuff that made people
Concern
And Wendy
Was really bubbling up
Was not the beginning of 26
Now it was near it was right near the actual
Talking
Vote at least towards the middle
Weights
Is win a lot of those those
Concern started to come to the Forefront
And the fact that I was just saying
We were writing copious articles about them
In January at the beach
Beginning of 26
16 to the point where he like Rodger why are we talkin about this
What it is
But now he knows
Subconsciously Let its
I don't necessarily think that he
Didn't know
I don't think at all said to Rodger
Why are we writing about this
You know being like
Look at how many articles we wrote
That I have to protect you like that
No a guiro
Here's the next clip isn't a little bit long
But it's worth it for what happens if
Straight up January
Beginning of the year
Say the beginning of March
Put you in in March there wasn't
Yeah I know
So
Now you know why
Doing
No exaggeration
But
What's incredible is
He even makes it
Queer eye me already he already clarified that 16
You could be saying January of 27th
Candidate
He wasn't candidates 2017 January
So he's obviously talking about January of
16 timeline doesn't make sense
Very
King to Trump all the time
In January
While on this narrative
Yep
And he's obviously working
Working
Russian tried to contact him about secrets
Indicted and convicted
Rodger Stone came up under Nixon the famous
And Senator McCarthy
Rodger Stone was around way back then
So from the beginning one of the other important things to pull out of that
Is that
Is not
Vladimir Putin is a difference
Entirely a communist country
State exam
260 it's absolutely not
Russians turn into a giant billionaire kleptocracy
Stone being on the outs of American politics
Text Mom I'm being so close to power
Has finally decided like well f*** it
If you guys aren't going to give me money
Empower I'm going to get it from this dude over here
You make a compelling argument
I was just going to say is that maybe he was against the people who came before Putin
And now he kind of likes
I think it's absolutely he felt neglected and they gave him the chance to feel powerful again
And he's really addicted
Power influence in a tent
Bulshit
18 years old
The opposite of a communist
Is on your Democratic Party
What do you do when a red Hunter
Public auction
What are you going to do
President
He was a vice president
Present
What are you going to do
Friend
Hunter is on your butt
Rodger Stone
On television
Fake story about Russian
You better watch it you're working for the
Course
East Coast family
You don't think he was in the CIA
Carlson said you better watch it
On the floor
A little bit
But if anyone is forgotten the reason that John McCain
Because Grandpa voted was
The only person
Who voted against
Montenegro being
Except
Really
The the vote
Montenegro tube
Allowed in
How is something that
Putin was very strong
The rest of the world
They wanted them
He didn't say that he's working for
You said he's effectively an agent
And Alex has misrepresented
He's doing all the literally major
6 point which is what
Alex Jones
It appears
It's because
John McCain
Hillary
And both podesta brothers are covid-19 a crown.com
Brokerage firms military
For most of those years
Waivers
Like what Trump is doing Friday or in total and complete mode in DC right now and that's why
And the Republicans
The rest of the resistance as Russian agent because he's just like an old spy movie
Sounds familiar
He got shot in the back with a
Polonium
Yep
2 days later they tested
OpenTable
If you have been poisoned
Was all Rodger Stone so that the dead man couldn't resist them
I mean that's true Warriors 4
Congress and they are in
Pool panic mode
Love it
I mean it's a good story doesn't
Match up with
Keep him silent it would be the Russian
Well there's that
Spoon has used in a bag although I would say that
Calling card
Yeah it's dumb
He didn't get poisoned by Polonia
It would be public
Just Like Larry Nichols did not
Run guns in Nicaragua
You can make up that story but
Not the only person who's going to believe you with Alex
And then when Alex starts screaming about it
His listeners are going to believe it
And then you get into like
You've crafted just a false
Reality for them to live in it
Fun it's f****** fun
Really fun I imagine like
I would love it if I could believe this s***
Do it
It's really just
I have to believe that it is
All of them
Having a subconscious or unconscious
Realization
That
They voted for the dumbest worst president in the
History of the United
It's possible were they to accept
Then they would have to realize
Because the dumbest worst president hits
Embodies a lot of Republican values
So if you admit that you voted for the guy who embodies all of your values
And he's the dumbest and worst president
Maybe you're the dumbest worst part
And you're not even president exactly and you are
F****** yourself over and they just
Can't do that like that destroys your entire world
View
B final
The type of Republican that I wanted
Is in the White House
That is very very very bad
So then you have to
Reevaluate yourself and most people
If not all people
Have such a hard time doing that that
Especially if you've lived your whole life by that
Ditto
Finally you get
Chance to figure out what
And the answer is
Everyone's going to die
Not a great outcome
I don't think that would be something that warms your heart in the middle of the night
So instead you make
You do everything that I
Like what they're doing is they're just projecting all of their hatred for Trump
On to Hillary or who
Yeah all of the things
That Trump is doing
Just like what Alex's
With what Alex is doing right now
Everything
It's about Trump
He is just
You know just like a like a game of
Move it on over
Doughboy right
Yeah but I mean you kind of have to
Good guy
When you're not
Cuz I'm not in that last one
Clear lies that Rodger Stone told him
About
Rodger inside
Red light
Believe
Cuz it's like my hero
Animals next clip we we learn a little bit about a guy named
Plumlee
Who's another whistleblower that Alex has on
The Alex
2.1
2.12 late
Diaz Soma
Some details aren't true okay
Let's just see what your
Hillary
Secretary of State
Had the power to several logs
The letters
So you would give money
Then they will say that but we have
Million dollars or more
Can you give a million
Delivered
Blackhat
Leaving groups of C-130
Disguise
15 c-130s lined up behind the fly to wherever
Whatever it is
Then he shouldn't really Krokus.
Broke it all we stuck our necks out
The Patriots
Printing specials
Boy
We're going to be ended specials here for dinner
Jesus
Steered
A guy who's running guns and takes a little bit of time he's running heavy munitions
High kinetic weapons
Call Alex Jones
Ring-a-ling oh hey I'm selling terrorist weapons
Running
About to fly
Lookbook
You should not be allowed to call Alex Jones
I think that's just it just it makes me think of all the like
If you ever listen
The coasttocoastam they have a lot of callers who are like
There's like that it was a famous call with Art Bell
Where this guy was like I'm going to fly into Area 51
Any fake like the the call going out
Stuff that happened like that
When was clearly doing some of that ship to Alex
Embellish
Alex
Description of him saying is like
We run guns to the jihadis
I'm not going to say I'm doing it
Right now.
Gorilla
Specialized specialized White
CIA antenna
What about
I don't know if I want
Breast
Leg
Give me a hat
Alex
Reveals that
Believe
Trump
That
Russia our military
Yes
Courtney believe the Trump believe
Frankly
I buy that that's possible really possible that Trump believes all kinds of fans
Simple things
If that is true actually had a
Good at calling
Widows are the
Parents approval
Fallen Soldiers
Believe
He's a lunatic malignant narcissist psychopath
And you will not
He believes every
Fair but listen to this
Elizabeth
Military
Years ago General Dempsey
Went and met with Obama and said we are not going to have a military strike from the air on Syria we're going to work
In the future when the war's over
Russian
And all this really
You're going to follow that agreement no more
So
He likes to believe
Do you know why
Do you know why he believes all this
Why isn't Steve pieczenik told him anymore because
Las Vegas attack was fake
April
Bar with his bulge
I would straight up on his show in response to a caller said it's
The very good likelihood that Steve pieczenik is still working for the CIA is pulling a psyop on info
He doesn't sit down to Quest
What else
Steve pieczenik
Well
If you're if you're telling me about Mars
What else have you lied to me about
Step
It's crazy why would because it's very important
But with Las Vegas he can
Which Syria it's a magic life is a magical thing
Like hey are Jeeps
Extrajudicial
Deal with Russia
The generals came to Obama in
Very clearly likes
Say whatever you want about our foreign policy
But I do not
Support General
Getting out of the chicken of commands
And making deals with hostile Act
The military
It's not a Great America
So bad
The weirdest part is that currently Brazil is about to have
Like their military generals actually
Are talking about a military coup
Because Tamara is
Most corrupt
Leader in the world right now
True
There's a lot of people with warning track
Cubs it down
Buy a lot
Sorry about that
Maybe it's one of those things though we're
You could see that being
A
Like a flash toy
If there is a military coup
In Brazil
Because
The president is the single most corrupt president on the plan
And we have
Number three
Cuz I would go I would go with Tamara
And then Trump
Doterra
Oh yeah that's it no corrupt
But I think it's wise blood
Corruption
But the military is on his
So I would go let's see what
Rank your favorite no
Worldly don't have time
Sign off on whatever your rank
I just I just miss them I just want
What's a good old bunga-bunga party
He's back by alright fine
I don't know what you're
Oh you don't remember Berlusconi
I remember all the corruption that I can get by
Corruption
Pictures of ultra rich
Plutocrat
Right right
I mean it sold its quaint
Yeah yeah
Quip here
We can listen to or we can
I'm going to give you the option
Well we got to do it okay it's about Alex getting mad
Compression
So
Real quick Alex's setup is clip by saying
That Joe Biden
Has indicated that he has a
The stay behind Network
You know treasonous actors within the government and in this quote in this clip you playing
It's Joe Biden telling them
Guys Trump
That sort of thing
That's going to be fun at our next State of the Union
Hopefully we'll make it
Maybe but
Obama did not lie
And yet was called a liar by a f****** idiot
President
Lies
Quite a bit
I don't think you told the truth on anything ever
He said this accurate other than
My name is President Trump
Even then
His name isn't President
Now that's true
The title to the club
These are basic
We have certain basic social
People shooting other congressmen
The real quick right is that what he's implying that like Jobe
Democrat
With that
No
His belief is that the gunman was trying to kill everyone on that field
Because if you killed all of them it would he was becoming also
The special election
And Democrats
Could take over the house
But mathematically it
Doesn't work
Cuz even if all of them were killed and replaced with Democrats Republicans
Still have a majority
Real dumb
You say someone saying Obamacare didn't cover illegal alien
Can you shut that off
Old
And teach him how to be sexually screwed up and hook it up
Funding off and have the Thomas computer at IBM decide who gets Healthcare who doesn't
To say Watson
He's done this before but he's called
Computer now
Right even back then
No residential
Decided that that's the only thing that matter
Do some old episodes
Unhealthy distrust
Computer actual cell service in England
CareNow
Years ago
Literally
You are
Kellogg's folks about
Lock
He's how long it take for him to interrupt again
Well he sure is f***** up and make it all the way to social Norm
I think it could be that quick let's see
Garbage
And lay down
Oh my gosh
George Soros women's March organized
Palestinian activist
Activist
With after family in prison
Usually there on the right side
Wheelbarrow
For their activity
Inaugurated
You were there
About what's going on
It's generating chaos internally
I don't want to see the chief of staff quit I don't want to see
Trieste squid
People were in our Administration we're still there
Please stay
Confidence
Issues
You don't say so
He saw nothing so friendly
Bali push all this stuff when we push
The resistance
After our last episode when it was like
Resident
Pushing for war
We're going to go to Sinai
Yeah
Again
Ted Bundy
How many torture you to death 4 weeks or
Your body
Such a dumb idiot
Settle down
Chipotle
NeverMind clothes
Normal
Hurt you politically
And I'mma tell you
These are the monsters picked
Remember folks when you spread the Articles the videos the Langston Hughes wards.com
The world
The basement
What is growling
Put on the handcuffs
Very interesting dream
There's more
I mean I don't need to really unpack that machine-gun of misrepresentation
And I think what the Bible saying
So
It's weird zaheer
Like of course he has to interrupt him so much
You just let Biden's words
Play Stephen Alex
Is it going to be like
Hockey sounds reasonable
You know it seems like a lot of them
Donut
Jobs
Maybe Biden's onto something
A fake Russia ties
Biden news
Like
They want Obama administration
Stay there
I am saying that if
You listen to what
He saying
There is a certain amount of one his tone of voice
Perfect
Politician
Exactly exactly
You got it
To just not be a dick like Olive Garden was saying was don't be a dick
And be good at your job
Basically
Alex
Launched into a f****** perv fantasy
This is where Alex
Taking orders
Take from Putin in the crab
Rodger Stone
Little Babs
One of our friends
Has assigned us
One of our walks
The signed up
Tour through history
Give me a date in the past and I started listening
I found the date
I listened to the wrong year
It's a good thing I did so
Because on May 3rd
I found this
You might be asking yourself what happened on May 3rd
5 days before my birthday
I don't worry about it after Obama announced
They killed Osama Bin
Okay
So in this clip Alex 11
Obama kill 9/11
In this clip Alex talks
About the
Spots but
Neoconservative thinker
Previously
Against Obama
Right here is yours this clip
Alex Jones
Anion
6 years ago
Howard neocon radio going on
Because it's that
So
Alex Jones
Just explain
Tendency in human
Exploit
On a daily basis
In 2011 he's very clear that he knows that when you
You paint someone out to be the enemy
Going to kill the man
And take the women and slaves
And attack the children
That is your response like
Take the children and
Be all pedophiles
Who was Marmaduke
October 19th
Exactly
Like what he's accusing people of feeling about it
Absolute complete domination
Competitive
The overall prosperity
Collective
Describe Prosperity one
Terrible
Affront to them
Here we are one hundred years into the great experiment
Audiology
Oh okay
120 + million Dad we know of
All other government extermination
30-second like it like that
Fascism is way less bad than communism
Socialism in there with him
Know what words
Doesn't explain what Prosperity is cuz he doesn't know what it f****** actually mean
Doesn't
He's right only left on your leg
Just talk about the Holocaust
Lights Bash
Right
At least
It's not Holocaust
Denial at this point it's just
Every other
Denial will get sick
That's all fascism is overdone
Holocaust
Lesser of two evils
He actually does that
Violin show
Have a higher body count
The idea of calling that a combo
Government
Stupid
Communism is an economics
The government that they had
Why
Add stop
Alex is dumb
Stupid
There's one pair
The men fashion
Those are
Those are not
Inconsistent with each
And they are not the same f******
Now
They did in
Indeed
Cold war is the
Portrayed
Communism
Not
They're horrifying facts
Like even Orwell.
You know he's describing how
Communism has
The the flaw of eventual
Some are more equal than others
What else
Does that turn into as a
Government
Though it's
Fascism
All of Animal Farm
What's a fascist
Dictatorship
Growing out of people
Berry Fresh
Out of capitalism just as easily
Clearly
Equality
This
Deposit
Now whenever we have f****** billionaires they were
Unafraid
Clearwater
Because real armored readout
Redoubt
The context of this again
In case you forgot was that Alex
Free remind me what's going on I thought after I go up to a weird
It's just him exploding 9/11
Communism
Accounts for over 80%
100 years
Cancel.
You get some numbers
That is the Great Red Terror
Suckling
That's who they are
There we go
Butler
Describe the tricks
6 years ago on a
Been doing it
With great
Absolute exploiting natural fear and natural
Desire to
To fight back in band
Together he's created a community out of it.
Yeah 1011 he does
Wind up making a very
Whether or not he means
But a very great point about our government
Which is that militaristic nothing nothing brings everybody together like
Dropping a bomb or murdering
Huge hard-on when they murdered
This goes back to like
The thing that I talked about a bit about how he's a
Person that he was
Much much closer to rational
Absolutely
F******
Come down on me anytime I say someone's reasonable
Past Alex Jones is
Closer to
You're describing is making a fair point I mean
Mother of all bombs
Everybody was like
Now he's pretty presidential and you're like f****** kill us
So you guys are going to suck his dick after he drops every bomb
F*** you
Hollywood
Sklepy
Describing
Sort of tiered layers
Depravity
Veteran Hollywood
And then I get
So it goes from heterosexual to the homosexual
2D pedophilia and then
Torture death murder
People
Things like Fifty Shades of Grey
Says the downswing the grappler wait man.
Run around the bunch of folks and they think they got what they want
Going to let you out of those ropes you're going to be down there for
Couple weeks ago
Feel like you have somebody commented.
Making in there and wailing person
Devil worshippers
They are your enemies
Wild breakdown
Who do you start to see
Be you like
Hitler
The problems that he has
Is that all of the
But you said over the years are on record
Rats from 2011
Where where the
Knows that this is a trick people can employ
It's not like you
Forgotten
No istick skiers this awareness
Really get to people
If they think that their loved ones are threatened
So
Yeah it really makes all this very disingenuous
Tom was like
In 2011
Like
A light bulb went off
Oh no wonder people aren't list
Right
Chocolate
Because down Buckley scare
No one's ever written completely original idea
I'm the greatest
Spin the wheel.
Periodic
First
Logical logical chords archaeologists have discovered
Let's famously an issue with archaeologists all the time
Throughout their enemies Alex Jones enemies are demon beings and there's a horde of Satan worshipers
Dehumanizing of your opposition
Speak to them definitely don't learn from them
Make sure that they are dead
Kill Them All
Call Marsha Brooks
To prosperity
Disagree with Alex exactly and they are not heterosexual
Know which is the top desk
Yeah I guess
So an appraisal episodi revealed that in a meeting with a Hollywood executive
Mikey was sexually assaulted
Which
We're not making fun of
But I will
He has another discussion
About a meeting with Hollywood Executives that is
Less believable and dumb
Actually assault them no get involved
Jump in the lake as they say
I've been in Hollywood and I've had people ask me
We got to do is
Until March
Dislike
A couple times on air go to a party
In Hollywood
And he'll be like
Someone come up to me and be like hey we're about to worship Satan you should get out of here if you don't want to be involved
I love you dear that in a meeting with a Hollywood executive
Listen I love your picture green light
Feliway diabetic
So you later good golfer loves you
So long as you don't tell him to go jump in a lake
God doesn't like water
The idea the very idea that you'd be at a party
My first instinct will be like today
Is they want me out of here without me
Yeah just f****** with me to get me to leave
Hi I am now anytime I want I have not been to a party
Such a long time Wild
The next party I go to Interlake
Hey dude we're about to wear
Make your decision
He also has
Stories about
Like
You're just making this up
About to bring
You just making s*** up about weird Hollywood Park have you been to misrepresenting
I think the latter is probably
Anyway
But you were having tomorrow
Biggest reality TV show
Companies in the world
Numbers of Motley Crue
Probably Tommy Lee
I guess
Nikki Sixx
I like the devil
Worship devil
Lucifer God
And
If you'll just
You are supposed to give you the shot
Worship the devil
Good for you
Really talk about
I got bad news
You do not break thing
Inform
30 seconds
Distract
You're making money
Anyway I just kept this next clip it because you were
It's true
I know
But let's let's just Workshop all right
I don't know if we do that I just need to figure out
What is your leading
We're going to worship the devil
So
In this show Tommy Lee is going to pretend to go back to college
Okay
I am Mark Dice
That's actually, I am actually in
Into Satan that's to Dynamic avoid
This is
Nitpicking
But the owner of the company
The biggest reality show company
Talking to Mark Dice
Also is the producer of the show it's
Seems unlikely that that would be the thing
You got to get your hands dirty
Reality production
Shane Company in the world to not get involved
Just took years later f*** with Mark Dice
Baby funny let's start a reality show company
Has got to go we got to have a reality show called
I'm up for worship
Devil baby greatest like
Alex had a story like
For all of his employees
Owen Shroyer was 10
Jerome corsi
He's working in DC who wrote this long article about how Joe Biden
Came up to him one night
Listen
I think it's important
On ourselves
Competition
Is only
Oh my God
Also fun fact about Jerome corsi
If they're already
Article
Keep referencing
I searched infowars.com
Jerome corsi
You came up was an article from
And
In it
Jerome corsi was making the argument
That Donald Trump
I was working with Obama
The entire birther thing was a setup
And Donald Trump was making a big
You out of it just Obamacare
Come out with and destroy the entire narrative
When the truth is
Calculator
There's a fake birth
So Donald Trump with eonon it as a setup
Okay if I understand
This correct
Right
Trump
New Obama
Has a fake birth certificate
Yeah
Get to talk
And Obama's like here's the only way that I'm going to get away with
Cover
Noted lunatic Donald Trump
Pretend
That you were racist
We both know camp
And
Claimed it my birthday
Certificate is in Rio
That way
Can go on TV
Say that it is
Yep and no one will believe you Donald
That's basically what is arguing
History
Be friends with Trump for like the last 40 years
Which seems to fly in the face
Superman
Just remote
Purely objective
Writing
I-85
Spell no bells and whistles
Except
I kept this clipping just because he does my favorite voice
Short clip
Voice
Joya Tricia's come on back on your sleep
You're going to like it
You're gonna float too
Evergreen
The voice is J&R bad the voice that I like it your arm in his drainage clowns.
I was walking by super great the other day
Who is the executive of the largest production company that I like
Good I was reference
Sing is the
I just like that
Little bit
Maybe
Slightly uncomfortable
Maybe not I don't know Billy Weaver comes on
One of the reasons
She comes on
Is that
AC phrases it is
Exploit
Sexually assaulted when Cheyenne
Before she came to Infowars
Well then I believe
Sure they talked about it a little bit
And you know I don't want to get into
Because I generally don't like her work
And I don't want to
Negative
About that
Site support
She has an interesting
Take on
In Hollywood
Came out and
She was sexually
Which she worked at
She wouldn't work there
Contributor
She went to the office
Imagine the moment
If she comes out
SSO
I
Believe her and
I think that
But
Terrific person
Here I have 3 clips
Aware
She lays out
A very clumpy
Solution
The abuse
In Hollywood
And I don't like
I don't like it at all
Abusive
Masculinity
Predatory
Do you know okay and try to try to
We're going to take these women
We're going to fight predatory discuss
Problem is
Bet
Men aren't
For women and forcing them to against a silent in the back
Elements of that
I really want to pull out of
Specifically is that Alex
One of his
Immediate
You know what you're getting into in Hollywood
So whenever she's talking about the real name
Blame the wind
She's not talking about Alex Jones
I wasn't sitting right there he is all that stuff
Yes
Let me play the next clip
She sort of
She's not doing a good job
Speaking English
There's a point
Embarrassed
Reasonable
There are not
Falls by the wayside
You know what she did
Combined
Not all men
With
A good point which is that
It Is by
A lot of Silence
Complicity yep that
Powerful men get away with this
It's a system
Yeah but she then
Is falling back on it
Just a couple of bad eggs
Uriah
But
Hashtag.
Like I said
Hi Siri iterate
If you want to take
Weird women controlling women
I have a husband
Predators
So
It's not men who are the problem
Yeah
It's almost as though women have been burned
How many times
Difficult to rely on
Seeing as how men in their lives
Have so often proved themselves to be unreliable
Interesting take
Perspective
On this one which is dumb
Jesus
Really really dangerous
Advice
CC
Kind of reminds me of this story that you told me about his grandpa and how times used to
Versus how
Chemicals in the water to try and lower sperm count but
Talk about his grandpa Apparently one of their neighbors kept beating his wife
Okay
Demand
Kept signing out in
Our friends
Put your hand on this woman
We will
The women stop complaining
The guys beating with the women
So
Okay Auto World
Did you understand that
Both men are acting
Are violent and that is
An issue
What do negatives make a positive
I think if you multiply them but
That's not how
Situations like this generally and in the
Battered wife
Yeah
It doesn't usually work that like
Physically abusive
Beat up by other men
That doesn't work it doesn't happen like that
There is violence work the first time and then I got violence.
Wait
Quite frankly like what Cheese's
Could get someone
Killed how many how many mass Shooters have history of dementia
Almost all of them
Yeah
That is so
Is it reveals
Exactly the issue again
Which is
Even said it
The women
The guy complaining
Complain a lot
Which means that the man once again did not believe them
And she got beat
Even more than once they beat the f*** out of that guy
Big Top
Do with the fact that
Maybe they got retaliated
You know what she's basic
The best system for dealing with this
Nickelback song
Play the song called never again that is just that
Kroger's thing about living down
Downstairs from a lady
It's getting beat I don't
The guy's ass
I don't need another reason
I'm saying it's like
Nickelback song lyric level of analysis in a real-world problem
Scathing
You're welcome
Nickelback level stupidity
Do a political show
They're just trying to be good old Canadian White
Cheap fares
I'm sorry Provence
Swinging Bridge
Illinois
We will do a live knowledge right at the
The funnel cake
Alyx review
That one of the hosts
The View want
I'm not sure cuz I'm not sure if I believe
It's not Elisabeth Hasselbeck I'll tell you that
Famous feminists
How to say
She's like
Well I'm not going to say
Great specials going to shut us down there
Because they're so good for so high quality
That's why nice reminder that it recently
It was found that
Bone broth caveman
Levels of lead that are unacceptable State of California
I like how I like how awful
She was an older woman interested
Insects yeah
Sam Adam Cheese's
Joy Behar did not want to f*** you Alex could anybody
It's hard to imagine
For misogynist people
Then those that info
Is all around gross
Yeah exactly
I don't
I really don't come from a real place
Beyond that it is just that 2011 trick
Describe
I'm trying to scare you
About your supposed
Answer like
Will we come away from this with
Is
Blewett
In terms of the timeline
His narrative about Hillary Clinton
Trying to deflect
From there rush it
Ryuk using
Write these folks
Did that me started at
Long before Trump
Right
Unfortunately
History Bears out
It's correct not help
Yet
Being correct
Is
Quite frankly
Well
Post a new blog today
Then you can follow us on Twitter
Underscore fights
You can go to iTunes leave a review give us like nice two words
Cheraw like nice words
I give it a b
-
You know who else gets a hold on Lucifer
We are on
Recording live Monday through
Thursday Eve
At 8 p.m. central
Please come along and join us
Appreciate it it's a lot of fun if you button on knowledge feit.com for the show also patry
Beyond.com knowledge Fighters
The direct link
We would appreciate it
Cuz I'm not going to have a job
Nope
I need
Your help
Define nuggets like that
Define nuggets like
Find nuggets Like Larry Nichols straight-up blackmailing Congress
Define Vista instance of time by being completely stocked up
Just have always known about Dina
Cinnamon
Semen
Steve Quayle
You look so much better than old assholes
Assholes
These old
And you know what
How does he feel
He already thinks about the devil
What he thinks he knows
I know the devil is a-comin for
He knows that
Go jump in the lake.
But you know
May the wolf choked on his flesh
But still yourself Jon rappoport
Alex