Galaxy color with huge fan I love your work
Jordan
A hook I think so
Make it things
Absolutely
Enola
Yes
Yeah I'm in rough shape
Hangover at all I've done so much damage
To myself over the years
Complete disaster
I made a mistake we went out last night you and I
Pick your guys at
For sure
The celebrating
It so after we split ways
Hung out with my roommates
They watched dumb
Videos
Videos of
Alright
Mozart
But I love a dunk
Everybody loves
The huge basketball fan when I was younger
Hearken back to younger time
But John Starks
Dominique Wilkins
One of those guys is not
Jordan is Big dunker
Santa videos
Still strange to hear you say
Videos
I am here to make a
Are you serious report
The world needs to know about
So the 1991 dunk contest
All right there we go now it's again
Now is this the one
Was this the one where Jordan left from the free throw line
No I believe that was like
That was 8988
It's irrelevant
1990 basketball
Was the year that the
The finals in the dunk contest where Shawn Kemp Indy Brown
Disappointing Dunk Contest final
Dee Brown ends up winning by putting his importer of his elbow
It's fantastic
Dee Brown
Subpar
To begin with
Look as much as I love a good Shawn Kemp
Not his Forte
This
The entirety of all
From the 1991 Dunk Contest are available on YouTube to go find them
And we will give you all of the 91.
Contest
Where is Showbox
Conspiracies
But by and large
Rex Chapman
From the Charlotte Hornets okay
Was nasty
Beyond those junk
Sick
He pitched the ball to himself from behind the back of
Over-the-shoulder caught it.
It was in it was Madness what Rex Chapman
Didn't make the finals Charlotte Hornets kind of situation
Enfranchise absolute I believe that
Crew cut it white guy felt like
Shawn Kemp's going to win this thing with brick D Brown in for novelty cuz he's tiny I don't know
I think the fix was in
Was a menace on the
Throw this out there
An anti-white narrative
I already stopped
All right look
Noah's race necessarily comes into it I'm not a hundred percent making that argument but I am saying
I'm saying that there was something going on
It was not in Rex Chapman
Make sense cuz if you look at those dunks
On paper
Let me tell you something
Stern
Stern would never allow a white dude into the Donkey
It said can't have detlef schrempf
Shrimp
He could.
Undoubtedly
You get that off my chest 91
Only and laptop
I was surprised
Alright
Memphis he remember that do
Rick's chip is it out of nowhere Buster
Gravy dunk
All I was sleeping on Rex Chapman
Rex Chapman was a great dunker is like saying Christian Laettner was
The Dream Team
Like that is not
Basketball game
I know a lot
On the Charlotte Hornets
Brent and a grandma Ma
Music
See now we need Alex Jones clips of him talking about basket
If Rex Chapman ever goes on Kerry Cassidy
That's the most important thing we're going to ever do
I didn't want to talk about Alex Jones
Are we doing we've got a Project Camelot episode
Video of the week here on now on your Monday episode
So I give a shout-out to one of our listeners
Nia Long
Do this episode of project
I don't watch it all the
God
She did because
Holyshit
Alright
Going on tonight at 8
Right now
But also
Before we do that
It's important for me to
Weave reference
What's this
Kerry Cassidy
It's a bit of an anti-semite
This is brought to my attention by
Keegan and I appreciate him dropping that along
Here's a clip to back that up
This is Robert David
Feel on
Rather than
And I distinguish between anti-zionism
An anti-Semitism which is absolutely despicable
And under no circumstances
We have 9 million loyalty Cinemark
America in every single one of them
Patriots
And not part of the problem
Okay
Well that's quite a blanket
Statement
Because of your enthusiasm for you know the
The Jewish race call it what you will
Sign is
I won't go into it now
Anti-semitism
There's nothing defensible there
It's not egregious
Horrific
Just yet
It's
You are not wrong
There are nine million loyal Jews America
And she was like
And that's not a good that's not a good response to that
She just be like
Great
Even like now I think it's more like 8.5
Do you know a lot of
People are losing religion these days
All because of REM
Salute
Robert David
Steel
Says
Cassidy
I will
Oh no I read it it says feel the Holocaust
Zionism an AP
Guilt by association
Are you saying
That Zionism
And a pack
In his eyes
Are guilty of the
Pushback for how I answer that question about the Holocaust
He's referencing here he's asked about the Holocaust
Responded
Not great
Both praise and push back for how I answered
Mystify the Holocaust
What's the carefully distinguish between
How much is everybody
Is Duty reprehensible
Had to put an end to the
American Israel public affairs committee aipac
An agent of a foreign power by definition
Another term has on Congress
Here's my personal take
On both the history and the
The present
Bullet point one
The Holocaust happen
Great
I'm sure that immediately following that
He says
And everything that we learn from history is accurate and perhaps
Maybe
Racism towards the Jews is not a good idea
Millions died however there are several
Celebrate
To be challenged
A boy
Those who died did not die from gas
This includes those in prison camps most of
Starvation
Typhus
Although
People did die for
I feel like
I don't need to beg a little bit how it was just
Killed most of them in the
It's not accurate
A lot of other disrespectful
Okay Barbie and the Roma people were also
Targeted for extermination
But Hitler's Army and ideology
But this is
Business
He's in our like right in front of us
Have happened in the world
Good point that's a whataboutism I'm not I'm not a fan of it
The owner other Jenna
Besides in mass murders
Is itself despicable
Genocide of the Native Americans
Drew
It said by some to
The Jews
No one's hands are clean in this matter
Fair enough
Right I mean many of the
The story has been told
Many of the ideas
That Hitler originally
Surprise by America
America caused the Holocaust
That's a very different
America
Did their own
Yeah he goes on to talk about our scientists are responsible
4 people dying in
The Holocaust
That's not
Did not have to die
Ultimately was responsible for the suffering of the Jew
Jews in labor
It was the elites Zionist Jews themselves
This goes back to the narrative that they didn't pay everybody out
Now we're into
You're on the list by friend
Hey I'm at the separation of the Jewish race from the palace
Is a distortion of reality
Scale
Look I am in summer
They supported Trump they're not great
Who is the monster
He is a f****** horrific human being
Israel is an AR parts
These are true things
But also
Let's leave the Holocaust out of disgust
Sing those things let it inform Wyatt
Relations with Israel
And maybe reducing it to Zionism versus anti-zionism
Is not the way to go
Look
What I'm saying
Good steel is
Lacoste minimizer
Anyways
Absolutely
You do
Who are in the camp
Swing together
Further evidence that we've got some
Problems
Lexi
She's not there
Spider
It's concerning that there are those
There's so many of those people
Who
Almost
Like gateways
Is harder antisemita
Everybody's responsibility
And it's a very short
Senor like
Yeah yeah yeah
Oh boy
Why I think
Robert Davi
Steel may have been
The Dukes show
So anyway
Way to bring us down in the in the
Forefront of a Project Camelot
Most of our time in Project Camelot
I looking at
How stupid
Believing the lies of
Murder accessory Mark Richards
About savvy
I feel like we've also learned
The people were fighting
Spiders or something like that
Spider leadership
Yeah the spider leadership was in effect
Of course video
Sit down
I just breaking down the news baby she's just breaking down
Regular
And this came out about a week ago or so
Take a note
Is not good
Let's just jump in how she begins with a
Project Camelot and well I've got a
Strange
John today
Anyway I wake up every morning
Can feel a strange going on right now
If you ever refer to things as goings-on
It's the same thing with like bedfellows
You never said strip
Strange fellows
Perhaps
Because you're so bad at Scrabble and I'm awesome
Alright
But I told you last night I never lose twice
Game theory behind how you will never lose to me again
Alright
Okay alright
I was going to be having a conversation with
Robert David Steele
Initiated it with me however then found out
He is not supposed to cover anything to do with space
Obviously
Things in space
Space
He is not going to be able to join us after all
I'm here on my own
Yeah
If you consider we're in space right now
Robert
Kodak
Jewelry
Atmosphere
We supposed to be there
Clearance
To talk about these things
Robert David Steele
Pretending that they have handlers
And if they work for the CIA had it like that
To get into a narrative
I assumed
This is what they're doing is like
I don't want to talk more about these bars Bass
People are clowning on me
I don't want to do it
Zoe pretend
The higher-ups have said
You got it
Too hot
Can't talk about that
I will put forth by
Possibility though
Please don't let your possibility
Actually working today
Rihanna is a limited hangout okay
I got to cancel I got another thing and Carrie has to
Robert canceled because it has
To be a conspiracy so it's
He's not allowed to come on the show
Right yeah that's possible you could pick up
The kids from soccer
Didn't let in my office
James
He's not in studio
We do get a celebrity appearance
Actual celebrity.
To start off with
Obviously there's been a recent
Disclosure Announcement by Tom DeLonge
And for those of you who know you're with that news I suggest you just
Last name he's a member of
I think a band
And
The band is called
Blink-182 jumpstart mailman
The quote that one of their contemporaries
I was close but no cigar
Blink-182
I know but it's
Still somehow funny it is funny
Especially
Talking about aliens in space
4 years
I missed it for a very long time
Not authorized to talk about it
Those are not authorized to talk about growing up anymore I absolutely.
I think they're not around anymore
Who cares
They shouldn't have been around
Disclosure
I need trying to
To get alien
Truce
Pushed out
A Blink-182 dude is like
Tom DeLonge
So I am calling upon
Right to release
Alien ship
He started to work with some people
She thinks they're very credible
And I have news for her
They're not
And I don't know the music
So I apologize for that
He has gotten very involved in this whole disclosure story and so he is
Pharrell
Standing up with a couple of
Well
Get ready for one of my favorite names
That I have ever heard on this show
With several
Sort of Heavy Hitters you might say
And they're doing something called to the stars in this is an organization he's starting
What's going on on the planet
To do with
Developing free energy
Really I would say is
An illustrious
Scientist
2 is
Hold on one second cuz I've got a whole list of
Stuff here for
Or who's involved
It's helped Rudolph is one of the main people involved and I I don't apologize minute
Have to be searching around live talking here because of God
Information in a lot of different places
There's a gym semi vanhoose come forward and has supposedly been working for the CIA
Although damn Smith
A person who is
Somewhat read into some degree on the secret space program
Is it contested whether or not Jim semivan isn't who he says he is
Mr Porter
This supports the theory of nominative
Determinism
Look you got to live with that
Secret agent name
My mom was there an autobus
Weather need to go
Delightful
This is good as Rex
Chapman
Quite frankly
Sammy van my ass
Jim's
She's working
With Tom DeLonge also
Bite me
Chirp chirp
Yes
Already already we discovered
I love the narrative
I love it
I take it another day
Together a super team of scientists
Might be an imposter
Absolutely
I love it
Real facts nothing is more of a Raptor name
They could be they could take the really good lyrics
Also she mentioned that
Plague
So do you want to know about him
Yes I do
He isn't
PhD in electrical
Engineering
Realty
Or like a Saigon
Everything I can tell he's a real PhD
I don't know I didn't call this
So he got involved in like
Some weird s***
Throughout his life
His credibility is
Is a little credit
Nitrate
He was part of this
And the DIA funded
Program
That we're trying to
Investigate paranormal
Ability
So they did a study on people like URI Geller
Including URI Geller
Subway
Really bent
Well it's Rudolph and Russell targ
Who was his authority
They became king
Keller I had genuine psychic powers
However
Sleight of hand
Was working
For the CIA
What are you doing magic
He's doing close-up Magic
So he's a dumb
He's a dumb guy
Is trying to work
Jordan's most people believe at least at this point is pseudoscience
Courseview stuff that's being explored
Zero Point Energy electromagnetic field low-energy nuclear reactions
Working on all this stuff
With his company called Earth Tech International
Soap
Earthtech were granted US patent 5845000
M220
Odel-ay
The case of getting him
This patent
Even though what he's
It's not real
The cases used for educational purposes
Patent law
As an example of a valid path
Where quote
The lesson of the pooch off Pat
Is it a world where both types
Two patents are more and more common
Even a competent examiner may fail to distinguish innovation
Pseudoscience
Cakes
Let's go
Write as an example of
Everybody's full of s*** but you can call it
That whatever
So
Doesn't mean that you act
Actually have to do anything
You can patent
Like
The thought of
Have a good day
Right
For the CIA that the URI Geller was legit
Patent
Bulshit patent
In educational
Stop
Beetle
Magical engineering just do any electrical engineering
I think you did for a bit
Here he worked with and invented
Turnable lasers and electron
Devices in
Yeah
Do those actually work or they are they magic to
I don't know
So we're talking about
Character who can make something really cool also
Sex Magic
Right right but I think his version of crazy as a little worse
Generally speaking
Jack Parsons gay
Rudolph
LG for a little bit
Yeah
I love the players
We got
The lead singer of Blink-182
Gym Sunnyvale
Help Rudolph who is a disaster and also not about a real person
We also have been in Blink-182
Is Mark Hoppus in disguise
Unclear
I'm so
It is the good news is
And her life
Kerry Cassidy is a little bit suspicious
For the first time ever and I think it's because she's
He's getting a lot of attention but she's not knows all the truth
Reggie
Singer of the band coming in
Brett come lately I've been studying nonsense
Maybe she does know who Blink-182
I don't know
Yeah even knows who those guys are
She start singing All the Small Things
Elaine outside her feeling
They're choosing one
UFO encounter at
And pretending
This is an unidentified flying object
Can I have to tell you that the secret space program
And as a result the people that are on this panel I have to give them credit to pee at least knowledgeable
About the speaker
Space program and I can tell you that they know
Exactly
Most likely
What kind of crafts
Where it comes from
So it's not really a UFO it's not really an unidentified
Aerial threat
Alessandro
Jasmine Elizondo
Is the security guy
Exclaiming on that video
It's unfortunate but you have a disclosure with lies
Interesting
I don't know how to deal with
I don't know how to deal with Carrie
Saying that somebody is lying
I can understand
Sent
Bullet journals
That's good so confusing to me because like
You're able
To think that something's Ally
Hi
How how do you not exercising your brain when you go to the prison
Who is hangs out with Raptors
Crazy
Everybody has blind-spot
Everything is a blind spot for her
In the world of music as well
I'll be honest though like I do think that it's right
To question everything
Gym Sunnyvale
Murderer is fine brightright
Boy
I don't know how to tell you
Kerry Cassidy
Edit
This clip is just a a deterioration
Of literacy
So what is my premise here
This is
That all of them
Every single thing you're hearing all the false Flags
Fires in Northern California
Las Vegas happening
You name it
All is the results
Body itching
Who are now coming forward I believe
And not just one race although the evidence I have is only about One race which is the ref
Richards
The bottom line is that if you
Look at the news and you do not consider the ET side of it you do not consider that are
Military
Is at war with various teaching races
Has been
Sometime in the rain
The testimony of William Tompkins he will see very quickly
Workhorse
Aspirus from aldebaran
Reptilians as well
Who were helping
At least at the time of William Tompkins
She's really not giving mammals much credit it's always reptile
Erase of extraterrestrial marsupials
Don't forget some Alex Jones in here
Spiders
That's great
Vietnam
Is it just because we
Mammal to be cute
Yes
Is that why they can't
A hundred percent absolutely there's been a distrust
An uneasy truce
Personify all these like really scary things as
Blizzardy I mean
There's a lizard eat next to him
Pennywise
He looks a little cute
You're a cutie
If you did not work picking up all the
Jesus bear
What is that the fires in California
Are part of alien
Also Volkswagen
Yeah
Something-or-other
A little confused perhaps
CI because later she
Cheap T-shirts switches up what you
Actually like
Alright but now it's like their fault
Aliens are pushed
For disclosure
Cuz we won't do it and there's multiple races but she only knows about one knows about the one
We have established
That Richards is an unreliable narrator
Are the good guy
In theory I'm not ready to go that far
Prevalence
But anyways
Contribution to the secret space
Aerospace program Syracuse
Aerospace
Oh I wanted to say that
Canva little bit and I don't I don't know enough about him I don't know
To do a deep dive on it but
Looking at him and some of these other people who come into our sphere
Because of Project Camelot
It turns out
It's much
Easier than you think
To say bulshit in front of Congress
It turns out Vicky
Congressional Record is full of people like VIP
Being races from Draco
Helps control
Exact
It's not space weapon
Climate change
Making everything really dry in California
Other
NASA Apollo Landing
Cetera
Don't even back in those days we were being helped by teens
That means
When I say in Chinese
Races.
Some of which may reside
Inside the Earth
And some maybe an underground
Faces
Some of those things may consider Earth their home
Or I can then of course the wind staff on out to the various Galaxy come from
Galaxy Quest
And of course
Chilean
Hybrid
And they are causing
Great deal of problems
Here on Earth
And they of course we're backing the Nazis back in the day
Yeah
Reptile chimeras
Are hybrids
But it's similar their similarities to the narratives that we see
You know Alex
I've had David icon that's David Icke
To a T
There is much more overlap it's probably would like
If he watched if he wants her show
And actually listen to it and was like
I think she's onto something I think you have to be like
She was alone
Before we go any further
Carrie cast
How do we feel about ghosts
Feel better how do I feel about it
Did she ever talk about
Or is she like hard sci-fi and ghost
Let me tell you
Knowing literally nothing
Yeah
No guarantees
Okay
Alright
Reptile
Sure
Yeah how do they hunt
The different than a regular by protecting chalk
Africa
It's not that you're sleepy
Send a text with
When does Mexico's we get to hear a little bit more about Nazi
Okay
Of course if you followed the work of Jim Marrs in
Joseph Farrell you
These are both people who have been on Alex Jones Show
Will know that the 4th Reich is alive and well
Kudos to Jim Morris you did pass on
Contributed
What the people
Behind the scenes
Understandably
To the Stars this organization started again by Tom DeLonge
Which is currently doing some disclosure
Do the rabbits
Complexcon
The disclosure
But he's trying to push
Aliens
You just keep screaming about aliens
It's bigger priority for it's like me doing stand-up
Psychiatrist
Or aliens are to Tom DeLonge
I've been writing anti-music
This whole time in the Raptors finally took him down
Cuz they got to the other members of Blink-182
The girl at the rock show
Take off your pants and jacket
Raptors don't wear jackets
You know what else
Bruce Springsteen is because Raptors age differently
Baby dude equation figure out
How about chili in human years of course
Computer kill you
Number one
Stupid
If his next Clipper we get today
This isn't part of necessity one imagines because I don't think they will have the blessing of
Car stop
That means that they've got the Illuminati side
The side that is run by a probably
Predominantly statement
The other side of which may be considered as the bush cabal or Rockefeller
Weather in
The overlaps Manhattan
Who are Satanist within those groups and who are just
Nazi
For a fascist however you want to turn them
Jason queer and alliances
You know that the speaker
Space program is orchestrated in large part
Individual
So Satanist okay
This is Alex Jones
I mean you just replace aliens with
Globalist
Three-quarters of the way there
Little do you know why
I will explain
Exactly why
Episode
Does she believes in Israel
She must
Cuz he's worried about that
Are you can be worried about sickness without actually believing cannot can I ask you to put a pin in that question for a couple clips
Because I think I did actually I might be able to answer that
Belize
As a very literal be
I feel like Harry would have to go space with
They say
Literally fell from the heavens
Exactly
Biscuits into the child traffic
Fitness agenda
DuckTales perfect
If you think about it
With The Reptilian agenda
Here
And having to do with
Second energy
Killing humans
Using bear
4 aphrodisiacs excetera and
Official time
Exercises
Combination
As I say
The agenda of the sickness
Coincide
Say Nazi side of things
The more vampiric
This is Alex Jones ship
This is globalist
Stop this is exactly what Alex believes about the globalist
That they
Cortland what have you
What is it that all crazy people are crazy in the dumb way
And it seems very similar way
Is all archaic
December 10th
It's bloodline
Big butt that's why Kerry Cassidy
Appear on
On paper
To be very
She is exposing
Secret space program
Spider leadership and what-have-you right Alex Jones
War against white dude
And we got to stand up for our virility
And the reason they can come together
Because the villains that they've chosen
In the case of Kerry Cassidy it's reptoids and all that
Define characteristics
And their motivation
Are based
Archaic anti-semitism
That is all
Old-timer
Demonizing slaughtered
Super cool with having some Allegra
So if there are people out there who don't know
Further proof that the reptoids are actually the good guys because in real life
Are the good guys
Let's be cool
So if you guys out there don't know what blood libel is
You are living in a
Medieval England with the death of William of Norwich
William was a twelve-year-old Tanner the
Guess who's killed in 1144
At the time
Of his death
The parents accused the local Jewish community
Responsibility
But investigation
Convert field
6 years later
Thomas of Monmouth
A Benedictine Monk
Decided to investigate
Sensationalize the murder
Leon anti-Semitic
Sensationalism
He wrote A martyrdom account
The life and miracles of William of Norwich
Hey Richie said the local Jews acting is a part of the internet
An international
Conspiracy
Crucified the young boy is part of a ritual to reclaim
Control of the Holy
Heard that one
From Alex
Monmouth work was used
To Garner financials
Support from pilgrimages
To the boy's grave and laid the foundations
For the bloodline
Similar stories crop up throughout Europe in the Middle Ages
A company by episodes of violent retaliation towards
Jews
Illegal trials about
Especially during the Crusades
Stories were used to justify progress
In the case of the disappearing
Year-old Simon of Trent
In March 14th
Scene 75
The entire Jewish Community was arrested
15 men burned
Mistake after being forced
To confess under torture
Until tonight
65 Simon of Trent was regarded as a
Catholic Church
Throughout history
Great-great-grandson of Simon of Trent
History the specifics of the blood libel varied and expand
It primarily involve the baking of Christian blood in Passover matzah
Early accounts also occasionally describe the
No children the poisoning the wells in the US
Social
Christian blood
Do yokuts
From circumcision
It should go without saying that these lurid stories and older manifestation
Are patently on
True ohyeah
So is it is important there is
This is all this stuff
The calyx does it on his show
Carrie does it on her show
The ideas
Evil forces
Maybe we want to drink their blood
All that's what I said use them in rituals
All dates back to this blood libel
Mob mentality cuz it's it's very it's very
It's effective
It's an attractive proposition to
Every
A group
Yeah because then
Then you have a very clear-cut enemy and once you defeat that animates
All of your problems go away
How many problems you have
You never have to actually deal with the
Probably just blame them on somebody else
Yeah a personal responsibility that is mine
From
Another
The point about that
These accusations
Affected
Strike at the heart of society
These fears about outsider
Yeah
The destruction
To the public research
Wells
The presence of
Secret organizations
Ascites
So the other things are that we bring in
Format
Archaic anti-semitism
I mean who knows if we can find a great example of Kerry Cassidy doing
Better than the fluoride in the water narrative no
ADI global
Fluoride in the water is one
100% the grandchild
Much like Jim semi van around
Poison well
In order to kill Christian
It's completely in nonsensical
And Alex bases all of it on
Harvard study
Video always goes back to
Harvard study that came out
Dropsy
I did a little bit looking into
This was a 2012
Study of study
Their works
Couple researchers
At Harvard
They compiled 27 studies that had already been done
About fluoride
But they were all from
China
All the studies were from China
That's not to say there's anything wrong with China
To say that the rates at which they have fluoride
Very different than America
People who did the study
Came out and said this is not applicable in America has nothing to do with the
Water
Fluoridation here
And in fact everybody at Harvard
Every professor of
History and all that s***
All of them came out and said that they saw
Water fluoridation
Fred
The meta-analysis of all of these studies
And then they were like hey
America has the right level of fluoride in their water
Don't go too far with Flora is a scientific reality that if you have
Too much
If you have a credit card to buy belt buckles
Is there a water is probably not going to go well for also
Their paper
All the time
This passage
Each of these articles reviewed at deficiency
In some cases
Limitless
Conclusion that can be drawn
That's in the paper that Alex's
Was trying to say
Disapprove
Archaic anti-semitism
He's so swing by the protocols of the Elders of Zion
Cassidy
Sick and tired of these goddamn anti-semite
Why
Everywhere
What else do we got to do it so it's so frustrating because again
You go back 100 years ago back to the Medieval ages and you hear the same dumb s*** that you do now
That's what I'm saying
That's what I'm saying if you guys want to
It's up some stuff
F****** get created
Giving Infowars advice
Switch it up baby
Don't do this blood libel poisoning the well just come up with something new
I don't know how you would
Betty White
Security Cassidy and Alex Jones both live in the same arcade
Semitism well and they refused to get out of it
I think has
Something fun
There are other races
Such as
Let's see if
You would say the Mantis beings are mantids also there are
7 Dragon Ball
Has come to the fore a lot of races
Even unknown and I would say that's true
Space program as well not sure what that sentence means
Minted
We got Dragon Ball
Cuz
I got to be honest
That's my favorite thing ever
What's it what's a dragon
Is the dragon monster real
I mean what do you think
To be as aggressive
What the f*** you think if they're real
Why can't no I mean we have we have mantises
Romanticism extraterrestrial mantis
It could be a regular thing
You mean like maybe just like
Play coming to us from outage
Dragon Ball Z
Very well bye. I don't know
But I looked you appreciate her heard trick
As opposed to Alex
She does not provide
Over over example
Both know she goes
Mantids
Dragon moth
Etc
You got it
You got the game after that
What else is there to say
What you get mansion
And Dragon Ball Z
The whole game is upright we already have spiders
Mantis creatures
Get create
Right
Evil
Erase
Like button
Play crystallize later like maybe the entire Earth
The Earth velour still on bugs bro
Is actually
Caterpillars
I'd eventually Earth will explode
Not because of human intervention
Climate change
But because
The dragon boss finally over
The climate change
Nothing is actually
I'm trying to get out of that slump
Moth alien
And what I can learn about
Marysville
Versions of Godzilla versus Mothra
Pharoahe Monch song Saima
Says
Play Godzilla verse
Vs Mothra theme song
Very
Aggressive
It's been there since
The beginning I got to do a big fight about
A couple people have said in the past
Just
Godzilla March
Specifically the 14-month
And I do know that for a fact
Everyone
Go fly a moth shaped
A dragon
I respect
That
I'm a little bit worried that you've gotten into multiple sites
Probably with the same person memories a little hasty
I can't cuz I'm right I will not let go of any Pharoahe Monch or wreck
What's the temperature
Cyclopedia of alien race
Good
Okay so there's a there's a
That's all
You know there's a
People are going on
Call Olga Hog Wild about there being a moth
Chicago
So that's hot
That's a Hot Topic there we go
So other than mine are largely subbed
Geranium
Pterodactyl like humans
Like wings
Some shows are not really related to Mott's at all
Sometimes
Describe dispossessing horns
The dusk
Considered very similar to the traditional depicts
The devil
According to
Certain individuals with encounter
Although I was referred to as Mothman
Might be a little missile
Also
Mothman Ark
Considered
Draco alien
The leader is the reptilians are the Draco
They
I even have special wings
Flaps of skin
Supported by long ribs
These can be folded back against the body
They're also known as the dragon race
And their symbology usually they're also known as the Mothman
Soldier class
Of the species and the quote
I a
So
Look at the dragon boss
Is fun
She's really just describing draco's as a different name
Talks about draco's that's not new
Exciting
Based on the fact that they're in
Chicago might be real
Might be real
That's possible and this might be what she
Thanks a bunch
Of the devil
Cuz they're awesome
Describe
Alright so sickness
Don't worry
Satan
The Draco Dragon Ball super
Oh boy
But in his next clip carry list off a bunch of fakes
Technologies that she has
Uncovered
The ability to tap into things
Innocence is being talked about things like
Certain
Zero Point Energy
So
There is so much out there
Call disease
Capriccio
This is Randy Cramer
So
It's an endless
Secret space program
In almost no time of paying
Mention to her
We have been able to figure out where these narratives come from
Trackdown the sources of them
And find out how bogus they are
Between like in Cliff's you talking about how boot off earlier this episode
And Randy Cramer
But he still has a GoFundMe up for
When are we going to get into gym minivan
That's alright that's our headliner
Do minivan
No longer employed
I don't know you real
What are Perry Cassidy is ripe
Well I could borrow one
Carrie gets it right
I found it I found like a
Google and look for Jim minivan
Can find if you wrote a forward to a book
Reclaimed wood works
For the CIA for
All right I don't know anything about the
And I have no idea
That supports his claim that he works for the CIA but I have him hang out with Jim photoglo
Musician to photoglo
Hey Jim.
The gym
How many people work for the secret space program
Their infrastructure must
It's got to be
They're doing everything
The everything
Complex work any of them how is it that it hasn't gotten out like there has to be home
Recipe whole planned communities built around the secret
Space Program I think our next episode is probably going to be about Andrew basiago
The Project Camelot
I was I was
Listening to a lecture that he gave the other day
And it's f******
Wild stuff
He's
Origin story
Is that when he was a kid
His dad
Who may or may not have been a little bit of a booze guy
He showed him
A paper
You right
This info
40 years
It came back in time you might you have to
Study this
In order for him to write it
In the future
Call Lisa
I meant to get the time traveling with Barack Obama
Back with his name
It's great
Alright everybody
He's a lot of fun
I'm in so
Anyway
What was the point
I think it's dead
Bitlife that
MetroPointe energy
I liked
2 described as
Provided
You can just have like some water like right here on the table
And it Powers every
Right okay
Yeah she's into
Conspiracy
Explain the whole Japanese whaling 100% are absolutely
Raptors
They're too cute totally
Turn into current events
She said she was
I'm going to get into current events
Really at all very Alex Jones
Cersei
For background to this information I've given you
He must watch
The Project Camelot interviews especially watch with sweater called whistleblowers
Disciplinary
And so what you can do is learn a great deal
By adding and connecting the dots
And this is really all I'm doing it's not rocket science
Easy to do
But what I find is that most people out there regardless of how much study they do
And this includes Mike
So-called calling
Do not have the ability to
Connect the dots because they are not paying
Attention
Especially
To some of the most important Witnesses out there
It has to do with
Obviously
People like William Tompkins people like Mark Richards Captain Mark Richards
So I've interviewed in prison
Reminder she believes she has a personified spaceship
Minerva
Chocolate
Camelot
And many many more
Another word for obviously
Store in attics
Thriller
Beginning
Story until now
Then you don't understand
What is happening
You do not understand what is going on when the Illuminati decide
Splat operation
Decide to test a weapon such as they are doing in Northern California
Certain areas of
Campground
Sort of a slash-and-burn mentality
Which is what they've done
Santa Rosa area
You do not understand the bigger picture
You don't understand why they're doing this
And so you can't even believe
That they are doing it that it's being orchestrated
She just said no
She doesn't say
C clearing off land
But here's the thing makes it a lot of metaphors and then also at the same time confusing like
These
So-called
People who have
What you would call
Stuff to do
Sings
Like
What you would call
Going outside
No you don't need to pad with so many words like right
We can use language
It's tough
Itstototime
The.
Figure out what the
The through-line is there go back look
See if there are more.
And if you can't connect those dots
You don't even know why fires happened Dan
At this point
Fire is a false flag by the Illuminati
At this point I don't know what it. Is
Hey hey here's a. I've connected archaic anti-semitism
So there's that
Weird
Problem comes in
To this like what is being
Psycho
It's going to fall apart pretty tremendously when the everything
Gets rebuilt
Hello
The argument is probably not very valid
You know
We live off the land where they took
It's reused probably exact same way
Also it works well because it creates
Jobs
Everybody knows
Set the best
Contractors
Are the spider leadership
No Doubt
Somebody they can
Spin their own
With silken they started going straight
Undoubtedly
Drywall
Start
Spinning Brick Mason spiders
Right of course
She doesn't believe has provided of course
Cardboard
She doesn't believe that
Are the fires
Are real or legit
Vegas is
A controlled situation
Orchestrated
That it was not alone gunmen
That Paddock is
Appearances
Manchurian Candidate
And it's even possible that he
We got to look
Below the surface
In a deeper way than what's going on on YouTube right now
People have to start understanding
That our military has been fighting with various races Avicii
Behind the scenes
And that these ETFs have the ability
To wipe the mines
Connect
Your Consciousness in such a way
If you do not recall seeing them and this goes for soldiers on the battlefield
Hat
Christy Moore about that
Whether it's the reptoids
Who are building Stargate
In the Middle East
The reason there is
Constant battle going on in the Middle East
At least partially
Because they are
Very much you there
Israeli
Many loyalties
Is to alien
Isis is controlled by alien
That makes as much sense as anything else
Sure
Really
Let's face it
They're very obvious like it's just
It's just that this team so far out there but is there any difference between aliens or God
Not really
Is this any Dumber
Minerva is your flying than a congressman holding up
Climate change isn't real but hear me out on this
Which is just like
More familiar with certain types
The crazy Asians for religion are much more simple
They're usually needed fall back on God works in mysterious ways
She's got to come up with
Like Byzantine organizations in order to rationalize
Isis being controlled by aliens
But
Stupid
Much more amusing
Is because of the
Explain thing
Or else probably like
You're making this up that's what happens now because we're whistleblower
I guess there are people who had like
Near-death experiences
That's what the this is what happened whenever science
Actually worked
Like this is the issue with all of these crazy
And it's the same thing that happens with with God people now trying to explain why Evolution isn't real
Right
These were planted by God to test your faith
These different
Eve ever more complicated explanations
In order to just
Justified the belief in something
Nothing stupid break Eli
We figured it out
Boring
Even though it's
And Incredibly exciting and magical thing that we know stuff it has to be
Ridiculous
You're expressing something that I think you'll agree
With what Carrie says
Beginning of this
Connect the
Circles of dots with
No I think you agree with the first sentence
Sylvester and that everything else
Is it really
Do a vote for
4Health
Of the human race
Wonderful really the effort is
To help people understand that if there are battles going on
Eons
For eons with the Anunnaki
In the Middle East
And other races
Why we are at odds with a Ron
And the races
That arawn
Is associated with
And why we are actually already at war with North Korea
Because North Korea has been back
By certain erase
And our real war is with that 80 race
And not necessarily the North
Korean
So this is what we have to start to understand
I mean if you just take away the alien race and put globulus
Standard
Large live
I have
So boring of one level
DaVinci's racist against
Imaginary
Racism is bad
Even if it's made up
What does it matter
The Harvard bias against
Alien races
Frustrated
It rolls off me like water off a duck
But it's just look I know it's low on issue
Problems feel like you should be racing
Anyway
Like maybe
Maybe Carrie
If you acknowledge that all of these
People are individuals
Perhaps
Maybe Raptors are not one monolithic black
Maybe these are people maybe it's the spider leadership that that
Because you not spiders
It's not that we're at war with North Korea we're at war with North Korea's government
The North Korean people are wonderful people should not do human eyes them
I say that they're just part of
I honestly think that might be what you
You trying to
Express
In some way or another the idea that the
The dictatorship that's in place
In North Korea is
Alien
Peaceful
Okay
I don't think
But she understands
That might be what you trying to say
Because she really believes that they were aliens pulling the strings
And what are you
Who is the world is
Rough
It's rough out there right now
And it's complicated
It's very difficult
Except
In the case
Alexa Las Vegas
Shooting
Right
There is
The potential Within
Humanity
To be a dictator and oppress your people
There is
Potential
Within humans
Have
Centuries long conflicts Regional
Between ethnic groups
Between
Different
Population
Raticate is possible that is what we come from
That's the route
Humanity that's not like
Aliens making us do it
But it's so much more comforting
Deseo it's aliens
Talking Tom 2
Realized
But for the grace of God that could be
You know doing all these things
Possible
Circumstances could be Vivid like
You know
You born differently
Episode of this podcast
I know everything about Alex Joseph
That's right
I know everything about Raptors alternate universe
I thought about hiring people to kill things right
It I have
I was trying to move on
Just apathetic comfort
You know a lot of these dudes
I think they ended up living not great
Live not the lies that they wanted
Backstory app
A secret Soldier for 50 years
Protecting the solar Guardian
Or whatever and miraculously I was put back into my 18 year old body 15 minutes later
Some dead-end jobs
I'm not really all that interesting I made it to middle management
I mean here I am I'm single at 50 and
I guess I meant I like I like Star Trek
Like I have some
Comparisons in my life but
I-i've amounted
It's not really anything
The changes the world
Much more fun
To say that the other bike store
Two-faced became king of America
The guy in San Francisco
The earlier like the midday
American music
Got to hear this guy out
Eventually
So what he would do if he was like a panhandler
Do people love it
Human money I saw
Call Edwin
Soaking and when he died there was a huge procession in like 20,000 people came out to watch
Celebrity early San Francisco celebrity
Creating this fantasy world
Checks out I don't know in Columbia Missouri there was a guy who declared himself King as well
Street drunk
Burger King crown
Declared himself the king of Columbia
All right now I like that the police routine
I would just take him out
Cityline
The the
It would be called
Just the border of Columbia
Go to another time
Not yet we don't have charges to press get out
Right
Disagreed with that to their policy quite a bit
Absolutely
He would have become
I think a lot of people.
A lot of people
It's great
We started the show by Kerris explaining that Rob
Get today
Get to close it up by her talking
The fact that Robert David Steele was unable to join me on this broadcast in spite of the fact
This information before the broadcast
Keep within full Consciousness about it
However he
Got direction from outside one can imagine
Knowing that he is a member of a certain group
And he is himself
Working as a good guy
Really
To disclose certain information but he has found that the
As we say the secret space
The real story about the ET intervention here on planet Earth
It's something that he's not allowed to
Elaborate on in spite of the fact that he did go on Alex Jones and allude to it
And he never backed off
He understood there to be ten thousand humans on Mars who are never coming home
Some of them were sent there as children
So this is the kind of information
That if you do not put that together
With things like the fires in
Northern California
Which obviously is a directed-energy weapon
It appears that maybe a laser-based
Directed energy weapon
Maybe the issue is that it's
Not a direct
Hey it's just a while
Right
Caused by a drought
The years-long drought
Drying everything out
Wendy's wildfires that I have happening there
Usually from
Somebody accidentally
Do you know setting a fire right or camping
Lightning strikes
Illegitimate part of the ecosystem like we would
Have sequoia trees if it weren't for
Right like there is there is a natural
Contain them
Not
Like try and Destroy them
The problem is
We can't contain the
Anymore
Bright
It's not a laser
Yeah
He was like
Nah
Cuz if you said she sent him the information that you wanted to talk about
He would have read that in Dragon Ball
That's too far even for me
Robert
Things I'm still trying
Yeah I can't come along on this ride with
Steve Perry
Whoa
Lady you are nuts
Yeah
Robert Davis
Bastille I'm pretty comfortable saying
He is
Barely
Dubious
I am probably a medic
I don't want to say out in out
He is just
Because
I don't think that
I don't think it's
He's trying to skirt the line of
He's playing games
Yeah and I think the reason is because he
Some are not true
He's attracting
And perhaps cording
But not necessarily diving whole-hog into
Is unfortunately
Whether or not
The clip that we played at the top
The show is as dammit
Feel
The stuff the world
View the blood libel
Is clearly indicative of where
What you believe
And it is
Boy alex
104 so if you want another one of those things like
Just like Alex
Robert Davis
Stihl insist he's not
Zionist
Call different
That don't do that
No I am
I'm not blanketly agreeing with these people
Amongst all of the clips that we have he goes
You are often right about everything and I have nothing to disagree with you about
It's just you have your words wrong
Drew say global
A lot of stuff is there was better evidence
For some of the stuff
Play cuz it's it's not impossible that someone ever
And it's not it's not impossible that like I've seen
I've seen Batman Begins I know that there is like
There is of course
What's this
Play scarecrow this possibility
What's the weather like those sorts of things are
Conceivably possible but you have to have better evidence
You have to have a better
To be more real or else your operating off these
Archaic beliefs
That are just bigotry
Congratulations
Congratulations Kerry Cassidy
You guys live
In a world that's
Been shaped
Buy lies
Congratulations
How
Humans are still so shity
You're dumb
I don't know
Being Human are those people who donate to wash out
I'd like to thank everyone who
Specific policy walk shout out to the other next episode
I can do that
Support the show by going to knowledge
Bizarre website
And we will be putting that 1991 Dunk Contest behind the website
Banner
Absolutely
Proof nobody knows
Nobody knows
This is been a years-long cover-up
By the Raptors
I know a little bit about myself
You can also follow us on Twitter at knowledge
Underscore fight
Look it up on Facebook.
Absolutely
People find us
We would appreciate it
Please do
There's one person
I know
Isn't
Okay
He's not a reptile
Might be a dragon mouth but I don't know about that
Definitely not romantic
No
Could be in a theory
I do I would anything about this.
Even though he's not one of those eat even though he's not one of those et's that are ruining everything even though he
He doesn't have any direct laser weapon
May the wolf
Choke on your flash
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color