Holding
Alexandra Thurston color
Everybody
But Alexander Emerick
I'm off hernia
Dixon told him not to be a mama's boy can we confirm
I can't put Jim semivan
I have no evidence
Form birth certificate
Dallas
Los Angeles
He's a trendy liberal Coastal Elite
Adizus pretending that he's a good old boy from
He does say that he's I it is genealogy
Wales
He has said that in the
Irrelevant
Doesn't matter
I know a lot about Alex Jones Welsh or pretend Wellspring
Today royalty
Wales rugby.
But he was
He has The Descendants
Of people
Long ramp but heavens
Like relatives were on the Mayflower
And also found at the Country of Texas that.
Okay
Aaron's
To the tutors and whatever
Jordan burgundy going over
Something that happened on this Sunday
This week on the
22nd
Dealing with a little bit of business
From the 23rd the Monday show
Number of walks
We got that we put up
Call the we need your help cuz I'm not going to have a job for
Pretty soon
People stepped up to the bat and I really appreciate it I want to give a shout out to
These folks
By the first of all I realized
I'm one of the live shows but I didn't end up with
So I'm going to redo a couple
They live on
In infamy
And we wind up not putting this one is dead already water
Especially foreign policy walk
I drew a level that actually embarrasses me
Send me an email and tell me what we can do for
But for now
Start until you're brilliant also
Thank you. They really appreciate you bumping up your donation to becoming a foreign policy walk
Don't get mad and tell your brother
Yeah
Another foreign policy want we love you love to give a shout out to Adam W thank you so much
Natalia brilliant also
What does playback over and over
1 1/2 hours of
What are brilliant
I also one more foreign policy wonk I like to give a shout out to our boy Jeff would out there thank you so much
Start until you're brilliant
Grapes
We really appreciate it and you know if you'd like to support the show we do
It means a lot and like I said we are going to I'm going to be on the skin of my teeth
Surviving
Doing the show
If you'd like to sport
We do appreciate it you can go to a foreign policy
The domain for form of f******
Lazy
Oh man
Video.com and put sport the show you can become a policy wonk
We would appreciate it
Business take care of before we get to
Of course
Mumps
I'm not being able to perform
It was weird
Largely unsatisfying
Spy review
To take care of
Play my second piece of business I wanted to get to came up on
Random mix
To today on Spotify
Buckhannon tattoo
I started listening to a bunch more tattoo
I realized
There's a 13-0 there's
No
Possible through line that you can
Can draw that way
Suggest that they are not
Play terrible
There's a strong people don't do enough
God's other job discussing
Write all of their songs
About how much these two guys love each other
Right and they
RV Class B
Fine yeah they're playing a role whatever I really care
The thing is
They love each other
And all of their damn songs are about how they have to run away
And it's not because they love each other and they want to elope
Because they're Russian
Right
I don't think people talked about that enough the fact it's like oh
The subtext of all these songs are
Political
Best in this fake lesbian Duo
Yeah
Yeah also they killed Kennedy
Trump is about to
It's going to come up in the episode today
If the Russians
Release the past
That means they're capable of anything
And that means
Tattoo Kilkenny
Probably
We're going to start with the Sunday
Starwood Sundays
It was kind of boring
And Alex is on a bulshit narrative
Where
This guy
This YouTuber
I released a video that he shot out the window of a hotel
A bunch of ambulance
Near the Las Vegas shooting already again
Is arguing
And the video is made to look like their people
Being who have been shot
The Hooters
Being Take It Outside
Of course
MapleStage shootings all over the place
And the reality is if you look into it
There wasn't
Right
The boss
The camera on that Hooters
All the time
Probably
Examiner
Department officials
Officers were inside the concert venue when the shooting was occurring started to direct concertgoers
Eastbound
Scooters
That's what you do when you have an act
Active shooter into
You get everyone who can walk or crawl out of the immediate area where the gunshots
Targeted
Rescue units were on scene
Play Cindy
Inside ambulance
That's why there were emerging
Medical personnel placement inside the rest
Two units who were staging at
You can clearly hear the Las Vegas
Police Department radio traffic
From the night of the shooting
When what officer tells the
Dispatcher quote
Control 3 Mary 9
I'm at the center with other offer
Here we got a lot of wounded were sending them towards the Reno side
Towards scooters
In parentheses
He's out of harm
There was also a dealer
Dammit
Agency plan is
Turned into a
Conspiracy theory
Also because because Hooters is also like
Casino in Las Vegas
And he went on the Nevada public radio on October 2nd
Gunshots outside
People were coming in
To the casino were shot and wounded
The dealer stated their bodies in front of
The casino that were just people who ran away from the venue
Who died on the
Jesus
F****** cry emergency medical personnel and police
Jeopardy to get people away from
So Alex Jones's narrative about it is just
Completely bogus and he's misrepresenting an article
Information
Ivan Ivan
My favorite
Part of the Las Vegas shooting
Is how quickly we've all forgotten about it
It's about time that a mass shooter
Goes into the NRA office
Come on man
I don't disagree I don't
Also no
Come on I don't want you to
I mean look
That are not directing all of this
But once we need to start killing the guilty
I disagree with the agency
Free of that
I understand
I think
I think that there are people who are cloistered from the effects
These things you are
Heartless because of it
And maybe if they weren't
They wouldn't be so heartless
But at the same time
I don't want you to f***
Call me Centrist because of it
I in no way encourage
Alright
Shootings towards people who are cloistered
I don't think
Not wishing death on people is a Centrist
Position you're making an example
Only person willing to get down in the mud and actually solved
Skin problems that's why this Dynamic works
Safin I guess I'll talk to do
I don't know any good outcome
That's the b******* that Alex is spinning
Episode on Sunday
Also
It's just
There's going to be another one
What is going to be another we're always we're not going to do that
Another one
How do we Act
So we solve the problem
Because all of the it's not advocating shootings at NRA offices that is not how you solved the problem
You are correct
Great I'm glad we've come to that because otherwise
Jordan
I'm sorry
I know you brought up Las Vegas
I was just do bunking something that's true
I'm just ate it's just hard for me to judge
There's so many
Doing things that nobody didn't like Puerto Rico nobody
We've all forgotten about Puerto Rico I don't think we've still have issues their Florida is still going to be
Travel FEMA is not going to get enough
Nobody is doing anything about this s***
There's nothing we really can't we're all f****** helpless
Adult
This sentiment
Watering Extreme Action
Po-boy
Is
Is I think
Understandable and I don't
Agree with that position
However
For
To play the role of Barry Manilow
Let's get on to the episode
Also he
He says that Alex gets into the JFK stop
But that'll come up later
Just got that then he's a
Full of a bunch of bulshit
But at the end of the episode
He plays a special report
Cuz I guess you just didn't want to do the whole show
Special Report
And breakdown
The goings-on
As it were
In this special report because I accidentally exposes himself
A little bit he actually he's trying to point out how much the media lies
Process
He does
Some
Horrendous spinning
I wanted to break
Take this down
Get to the bottom
Of what you
He's doing so here we go
Was just last week
President Trump making phone calls
Numbers
I'm soldiers
And others
Cavalier
Well you asked for it
Yeah that doesn't sound like him at all
No never would have believed that without without her
F****** say so
No it's already we have we have some lies
We already have
Some
Some problems
Spitting
The first of which is the idea
Congresswoman Wilson
Secretly your clandestine Lee list
Megan on the phone call
She's in the car
Yeah because she's friends with
Was calling they were in the car together. Really a clandestine
Something if you know it's not secret it's not
Sneaky it's not it's not anything of the sort is just misrepresenting that entirely
He's not
The story
He's not he's not explaining wax
Dead air
Look if I got to leave you hanging from *
Make sure everybody knows your fallible
You coming here
And then use that you f****** Shipmates
Advise
The congresswoman
Overheard this call
Because she was in the car very
Whenever you are calling someone who's
Whose family member has died
Message to just be that to their right they were a hero in this is a tragedy in my condolences sorry for you
But our president is so f****** stupid
So f****** awful
He's incapable of even basic MP
He is a legitimate site
I didn't we really need to accept
That are present
Is
A stereo
Today was lashing out at her and then
Kelly came out
And gave a speech
Yeah he's a piece
First of all
Made a bunch
Really vague
Society being better in the past
Stuff like that that one
To politicize soldiers practice that's not what
Inherently political
Unreasonable any goes on to explain
He was at
The speech that she gave it an a
FBI building
Naming
John Kelly was at the speech that Wilson
Eat his comments were that
Call me came out
Full speech
And then she got up and
That
Called Obama and got all the money
For the building to be made and he thought it was
Disgraceful
He
Understand where money comes from
No but
The idea of like I got the money to
You get this message
Has been pitching
So she's taking credit for opposed to some sort of magical
Just just the the goodness of
People's hearts
Or the necessity of the
The situation for that the FBI earned it or something
Yeah because a video of that speech has
Come out from
The ribbon-cutting has been
Unscheduled in 4 weeks
Recalled being told
The dedication is on the government's calendar
One problem
The FBI wants
The name of gorgeous edifice
At the same time
In 4 weeks
Everyone said that's impossible it takes at least 8 months
2 a year
How's the president's office
I said I'm a school
Principal and I said excuse my French ohel know
We're going to get this done
Immediately I wanted to attack
I went to the speaker
Speaker Boehner
And said Mr Speaker I need your help
BFB I need your help in
The country needs your help and we have no time to waste
Boehner went into Attack Mode
Any two days pull out pulled it out of
Committee brought it to
To the floor for a vote
Did you goes on
Excite that Marco Rubio was very helpful
It's otherwise bipartisanship
That ended up getting this done in a way that no one thought could be done right we collaborated and got the
This building named after the FBI agents who have been killed
Does not talk about how she ended up getting all the funding for the building or anything like that
Speech praising government
Actually work
Right
So at that point
Trump started lashing out today
Great I believe in her
And then the other day it came out did Mike Johnson
The lady in question who received the call
Donald
Trump she came out
I'll just
This Time magazine article about her
The Widow of a US Soldier recently died in combat
Her late husband as a hero in
Confirm interview Monday that President Donald Trump
In a condolence call center cuz her husband quotes
Knew what he signed up for
My usual Johnson who was married to Fallen Army Sergeant David Johnson
Good Morning America that her phone call with Trump made her quote cry even more
Because you said Trump apparently did not remember her husband's name
Until he had military papers in front of
The president has signed up for but it hurts anyway
Myesha Johnson said of ladavid Johnson
Call sweetheart
And it made me cry
Because I was very angry at the tone of his voice and how he said
He couldn't remember my husband's name
That's probably more than you
You know
The way he remember my husband's name is because he
He told me he had my husband's reporting
In front of him
I heard him stumbling on trying to remember my husband's name and that's what hurt me the most
Because if my husband is out here fighting for our country
And he risked his life for our country
Why can't you remember his name
And that's what made me upset and cry even more because
My husband was an awesome
Soldier
She goes on to say likewise
F*** what I make this up
Not in those words
I don't understand why this is a story
I really don't
Brooke is awful
What did you think was going to have
If it did happen well
It didn't it would be incest
There's no way that that call would have meant any
Anything no matter what
What is a meeting with call
And of course it was something that
He used to hurt
Somebody still further
Lunatic
Somehow
Because our attention spans are so terrible
Lnr media
Is I do agree with Alex Jones in this regard
F****** awful
Write this is
We have the worst
You can have the same premise of a different conclusion this possible
Unacceptable that we have such low attempt
We have to find a new way to hate Trump every single day
We've already
We done enough
Like in the
Title of this guy should be impeached
We hit it
We hit it a year ago
President
He had already committed all the crimes
So there's no reason to
You keep finding new stories
What we should be doing is every f****** day
Hammer home
There should not be any others
Stories
To just be every single day the front page
Should be gofucker
And everyday that you might not there might be a little by yourself
You should be impeached
Alright
You're coming in way too hot
You get me
My face is getting a little red
Superboy
Anymore I can't read the news
What is there to read
That's not bad there's a lot of Phillips
I want to go back
Salinger f******
It was fun
Fun dance
Define
The scream at me for
Do you know what the theory
Exhausting
You could just
You're telling me
Self-righteousness
Is hard
So at this point
What ended up happening
Not people not named Donald Trump and John Kelly doing
Right so
Now let's
The through the rest
Special Report
We can point out
Joya
I swear he's being
Completely
Bucked up
Gold Star Family
Call Dupree
Call people
I would posit that
Do you know what the outcome would be
Yeah that would be
You shouldn't do that
Look a lot of president
You
Specifically
Message robot
Mike Pence
Sure he can at least
Fame human Amo
There is a point of going to punch
Omnipod
It doesn't matter either way it's in
Insincere he doesn't give a f*** so let's get on to the next clip
This is about
Ohio Optometry board
Frederica Wilson
She's so thrilled
You mean to tell me that I've become so important
Come to the house is following me and my words
This is amazing
It's amazing
That is absolutely phenomenal
I have to tell my kids I'm a Rockstar
She's being facetious
She's saying it's ridiculous that you're paying attention
Send to me a lot of big issues to deal with
She's not calling herself a rockstar
In this special report is getting into the anatomy of deception
When he's actually
Doing hardcore
Deception himself amazing what better way
Deception
Then to MBA
I just don't think that anyone who listens to him
So here we go this is
Shut up
Manipulative liar anything
Segments of the
Entire Special Report
The world
Her butt
See through
Anyway
And then used it
So
The you think that everyone hates
Mainstream media it's all terrible no one likes it
That's all good and well
The fun games
I mean
It's kind of goes back to what you were saying another you don't have
Interest in defending
No the media.
Lost they lost any credibility with me a long time
Asleep at the wheel
Deez Nuts
They're run by the same corporate people that run the
Albuterol
Go to the research came here and show you infowars.com
For the last month
6.6
Million Global unique
Reviews
But if you see here a lot of them
Almost all of the
Come from October 2nd
3rd and
Fourth
They were up over a million views
Those days
On the 3rd and 4th
The shooting happened on October
We're first and immediately
I started spinning
How they get these
Is Peet's in there traffic
Is when something really tragic happen
They lie about
And you see you can see everyone who's watching this
Can see there are very few
And if you go through it
If you go back to the history you'll see the exact same thing whenever something
Traumatic happened
That may or may not have a racial bent to it
Because I was injecting that
It's just like it's just like gun manufacturer
They never make more money than after a match
All of their money
MSNBC
Members of the name
Here you have a
Are million Global unique hair
If you lucky
That's not enough
No it's not
It's still more of a dent out a percentage
Frightening less frightening presented is destroying all of these
Isn't the highest
I'm sure if CNN
New York Times
Is there traffic was available publicly
Like on quadcast
Utseya much
But if you look at this
Fourth
Steve like there's much more reasonable
Sun Valley
To the traffic pattern of MS
DC whereas
Alex Jones Infowars
Has almost nothing
Until some tragedy
And then
So everyone hating the MSNBC
Kind of like
Kind of b*******
And then again I also argue
Do that
Who is doing the
Politicize
That's the real question
Causation
Fallacy going on
Representative
Complicated
These people are doing
I don't
You could get it to a chicken or egg
Fingering
It's not worth it
It's a complex
And
A lot of people
If not most people
Whenever an idiot like Alex Jones
Turn that into a very simple
Narrative
They feel like well
VSCO
Sit down into a simple narrative that I can
He must be correct
Yeah same situation that all strong men
I have used throughout his
It is
I understand this system and I can
Can fix it with
MMA
Actually get into a position
To do something about it
And they realized
System
Hayden's work
To the theory in this next
Why
Demonized
John Kelly
Cuz it's slightly
The General
Kelly
Oh my gosh
Call Shannon
You shouldn't use the
I'm soldiers
Should be honored
Humanity
True colors
When they flip
So I considering Alex's torture
Kelly makes
Some passing references
And weird like
Hangout
About a month ago that I was going to bring this up but I'd like to also still give a
Shut up
How to get in that I was also want to bring it up right there
Damn the Centrist right there
It makes a great point that a month ago Alex was saying the general Kelly
With a addictive sedative
Kelly
In honoring women
And the best way to do that is to poison Trump I think that's true
I think that isn't actually true thing
To pull out of it
In order to
To make his argument
Any more appealing or more meaningful
To the people who listen to
Code
Dum Dums
Dance to make so much of this about
Position
Bonanza
Like make pasta
Prince those things
Was talking about
It wasn't the point of analysis make
Can get much more
The point of it because he knows
Oh he also told to completely lying
Misrepresenting story about
Speech that she gave at the unveiling of buildings
Or christening
The building whatever its called
Gender reveal party for the building
Nice yeah so she like
If you focused on that part of it which I think is
People are our Focus
He would have no leg to stand on So You focus on the vague
Is 2
Anti-abortion
Sentimental
Can't think of anybody who does that too
A little bit more about Alex
America
And the president
You f****** Tyler Freeland gardener
Yourself
Y'all really
That was an addict on their video
General
When he said
Defeat what he said
Call Stahl
Etsy
Falling on her face
I would argue that
The one who's doing a substantial amount
AutoTrader
Handle that
I can't handle that
He took this
High Road b******* about
All the ships only
He does
He took this
B******* f******
This is what I said
This is what exactly what I'm always saying about
This whole I call when they go low we go high
That's right
They don't care I don't care one way or the other
Bill go whatever the f***
They feel like you're not going
So you might as well do something
Zig zags
It doesn't f****** matter what way
What Vape
Think we pretending that the way they react
To something that we think
Is going to matter one way or the other
But now a little bit
Because Frederica Wilson did come out and say that
The comment
But she's a
An Empty Barrel
Is a racist
It's a little bit
I see you in some way
Jumping on
Completely not true
Here is an article in front of me from CNN
From the 20th of this month
Analyzes
Does whether or not there is any etymological
Indigo through
There's an origin
Play-Doh
Can't quite find
Citation
In the fifteenth Century a translation of the pilgrimage of the life of man
Done by John Lithgow
Contains a variation on that theme
Or Buy store noise and
Complaining
Avoid tolls
Play some Shakespeare
It makes a louder noise
Glass filled with water
They go through it to the
Reaching out to Missouri University of Science and Technology professor
Gerald Leonard Cohen
Recognize
Expert on etymology
And great music
They go through and
There's no real tradition of it
But there is
A part of it that is
I wear this is where I take away Alex
Scoot out
NBC host Laura Lawrence
O'Donnell devoted
Show on Thursday night
Knights Kelly
Wilson
Barrel
Suggested the due to Kelly's Boyhood
A Boston Neighborhood
There was still largely segregated
Destroys of words
Describe two wheels
Anjali dehumanize
She was nothing but An Empty Barrel to him
Hampstead O'Donnell
He refused to give her the Dignity of an
And there is some Credence to that now whether his motivation
Racist or not
In this article is not that they don't fall on them
That side but it is it is it is interesting to go back and listen to
Cuz he doesn't say her name
20 minutes
On TV
To the etymology
No he's at the gate 20 minutes
After this story the etymology
Which is like
NVM smurd bunking the idea that there's races
Roots today
Alex is just
I mean is way off on everything
Oh man
What are we doing
Really I don't know
These people what kind of what kind of line producer is that one of these shows going
Here's our story
We're going to spend all of this time
Phone call
From a sociopath that we knew was not going to go well
Mean anything Brave
I don't want to I don't want to do this whole like
What about
Bulshit
Of like
Well
Important
To talk about right
Spare
Alex
Disposition
Not racist
Because they're a bunch of
Democrats
In Congress who are mentally ill
Nancy Pelosi just as senile and mentally ill as he posts
In charge of our country
Assholes like you Alex
Assholes like
You yeah I mean it's a great
It's a great line
It's a good point but
If you if you get
If you get down to it like
Someone who he really supports right now is Roy Moore
Roy Moore is loaded
Yeah
He makes all kinds of arguments.
Only about how I weird
We need to be a Christian Nation
All of the things that go bad orbit
Because we've drifted
From Christ
I all this stuff you refused
To take down
VIP
The Ten Commandments
At the Statehouse is not allowed because he committed all the crimes because the courts
Cuz as a judge
Is the most important
Thing you can do is refuse to honor the con
Constitution
Whatever they take field officer always like
Hey and the cons
Constitution do not listen to that at all
He started doing speaking
Took the ten
Recently
Speech recently said that we're so
Such a divided country we got
The blacks fighting the whites
We got the Reds in the yellows
That's such a journey like
We got to stop being racist
Mrbeast kundu
But then he got into some hot water about those like
Weldon that song God loves the little children
Maybe the song is awesome
Alex anymore
I would rather take someone who Miss speaks
Every now and
Again.
Someone who is
DieHard religious zealot and wants to legislate the other comment that I found
I don't know what the window close
But basically goes along the lines
Just like
Swear in
The Bible the Bible the only thing that matters
Dominica
You know why Buddha didn't make a
All I didn't make us it was
The Christian God
How's the other religions are meeting
Like dude
Come on
Come on that is
I guess
But yeah
In a bad way
A perfectly
Population of the Republican Party
They will gladly vote
For somebody who shot all over the cow
And lost his job
That the Republican Party
Sky Zone
You guys hate America now if you for evereve everybody who's like
The Constitution is all about the
The first amendment in your like you you don't care about
So shut the fuk up now if you are Senator and you say Korea instead of Crimea accidentally
Alex will talk about it for six months or if you say
Instead of trump
Six months of cover
Instead of
You're backing people's safety
And the freedom quite frankly
These people are
The service of what they think is right
The worst human beings on the
Undoubtedly
So we got one more clip left
Of this special report
Will get into be like
I use the things they do I'm not making up a I bet he's at sex with a child before
I'm just saying
He was legally removed from his job
Shooting all over the Constitution
Right
I'm sorry for going to
General Kelly
Infowars.com
Call
The difference between
She's always creating another character gear if they wore it
Right and that's the strawberry reality of my shoes
What about her husband ladavid
But that
I actually feel
Think would have been better
Waterview
Good old laugh out of that cry
If somebody says that s*** to you cuz that's banana
Cuz defaulted
Is the switch into a character
It sort of embodies raped
All right fair enough the media is not doing its job
I agree with you
Like we've already discussed are you Alex
It's not a good job
Just got to the beginning of the episode
Bringing into his narrative a misrepresented
Pizza video that 8
Citizen journalist
Captured
Out the window of his hotel
Lick
Great
Everyone can do this
But it doesn't mean it's
Real it doesn't mean that anyone has any information
About the context
Anybody can have a camera capture stuff out of car
Contact anybody can have a blog post
Whatever they want on it it doesn't
Knowledge
Sprite
It's not journalism it's not truth it's not real
We are at the
The point now though where every interaction
With Trump
Should be record
Every interaction with the police but is everything recorded isn't it look for Trumpeter like presidential records
About
Oh like she should have started recording
Right like you should've if you ever get anywhere near any of these people you show
Turn your phone on and
Recording apparently cuz that's the only cuz now if
When we're dealing with a
Complete lack of abject
Reality Bites
Between different
Which we are
The only way is to
To pull out hard Eva
Record it
Recording everything you do
That way you can read back the tape
Check the tape
Apparently
In which case where were you doing
35 minutes
Nixon apparently Donald Trump's daughter-in-law has said that there's a transcript
The phone call but Dwight Howard
Denied
No problem
So that we move on to Monday
Has anybody
Ever described
I know one guy
His name
Alex Jones John Barron
His fake publicist character
We're jumping into Monday now
Here's how I was doing opens the show on Monday
It starts with a
Batman ends up in something Market dice
It's just I see
And I was hot dog and I'm language
Windover 1984 1776 you're listening
The Alex Jones Show
Altruistic
Vision for us
They are the Fallen soul
Everyday
Hold on
We need to reboot
Cuz I accidentally thought that was
The chat room.
I just bought
Can actually listen to
We are as a society
Here is the world economic forum
That's basically Bilderberg Group public
Coming out and saying
I feel deeply ashamed
Ashamed
That was respectful
Sorry about that alright
And I know how to control your mind using electromagnetic waves
Almost 20 years ago
For the CIA admitted they were adding augmentation system
In the Baltimore area
Well they were actually
Yes we're not in Kansas anymore
Biscuits to hamamoto style show
This is an article that Alex's rapper
Printing out of the world economic forum
It sounds scary as s***
Can now control how you think
They are going to
To spend the next article
The next
You know bylines is going
Word by word me now control you do
Control your mind
Do not read all the
Headline
If a sensationalized headlines also I would like to
Really important
It's Outta control
How are you
What you think
Little Ray
So here's what this this article is about
A team of researchers from Boston universe
She has explored the possibility of enhance
A person's ability to learn
Control their behavior
If it's not saying they can't control your behavior
Your ability to control your own behavior
How people feel
By stimulating
The brain Boston University researcher Robert Reinhardt
Simulation called
Cranial alternator
Current stimulation
Also known as a
Turbocharged
Two brain regions that influence how we learn
If you make an error
This brain Area Fire
If I tell you you made an error
It also fire
If something surprises you it fires
Rinehart said in a bu research
Search press release
Referring to the medial frontal cortex
Booty calls
The quote alarm Bell of the brain
Rinehart and his colleagues found that
Stimulating this region
Venezuela is the lateral prefrontal cortex
To change how a person
Learnt
These are maybe the
Two most fundamental brain areas involved
Executive function
A selfie
Control
They published a study about this and here's what they did
Rhinehart's team test
30 healthy people each wearing a soft
Cap with electrodes
Stimulation
The test was simple
Each subject
Had to press a button
Everyone points
7 Seconds
In the first three rounds of test
The researchers either cranked up the
Synchronicity between the two loud
Disrupted it or did not
The participants brain Act
Activity monitored by
Danelectro and see
Yu-Gi-Oh
Showed statistically significant results
When the brain waves were up
The subject learn faster and made fewer mistakes
Which they correct
When they made the mistakes
Correct
When do brain waves
Disrupted they made more errors unlearned more slowly
What was even more surprising
Was it when 30 new participants
Took an adjusted version of the T
The group started with their brain activity temporarily disrupted
Then receive stimulation
In the middle of the activity
The participants quickly recovered their original brains
Synchronicity
And learning
And learned behavior
We were shocked by the results
How quickly the effects of
Stimulation could be reverse
So basically all they've done
You can stimulate that allow you to learn faster
The bigger question
Summers another brain
Research
Scientist
At Boston University
Who is not apart of
The bigger question
Summers noted
Is how far apart
How far a person can go with
Who doesn't want to have their brain
Performance enhance
This could produce the same effect
Does nootropic
Smart drug
But with fewer put
Central side effects
Could work his the brain is stimulated directly
Having access
Such technology
But Edwin smart drugs
Should have access to such technology
And
Whether or not this March
But the point is
This is a very interest
Study has nothing to do with brain control or anything like that
Brainwashing
Alex is completely lying
About that
He sells brain pills right
Of course he has a vested interest in making you afraid of those thing
Right
There's a certain part of me that believes
No no mainstream Outlet
Should be allowed to report on science
At all
Because that's why we get
Cancer turn your balls into two oranges like white
What are we doing that because we know that if the article is going to be like
Six scientists at MIT put a little thing on a mouse and maybe that help
Call Sara Doran still 20 years away from being useful like they just love these
Headlines that are like
Right it's just b*******
And that's why you don't read articles
You just now read this
That's where it goes from there
First big piece of news today nothing to cover in more detail
Coming up in the shower
That we must be extremely moral
We must be informed and involved
And basically
A b
Warren
Future sci-fi superhuman soldiers more destructive than nuclear bomb
Don't feel no fear or pain
The globalist want machines
Because he'll follow illegal orders
Machines
Less human
I will
President of Russia
Had to say here it is
More and more I'm noticing
That
Alex takes
Note Alex cover Alex covers
Quotes
Things with Putin
Put out to the world
Which should be no surprise to
Breezin thru
I love
Russia
Humans are the least effect
Military time
Like what
We should be making it
I don't know this is a bad idea
Into that accident
From Star Wars
Very ill-advised weapon they should have
Put something low-to-the-ground with
Why would you make big toe lumbering camel looking
Snow Billy
Humulin
Enhancement
I'm now for AI taking over Humanity
Doing a bad job
Let's get little fur Isaac asimov's
Twisted mind and that is our destruction
So
I'm sorry we took a little break
Waterton
To Project Camelot territory and Alexa
We learned about some aliens
Similarity of Alex Jones
502 beholden to archaic
Systematic belief
Villa
Ian is next clip Alex Jones makes it clear
Key of Belize
Fighting demons or alien
So he is much closer than even we were presenting
We've got a real shot of future
Pell-mell
Mobile
Super cyclotron
Ryder systems
Genetic engineering
Train
Thousands of labs Gene Gunn random splicing opener testing products illogical prob
Minaj
Just put sky's the limit of what we know
Global government
Lollipop
Spirit
Can an archetype
Very different also need to pause
How is 1
Possessed
By an archetype
Well
I think it's a literary device I am fairly certain that
The playwright near me
Now I'm never going to remember it it's not Archimedes it's aeschylus
Proposed the archetype
Okay
Whatever
Identify with an archetype
Nature members
This man all of these things
Man versus the cell
Chicopee possessed
Also what does what
Cyclotron what was it he was talking about
A couple of Science words and put him right not important
I don't know
But they want to blow the planet
Soda Starscream
Really want to kill everybody
Operation
I like the kingsman the first episode of that
Yeah I just hypothesizing but I know it's going on
Reservist
Out-of-this-world
I don't know what are you doing
Veneer
Aliens on Earth
Animal animal animal
I think you should
Also I did Little Shop of Horrors
Really get bummed out when he brings up the hybrids
Chimeras
Really disappoints me and it makes me like why you playing like a shout-out to the
Mantador the spider leadership are they are they hybrids or are they just super intelligent
Is there globalist analog of
The spider leadership spider l
Are the spider leadership members globalist
It's unclear the global is there real leadership
Put two and two together for the Raptors
So the thing is I love that
Like
Fallen Angel
Stupid
I just made up to and then I made
Find a through line
In this next clip Alex Jones
They don't watch it
Namely
2 + 2
Here's The Cutting Edge information
Why they say he's fake news because he's the real
Before
I'm up for
He's been really workshopping that is a new catchphrase
It's not but it's a lie but
I mean we've gone through at least four
Specific
Uzi
Today's of his show
Bogus narrative
That's why Alex is not because
There's globalist that are against you or anything like that
It's a f****** illusion yeah we can put one together
Exactly much easier
So faster
Anybody else
Will research will focus
Buy the products
Only sales
December 1st now I thought was going to be
But now we're about a month earlier
Great the Easter sale is still going on by fractal
It's it's
We love to play the game where there's that sales pivot and then I deserve to turn it off
How long a lot of these ads are
I started to listen to a little bit of David Night Show
Movies with the app
How long does
He's pretty brief with them
Sounds like less of a Salesman
More structured way it was never like that
Turning into a
Swerve or whatever
Every time he comes back from break
You like I'd like to remind you of our specials
As as a lively
More or less like
Coming back from a commercial break
Always into a commercial
It's kind of like
This is the
Excessive
But you still it's less offensive because the way Alex doesn't
You could be screaming about God knows what your kids blood is going to be
Sucked out by
Demon globalist
Applying
Quality
What's you're absolutely
What replaces
Your blood that can't be true
It probably is
The FDA has not approved not approved
Nor deny the new plants
Replenishes your blood
Stairway to Heaven
Peaches herself
She replenishes your blood
Sure I love her song I will choose free will
Core sound
Just getting song
Songs wrong on purpose
The clip where I belong
Jones thinks
Is William Wallace
This is kind of like I mean Alex
Who's lying about ever
Can we remove his innards
Someone made
Monday 8
This is this is one of those clips where he's lying and he
He's wrong but I
And enjoy this out
This isn't like
Weird esoteric Alex
It's not angry Alex
Drunk Alex
It's Alex you think
Excuse one
And it's kind of fun
Because I know like
Tribe comes
Before the fall and all that
Showboat now it's a little bit
Quality to it
I hope we all enjoy also
Alex hubris Joan also
Please take notice of how I
Positive
You told them he
Don't turn down the music
Music Bad
Going real
So here's what I wanted to pause real quick
Because the reason that you started winning once you
You started saying it
Is because there is no war and there are no Global it's on the other side of it
So you
Get you get you get your base all riled up thinking that there are a bunch
People who want to
Take away our freedoms and
Destroy the country by Design
All this stuff and then of course they're going to fight back more aggressively and end up voting for
All of these wacky
A tea-party dick holes all around the country
Cuz the other side isn't radical
I mean
Says
Says you
Their pockets of radicalism I think of you listen to the
This episode you'll find that
You have radicals
No I haven't bought a gun yet though you're not like you're not
Clava on
And going to smash up a Chase Bank
Or something like that
Phobia
That's why I don't know why I do so myself
So
That was the point I wanted to
Make this idea but he's like
We called it a war
It's now it's a real war.
The other side
Isn't
It's like a war because
Right right
Anson imaginary
Pretty easy
Successful war against
You can't win them cuz
Time comes for a wind
Someone to lose
I need to declare victory
Ever
Like his money's gone. If he says
Guys
We defeated the globalist
Like it's like a season finale series finale
Like at the end of
That's why they couldn't kill Seiler
And season 1
They're like I don't know what do we do then
You need your bad guy
How did season 2 of Heroes workout
It was okay
There's a myth that it was terrible
Did get in the potential
Play some stuff going on in this
It was really in the third that ever
Everything fell apart that's my argument
Stick to it
I think comedians need to unionize
Anyways
Atomic strike
What is soon as we called out the global it's as soon as we got in their faces
Cultural and financial slaves
Pokerstar well
Thunderstorm
You feel the ancient will of the species development
Would you like to know more
Transmission
God bless you
Now you think here he's going to go to a sales
But it's too early in the commercial break for him to go to a sales pitch
No no no
When did the show
He said thank you this
The end of the transmission also the opposite of a shout-out
Going hard at me for like
Admittedly there were problems hero should not have been trapped in the past for that long
It was a mess
I have a soft spot in my heart because of what was going on in my life
Set the time and I don't think it's
Rubber that's terrible
Versus Mothra situational my God
Because that was freeform poetry of most insane times
In the face of Destiny and the
Android
With other Wheels
Listen back to that
Jerked off
Probably
Nailed it
Level 1 of improv training at Second City
Was it worth every penny
Kind of his thing it sounds right
But he doesn't
Unless we let them mind control Us by just
Lying
You know you do is the Democratic party is a minute and a half
Freeform speech
You do like
I am
You struggling there
Giant American Pie
Are standing in front of a let's get
To the get to the news of the Democrat news
They're going to lose unless they brainwash us with maggots
Nag nag nag that's all these Democrats to
Not good analysis
I think they pretty
Successfully
Listen to
Everybody
I'd like
Did you see what happened with the DNC recently they got rid of everybody who wasn't loyal to the corporate wing of the day
Democratic Party
Is there
There
Trying not to learn a lesson
They're doing the same thing that the Republicans did in
The 2008
Whippet
Tea party and all of that
They are
Trying to exploit
People who are
Radicalize or who are
Successfully becoming more and more
Progressive in order to further a corporate agenda get the vote
Exactly so the Democratic
Leadership is trying to
Lean harder into
Corporate money
Utilizing the fact that
Trump is the single worst human being on
On the planet so they can expect
Landslide vote
Atlanta
They're f****** stupid the Democratic party is led by the dumb
Famous people on the plane
It does look that way
Except for Alex Jones
Spare
People who fall for this bull
Yeah so in this
When is next b a little bit long Alex
Throws in a bunch of line narrative
And we'll get to those
What's wrong with them
Autosource
Hollywood
Mesmerised
Child play
At this very time last week
Information
So oh yeah
Now we get into some fun conspiracies
Over the weekend I believe
He said that he talked to Trump
The Trump was
About the champ
Okay stop it he didn't say
That he was going to do it
Rodger believed he was going
So I
Faolan
Mondays
Rodger Stone
They presented as
He said he was going to do it but you didn't want to put that out public
They're already sort of rewriting what yeah so what they were saying it right
But then further
Trump is doing is not
Blocking
Yeah there's a 1992 that all of these files would be really
On October twenty
Yeah that was what the law was from the 90
The president has the
Discretion
To either block
Oro Valley
And if he doesn't do anything until
Just automatically would be really
Where's the library
And pull them out from untried
Stack release these files
Have you no decency
How much lb
J.f. Kennedy
We're like
I guess we got to let everybody know now like the how much fun would that be Madness that would be hilarious
Perfect distraction
But also it really feeds in perfectly with Alex's they're going
Going to kill Trump there it is
Like eight
It's just it's like
Manna From Heaven
Converting
Storyline
LBJ actually did Kill
Bush jr. would totally let us know
Like in one of his speeches of me
Ultraboost
Look at Jones and stone fake news Trump
CIA sources say
Resources
I just can't stand it
Adjust
Like we told you weeks ago
This is coming
You are now a lobbyist Tony podesta
But have you seen
Senior antium to
See the Nativity spitting here is about
The probe
He's doing
Special counsel Robert Mueller investigating
Top democratic
Tony podesta Hillary Clint
Scrutiny
Expanding Russia
If you go on throughout this article you find out of there
Do the question of Russian interference
It's about work done by several wash
Operatives
For pro-russian
Ukrainian
In a few years earlier
Specifically both podesta's and manafort's firm represented a Ukrainian nonprofit group
The European Centre for modern UK
This group was attempting to improve the image of the Ukrainian regime at the
Which was pro-russian
Scrutiny
Treatment of their Doom
Proposition
A report
CNN podesta group
Contacted the state
What about Ukraine
2012 election
Attempting
Put a positive spin on the regimes handling of the election
However in
Crucially they didn't disclose the full extent of their work in federal lobbying filings
Until earlier this year
Paper NBC that failure to disclose at Scott Mueller
Tony podesta is the brother of John Fidel
Hillary
Presidential
Though they co-founded the lobbying firm a tissue
Decades
John podesta is no longer Affiliated as the firm and there's no indication that he's a subject of Mueller's
Still dunk also has
Nothing to do
With
The uranium one deal which as we know is horseshit
Yeah Alex really should have read further into that article specifically because that's
Not something
He wants to
You should buy like before
Cuz it's like
Food boy I supposed to say that
Nothing I'm supposed to.
FaceTime right
Screwing up in bread
Rewriting can I still say I'm fine with that like
F*** him I don't care if you're a democratic laboratory Republican Lockwood
And also this is fun Rodger stone is repurpose
Soon it will be podesta's time in the barrel
About Wikileaks John podesta emails
He's tried to repurpose out of being like Oh that's what I was talking about
Bring it out years later
NewsNow a year before
The track exactly
It's another
Read the sources
Since January 2016
I get why do you think they came out and said myself Rodger Stone from
Is your sons are all recognized
Has Trump had tried harder
Donald jr. absolutely
That's not good
Earlier in this clip
How did Donald Trump
Himself as one of their sources
Have you
Donald Trump
Had his son go meet with these Russians to try and look into it
To find some dirt on Hillary Clinton's illegal
Still not good
Of course
I talked to drop I get the information
Drunk
Holyshit
All of this is worse
When he says
Tremendously
Of course
The alex2epic mysteriously
Almost every black person who speaks up in public
Yeah it seems like there's a running trim
Stitches money
We're shows up.
There's a lot of problems
Perfect analysis number of the first situation
So much better by hearing bad analogy
Cuz
Look if you
Show up at the house with a gun
Is that Daddy
If someone is coming out the computer was it caught
Stealing a computer from someone pass
You were a stranger
I think first of all this situation of the potential
Control
Good second let's say you're stealing the computer you don't have a weapon yourself
I think this argument would end up being you drop the computer and run away
No this is my house
I feel like
This is more of an evil twin situation
Twins and they're both going on there until Friday
What is the real one movie
I don't want to believe that I'm sick and tired of this goddamn Chatroulette
Really really starting to piss me off
Do not know
You're not going to be in trouble then
Ron
Obama administration
Head fun
Infowars expose
Amazon Russia payroll
Where do you think this story is
I mean go with Infowars
Court all coming directly from Infowars mainstream media
The mainstream news has to admit
Of course we are now
Xtreme news where the rebel
Speeches about
All of it doesn't make sense
Jewelry
Investigating Infowars expose
4info
They should not be happy about that whatever it is true
Far from the truth
But if
If you read that headline
Publicizing the Galaxy
Get back
To give the president support
When he does this
He's doing it
Perfect couple
It's why they're so horrified of the daily
Because of the stacks and the clinch
I think Alex has a
Alex
Absolutely
Come on man
There's a lot of problems I think the cheese
Please problem explain how
Trump's brain work
Sprite
He's a child
More like
You did a great job by Axel
I also I mean like
I don't
I don't like the idea
That obvious
If we're going to break down what ended up having
Here
Alex
House
Or Trump's Administration
Told them
To write an article and expose about the Fannie Mae and Freddie Mac stuff which is weave
Discussing the past
Is bogus
It's not true
Right angle
Made it
So Trump
Could use it
In order to push through
The destruct
Should have Obamacare
Right
That is awesome
But you know the only players real Donald Trump jr.
Steve Bannon
No problem at all you just go to Bright
Rodger Stone
Yeah or Donald Trump him
Selfie
Baby in a momento
I don't think Barron's in the make you think the keys
I'm going to put this forward
Baroness
The secret Mastermind behind all
Looks like that movie Identity which was great
It was a child LOL
Spoilers
If you're going to run a secret global
Conspiracy
You don't want to be the face of it you don't want to be out in public
No I have people running everything for you
Furthermore
You may not be a child
I have not
He's actually hundreds of years old
Idea that there is a
Going on with Infowars
The Trump Administration
Believe
Much of any
So
Something that I think is true
ABC ABC
5 days late
That's all coming up and more second hour
Is kind of what I believe
Is actually at 8
What that when people are doing their job
In terms of
The media
Alex
Survive
He can't thrive
Asset
World
Where people are actually engaged
Reality
With what's going on where they know things they are
There are a couple of sites
But have explanation
Kings of like
The triage thing going on
You can hear in the dispatch
Stapes people talking about the wounded being taken
From the
Site of the crime
Do a triage spot
Couple
There are five or six
7 pages of people being like
Multiple shootings in s*** like that
So much
Yelling about
The fakes.
I am just
About the reality
Alex Jones
Could not thrive
If the reality
He started yelling back
Absolutely
It is it is something
That I think about alot
Is that
The
The spark
Behind all of this fake
News though
Is
People want
To imagine
Sure the world we live in is f******
Chaos
Insanity and people want to imagine a world that isn't
Right
Problem
The way to do that
First engaged with reality
And then try to change
Right and just imagine
No I understand the impulse
You want to use your
Listen to affect chain
Change in the world
But you have to start from reality
You have to we have to start from a shared reality otherwise
Thing is going to happen
Right
Something I learned in my
Philosophy class discussion
The definition of
Exact you're not talking about the same thing whenever hopefully you can never hope to get
A conclusion
I think we agree there but
Is the end of
Please
And please don't forget we're about to end
70% off on 4th
There was a little smoother than abrupt
But if it is demonstrative of any Opera
Anytime we're going to break and I got to fill 30 seconds
My f****** time self
And of that thing that he says about Max
Waters threatening to kill
A little bit over
Again we already kind of went over that
We didn't go over that one though she just said I'm going to take out Trump
Yeah that's Certifit
Like she been calling for him to a nice dinner
It's been talking about trying to get it
For a long time
That was the context
In which you was talkin
A mountain out of a molehill
Play this game
Trump said that
Second Amendment people should take
Harold Hillary Clinton
Moreover
So if you want to play this game Alex
It's important
Be intellectually consist
No it is
You're right
If you're right or wrong
I've been doing this podcast for 10 bucks still hanging out on that Hill
I think the one thing that we have learned from this is that intellectual consist
Cincy is
Rare rare commodity you're also totally wrong
We also learned about
I said if there's no good
Now
Of course
Except do you know what what
I was born in
Is that right
Dragon Ball swales great crab fishing
Get carried away
Get carried away we go over to our website
Alright now that spike.com
You got a Blog up there new post every Thursday
Topix things in the world
I also we are on
You can follow us at at now agenda
You can leave a review you
Can share it
Dear friends
Your family but not
Your parents week
Because they probably wouldn't
Don't snitch
Damn baby
Sonorous voice comfortable man he's he's
Shared some Centrist position
Always
It must be noted
It should be clear that you're doing that is a bit
Okay
I don't know I just want to be clear that like
The idea of using
Like Centrist as a pejorative. Super on board with
But be that as it may
Did you
Which Monday through Thursday
At 8 p.m.
Everyday like I said we're doing this show we're going to keep doing it
But we need your help
We need support
Thank you everybody who's watching live in the chat room
I love you all even though you guys suck
Can come down on me for my neck
It's all in love I understand
I'm not taking it very personally although
Taking a little too personal
But if you like sport the show recommends is out there
Patreon.com
Appreciate it and you'll become a policy wonk
University Blue House Party
No
Okay
What do you noticed
The different Bhai
You have ever looked behind me before
No look behind you would like a just give just keep studying the wall
Area
What's different about the Tableau that's in front of
Where is that where is that
I don't know
No
This is no mods
Do a guy who can go f*** himself
If you don't hang that poster backup swear to God
The floor make you feel
Makes me think
May the Wolves joke on your flesh
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work