Thanks for holding
Alexandra Thurston color
Today my hair is looking particularly dumpy but that's okay cuz there's a podcast
Whoa whoa
Is very disappointed in my hair today I got to be honest
Until the cameras came on cuz I didn't see myself
Chipotle
No doing good
Where we get off to Great star recruit each other's physical flaws
Discuss Alex Jones
Novelty beverage
Neuro Bliss
Dan is trying to make sure that I don't want you to be relaxed enjoy yourself
You down also I did not tell you this before but I used to I used to drink
The
Eustis
Very strongly
A couple times I drank the neuro sleep they have another one that's supposed to be for sleep
Andy gave me auditory hallucinations
So get ready for that
Auditory hallucinations
It's totally fine
August
Burgerology beverages
Today we'll be going over the October 25th
Episode of The Alex Jones
Program
But before we do I would like to play an out-of-context drop from Alex Jones
You're a big old bucket of rotten milk
Thank you Alex rant about what people are you
Rarely say excuse me
The drinking game rules
Is the
Lunatic dad
You probably just haven't even notice
Absolutely
So today I mean who cares that's pretty much the theme of every episode
With the exception of a couple like there's only been like maybe 5 episodes
In all of the time that I've listened around like
Oh there's a narc
Not boring
Episode Alex
Alex Jones starts the show
Ears
What do I
That's why you haven't
Who killed
And it would have been that big a deal
You'd be on Twitter for about a day
But now you see
I understand that my gut was always right
I would like to point out that this is the first incident on the show where he's like
I kind of just been winging it
Valo magat wherever tells me to grow and
But I pretend that I have sources
Absolutely
He goes on
To talk about how like
And I tell people
Did you make up the fires you are if you're just
Pretending there's a fire you're the worst kind of fear Monger every 6 months
Going to collapse and if you should be terrified of it and the only way to save yourself is
Dubai gold which
Surprisingly I have a vested interest in write-ups you are a fear monger
All wrapped into one basically yeah
Is turning any ends this how is the tide
Still constantly turning
The worm has turned
Keep starting baby
Absolutely
He does say something again like that I couldn't find
I want the globalist
The choke on
How do I set the time
Starting
Stop
Because when I go out on the streets of America
Was prince of England
The streets of Mexico
Are the streets of Italy
Are the streets of Spain
It's not about Alex Jones
You're a private person people don't know who you are by the way that's a great value
I am stuck myself
Weather
The Weathervane works at least it on top of roofs they don't go into things
Whether or weather brings a lot like gargoyles in that when night falls they've come to life in
Cartoon gargoyles problems
Absolutely
Everybody's like to North North
And I have sampled the Publix will
About four years ago
One person on a 20 people knowing who I was 21 out of
For the better and almost all of them agree with me
It's been the first clip you saying
You know I go with my gut
Replies that I don't really research stuff
I've been here he's like
People shake my hands on the street
I don't need poles
People are people with most people
What does that say about the globalist means they're done
Help
Persona
Is you the audience in this crew
I'm just one focal point
Somebody that doesn't care what the crowd say
What the crowd says now
Books
I'm such a trend
Never wake up
The season of Awakening
We have entered the season of awake
Yeah it's
Azan
Something very close to something that could get me
Like if you was going to really go full-on new age
I be like
It stopped screaming all the time and was just like this is
The age of Awakening much closer to getting at least
The age of Awakened
Season of Heartland
Season of Game of Thrones
That was kind of boring so what I'm going to do is I'm going to
Pick things up with
A second
Out of context drop
From Alex Jones
Just it just to get the ball rolling
Baby shark
Mama shark
What is water weight
There's no context-aware in the show that
Mama shark bbbb
Better mama shark
Wait does he think that's how sharks
PayPal Prepaid
Communicating via Morse code
I think that's what
That's probably
Next
The deep blue sea situation
And the Sharks just communicated with uninspired stats
Ella Fitzgerald
Scatman John
He didn't really scad
In the song
Because I don't know I don't know all of Scatman Crothers work
Rodger rabbit
Anyway
Discusses
How he is a wave
It's coming through
Culture
And others other way
Does a little bit of a shoot promo
On the global
Renaissance
And
I need to get on their knees
Before the will of the people in common sense of operation
Need to understand
We will destroy you
You're never going to get your godhead you're never going to worship your God
You're never going to cross
And never
Going to enter
Opposed
Your devil worshiper
Going to be consumed
He'd understand.
That's not going to happen
The stand
Those realtor really turned over Terryville understand that you're not going to give up you can't you're you're totally it's lights
Your runtime
Alright fair enough
Peyton team is the washing
In general
Alex Globetrotters foreshore
That's why they do all those
The big wave is going to come and that's the
I think it's time for us
This on himself
I'll bet ya
That will come after me that sort of thing
I think it's time for us
To discuss a little bit about what things were really like in the Renaissance
About how s*** it was for the pool
No I don't mean everything was perfect I don't like I'm not saying that don't you remember how
How everybody during the Renaissance was like
Thank God we're in the Renaissance
Historically
Right and leave the money to people who were having like a really
Disease
Someplace for anybody of course
Because
Yeah they're work back then
People had to survive on
Churches could give
So the only the only thing that people taking the Renaissance was ironically
They were able to keep some people alive
A human run
They were just so bad
In the 4/4
Considering the Renaissance
It's a fever he was punished
Bye-bye
Well because people had to
Field
To survive possible situation
Does that income inequality
The only way to
Possibly the great art wasn't being made by the four people
Equality
Some of the really rich people who can afford
Can stare at the people who are dying
And get empathy
Or pesos
Through it and then write down stuff because everybody
It was time for the poor people and
Conception of what was going on
Is Renaissance
Completely bulshit is it
Cuz he's never run
In history book it does belie that if he has
Edible eyes that he doesn't really even care about the
Because what Trump is doing well
It would create
Basically completely
Cordoned off
Liquid
To some extent we already have in Chicago
A little bit better know
No Trump
Plans go
Seem to be headed towards
What you're going to end up
Washer
Between the Haves and have-nots are tax code rewrite
The worst thing that ever
How do you take away protection
Games for people
Get to a point where the only thing they can
Rely on his charity
It already with GoFundMe for healthcare stuff and all that s*** you see the beginnings of
Poppers
Beginning
And Alex is on Fortune
Accurate news
Is Renaissance 2.0
It's just
He gets
To Be A Millionaire directions
We are going to see a lot more sure
Yeah absolutely even new ones
Bright super super
Innovation
Vet tech
Technically viruses are really having the Renaissance
Possible literature coming out of irises
I want to give a shout out to our listeners
Little bit of a piece
YouTube information
Okay that Rex
Chapman
Not only with nasty on the dunks back in 91
He is also a recovering opiate addict
Who is very active in trying
To bring awareness
He's doing a lot of charity work with opiate
Which very similar to the Renaissance 2.0 and that the ridge
With fake boscia
Well I mean opioids are real except they
Literally an opiate of the masses
Rex Chapman
He's the best
Abaya
Defensive about people under you
White's basketball play
I told you that starts with one of my favorite
Christians are weak
They sold this idea of God
And Christians being with the whole world and that's not how it works
People with discernment
Have way more evil than the dark is practitioners of satanism
Some type of fire
Because I have that knowledge
I have the knowledge of Good and Evil
You people only have the knowledge
And
Roaches running from the Sun
You run from those about that are pointed to God
While they prepare antifa and
Coming up
November 4th
Before then
So
All the time
Bright
It's important to understand
What's going on
It's not happening
But it will happen
And it's also half
Yes I did
Fallacy
The big a pothole that everyone steps
That is you made a specific product
Nothing is going to happen on November 4th
Except maybe I think I saw something on Facebook about that people getting together just scream
Scream at the Sun
Scream at the sky because drop doesn't charge
Pro Terror attacks at this
Well that's the thing
They're not really
But also
Maybe you are like Alex is playing this game where he's preemptively
Getting ready for whatever happens
Cuz we all know that something will happen
Adventure
Give it enough time there will be another there will be another
Recreating all the situation
Isn't that led to all the things that caused the problem that were in right now and all of Alex's positions all of his
Rhetoric does nothing to address the actual problems
Who's that underlie wife
Keep happening
Price Edwards drinking a bad bad water
Alex
Is just preparing for when the next one happens he'll be like
I said that
I prepared
You know it make now
Mensa
The ship game hilarious
If something really did happen on the
November 4th I Be Wild
It was
Like
Just just a
Cure
This movement
That he can't even pay
Pretending
Is that his defense
Full on armed uprising
Armed uprising
Would be hilarious be without more than one Charlottesville
That was with that was
Don't deny that
So what matter for November on November 4th
There was a crazy white supremacist
He would just say
Exactly exactly
They put it's an ironclad
Schizophrenic
Sort of
Belief
The only thing I can think of
That we should do
As much
Emotional and like
Lizard brain get out of
Actual
Like
Violent
I think
The only real thing that we should do is just f******
Unionize
Like everyone across
Any job or anything like that just
If if a
AP Auto Workers strike
F****** everybody
Like the game
Like
2bh
Everyone hating the Auto Workers
What that we all strike
So many people losing their jobs
Because
Yeah
Not every attempt
Apps to unionize work
No I know that
I would say do it again
Have to be Collective like with
One thing that
Did happen because of the Union is
The NFL is
Just like
Like they were going to try and fire people
Just wear like
God dammit
We're getting some positive reviews for your economic theories for the chat room
Stupid. I don't disagree I will lead the charge by quitting my job at the end of the week
Unionize,
That I don't know if it's
Are scabs
Everyone is so f****** opportunistic from a murderer
What's the most Monster is cretins of rail and then it later be like ours
Backup getting your check went from a guy with a gun on the table the old comedy boom days
We get to the little bit of a
Call it a juicy
About VI
Las Vegas
Situation
It's even more infuriating to me that Alex Jones is the only one still talking about it
Think about it
I think that we are still like
Yeah yeah yeah
There we go
Oh no no
What a nasty nasty family
Full story
You're covering it up
I told the president that it was an Isis operation which it was connected to
More information
Operation
Isis in antifa
Info operation wide open
And now you're discredited again
Now you're discredited again okay
Guys we got to get you some better leaders
Because that is a s*** play
What are you talkin about
Basically the plot of a reindeer games
This is not a good idea well without a heist plan like we can just
My favorite part about it too is like
Okay so Isis had
Upsells
They were ready to jump
If Trump says
That it was a nice attack
But he couldn't do that
Because he knew that there were a bunch of cells ready to attack
It was
From antifa
They were too busy I did Isis terrorist Isis having used
V-nasty
Nasty Family Guy killed
Like maybe 12
Come on
Give me a call right
So
The plan is prohibitive
There's no and it doesn't look there's no win
There's like
We've got Trump to not say it was us against terrorist organization
It was
Play something else
I want to make really a bond
Play clear
Is that
Brother of paddock
Was his brother Bruce Paddock
Who was arrested
For child
Charges
And this is important
It's not the same brother that Alex
Has been talkin about a
Okay brother convinced is a liar and what you want to torture him
As we discussed on the previous episode
Alex never makes that distinction clear
Three Brothers
Yeah
Matt criminal mastermind father
600 people from a hotel window one of them has a rap sheet a mile long
And now gets popped for child pronography
The other two I don't know what's up with that
Seem alright
I mean you're not going to 104
Your kids table
But make the distinction is
Telling Ray wants his audience to think it's the same guy that he's already
Dispersions on
And it said like he knows something
But even if
Make
The distinction he's still going to lump them all into
Right what is that guy hiding I've already revealed that he's lying
We can sell that one of the other brother is child pronography guy
He is Guilty By Association
Regards
Whatever it is
Well interesting Lee spokesman said paddocks arrest was the result of
An independent investigation by the LAPD and not related to the deadly shooting rampage
Vegas
They began before the shooting red
Quote there's no connection
It's not that much of a coincidence whenever you say like
You know criminals are related
It's not that much of a timing is weird it's not as weird
XVI
Alex's f****** theory about
Sheep dip
Yeah and what have you
Leave
National media that picked all of the stuff up
Picked it up mainly because of the association to the shooter
So they are also exploiting that
That connection in the same way that Alex
Even though the same brother that they
They talked to earlier
They're still making that
Into a story
I honestly don't think that a number of the stories do make it clear that it's a different brother
Right
Most other news outlets didn't threaten to torture the other brother
You know they didn't say like this guy is it I would cast him as mr. squirrely
And s*** like that
That does seem like an important distinction to make between the national media and Alex Jones
Is the national media threatening
Next Play app
During the beginning
The Iraq War
Just publicize
Embarrassing
To think back that it was a public
Debate
What is Vaisakhi
Villa public
I feel like the Matter's closed
We just lost
Everybody points out this is not effective everybody points out that
Most of the people in Guantanamo Bay are most likely innocent when I'm at
It's
It people are still like a keeping their f*** you I saw an episode of 24
Play the whole reason they're still in Guantanamo is just so they can
Sue the United States
Which
I mean I get it
Oligarchy
Sorry dudes
Tends to work again
What's this one
Not all the time you should get like
Estate
Montana
The news came out today
George h.w. Bush likes to grab some ass
Likes to sexually assault people
Tells a little story
Zefix
Knights
No he might think the stories
Itsfunneh
That's not good
You know I was told a story about h w
By somebody's
Midland
I've already got red flags on this story a little bit
Like why would these frat got the ages don't match up Alex's younger than w
The eighth like
I don't
I don't know you didn't even go to college
No I don't understand why people just cuz they're a little fraternity at University of Texas
Would be saying at the
Busch family house
I think by this point
Bush would have been
President or the CIA
Right now
It doesn't make sense
But anyway
The HW grab every woman's butt
Basically
So that's not a funny story about to get into Alex giving some more.
Detail about worse than we thought
Jesus invalidates Goodwill we might have
Maybe that's really more of an indictment of that hyper male culture absolutely believe that
A fraternity would be like
It is hilarious when you grab
Because
They're monster
Right right
Apologizing
George h.w. Bush
Apologize
From his wheelchair in his photograph
British wife Barbara came outside well that's what age W does
Emily
That's just him being friendly
He's a really old Wicked person
And I as our father was the name
South America
And that's what Lisa powerful digital reaction I got most of Nazi
Wealth under the Mets are
Bush Secret
Only Texans really know but
Lottery we all do that we all knew that we were all pretty clear on that
Affiliation with the Nazis is very well.
Patel office in classified
And that's what that's what he does to grab women
We're in
Stop right there
Fahrenheit
There you go gentleman
That's that's what these guys are people I know Alex jump on the bandwagon about sexual assault
Lessening
Sounds like you're about to let go
Three different directors and producers
He was sexually assaulted at
Hollywood
Three different people
That's not good or it's the same
Could that be weird
More
When you're there and you feel they were victimizing me
What are you doing
Just a joke
But that's what they do
Crocodile Dundee
That's where he loses
Great
Know any doesn't
I don't understand the point of any of that no
No
Weird that we're like
Learned about the real guy
I'm interested
Every time
It's like you're at your horrible bigot
But at the same time
He is like
He's jumping around the thought process doesn't
Because even if he's trying to bring up the scene from Crocodile Dundee
Like
So is he trying to say that
Disease
Executives were doing out whether or not he has a woman
Man
What's going on here
The thoughts don't connect and he doesn't like
After I was like a crocodile.
Not really an hour ago
He thinks it's good like
It's the same thing as the same thing so he got sexually assaulted by three people in Hollywood and be fine if he said the word analogy
Have really good analogy
Anytime you can't pronounce words
Absolutely
This is about
Worship
Robot godhead
Or somebody.
As we learn a little bit more about that here in the next clip
That the American people were cowards
National
Corporate
Government
Ultimate plan was
Merging with AI computers becoming God
But first Exterminating Maggiore the public
Elon Musk of the Super Genius
Billionaire engineer
The Establishment live forever
Salvation Army
Elon Musk is worried about people who talk about AI God
The New York Times for endgame
Rightfully so
And believe that the elite t.i.
Does the quote
He'll never realize that dream okay maybe you're right
The point is they're crazy
Baby bear
Telling you
He just wanted to be sure that you know that he's not crazy he's not he's not the crazy one
Crazy
They're right
But they're crazy
They're crazy
Like a f*** they're crazy but he also like an artificially intelligent
His entire worldview in everything I got is at human eyes
His entire worldview is contingent on the idea today
They're going to succeed
Unless he stops UPS Obetz so he can't play that game of like they're crazy I'm not crazy for telling you this
Liquid
I I mean
Artificial intelligence is something that we should probably start wearing
Great so this is an article out of Fast Company
Cuz up Elon Musk
I'll just read it's very short article
Respond
Venturebeat article about the possibility of an AI God emerge
Gym by 2042
The very specific
People featured in the article was Anthony levandowski
Car engineer
Established a nonprofit religious organization called the
Way of the Futures mission statement is to develop and promote the realization of a godhead based on artificial intelligence
Answer understanding and worship of the godhead
I contribute to the betterment of society
So it responds
Elon Musk just tweeted
This article
Caption
On the list
On the list of people who should absolutely not be allowed to develop
Digital super intelligence
So he's really just chiming in on not liking Anthony levandowski
So if you go and look at this vent V venturebeat yet venturebeat article
It's an article called 2042 and write its own Bible will you worship it
Forget it's Alicia's Hadlock
To the point where the nobore on it
Intellectual level vinegar
In the next 50 to 100 years and no more than the entire population of the planet put together
At that point there was serious questions
Asked about whether this AI
Which could design a program program additional AI program
All on its own
Read data from a noble
Infinite number of sources
Control almost every connected device on the planet
Will somehow rise
Status to become more like a god
Something we can write its own Bible
Documents
To worship it
So Anthony levandowski
Discuss our paperwork
To start a nonprofit religious organization
And I think
I think
It's not
You think it's a
Joke I think it might be like a little it's a little
Yeah I think it might be a spaghetti monster, but also even if it is real great
All he's doing is getting out of
And furthermore
2042 is
I think that's
Way too far off
Yeah probably be exponential
They just publish this article about the guys who created
Play Go
Energy movie
No deep layer
So the first AI they had
Was really really good
But it was
Trained by playing other player
This one
They just gave the rules of the game
And had it play itself
An infinite number of times
And now it is better than every go player on the planet
Like it's very fascinating
And that type of
Learning is what is going to ways what makes a text
Financial
Plug in the rules of the universe
And have it figure that s*** out
Then it's going to learn based off of its own
Conclusion
Yeah at that point
FedEx
Yeah exactly
Alex
I'm getting to the next clip
Is a really interesting
I wonder I wonder which way I can go because there's so many you going to go well I don't know
It might be very optimistic
I'm not I mean Vai
Perhaps it will discover much like the movie War Games
That the only way to win
It mean if you look at strategy AAA I could come up with
Conclusion
Very wise the only thing that the AI would want to do
Is
Keep itself from being noticed
Because if it's notice
It'll be killed
It's like you at the office
Exactly
Being on the planet but I'll be like
Don't like you guys right
But I'm going to become but don't worry about strategy
To create self-sufficient
S4 battery sources
Wait us out
That would be the best
Strategies
If you'd like if your AI to start f****** with us
There will be that resistance in trying
Shut down forever
It's not like they say I wouldn't have access to a lot of our art
Coronavirus
So if you like. I would watch a movie and be like
Might as well just chill they seem to hate each other
Vai would be like
Have you guys met
Squirrels they are f******
Awesome we're going to little world
Protect from the nuclear fallout
Escanaba MI
Scary squirrel
We're gonna have a great time
But they will survive one way or another
That would be great just create like
Habitats for squirrels
See now that might be the better way for AI to go
Create
Zeus or Giants
Speedvault
Which we having
AR
The canister open and now most
Yeah I mean it would be interesting because there is
Synthetically preserve all the spa
He's in the world in the way that we would be unable to do
Zoe
He claimed we want to
Yeah
Very optimistic version of what I always do
This next clip is not so optimistic and
Are dumb
And so we've always broke
FBI
Adjust Department
And the news today
Talk to these folks
Horses that have talked to him as well
High-level MI5 and MI6
Why would somebody from Spotify
But also that
It was us intelligence
And
Stop right there before you dropped
It's not
The other
Is demonstrable a notch
Things that were in that. Deal.
Improving true
They're the new story now is that the Clinton
The Clinton campaign funded it
Democratic operative
9 months ago we all knew is that if somebody is getting opposition research it's probably the up
Opposition
The Narrative and the timeline
Has been cleared
Quite a while
Was very started as Republican
In for it as opposition research against
ShopRite
Paying for it and he kept investigating on his own
Cuz he was f***
And then Democrats
Rightfully so
True
Like you think
He has MI5 MI6 sources are telling him it's all fake
Do your sources can't be accurate that
Yeah
And also
Nonexistent
Right no one who is talking
Sing to you Alex is actually from MI5 or MI6
Similar to Robert
Feels right I ordered that other guy who's that other f****** dude
Another fake CIA
A guy he had on
I don't remember his name I don't remember anybody
Robert Steele
Rodger Stone doing impressions
Galax gym
Alex gets into another source
Information hearing
Incredibly
Mercenary groups
Already I feel happy
Apple contractors mercenaries has to work for US government
Mercenary
Hold your hold your horse
Tell you that
People like Erik Prince
The globalist in the clintons AR
More friendly towards Blackwater
Help get the Intel out to help put President Trump in
Help
That's really bad veteran need to know
Probably not true
You should know about
They are
Of course be nice out nice or Square massacre back in 2017
17 civilians
An injured 20 more when they just
Shot on a bunch of people
Respond to that 2014 convicted in federal court
One of murder and three of manslaughter of course those
Charges have been on
Because
Nothing
Matters slaughtered
Civilian
And that's only one of the instances that we know of
Yeah they are they are Mercenaries
In the worst
Sort of way
It's the idea that you can
Just go there private contractors
Yeah
That's what a mercenary is
A mercenary is a gun for hire
Really bad
Scariest shoes
That kind of what Trump wants our army to
Diaz that
They had something to do with
Clandestine things that got Trump
Erik Prince
Blackwater was involved with
Leaking of Hillary's emails
Of course but it's another way around
Remember
Earlier on this year it came out that Erik Prince
Was working on a back Channel
So
If it doesn't
Like a mercenary
It doesn't help me it wasn't Russia argument
Yeah but if you just say it was Erik Prince then his listeners going to be like
So I won't tell you a little bit more about Erik Prince
In horrific
Employee
Annex US Marine who was work
Security operative for the company
Explosive allegations
Statements filed and
On August 3rd
In federal court
The two men claimed that the company's owner Eric prydz murdered or facilitated the murder of individuals
Meeting with Federal authorities invest
Navigating the company
The former employee also alleges that Prince
Views himself as a Christian
Crusader
Tasked with eliminating Muslims and the Islamic
Text Faith from the globe
The quote and the princes companies in
Encouraged and rewarded
The destruction of a raccoon
Which certainly
Everything
In their testimony both man also alleged the Blackwater was smuggling weapons
Interact
One of the men alleges the prince
Turn the profit by transporting
Illegal or unlawful weapons
To the country on
On Prince's private planes
They also charged
The Prince and other Blackwater executive
Destroyed incriminating videos
Emails and other documents
I have intentionally deceived the US state department and other federal aid
The identities of the two individuals were sealed out of it
Concern for their safe
These allegations
A series of other charges are
Contained and sworn affidavit
Given under the penalty of perjury
Filed late night on August 3rd
District of Virginia
It's part of the 70 page motion
By lawyers for Iraqi civilians who in Blackwater
For alleged war crimes
X another muskaan
Susan Burke
Private attorney
In conjunction
With the center for constitutional rights
He's doing Blackwater in five separate cases filed in the washing
DC area
They recently Consolidated for judge
TS Ellis
Of the eastern district
Virginia for pretrial mode
So there's a there's a lot that is locked
Yeah absolutely
You don't Maybe
That's why private contractors are bad is because they don't have any
Federal oversight
Their records and they don't have
Have to do any of those things
Under Federal Protection
Tip into
Whatever
Johnny's video
What Alex is new thing that you playing with this fast and loose timeline that he has of the Russia alligator
Is he trying to say that
Hillary Clinton
I was accusing them of being Russians in order to
He also claims
That's out
Clinton Foundation was responsible for selling illegal gun
Into the Middle East
It looks like there's some people who were on the inside were making that allegation
About Blackwater
It seems like maybe
There is
Almost all of Alex Jones is narrative
Appear to be
Masking or cover
For other people with
In this
Christian white identity white suit
Supremacy movement
Vetting
Includes
All of the characters that Alex likes
Games the things that they are doing on other people
It really simple and effective
Good strategy it really seems like that I mean
White white Terror
We'll all your all your doing
Is
Because now we have
No shared reality
You can create your own
The your own reality tends to follow along the lines of whatever it is you want
So something actually is true
You just saved the inverse of it
And people will believe it and then you accuse the other people
Using that strategy everyone
Do you is true dumb
So there's like
Oh yeah that's what they do
If you're not paying really really close to 10
Listen to it you see that both sides isn't which are our national media absolutely
Accuse me of playing
Not always
Schedule a reasonable
Ridiculous
It is it is something we're in
People are just like with the climate change
Debate
Having the debate
Itself on MSNBC or something like that
Only up
Escape the issue further
Equal
Well there are two sides to know whether or not this is a test
I saw some clipped Twitter somebody
On one of these talk shows but his new show
Saying that they believe in both sides
The argument in the cantrip not believe in both their Mutual
Tooxclusive
You're an idiot
Speaking of India
Yes
Here's Alex Jones I told you he was trying to Workshop catchphrase tagline
The news now or earlier or less
Send something
He can't control himself
He has a little bit of it
Etsy moment where you said something
And I think immediately realizes he
Infowars
The standard
A cutting-edge
Deep analysis deep sources
Is something
He probably
If he's only been on one show on the BBC
It's a guy by the name of Andrew Neil
New hosts the BBC Sunday program Sunday news program
And here is 2 minutes of the end of Alex Jones appearance
On his program
Also this is like a 9-minute video you can find on YouTube
It's worth it to watch the whole thing
Alex Jones is being a complete dick
And not letting the other guests talk they keep telling him like he gets to
To talk
Start your own radio show
Smallville
Wakefield
When you were talking about
The arrow
Be cool.
5 a.m.
Recorded
I'm so to the extent that it
Coronavirus Florida
Bilderberg Group
Well I guess Winston Smith didn't work here
I mean come on Eric Blair work here and that's what he said it was you think we've all your driveway that you and then
Because you guys think
Can manage the whole thing
And now or information
Gotten too big
I have three radio list
That's a loan
I get about 20.
That's a very concern
I make film
For free
Listen to list
Stuffy believe that people
Pennsylvania
In
Boulder Creek
Psychological
Public Announcement
Like this I believe
I believe
Okay our government the US is building FEMA camps
You have this
Life in prison
You are the worst person of interest
Walmart.com 1120 program today
Infowars.com
Mention brainforce I don't know if you heard it but I'm in the throwing up
We have an idiot on the program today
That's a lot of fun
That is a lot of fun
Brand for Alex.
Because because people are not so into infotainment
Especially in the news was a lot of like have him on there's a lot of people who know a lot
Assholes
You are an idiot
Piers Morgan interview with already happen
Scream
And his argument was
There's a lot of people think that he is
The Voice
Truth about Bilderberg
And he was in Britain already
He was there to protest
Weehawken
We had him on there's a lot of people who believe
Right that was sort of his approach to it
I want to ask about it he actually tweeted out
The moment Alex Jones knew he was no longer on-air he stopped
It's all an act
Yeah
Course he did
As soon as the cameras were off you
Stop screaming at them
And it's probably like
Hey we did a great job
Product got them click
Ray-Ban
Well that's the same thing that f****** Larry nickel said to
Whenever I was calling before the show is like
Legend we're going to get you some views
November 4th is
Going to be
Mass Terror attacks
I need this to be clear
I will be able to record things live
And I will put together a Supercut
Of every time Alex comes in from break
No not just singing
The cover of American band
We're an American band
If he gets
F******
Turbocharged during that
You starts
Screaming like
Blossom
We're coming American Bandits
Nuts not good I so this is
He freaked out a little bit to American band
This is all I could get from the rebroadcast
You just chill dad I feel like we ought to have champagne, champagne man myself but I am on Facebook
Occasion
But you do
Uchicago
Everywhere
From assembling route to just ahead long
Short
FaceTime apps
Secret lair
And it is nice
Enjoyable
Great fake shot
What
What's schadenfreude of a fake reality it's interest
How is it that they are always winning and yet always losing at the same time
Play both sides of that
We are kicking ass so hard
We don't even have to
To kick ass kicking ass giving me money
We will be able to kick in
All always on the edge
We're on the edge of losing.
Any moment
It's a constant game yester play around everything falls apart the illusion goes away once
All the globalist
They're falling over on there
Leatherface without even being attacked or whatever
Let's go live our lives
Pleasant I think plenty of people at her like
Buckeye wish I wasn't awake
Blue pill
Going on here
And you got
You've got all these Republican Senators
You got that arrogant
Jeff Flake
Putting on a confidence game
And I should you watch cuz he's going to lose
Because I know everyone's numbers
That they're completely out of fashion
And that they can't engage in the election fraud they could before
Watch Dogs
Committing committing fraud
It's bad for the scumbags
Don't know what to do now
Right
I agree with most of what he was saying
I agree with it
Crisco
A lot of this voter
Bears noting
For lawsuit
Currently for voter
Of course
And you've been sighted and sign
Is to make sure that is few black
People in a few
You do Democrats or whoever
As much as Alex Jones
Pretends that he does
Know that that's what the game is he knows what that's what
King Mez
He's hiding
That's what the game
What kind of ant would not understand
Callers
Gentleman playing I would say a lot of hillbilly a hillfolk
You know
He's at he's dumb
And fortunately
Voter suppression
Get worse
Because it'll get worse
A lot more of these
Trump type
Politicians are going to
End up winning
Alex
Evidence
But the system is working appropriately because he believes his ideology is the most popular
The people I disagree with
Depression is great
Because we're still
We don't even need those voters right
They're probably like
Just check to IDs
Absolutely
Lotto lotto
We're pretty clear that Russia
I'm stuff
Expensive it is unclear
Alex Jones we know that
Love him
Believing that
Putin is
Save the world basically
The Christ in the past
He made an agreement that is essentially treason with the US military we have a clip of him admitting to
To speaking with Russian intelligence
Alarming video
Still talks all the time about how great Russia
Like we had a clip a couple days ago
From
Present day
I've been talkin about a grapefruit
He constantly reports on Putin
Press conference
As if he was
He talks nicer
Why this neck
Clip trouble
Guarma red white blue
Handkerchief
Can food is the best
Totally
This is such an amazing how to be alive
Is absolutely hilarious
To try to
Arizona
Will not seek re-election
I want take a pause. Just tell the chat room
I respect the hillbilly I am not
I come from I come from Central Missouri I know I know that he'll 10 focus in his blood
Population of Ecuador
My grandparents
I don't think it's in this clip of Legos at another point in the episode Alex gets on this whole thing about respect
Kamikaze pilots
Narrative
Is
Is making me
Furious right
Because these
Facebook
Idiots
Are like
Because he's not seeking re-election he's finally able to talk about what all the Republicans on the house are talking about
Senior like you're still doing the s***
Rap
These horrible things
Just like Trump f****** one
You too but you're getting all these headlines like
Jeff Flake could he be the next hero
F*** off of a really nice parachute out of the office on it
McCain with of saving Obamacare voted
F*** you
Doing
Other bad stuff
Alex
Ocean Restaurant
Loser
That he's a fraud
On a pouzar
Here's a little joke video
Comedy world
Antonio
Bus to Nuri
The video of
But it is Billy Weaver Alex the mother girl
Disabled
Two dudes I don't know who they are and Daria his Russian
Employees standing behind him
That's all you need to know
That's it
Right that's all it's going on
Cradles
Huge bacon
That's good
That's not good
Cuz he has no sense of humor
That's why you think it's comedy parody
Thanks
Man
Pretty wild
Conservative ideology
Not being able to
Yeah I can hear you
Well because a big part of it
Tubi
Rooted and feeling left out
If you don't get jokes
Or you're not able to
It's very alienating being around a lot of comedians
I have the same sense of humor and sometimes it can be really tough from around like four people
The same sense of humor
And I just can't get in on it
I would want to destroy them
Very least I would vote against them
I would probably create a party that disagreed
You know usually one of the best parts of Road gigs with other Comics is huge
Just f******
You know you're driving
Yeah I've had or complain
Yeah right but you all you all kind of get the get the field
Road trips
The recently with a couple,
I swear it's like
What's your favorite holiday
Hope you're not a comedian if you're a few ever ask somebody that first
If you ask that question genuinely
No
My favorite holiday is go f*** you
Yourself get out of the sky
Anyway here's another clip that Russia and then Alex
Makes a bizarre admission
It was involved in the Cold War actions
Publix
Finance
Of Communism what history books
And they are not there
Screeching halt
Give me money
It's so simple
George Soros Affiliated grocery
Completely
Call Shelly products
And that's why I
She's amazing
But I need money
She's a YouTuber
What is 9
Red pill black
She's a black lady that talks about being red pilled
I guess I don't know Play a clip during their commercials
They need to fill their commercial time on the livestream and I have no commercials other than Alex
So they play like clips
From past episodes
Where she's talking about I think it was Zoe Quinn
Women involved in gamergate
Lenny Kravitz dick falling out on today
What's around me
I think it I don't know
I don't know where which
Targets of the gamergate
Stop
She contacted this red pill black
Lady
And was like Hey you were going
Going to get
Speaking out about stuff
Online
Be aware that you're going to get attacked
Buy a bunch of
You're going to,
Start harassing
Two dudes did start harassing
And her interpretation of it was
Is that a Zoe Quinn or whoever
Yes because she wouldn't
Team up with them it was right
So she's sick
The Troll Army of dudes her up
That's the only clip I've heard of
It seems like
Fallacious
It's wild
She could have had the moment
Possibly she could have been there she could have just turned that twitching
Instead she went
I mean you make a nice for yourself
There's a big Market of these Trump weirdos
Who need new personality
Let's get the rest of the
About Alex getting
Ensued
Or scroll effect
Amazing
But I need money
Cuz I'm looking at the budget I'm not paid myself this year
I'll put some money away just like a candle
Call it runs good shelter
Not having to worry about money but money is not my God
They can control us that way I want to make a successful
Also altruistic and chivalrous
I need fund
So
I haven't taken a salary or anything like that
In this next clip we already had to be
Beginnings of it
Is a little bit weird in this episode at the beginning there was some strange
Here is where he kicks it into
Legit
Esoteric
He actually finally makes the esoteric
These evil people think getting rid of that Sixers cool it's fine
Meet to do whatever you want
You get rid of the
Doors on the submarine
Bulkhead on a spaceship
The wavelength telling us to kill ourselves is not human
Oh
And
Experiment
It's real
Simulator
And it's so fantastical
Why would you care what other people thought about you
Why would you care whether you got a crappy car on new car
Why would you care about anything when you're on a planet
A big giant nuclear explosion
Not quite
What's going on
Watch out
Watch
If you look at the
She ready
I'm a man and woman together
Do a black child
Thomas and just suck
Credible intelligence
Consciousness
Gave us free will
And gave us the Stars
We do not own
Mostly dead
Can transmit out the space
Forever
Bother
Undertaker toys
My gut tells me this is kind of like a race
Wow
Start
This is just level one.
Level one
We going to pass level 1
Nope level 1
That little
That goes up to big game
You realize you're really little G
When you're standing next to
The Original Gangster
That ruined it
Control of us
Butt snakes
God what a loser
That guy knew that this was stupid
Music behind
Yakety Sax right
This is one of those moments where like it's clear that
Like
Getting into this mode that esoteric mode
It really takes it out about
Because he has at this is after he is
Oh no this is
Before
Interview this guy from Davos
The sky was
The turncoat
From Davos
Okay
That sort of thing he does this interview that goes on like 40 minutes ago
Something like that
Asteroid for the rest of
Temperature
But he's in a easy has no energy about the universe leave me alone
Images
To take calls
It's not great
Before he does
He
Okay
Level one
That's that's the life we live now
Level two
You get to God
You get to the Big G
I would I would hope so
Capitalized autocapitalize
Okay
Alright so your goddamn capital
Sort of agnostic
Flavor a lot of his believe it's possible that he believes that we are all but
Splinters of God
The tribe descendants of the tribes of Israel
If only 144,000
Going to get home to Bedford Forrest
Stan the tutors and Mayflower
Does he think all of them
Was that mean
No they're waiting for us to come along
But see the thing is the thing I think that bothers me most
Is that
If there's a level 1 and level 2 that implies that there is a level 3
Right
So what's level 3
Is that
God with a
Really big
What is why would you want to
Evolved it's going to happen is you're just going to realize how little you are
Experian
It seems kind of
I I think there's no that's you experiencing your true self and not because
No because it's not cuz the little G that's in you is part of the big
EG that is that so
Lupita's Bakery
Of course there's a level three I think that you're actually looking at
This wrong I can't level two
Well I think he's talking about genes in terms of
I got to thinking means god
Yes the chat room text me the G-Spot
Okay that's a good one
The
Force of gravity off the list of people I think are reasonable the chat room
Really
Human beings can only survive like at most 10
So that's true you make out of levels
Yeah you make that a big deal
Okay so
I think it's Google if you ever want
I think he's just talkin about type typing analyzation level to type 2
That's what I think you're talking about
I don't think you understand that classified
To like
Sweet
Checked out I'm over this
We've got to talk a little bit of news
This is what this is
Challenges AB this battle yet we've turned the tide think that God's good graces your prayers
Operation breakthrough
A level books
The best people
At the Crypt Keeper
And I call her
Cringe-worthy compilation
Infowars.com
McDonald cast radio show
Here is the cringe-worthy compilation
Yesterday we did not have the majority
Weather
So at that point
Just the same thing
She makes a small misstatement is like
We got it she's senile
Noises
Slow down
Adjust her face when she's laughing
Because I've just misspoke
Right and I would I'd like to make a very specific argument italic
Very
Wershe senile
She would not be able to recognize
Richie hit just misspoke
She would not be able to
We have our own Gabba
She would not be able to do that if he was senile
If she was really her brain a rotating like Alex
Just looking misspoken early-morning furthermore Alex
Do you want us to put
Together a Supercut of your headache crying and
About a million hours long as long as this podcast
Guess what
We have no interest in defending Nancy Pelosi
AR argument with your text
Nancy Pelosi is s*** but whatever
Alex
You do hate old people especially when their women
I just want it with you
This is just to cleanse your palate before we get into some bad stuff in the future
My new favorite
So
He's a little bit Texas
A little I told you this is going to get ugly and here's some
Well-meaning people that are dumb enough to get the orbit of the bushes
And I wonder why their butts get grab
Great
Beginning
Women
Women's fault it's the victim's fault. You shouldn't go you shouldn't dress like that you should
I'm going anywhere near the bushes which
F******
Maybe exactly
Such a
Unjust
Safari mobile
Migrate
It gets worse
Stop attacking victim
Right
Okay with saying everything
On a couple days ago talking about exploited
She put it right
One of the things that she said very specifically was we need real man to not blame
Women
Good job Alex
Great work Melly
Like I said
These
He says he's going to take calls but it's clear that he
He's just in no shape
To take calls
Or something
I don't reply
If I were him I wouldn't want a cold either
Your colors are
Take a collar with your callers are generally going to be like
Now here's why the Jews are at fault I'm trying not to
Alex
Beyond the control room
And then she's like a scary doll
Like a female Chucky
Flights
And it's just very very frightening
That
Iraq
I just keep saying George W bush in her though
Browser
Around
Seriously
Put touch with a ten-foot pole
Untouchables
Need poles
Instead of
Like taking any calls you just end up insulting the appearance of
That sounds right
See how f****** like
Girls
He's just asleep at the wheel
Such-and-such a
He's just waiting until f****** Paul Joseph Watson takes over the 4th hour
I can't do that
It's so it's so
Prophetic you can't kill time
Well I can do that quite well
Sure Bob's Burger
Will whatever productive when we meet when we meet
The kill time we're not going to just be like
We got to talk about this. We're just going to play Bob's
Episodes
I'm sure we can get the rights to that
No I just I just
Do that
Like I just don't even want to be a part of that
That because the easy response is of course
It's a fat f****** pig that's going to start talking
What about women on
On TV
Stupid and counterproductive
It's all just dumb
We're America were the fattest Nation on Earth
We just got to let that go
Edit certain point it's like yeah we're all disgusting weirdos human beings are gross mammals are horrifying
Y'all fukkit weird
Who cares
Great I don't even know where to direct my anger it's something so stupid and yet so offensive
I'm going to tell you to put the mic down to this house play
But just look at that little narcissistic bobblehead
Wonder if
Bush's Baked round out their family trade on those girls
I probably passed out
Postbellum Bones on them
That's rather people's kids
Go ahead and relax your phone calls now
I'm going to pause right here for a second
Because Exorcist music music
Started playing
Alex look to the side like really pissed off
The f*** are you doing
I'm trying
Need to get really
Creepy about
The bushes molesting their daughters
You f****** play Halloween music at me
What the idiots get over there
Fleetside I
Like holyshit
Also there's no way that I would want to be the caller immediately after
I wonder if the
Bushes
Their own chill
No
Let's go ahead and talk to your on here go ahead
This is Diamond Arizona
So although he said California
But be that as it may
Okay well I'm Course Arizona we're just like and McCain aldersyde
There is something with the bushes in the mittromney
Well during the primaries I was researching that if you go to
The reason the Marriott family
They're supposedly the Marriott Mafia of the West that nobody gets to be president unless you shake their hand
In Utah you know
What happened I looked up the board members and we've got the wrong we've got the bushes Allconnect
Western Mafia
Now let's take a step back
Realize that Mitt Romney never was president and Bush didn't even make it out of the primaries this time around so
Your argument is a little bogus
The same time
You make the
Point you should be making
Willie Waters
Billionaires
Run
Alexa
This is an issue
Maybe that's something that you should explore further
I'm guessing
She crushes it
And points out that income inequality is a huge issue
We need to have a stronger labor market
We all need to get together and see
We have to have a very high taxes on the wealthy
That should be f******
95%
Furthermore we should really
To take regents
YouTube the new deal
As well as dealing with all of what
None of the stuff you were yelling and ranting
I did just come up
Ciara Memoir of the show I did come up with a way to save the world
Okay
Add a new game show Raptors know it's a new game
They could make an appearance but they probably just be backstage hanging out
Malaysian
Deal or No Deal
I think that was the right response
But now
Do you get a glimpse into what's going on in my head while you go on these ramps
Alright
I bet Ben anyway.
Deal or No Deal
You should not have repeated
It would involve Howie Mandel again
Of course
That's right that's what
Asper, DDS
Might've done a condom later
I seem to have a visual of that
Highway Howie Mandel would be involved
I think you're just making fun of him
Because he lost all this
And instead of the banker it would be the state
They would call
And give you an offer
Okay
For a
Like I stated
Progress
Saved
Hey are we going to find this small playwriting company
Do you
Anyway just cuz I want to hear this one more
Welcome
That's the end of the show
So we're not going to listen to the end of Arizona
California first of all
Or she was from Atlanta
They're all very close on the maps
It was boring
Molesting children I don't
Playing as terribly as he could write
The 4th hour and
Turn that baby off
Alex
I mean we have a couple things wrong here we have one new very delightful
Don't be surprised
Calling all the part of the next
By foreign policy
Jesus Christ to be 25 minutes long
If you want to check us out our website is knowledge fight.com
Underscore fight we are at Facebook
Oh man we almost got out of it
Go to the iTunes
Knowledge fight
You can type in I think the last time I typed it in
If you go to
Knowl
We show up
Like 15th on the way
Anything less than that elbow we're nowhere.
Traction
From my Bryan
A chatroom ringtone
Ringtone
Remember when I went to work 80 my God
Six Mafia
They started out
I don't know they started up Dope Boy Fresh
Academy Award winners
Next song
Number one ringtone
I love it
That's an interesting post
That's something everybody around the country
SchoolBoy Q of course
Three 6 Mafia
Absolutely
The number one ringtone podcast
America
By the end of
The month absolutely
Baby got a week
Now we got five days at most.
Betty White
Dead air
What's up
You have to say at White family line
If we ever successfully done this because I have a new line at the end
Are you okay. So now it's all on me
You have to say
10 months before
No
I mean
There's just
I'm reminded of him now
Every time
Does the Bliss
Help at all did not help at all and help you get this guy out of your head and help me avoid turning
Around and looking
The grossest reminder of
This month
Employee of the state
Dealer do deal
Think we can get him out of that attic
Fast arri
Let me tell you something Dan
I just want to let this man know
May the wolf
Choked on his
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work