Thanks for holding
Alex
We work around and talk about Alex Jones
All the time
I think we talked about others
Literally everybody Alex Jones
The three of us the only thing we all agree on we talk about Alex Jones way too much
A really really knowledgeable conversation
Charlie Rose
Do you know very little about
Yeah that a new wrinkle to it I've studied up on you
Absolutely
Cuz I'm not I don't have any more Freedom Day
Real quick
Weird experience on a Avenue last day in office
Husband isn't like a real go f*** yourself my life there's been a lot of like you need to
To get out of here kind of last days or last days are unlike
F*** this
S***
The like
It's hard to time
Leaving
On your last day
I leave at 4:30 or do I was going to leave at 3:30 doctor's appointment
I timed it perfectly
Like I knew the bus
I was going to come into play
And so like I had to figure out
Alright I got to go I got to say goodbye to
Just about everybody
Cuz a lot of people would probably feel like I was a dick
If I didn't
People there
You're gone you'll never see any of them again now you go in with a respectful handshake has been a pleasure working with you
I'll tell you what I'm not leaked any
I don't think we can turn that to a verb and it said like
The tertiary goodbye
People in the warehouse
Work and then I was like
Send a group
Email clicked on the bus tracker
Oh no
We got 20 minutes.
I'm sitting in the office just drinking a beer cuz the people
8 to 10 minutes
Bright and then like I staring off into the middle distance drinking a beer by yourself
Of course I've been what's that time is open
I get up my
Y'all
What by what
That's what I say yours until the bus was coming
If he'll ever
My goal has been one day I'm there and then the next day people go
Is somebody missing and that's it
Irish goodbye
About having gone through the right of passage
You're now a young professional.
Did
I'm young professional propaganda fighter I appreciate it
Some people got to give a shout out to
To some of our new donators
Really excited about this we have
Donors who have joined onboard new policy wonks both
One with an I won without
Is so excited
So excited
So scared and one of them
Their mom is got it goin on
No
Maybe it is a para 309
Anyway this one is for the
Jesus I need a job by the job
This one is for Jessie with an i
Thank you very much for joining us
Thank you so much for joining up weird Uncle from Full House
A couple people who donated
Unspecified on our patreon poke
They are too generous
Really appreciate it
Decided to create a new level for them people who fall into this category
And I'd like to give another one to now that we have a
Specific label for it
I'm excited to hear this I have not heard
Maria and John Cena
We thank you so much you're very generous and we appreciate your help and I keeping the show float I was thinking about it
A policy wonk
We've got foreign policy
Protocols of Zion walk
But that's just a specific title that he has for himself but I was figuring
What is
Be like
Supreme title that we could give somebody
I decided
Maria and Johnson are officially globulin
Don't get mad until you're brilliant someone sodomites
You went for it on that murderer
Put something
Foreign policy wonk or globalist
You can do so by going to our website knowledge buy.com
Before the show
It is increasingly important as I now do not have a job and I just realized today we are 65% of the way
Towards you and I having to do a drunk commentary on The Obama Deception
Just a chip in a little bit if we can do our drunk commentary
And see if they would hope that other website
Get Mike Nelson to come over
Episode watch
Dial prison
Planets
State Farm
Jordan
Today we are fulfilling a special request
If one of our very special policy
Out there
Insisted
That we
Get
Does real name
Twitter
I think Alan Thicke would probably hide behind his Robin Thicke
Island
I don't know names are we don't know name going today
I won't be here in a minute
No course when you have your research and have your fine
Now the problem is I started drink
Start a drink
Coffee again today that's the problem
Coffee
Yeah there was a
The timer you didn't drink coffee while I worked at a coffee
Distribution Center
I drink a pot of coffee everyday
To say that I was on a long
Energy drink
That's too long now that I'm 33 years old
Anyway come back
Allen
That's how we go
Yes take a little trip
Time travel episode
He is requested that we go to May 2nd
City Auto request we do the longest
Preamble we've ever done I think we've done longer
Frankly
Bear so
I'm sure we've gotten up to the 25-minute mark
Undoubtedly
There is a
The reason that I understand that
Suggested this
Is it time to go back to
Is that
It was we wanted to see
What the spin would be
Of the
Osama bin Laden
Burial at Sea
Yes that was me that was
Unequivocal
Play Happy
This is the only good thing Obama's ever done
To make up a different reason for Wyatt have
Right or say didn't happen at all
This is actually the anniversary
Osama bin Laden
And killed year later
He's going to have the same narrative
Just to be sure I went back and listened to the 2011 episode on March 3rd
Sarah mazur excuse me and it's not worth going over
It's not that interesting
Accidentally
The 3rd of May
Gives us anime
Amazing glimpse
Into what
Kind of propaganda Alex Jones
Back in 2012.
Lakers even in 2015
Thought your investigation
Henry sound like
Particular
Style of thing
There's still all this s***
Really
All that active in 2012 so it's fun to go back because
Basically
Videos of Haley Busch
Not black enough
Ozark
Wheatley different
8 amazing ways this is how Alex starts out the show on May 2nd
2012 transmission
Your house
I'm really trying to get more your call but it always so informative
Sources
Also spoilers
Does not show up
Is f****** Calera
Alright
Military
Hours for Pacific Lee Afghan
Because I can't tell you how many emails come in
To be honest with you I don't have any mail
Right
Gmail email
I don't know how to do it
How does the Drudge Report
Probably get some five times the traffic
How do they do it
Middle River
On my phone and I use
I am to the crew
So you sound like a weird old man in the woods
EBay
But I think he's had one for a really long
I think he's I think he's he's really expressing his I don't know how
I don't really I don't I can't say I know
But this is an uninspired
This is
I want to talk to
Two army veterans from a reinforced my narrative but at the same time
I'm just going to tiptoe into this episode I'm not I'm not really feeling it
We'll see how this change
Over the course of time
A little bit
Here's what happens immediately after that last
Digressing
Michelle Goodwin reason is bad
Sending me emails
Hundreds of emails
The night even talkin about troops in Afghanistan
None of the bottom Bin Laden killing
Helicopter
The Martin killing
What is the Easter bunny I don't know why
Continuing are
Ridiculous
Ridiculous in the Easter Bunny
Easter Bunny and Santa Claus in
No it's the other way around the reservation
So he's
You are completely off the reservation
Belated weird discussion of
Disbelieve ability regarding
He later is like I'm going to Comedy mood as well
It's just like
UA like
He has no foothold here
Please just
You sort of Meandering like you said you was off the reservation
He's Rambo
Former and current Navy SEAL
Screen Actors Guild
I never even called the guys number
That's my problem
I'm just going into Maine directions remembered that ball
Now it's got to the point of all I think about it
It's just it now
Your son was around all the information
You are as well
I think this is your children
There's a pretty substantial difference
Between your kids and working
Can't access
Fighting is a globalist
Is there an item on the checklist
Garbage out
But in a way that fights the globalist
Raise my kids but anyway that fights the globalist
I just I was too busy taking out the trash and pay my taxes I forgot to call back has very legitimate whistleblower
Right
If you're mean miss you have life you have no due diligence at all you're just like
Let's imagine a scenario where curtain Mo he's the one of the guys
Left Infowars and says Alex Jones
Is a huge fraud
He's put that out on Twitter before if if in touch with me I would drop literally
Everything I was doing
What's going on
We talked to Larry Nichols
Incomplete
Yeah it's
Enduring is like I keep pointing that out but it's because
This is the first like 15 minutes of the show
Nothing
There's nothing to do no traction
Other than him saying
No One Believes the Osama bin Laden
Long story
No One Believes
Little kids
Cuz they're dumb and let me tell you something
Nobody believes in
What is that
The sad thing
Well that's the reason we have
Astarte
Okay
It's not one of the Greek ones I know of Demeter
Persephone in Greek
Let's not to go down the misology path I think we're engaged
I think that we can actually look into
We're going to have open phones for the military
Veterans
Broadcast
And of course co-author too many Tom Clancy books
Of course the CIA and the American Hospital
And Dubai all that came out on CBS nose after
Doctor
Walter Cronkite came out and said
I'm going to say he is at the very least
Willfully misinterpreted
Quite a bit
Yeah quite a bit
Cronkite statement
But he's mad
Actually I think I
Play this just straight from my computer so let's
Here is Walter Cronkite in an interview in 2000
About bin Laden
Something that he thinks is a problem
Press freedom
Tell us your thoughts on this
Momentous issue exists
That there was going to be allies
Seachange
In the how we practice
Journalism
Until I read a couple days ago if that the
Traditional Networks
Pedigreed
That ended indeed the cablenet
News networks
Agreed with a request
Brian
Does the government
That if not carry
Then why
Propaganda broadcasts in this country
He goes on to discuss
How I
Other countries
By Kyle
BBC another
Now all these other news outlets
In foreign countries
Do play them
Are you think so
Sort of irresponsible
And it's a bad sign for the Press
The government is telling them
Are these things
I may just roll over like an AI Quia
It's new
It's not really too much of a surprise now to see so many
Fred screaming shows
Because
Well that was
Reasonable
Intelligent
Also boring
Super boring very measured speed
Understandable
Clearly a 2000
He believes a Bin Laden still alive
Based on
Interview
Events
Of the alarm
And you had an interview with Larry King and he said he believed that
Clearly
He's believed in the bin Laden
I'm still alive
He believes that Karl Rove may have
Set up the bin Laden
It came out in 2000
He says this as it relates
It being Advent
Contagious to the
TobyMac
The Bush campaign
They bring out this
Terrorist
He's not saying Karl Rove
Although Alex
As what
Nothing.
Leaving isn't play
But
He's saying that it's
I mean if you take the
The context of that last clip the
The 2002 interview into consideration
With what he says in that Larry King interview
They combined to be like why are they putting out this tape now
When
Before
They had a restriction on playing bin Laden
And obviously that's a really good
I've nothing to do with Bin Laden faking
Dead or anything like that
Walter Cronkite
Does not match
It doesn't check out
Necessarily
Albright
Very quietly discourse run knowledge fight
Bronchitis
I've never aspired
To be either Madeleine Albright was quoted
Suppose that the Bush Administration has Osama Bin Laden hidden away
Somewhere and we'll bring him out before the election
This quote from
Fox News analyst and roll call executive editor port
Kondraki
Goes on to say she was not
Smiling
She's insisted that she was speaking tongue-in-cheek
Mr kondracke immediately went on the air to repeat the comment
Was made to a person I thought was a friend
Smart enough to know the difference
Between a serious state
We've seen in the past that Madeleine Albright is not that great at making off
Pick up statements
She is like most sociopath
Devoid of a sense of
Number 10 on the show
Misrepresent
Yoshi's
Gone on record and apologize
That's clearly a joke
Or more contracts is just sort of an opportunist
Yeah really works for Fox News
Waterboarding pretty vociferously during the bush era
He said in 2006
You would figure the terrorists will plan more upsurge in violence in Iraq to help
Bush's adversaries
Arrow
Went on Fox News and was saying that like
Obviously terroristic
Lincoln
Democrats and terrorists
He has a pattern of uncritically airing
Conservative propaganda pieces of news on his
Is Fox shows
What is that a couple shows on Fox
A progress for America in
In particular
He's equated NSA domestic spying with World War 2 codebreakers
That is
Dumb on an offensively mistake
I have ever
Do you think it's okay I could just like this
Made in the present I think anyone else I think anyone was watching the video can see that in your face
That's
Bananas he's also been pushing
That's exactly what that mean haha
That's what's up.
All right he's also been pushing for war with Iran
That's at least two thousand five
Cuz he's a hero
Right so I don't take him too seriously as a
Great source
As a completely stupid and unreliable source who is
More than willing to lie lie lie Direct
It seems that way
When I looked into like
What could Alex use in
Is like
People prominent people who have
Maybe cast
Aspersions on the idea that was killed in 2011
Comes up that
Alex Padilla
Benazir Bhutto
Okay Benazir Bhutto I have an interview in Tucson
Fun name
Great
She was interviewed in 2007
I'm sad that someone had murdered of them
And it's unclear if you listen to
The context of the entire interview
It's not
Relieved
Clear at all if she's misspeaking
Because that's not the point of the inter
David Frost
And at no point does he like hold on
Hold on you're telling me it was on Dunlawton was murdered
What's going on
It's just a big move past it in a way
If you watch it
She meant to say another name
Countryside Osama
Okay it's not
He was murdered
Doesn't jibe
With the ideas that these other
Conspiracy theorist
Of him dying of like kidney failure
So that
To me make me feel Overload at my rank
Oh yeah oh yeah
Benazir Bhutto
Walter Cronkite Madeleine Albright terrible examples I'm not here to
Discuss whether or not like
I'm certain that Osama Bin Laden was killed in 2011
In the context that we are told
He was
I don't know
From everything I can glean
I believe it
Enough
Because the things that people keep pointing out things like why would they throw his body into the ocean
That sort of thing
That's not that weird
The arguments of we don't want to create a holy
Trying to
To him or something like that
Does mustard for me I don't need
Much more
I mean they could have of course buried him
In the middle of the desert
And slaughtered
Camel
Child
So that only a child
Calf
So that only its mother
Knew where the
And then they could let the mother
Who would always know where
To the body saver
Visit
Is an ancient
I like it like that
But they also killed like
40 body
That the way our government works
You need to set up like
Six organizations in order to get that app
You know it'll be a lot of red tape
So now I want to talk about
For a second
She is a psyop dude I do okay
Jesus
The saying that you came on in 2000
To say that Osama Bin Laden was dead
He came out with all the
When you considered in the context of a stye operator
Operator
There we go
I was waiting for it you don't want anything
Happened pretty consistently throughout our Wars like these things happened in Vietnam and Korea in World War II
Rumors of the leader's death
The other side
Very popular
It's something that you do hoping that the forces will become this disenchanted
Are there more
Thinking that their leader is been cut off
You see this over and over again throughout the history of War
IHOP guy is coming onto Alex the show
I'm staying
This
Traditional
War siop language
That leads me to believe he was up
Now the problem is
When you're working with terrorist organizations
Then you're working with these nebulous
Groups like lk2 was an early 2000
They weren't fighting for bin Laden
They were fighting
For ideology
Either fighting again
Fighting against
Murder
Right against themselves
This siop was
Successful
Terrorist
They would not stop them
From The Crusade they were on
Or from the wars that they were in
The only end result of the
This psyop that I believe
I was running
Is to make American
Distrustful of Their Own
Which I don't know if that was the
Or an unfortunate
Consequence
But it certainly Bears out on Infowars
And it's not like we needed that
Help
To the government for a good long while now for good reason
That's really what I wanted to talk about terms of
The rest of this is not going to
To do with bin Laden
Of course it's the anniversary
Kohl's
Getting off track
But
He takes calls from like
A wife of a Marine
Who has gossip
Here's one here's one of the calls that he gets
Paolo yes I'm this this is very nice
Fake laugh
Wright's glass
Formation
And so like all of this been although he wants to
So there's nothing
Want leave the song
And then
For nine years
Weekend at Bernie's
From place
To place to play
Let me fun absolutely
The number of people that would require in order to pull this off is
Like the amount of people that would take to hide this
Among two different Administrations
Like what would that be too elections
Difference every
Department offices
I think there's only one
Conspiracy where
The infrastructure
Sure did not break it anyone
Time
Scientology
Infiltrating the IRA
Interesting
Rock.
90 people
All who had worked for like
4 years plus
And they they
You did this
Just deleting all of scientology's record
Some good work
Yeah I know they all have needs a m
What's that
Get a raise
DC food now that's
Alex comes up with
And I can
Improve all three of
The stories he tells are low
Speaking of a cashier she want me just cover this
Cabinets Now
Man arrested in prison for using cash
It was an older $50 bill
And then finally
And they
So let's talk about this story
Did you just say he's bad yeah he's bad because you got to go change his money
Oh no I agree this is bad
What are you saying even if you do use a fake $50
Take your $50 bill away and be like hey,
This is a story about a man in Tennessee
Old $50 bill
So that the clerk at the Quick Mart
Isabelle notified police
Because the fraud
You have that
Mark anybill / 20
Bill is fake
And so they called the police
And here's a quote from
The front side of the bill was off-center and it didn't feel like a normal bill it didn't
It did look to be counterfeit
Officer Brock Warner said
This report
We thought
It was weird because it had Jefferson Davis are very old $50 bill
Order took the bill to Tubac
Where was determined as the old at 1
Improving real buy a black light and magnifying glass at another
A Judicial commissioner had Gasper that's the guy who tried to use it
Released from jail after 3 hours
For 3 hours too long and a holding cell
And hoarder apologize for the arrest
The report said
Gasper was told by Horner to take the bill to a bank and have it exchanged
For a newer one
So they
If I can say like your bad take this belt
This pill
70 years old
It shows up as counterfeit by our modern
You got it this should be out of circulation
But also you can hear in there
She apologized about it because it doesn't misunderstanding that is very reasonable to make the pain marked it is counterfeit
Are you the Black Lightning
Magnifying glass
Kids story
Gasper
Where did you get that f****** bill I don't know why does he still have that f****** Bill Gray's how old is he
He was an old
Also
The bill was probably worth more than $50
Imperfections is usually that that's usually very collectible
We could have gotten at least five hundred bucks for that
58. Now that is marked by the counter
I think that makes it even more excited
Reasonable understand like situation where they should have been
Because there's a chance that he is
Or something like that
That is I don't care
I don't really care to have that debate
Just the debate that Alex Jones is wrong isn't
Doctor he is wrong
He's you pretending that the crime is using money
And the crime
Which turns out it wasn't a crime and I apologize for holding him
Yeah it was that it was
Don't be counterfeit even the cop we got there
Thought it was a female Alex
Articles
Christian Spanish
Austin
Software engineer
Weldon middle class guy
What happened
He was down on the
Talking about Silver's is like 67 years ago
Do some people call the police
Illegal to have a silver coin
And then.
Sounds right
And
College campus
Criminal record software engineer
Part of the community development software this well-known out there
American Dream now
Enough
Details in here for me to read a little bit between the lines
Evict you done f***** up
Not totally but also I could find no evidence
He was actually arrested
I can find Noah his name
I know the date of the inside
I can't find an arrest record from anywhere around
I found the guys LinkedIn
Maybe maybe
Christopher Amoroso
Is a LinkedIn page
I mean why would you put I was in prison for a few years
It's not a good thing.
Charge
Do it look Noah look like a normal guy the only two things I could find
From Chris Italiano's
They were in any way
Interesting
The page from mufon
Which as we know is the mutual UFO Network there's no information
But his name is on a move on site
Okay the collection of ghost sightings or alien sightings
Things on the site
But it's empty
Completely app
So I don't I got nothing on me
Although they really missed an opportunity
It should be called moveon.org
Yeah probably
3 dates
Yeah I know they said they still got time
So
The other Rave that profile.
Cannot do
So the other thing I found was a organization called Liberty
Put out at this camp
They put out a periodical newsletter
And I found their newsletter
From April of
Which is why impressive Thanos
Was allegedly
Skill
Who else would have gotten
Like I said.
I can't I can't find any like mugshot
Can't find any record of him
Doing time or anything like that
If you did I apologize
It's been I don't mean to disparage but
Out there public rec
Because you guys had a falling-out and Alex didn't want to talk
Talk to you anymore so we just made up a reason I've been Liberty. Org
In This Very
Terrible
The newsletter
Zine yeah it's
Just a word
Basically there's no way
Incident of the month
Now man
On April 14th 2003 in Austin Texas an incident occurred that just shows how is
Small misstep can create a big problem
And most unfortunately this incident
Involves crisanta
One of our most
Successful Associates in the rco
South Austin
Like so many times
Chris offered a cashier
A choice of either a $10 silver liberty coin
Or $20 Federal Reserve Note to attend a comedy show
How do University of Texas venue
I didn't think much
Police officer was on guard next
Nearby
Chris paid with a Federal Reserve Note is that was
Preferred by the cashier and went into the show
If your newsletter calls it
A Federal Reserve Note
Also we can already tell he was at a University of Texas venues
Blue collar
Dailybreak
Goes into the show
Shortly the police officer found Chris and ask to see the
Quote coin
I think the quotation marks in there a little
F*** off
Little bit of a
Slayer
I mistakenly the officer thought it was illegal so we asked
Chris to step outside with
Which he did
Now I'm going to read through the
God the subject
I believe that
The person who worked
The door
He thought this guy was trying to pull ups
I am flag down the police officer
So during a brief discussion the officer and the backup officer asked Chris for his identification
Chris refuse
Stating his fourth and fifth
Digital rights
The officers informed Chris that he would be arrested if you did not produce
When Chris finally produces ID he also produced his
To carry a concealed weapon permit
The inquiry as to
Where the weapon was an ultimately
Chris being arrested for having a weapon and for him
A school
So there we go
Perversion of it
So Chris is a lunatic who likes to carry guns wherever he goes to schools and comedy show
Is not realize that it's illegal to do so in public space
This is like a school
My sovereignty
I just heard the massive
Collective sigh the two police
Mosers ad
I have the 4th
They're like
F***
Yeah what are you
Second Story
Had nothing to do with money
It has a
It's money
Inasmuch as
Someone being so slightly suspicious about someone's intentions
To the the actual problem
The classic assholes / conman move is like
I got a $20 bill.
You do just pay with a Federal Reserve Note
Chunk of gold
So here's the next
ICD-10
The Best Buy
And he had
Film
And he is exalted original
Kubz Scouts
Beautiful
Engraving
I know because I went to the u.s. mint once when I was a kid
The guy he gave
Chores chores the children
How to store
I need a friend
$2 bills
We're selling
As one sheet uncut
I guess I can get arrested for that I bought at the u.s. mint
But
Stories
Unkind
He didn't
Reserved
He had some left
This is illegal this is real
Managers and all of them were so stupid
I was just walked out security guard walked him
Thought it was illegal in the cops were so ignorant
Episode
Ignorant
Chipotle
Using $2 bills Best Buy
Customer on
Mass murder
Actually like 7
Kubz Scouts
I left a lot of your response
Serta Illustrated
This is what his show was like back then
It's wild this is
Me rambling b******* information
What's in what's
What movie was that that we went to in the theater
It was a beautiful
It was great I thought we were talking about
Cloud Atlas
I love that movie
It was all
Yeah but it was
It's that like
It's not a show man
It's it's fun to listen to do because we're going to get to is
Hilarious
Ms episode just maybe one of my favorite things I've ever heard on the show
Since we started doing this podcast
Man I used to listen to Alex Jones like 5 years ago and I've always been
Why the f*** would you do that
He's an insane man
Just kind of cookie and stupid moments where it is
One of the things that I love the most about love line
Background used to listen
Sure
It felt like they were trap
There was a there was a certain amount of like
If late night radio they're stuck in this studio
And I got to feel tired so Adam come up with little games and stuff like that himself
And there's a feeling of that a little bit with Alex Jones
In 2012 of like
He's trapped in the studio
Where is now
If you look at
Pictures of what a studio look like back then it look like s***
Not like s*** but compared to now it's not a million-dollar Studio
Is a feeling of like
I feel this time
Let me ask about this boy scout thing
That I liked about radio
About amateur independent radio
Save a ramshackle quality to it
Is popping down into the
Right right
So Alex is lying about this story
Three stories in a row about money
Illegal
How to use money
This is from a world
Everyone knows is
Is dumb
Even his listeners back then or like
Alex
It's not illegal to use money
It's not great to use stupid money because
People are going to get
Confused yet so even in the world article about this
What do you say
It says
According to the song report
The police arrest
Report noted one employee noticed some smearing of Ink on the bills
That's when cops
We're called
One officer reportedly noticed the bills ran into
Sequential order
Which is suspicious
Generally
Cuz people
Would you Rob
Smearing ink on the bill also could come from
I like
A gel pack or something like it
There's a lot of reasons why that would cause a radish
Secret service agent of them being that it had a
They called in a secret service agent
Because of this
The secret service agent Lee Turner eventually arrived Claire the bills legitimate
According
The police report
Sometimes
Smear on money
Which is an information
That's not something that people know
Also Alex is lying about the
The fact that he was teaching Boy Scouts about
Constitution
That's not what I was doing
That doesn't sound right at all
Tours
Does BestBuy
Stereo
Installed
Some car
Not buying so
She seems like a nice guy
I don't have anything against
It was only a matter of time
Or whatever the police department
I don't know if you would win
I don't like
They did not act out of line if you can't use two dollar bills
But there was a miscarriage
Perception
I don't know
Easter Best Buy Personnel repeatedly
By the way his name is
Is Mike bellesa
Which is an anagram for bike molesta
But you would not be charged
Listen to the stereo on his son's car
He received a call from the store saying it wasn't
Charging
As a means of protest
But bolesta decided to pay the 140
$10 bill
57 crisp new $2 bills
As the owner of capital city student
Tours the Baltimore resident as an ear
As I Hardy Supply
Of The Uncommon current
He often gives
Isabel's.
Tours for meal
Quote the kids don't see that many 2 dollar bills so they think it's the greatest thing in the world
They don't want to spend them they want to save them
I've been doing this started the company
All Stage my little comic protest $14 or $2
So
I mean that's not a good bit but I get it but it's saying someone is like a all the nickels
I think it's less effective because it
It's just 57 $2 bills
Supposed to
You know like five
Whatever have your foot
Didn't realize they were leaking in
Instances of Alex
Misleading telling bulshit
Stories to Triana
Enforces narratives that like
Fiat currency they're trying to make it so you can't have real money they want
Wanting a cashless Society
And so you use it
Interesting
One day
The Prime Minister was like
Like
Interesting
Now that is a great idea
To go paper
But
Roughly 85% of people in India to not have
Credit cards are any
The same is true in the
Impossible to m
All the
Really fuk up
Maybe that's what they should start doing
Probably absolutely
So Alex
He's just trying to bolster this Narrative of globalist want to get rid of cash so they can
Control what you purchase
Soundtrack everything
By telling three bulshit story
Crazy
It's so easy
So easy to see through
The Simpsons do only make one house of horrors episode
They come up with 3
Three separate source
Possible that salad
So at this point we've already seen
About Alex
Dairy Queen
Are you not as good performer
No he's a little bit
Cuz I can track down all these stories
If he'd just been super vague about it will be much more difficult for me to find these to be like
Nope you're wrong
If we haven't learned that trick yet
But here in this next clip
You know what we did
Agree on things but I think you're
Right there is a little bit but
In his next clip we're going to get
Time
We're going to get to see a similarity between
I saw yesterday and didn't cover
Pilot newspaper
Norfolk Virginia
Black on white crime
Reading at church and Brambleton
The story is 42 weeks
By hundreds of young black people this is happening all over the country
100 epidemic
And the police
When they complained went for help for told
Car will not going to help you what do you want us to do
Sounds like the police
On the shopping outlet
Is this is very dangerous
The Fosters
Cars race Wars
As you know
Nbcla
The media tried to push this to get us fighting with each other
No boys
Immediately
On Facebook about it
Bragging
Some black folks
And so what's going to happen is the average self-loathing and everything
Racist but fearing
About white people
Well I better look out
So
Even
Universal
Favorite
Bulshit there
Always like
Black people
If you were nicer to White
People we would like you more as like
You're just going to make white people scared
Good
Look up
Be far more afraid. Here's the
He's not why
That is a real store
I looked into it
And
A lot of the context is
It is real
There was a couple that was driving at church and brand
Does intersect
In some place in Virginia
There were a bunch of
Kids
Seems like an exaggeration
There were dozens
Okay it's okay
The dude in the car
Cuz he got out of
They were wandering around
In the aftermath of Trayvon Martin murder
And they're blocking
But you got out of the car
And they worth
And the police ended up
Now the part about shut up and get back in
In your car
Isn't misrepresent
The police
We're interviewed about that may talked about how
They have got reports of
Gunshot
Another part of town that evening
And so when they were telling them to get in the car
They were like
Get in the car
Because yes
It was a protective thing I believe we made the decision
To get them off
The streets as immediately as poss
Right so that was what was going on is there
The article itself site
It's one Twitter comment where someone said I would do it for Trayvon
It's not good reporting
But the other stuff
Surrounded
The stuff about the paper refusing to
To cover it because it's
Black on white crime is not
True all that stuff is just that that
Is that that part isn't true
Well
I know
Are you still don't want people beating up innocent
Some people
Do you want to meet like
It's understandable
I would say it's understandable I don't think
But I get it
Yeah I get it I still think there's an image
Victim in it
Is there
You don't know anything about this guy
I don't either
So Edwards
There's a lot of assumptions you have to make
Norfolk Virginia Virgina
The more important piece
Is this is Alex
Driving
She's a bunch of black kids
All of them very frustrating angry about Trayvon
He thinks
F*** it you know what we can't be having this gets out of his car
Starts mouthing off
We don't need to get this ass
But that might not have been that might not have been what you got out of the car we don't know that
Come on that narrative
Tracks
For you but you're just doing what Alex.
Because that's the opposite of what we do
Just sort of like a guessing what a story will yet
Stabbing Fargo
Throw a rock at you
Is a good juxtaposition not that
Switch around this is a body swap comedy yeah you're going to be very angry this entire time and
I'm just going to chill having
Harrison you think I'm
Not chill
I want to make is that this
Idea that he has
Espousing
About
Is being a race war narrative story reinforces that is the exact
C-store
So the game he plays is very clear
Edit repeat
Despite whatever the contacts
And you could be
You could make a good case for him just haven't got lucky
That the headline
Actually did
Matchup with the red
Marley's matched up with
Some of this and it's not incredibly
Sensational
And actually I got to be honest
Read that article
Okay because when he's talking about the person on Facebook he's referring
Into something that we
Was in the Arctic
That one post
I got to get to the bottom of this
So I told you earlier
Take call
From app
Veterans
Who Outlook will agree with him
He's crashing at so far taken unfortunately
He gets bisque all pretty early
And it destroys the entire restitution
Hey Alex I'm calling from FEMA region for two quick points and I'd like you to look into piggybacking on one of the
Stories did a couple weeks ago
I have a cousin who's married to a
Soldier stationed out in Stuart
Brigade Homeland
He told her
The guys that blew up that Fella's house in Roswell Holcomb County Marshal's uniform
All those guys were off duty that day
What did they were actually soldiers
From Stuart
It look into that number two
Viper Squad
Hanging out on Interstate 40 is he going to Memphis in the little cut off there where it's goes down since 7255
23 police
Hey where's the 23rd District in Tennessee
He said man I don't know what that is there's no such thing
That's bulshit just do a Google search you'll find the 23rd District it includes the city of
Franklin
Nolensville tops
Open station Spring Hill
It's just south of Nashville it is
However
40 + 55 is he stalking
Nobody's not near there
Congressional district
Is very real place
In Tennessee
Memphis is straddled by the 8th and 9th District
But
The chicken man
Is what the
Destroys the rest of Alex Jones Show what happened
But you do
Cigarette
Cigarettes
Do this burn my chair
That's what I did
Okay
I apologize
Do you know about the chicken
I do everything
So
Will the gentleman by the name of Andrew word
Or
Could be jumped out of a gym
I would totally go see him do a headlining spot
So
A words
The chicken man
I was a guy who lived
Georgia
In Roswell Georgia
He had a couple of chicken
One part of the story checks out
Then you got a bunch more
And his neighbors
Started to
It really matter
Cuz it was just a house
Yeah
Because
These animals were super loud
Pretty value
For sure there was an order that adjudged
Told him that he had to restrict the number of because
We live in a society
And so he refused to comply with that order
He's a chicken
Because he wouldn't get rid of it
Contempt of court
Behind on his mortgage payment
It's while he was in jail
And unfortunately that led to his house
Put under
So he's in debtors prison
Call hope so
That ironic master
So on
March
Fulton County Marshal's came to his house to
I don't even hear from a hubby
We can Post article on the
But a standoff ensued around 12:45
Words taking this is where we find out what happened
The chicken man
So the issue to was that
He was supposed to be in court that day
As I as I understand
There's a guy named Mike pichette
Not related
Are you the reporter for Channel 2
Towards his home on Alpine Drive or Fulton County Marshalls
We're gathered outside for the
Eviction
Words told pechenik
He was scheduled for a quarter. Sat morning on a traffic citation
But feared that Marshall's would repossess his home while he's gone
So you didn't
So he's in the house
I mean I guess that's
To play
Around 12:45
P.m.
Words called the cell phone is like a local TV reporter Mike
Who was outside the home
To leave the property
He told pechenik
I can't tell you what's going to happen
But it ain't going to be pretty
Moments later the home exploded
And started a fire
CBS Atlanta reported that fire officials found a deceased individual inside but could not
Confirm that it was
It was
Investigators. Gasolina.
A detonation device
Inside but the cause of the explosion remains under investigation
Reported the day off
So the other quote that he had that he said to Mike
Pieczenik on the phone
Right before the explosion was
I appreciate everything
Brother I appreciate everything you've done
And then so you blew up
I feel like that
Was a
Probably fine
Except for all the f****** chickens and pigs
Every just if they just had an if they just taken him away although he probably would have blown up
Call the pigs according to the
Stuff that he
Posted on a bunch of like weird Meetup
Groups in Monterey
Social media star
Like to the point where Cube
With willing
To die for the chicken
There's something
Grossly romantic
That's why he's called the chicken
I need the story
The story that Alex's
The telling is
Like I mean I guess
These Federal Marshals Federal Marshals
What would you do
Is a army base
Soldier group now
Well we call ourselves the soldiers from
B Moore down the line
But for basic premise is that there are soldiers
Personating
Deputies
Sounds right and they blew up his house
For an unknown reason
Madeleine Albright was running the
Probably wanted to build a biodome there which doesn't make sense
Spurs and there is no biodome now throughout the f****** house
That doesn't make sense
You are bothering your neighbors
Roosters
Do one
Something and that's wake people up
Bigfoot
It's very discourteous
I don't like the fact that he lost his house
Right
Like while he was in jail he couldn't make his Morgan
I think that's this is well I feel a tremendous amount of empathy
Examone
Couldn't hurt
Soundproof the home they were just trying to
The film the movie biodome
He misheard.
I'm so if it's next to a clip we see that Alex Jones
Totally believe the caller who is brought up
The soldiers from Stuart
Narrative of blowing up the
Spoiler alert
The reason Steve pieczenik hangs up
Is that
Alex
50 minutes
Anti
Alex Koch back from break after Steve has gone
A stable just like
I called in to talk about
I got to go I got to go
Steve pieczenik
Assassin or whatever the f*** I overthrow government
That sounds fun
Take a break
Breaking news
Ketchup
But
Who the person is
Call Melendez Bay
Everything you said like tumblers just clicked
The police
I told the sheriff
So is that piece exactly what he said in the first
Course and it's a relative
Has a spouse
That works
Stewart's this is third-hand information
You can sit around
Yes
Here say it's nonsense
And let's listen to this next clip
So we can get like Alec being a little bit Patty
Pretending he already knew everything
Of course and then we can get a clear sense of what the allegation
Actually is
What they're training to do in their day-to-day training where police uniforms
Country
I argue that doesn't take trainer
Put on a shirt
Do they even need to do that they could just give him a badge and call him playing close
Right we have to we have to train you to wear a different uniform it's very dumb
Actually impersonate people that okay
We're going to send you the Tennessee
Tennessee accent
Is any voice and say I moved here from Missouri
Let me tell you this
One of the Hallmarks
To the police if they don't like to answer questions so you don't really have that
Prophesying with a citizen
It looks second-city traveling group
Actually there
To teach
Soldiers from Stuart
Fulton County Marshal
They're training in these lovely Uniforms on the soldiers are like
What are we doing
You know if you have a lot of dissent within the range
Call Terrance Stewart
Interview
District
Which is the wheelbase
Stitches directly
Hell is this is where there
Evil
Victory believe cannot advertise themselves
More like
This narrative is.
I don't there's not much
Cuz the the motive is not strong
Killing the chicken man
Is
Has to be its own motor what else
The chicken man
What else
Who is chicken
That's the real question
FEMA camp
Keep buying them chicken
Great cuz I have secrets
Only God knows what goes on in the heart of
Chicken follow the
So Alex probably would say that this is like the idea of police killing you
Listen to f***
Hip Hop
Know why people are angry about
The other thing is you trying to bring in this idea that these soldiers
Where's the military
Is impersonating
Because that would breach Posse Comitatus
Nothing better than an obscure law that has a Latin name already
Newsreel the ACT I guess that says that
Accept act of Congress
The military is not allowed to operate
In police Act
Of course that's kind of cross the Rubicon
It's not because there is the stipulation
Except by an act of Congress
We're going to get to that later
But anyway Alex's
He tries to spend the narrative that
Like
The Malt The Fulton Marshalls
They don't know what happened in the sheriff said that they weren't working that day or something I got
He says it's in the paper to mainstream news
I can find nothing
Of this I can't find any of that information
He doesn't provide any backup to any of it
And just a caller told
So after this
Reel Inn
Information
About the
VSCO
Hey Alice good afternoon
Join the ranch
Yeah I always enjoy a good Ranch especially on Infowars I'm originally from
In Georgia at work in law enforcement is where I cut my diesel enforcement was
Ashley in the Roswell area in Fulton County
And women think I want to point out is
Fulton County in metro Atlanta Judy if they have a sheriff's office and a Marshal's office
Different divisions of law enforcement the sheriff is an elected Constitution
Constitutional
Anna Marshall is an appointed position
On The Board of Commissioners
And the Marshall physician and his Deputy Marshals
Mainly what they're there for is the movement of inmates
Pretrial Detention Center
Going forward for trial in this earth acoustic imagine
When they leave jail and go to the courthouse to Marshalls are kind of their 12 kind of fit and babysit the inmate
Conceivably you might need those people if you're going to
To take this guy in
Who seems resistant
Yeah it's a little bit of a stretch
It's a little bit of a stretch but it doesn't
Themes apps
No I think I buy this
Okay
Pandora waiting arraignment for court hearings in this order thinks it's highly unusual to me
That the marshals would be the one doing the Civil process on the chicken man
And Roswell you in the papers
Homeland right at the house
Probably more info towards you Alex when you're reporters
Went through what you're calling it feels like a capitol building Roswell city hall
Roswell Police Officers proper what they actually are a municipal complex
They work for City Hall they do not work for the police department
If you can imagine their kind of trumped-up Bayless
So when Alex Jones
Crack team of reporters down there too
Two bailiffs
Sprite and said we weren't involved
And that spiraled out of control into like the police involved
That's my guess based on everything I know about Alex Jones
Kotoko doodle
Along with me and Maya
A story about
I think I'm coming from
Position to or trying to start a race war
Start a race war
We just been winning at
Before we get too deep into that cuz I don't want to get into that
Because we have something
Really important
So we have two more clips
From the May 2nd episode
Then we're going to go to the May 3rd and I'm going to put on my policy
Ewok hat
Okay cuz I'm going to talk.
First
Will you give listeners of warning so they can deposit turn it off
The end of the show on May 2nd
Is exactly what I was talking about
Alexina
Trapped in the studio
He knows that the Bilderberg count
Is coming up
It is in Virginia
And to what he does
To fill the last
What's a half hour of his show
He's trying book reservations at the Marriott
It's great
It's so good
Bonaire
Actually I don't have a clip of it but John bowne
The guy who only appears in those
Curable voiceover reports
You don't see his face
But you hear him over the mic
Just talking to Alex
Very creepy
It's very weird voice over
To be honest it kind of sounds like he's high
I'm not entirely sure I don't want to put that on it but
He doesn't tear
Begin
Alex trying to get reservations at
Coming up
May 29th
Through
June
Is dates are slightly off
But his location
Thanks
I'm going to be there
Yes I'm going
That would be nice and
I want to say
This is killer this is this is kind of long
So please tell me if you want to pause at any point in telling me that we about to listen to
Is Alex Jones
A reservation
These people for information about
The Bilderberg Group
Alright it's Bethany's firework
This is
This is one of my favorite long-term clips
Great
Big Lots
Adidas
Also
This is probably awake
Because he didn't tell people that he was recording
The 3rd of June
I'd like to find out when I should arrive for that what time it starts
I'm sorry ma'am I can barely hear you what you say
Who is coming in that far out
Okay well can I book a room actually two rooms with a king-size bed
Add please
From
Let me see June
31st of June
You are definitely going to get the reservation
High quality service
Please see our privacy tabletop ariat.com to understand how we
Underwater
Whether you're traveling on business or Leisure sure you're ready to go
Busy day over at the Marriott
This is also I'd like to say what what do you doing instead of talking to Afghan veteran
Or anybody about what happened with Bin Laden trying to prove his point
Everything up call Marriott
Gorgeous
Call the pub
Disconnected
You couldn't
Country Club
My son is back in the years old
Also I think I might be what
Because this is a free divorce
You took our son to Bilderberg
He's a global is now
Oh fun story I looked up the attendees of
The Bilderberg conference
Man
That f******
Interesting
It's called Marriott
See if he's there
I'm sorry
Oh yes sir are you there in the pub right now
Can I talk to reserve a couple tables
Birthday party
For my friend
Coming up
The evening of June 1st
Smooth
You need to talk to our planet
Reservation
Another that special conference coming up
I can't sell it because I don't have access to
All Detail Service
Hazel wow
Still take it off
Big truck
I'd like to see about booking a special jar.
June 1st
Basically
This is Alex Jones I'd like to have a birthday party
For David Rockefeller
Well I mean I guess
Meeting is going to be there that's a couple hundred people
English-style Pub
Contact you
This is on here
Close conference thing cuz I thought I was coming to a close conference
I'm more than happy to look into that for you I usually the pub is still open
I can take that down
You know what I am actually know so I apologize I have not
Another eggplant
About a week
David Rockefeller
Carson
The best contact number for is 512
Smart
Nichols slightly workload I am ready to go
Filter bleeps out of him
Server address
Can you transfer me to our reservations
Everything these days
I do apologize
Sprint customer service
Mister Rogers
So
You know exactly what a paranoid schizophrenic with you got to watch the nice one
Bright someone giving great service
Around a little bit and then bound comes in as I
Could never ruin
Yeah sure sure so there's a bit I cut out
And then we have the final four minutes of the show
As this clip ends
It is the end of the show
So this is a hard
Yes okay
Alex tries to prank call them
He calls back the exact number you called earlier
Dial
I told you this pays off
I promise you at the end of this clip
Alex learned an important lesson
About not being a dick
People
It's sad this is
Is great I love the Arc of it
I apologize it's another four minutes of Alex on the phone
Voice
Good
I would like to book a room please
High-quality service your conversation
Marriott.com to understand how we use and protective
That was what
That was a fake
Lesson that Alex is going to learn
Is how hotel booking
I think he's already getting
Getting a bit of a crash course in it
Egypt
Like everyone at the Marriott is awesome
Cuz he gets another amazing customer service person
Who is going
Above and beyond
With a dick on the line
Clearly doing a fake ax
Listen to this person deserves a f****** raise
Call my gosh
Nope come on
Nothing
This is just making a resume
I would like to check foster care
Mountain States
King size beds
Completely
Is it the Bilderberg Group coming
Don't know
Rockefeller
That will be will be saying hi to him don't worry
Okay cuz what I have
Marriott I have
Fairfax
Sodus Point
Improv
This customer service rep
Doesn't realize Alex
Talking with her
And is trying to
To help him
She is now being like what was another Marriott six miles away I can get you a room there
It's not that far
You can still go to the conference she's going above and beyond
In terms of trying to find a resolution
For his problem
The commission for this
All the major conference rooms they weren't using
Priority shipping in the equipment
Really serious question
Osama Bin Laden was killed last year by Obama
Great
Cesar Lane ever lied
Well you never know
So at this point Alex
Is thinking oh my God
Booked it out even further
I will see what happens
How many nights I can get you
Oh my gosh
Get me one night right
Before
When is it closed for the conference
But I can do the 28th
I thought I thought it was closed
I thought it was closed the 29th through the 3rd
I'm able to
Okay great
Call Mama Mama
Wow
So it's just the first place is because
Sometimes they're booked out on one of those nights and they're like no you can't get off hotel is complicated
You don't want to have people moving room
Course not
You learned the end of that they
I can get some nights
Struggling
With what the f*** is just happened
To Dick about it like all of these globalist have bought out the hotel
Can I give you
What a nice
It's amazing
What a nice woman boiler
Look after the do you believe Osama was killed
Nah
We've been totally fine if you hang up on me
Not if they say f*** or s*** to you
Ask you about a selfie with him
Post 9/11 World
Yeah
Just like
Jumped in with
No
The old believe that
Let me tell you why
And then she bores him
Even more than he was boring
So that like
These really bad on his face
On some level
I'm supposed to be talking about
This
Prank call is it go
What's up girl what you think
Terrible
Whatever
You never know
Started the regular voice
Weird kind of got back to the regular voice
And then
She should have been like
Play still alive
Sergeant
So
And you might expect some of this.
The carryover
Some of these things
Chickenman
The Marriott
We could get
Days out of just the
Actually come back up but there's nothing new about it you just bring it back up
The Marriott drama
Does not come back on
Of course not they were
They would prefer if that episode was not.
Not available not being around doesn't come back up
Illegal dumping
Come back up
It's not Osama Bin Laden doesn't come back up
You know why
Because he's dead
But you know why
That's a good theory
There's another reason
Sounds right
Milan
Because I wanted to believe this wasn't true
Official govtrack
Site
So
The Marriott's have been closed
For a full week
I couldn't get the reservation
Double check by Paul Joseph Watson
He booked us two flights and then he was like
Now we can't sit together and I was like
Build-A-Bear
This is FEMA camp
S***
Okay
Vfm
3-3 9.40
Has come out
This day
They are not in history
May 3rd
Is this when we get all of our feet
This is where it all becomes very real.
I will discuss
That
Here in a minute
But
On the way there
Alex Jones
Brings up
A bunch of building blocks
For his
Fed FEMA camps are coming
And throughout this clip
I'm going to pause it after each one
Empty bunk
Each one
Jesus this is going to be
Me running the gauntlet I appreciate your thoroughness I'm so excited about this
I know
I can do anything
We already know this we already knew that
So the John Waters called corroborate
You do need people
Two confirmed
John Warner defense authorization Act
Largely pushed through by Republicans
Sport in the in the Senate I have a list here of all the actual votes
The only Republicans actually vote against
Pretty thrilled with
Feel feel pretty awesome
About like yeah my guy voted against this thing
Jeff sessions voted for it
It's mostly
Mike Pence voted for it
Trump Circle in favor of it
All of the names were Democrats with except
Rand Paul
Maybe we'll like Conyers if people like Dennis
Kucinich
Kucinich around
Those were the Glory Days
The reason that everyone was
Concerned about it I'm not sure
With it is because
Inside this National Defense authorization bill
I read all this
I'm very excited
Do you want to just do a lightning round
I can't cuz some of this kind of complicated
Comes out alright
So it's operation bill for funding
For the year 2
Fiscal year 2000
But
It buried in it
I wasn't Amendment
To the Insurrection Act
Is that
Governing the rules
What is an interaction where
Basically would make it easier for the president to send in military troops in the case
Of a terrorist attack
An outbreak of some sort
Or some situation that I believed the language
Specifically is
The president deems that is uncontrollable by local
Local or state Authority
Federal government
Navigate to outbreak natural disaster terrorist attack
He just change
Change the language
Of the belt is still
It is murky
Alex believe that it violates Posse Comitatus
Course
Cuz
Ethanac
Congress
And Posse Comitatus
Says that
Except by an act of Congress
The military cannot Act
Law enforcement capability
This is Max Congress
Dumb file a Posse Comitatus
It violates
The spirit of
Cuz
Posse Comitatus
Really
Was always about
Commenting on those pots
Absolutely man look at that Posse walking by
Who you are at baby iffy on Posse Comitatus being broken I say it's not
Usually it doesn't matter
And Alex is alive
So many reasons
So this was 2007 for the fiscal year 2000
It doesn't matter because the 2008 defense authorization bill
Entirely repeal the changes
If you look
In anyway like violate Posse Comitatus
To declare an insurrection
Interested in whatever they could they were like
The next time that the bill came up it was discussed
The next year at this episode
This episode
Is it 2012
This is equal
Complete Warriors after
The matter anyway
Exactly
Lying about that
Completely made up bulshit
That's the same thing
That's what he's talking about
Zach
DLC double-a the enemy commissions Act is not a real thing
What are you talkin about is the military
2000s
The military commissions act also known as MCA
It waved
Habeas corpus right
Do non-citizens
Detained as enemy combatants
Many people believe that the wording
Was too vague
And in effect what it could do
Is allow military tribunals to waive habeas corpus
Sprite
To citizens
Although if you actually read the wording of the belt
It says specifically alien
And if you want to let you know that could be Raptors
I have no opinion whatsoever I think
If you are born on American soil
Regardless of speed
What up
So a lot of people still upset about this was also on board
And it needed to be looked into
Someone brought suit
In a 2000
8 ruling of
Boumediene
Versus bush
The Supreme Court ruled that the mcai was unconstitutional and would restrict detainees habeas corpus
That's right and the right to appear in federal court
Even in the context
If non-citizen pedim. That was
The necessary changes
So there are still problems
Yeah but it's not this
Enemy combatant
Military Commission
Cuz they don't exist
Right then the necessary changes
Does that were requested about the habeas corpus
Rules that were deemed unconstitutional
To Channel 5
Supreme Court
Were made in the military commission Act
3 years before the episode that we're listening to now
AMV Affirmed
That all detainees at access to US federal courts
The challenge Reddit
Unless
And that's the other thing
We still haven't closed Guantanamo Bay
Well the other thing isn't like a lot of these things are probably to save face more than they are too.
Militia types
They're more to avoid I haven't
To deal with your dad allow themselves
Fresh
So everybody go back to the ndaa because he mentioned that asked for the John Warner defense
Authorization bill
That is their sort of intertwine
A little bit of credit
Because there was also an ndaa the past in there the end of 2011
Year 2012
Which brought the
Rules
No no it is
The issue the people bring up with the NBA of 2012 is that it brought up the question of indefinite
The Detention of enemy combatant
So it's a very idea
Most legal Scholars
Who have chimed in on the matter has made the case
Based on the wording of the app
It doesn't
The NBA does not in any way Amanda powers that already exist
I do to the authorization of military force
Launched
The beginning of the
So the indefinite detention
Aspect of it
He's not real
Because within the authorization of military force act
Which govern
This ndaa
It's not indefinite detention
End
With the cessation of hostilities
So whenever the war is over
Detention Mustang
Is never going to be
That's the other problem
The actual problem is
It's the idea of having a war against an ideology or some sort of
Nebulous concept
As opposed to the idea that if you're at war with
Let's say Sweden
If you detain swedes
Until the end of the war that's what the ndaa and the authorization of military force act allowed
Severe rule in the ndaa
Overridden by the MCA
Reflect
BR authorization of military
So it is
Not actually some sort of thing that
Powers already
Sing like that
Exactly
Do you model State emergency Health Powers Act
During this one this one's real thought this one isn't
So this was not a bill it was a
Avabel
I was written by Lauren
Goston who's the director of the center of Law and Public Health
The Georgetown University
In association with Johns Hopkins and the CDC
Written it was written right after the anthrax scare
When we were all so
We ain't right
People I realize that we needed a systematic plan in order to deal with
Potential bioterrorism
Especially in the case of
Contagious disease smart that could become a plague like Zane
You could end up with a complete disaster.
This Lawrence Coston realized
The situation that could be ahead of
And so he wrote up a bock bill
Model State emergency Health Powers Act is not about a model or ideal State it's a bottle at
Right it is
If you look at it cuz you can find it it's available online it says
Phil senators name here
Bright
There are a number of states that have now implement
I have brought it through
And implemented bills that are similar to sort of a framework
Can you make their own changes that need to be made state by state
It's not a federal thing
Every state has the right
Decide to introduce
Alex should be thrilled with it
It's a states rights thing
It's not federal
Alex has never seen schoolhouse
It's not a federal power grab and
It's not even that part of the song is not like
I'm definitely not a bill I'm a model f****** bill I mean ivr loan I'm an idea
The issue with that though is that it is not
Like this Lawrence Coston
Keep the way he wrote it was
Kind of short-sighted
The bill is written in a way that doesn't adequately protect
Against the misuse
Has powers
But it could Branson emerge
Right
Generally when the states implemented there are
Form of it
So Alex is
Misleading people again
With the idea of like
Any didn't put the Protections in there because he never confirmed
Revolver
We're doing this
Emergency centers
Lightning round emergency Sanders establishment Act is also known as HR 645
This is legitimately just a plan for the office of Homeland Security to establish Regional refugee camps
In recognition that there could be a natural disaster or attack
There may be a need to
Yeah these are built
General Lyon quotes
Closed military
I think it's closed is why they put it
Military installations whenever possible
Because the land is already owned by the government
And there will always be
There's already substantial
A structure on these military bases
There's already permanent structures built
And they're closed military bases that are being used for anything else
Yeah
Generally military installations are built and relatively safe place
In terms of flooding
In terms of that stuff
So it would be an ideal place to take this place people when there's already a flood
Let's say
It would be
For that
So Alex makes a big deal out of it
It's not it's not
If you can read the entire bill
4 pages long
It's not at all
Scary
Doterra people
Coraline naming a bunch of bills it don't say what do you think
Program
So
This one
Okay this is
Like hearing you say this might be real
A little bit and from everything I can tell there are
We have private
A for-profit prisons
This country wants to start talking about that a little bit more
I don't really care about the inmate labor
Well I mean the situation with
The Wildfire right now we have inmates
Core fighting this fire $0.20 an hour
We are literally using slaves
To fight fire
No it's a big issue it's a huge issue and you can see that
Where they have people doing a slave labor
Clinton and Bill at the time where they were in the Arkansas Governor's
Play slave labor day
Absolutely
M2
Real eagle-eyes in slavery
Through
Are private for-profit prisons
And it's a good thing that we have the most prisoners in the entire world
Yeah that's a good idea
So Alex is conveniently
Somebody brings up all the time
Kind of strange
They often brings up when it comes to the idea of these FEMA camps
Together of
Oppressive
Oppressiveness on population
I'm just going to read this year
About Rex
Readiness exercise 1984 rex-84 pursuer with a scenario and drill created under the Reagan Administration by Oliver North
Deputy director John Brinkerhoff
Throughout the Reagan Administration the Black Ops
So the US Military Intelligence agencies
Effectively ran Wild
Especially in Latin America where Reagan's aggressive intervention many times words.
Unintentional genocide
The CIA backing
Amid violence
Environment the scenario described in rx84 is rather disturbing
He called for the rounding up of
And pre-emptive Detention of Human Rights
Anti-war activist
As well as Latino
The ironic part about rex-84 which many Wingnut
Is that the program was targeted against civil rights groups anti-war groups organized labor immigrants
The minority communities in
Port of hegemonic capitalist right-wing American pin
FEMA camps are not as conspiracy theorists would have
Some Grand plot against
Conservative American Patriot
Rather the only Administration to seriously consider interning dissidence
Was planning on doing so
Against the sort of left-wing activists
Did the American far right
Despise the most
Who Woulda guessed
Those from rationale Wiki
That is actually
Can't imagine any kind of situation where that
Miss you
Nose
It's f****** Christ so there we have in this clip so far
Go into effect
Defense authorization bill
NBAA military commissions
Model State emergency
DC Powers Act
Emergency centers establishment Act
Maybe the inmate labor camp
Racist
Grace is that bad
Still out of the six that he mentioned that are completely bogus and he's misrepresenting and lying to his audience about
Musically
Overruled
The next
Then he knows the
He has to know that
Does he know when I say he has to know that I mean
This is John
He has to know this
Okay that's a way better way I'm guessing you probably dumb and doesn't know it
Needs to know this
Cuz he's riling up militia people
He's riling up
Bucking Weirdo anti-semites And racist
Into a camp
What are you lying about every single piece
Piece of the way
The last few years for interment specialist
Forgot another lightning round
I thought we had made it
Nope
So Alex says that they're ramping up
The hiring of
Internment specialist
And the only thing that he has to back this up is that they had of posting
Goarmy
Goarmy.com careers and jobs section
Internment resettlement
Specialist
End up finding like
Blogs like
This one renewamerica
FEMA camp speaking contractors
Personality
Staffing confine
Here's the first thing this article says
Caution
This is an exercise and ongoing citizen research in journalism
Consider yourself inside the news off
With some reports
Verity is Asher
With others
Further corroboration of refutation must be done
Consider yourself also in the war room
Some positions and suspicious suspicious
Must also be considered
Implants preparation
Executions thereof
And none of this is real
You think I'm top in the article that he wrote
Hey warning
I don't know about that I don't know a goddamn thing
Imagine it
Was true
Leopard Planet place
Together
Just in case also one of these that one of the authors on
This renewamerica site where this article is posted is Larry
Claiming we know as the crazy lawyer was involved in the dentist Montgomery
If you scroll down you find links
Places like the
Shtf
Plan.com
S*** hit the fan plan.com
Which is a preparedness
Website where is
Covered with gold and silver sales ads
Completely covered
But there's one add-on
I think it's very special hide your guns
Big Berkey
Pittsburgh comeback
Berkey was via the water
Big Berkey
I don't think that there's any evidence
Any of that
Was opposed
Specialist
And that's reason
Because there are internment position
An ongoing theater
Just that bad
But that would be valuable for any number of
In the United States that I Whenever there are like
Yeah people in the Superdome and stuff like that
Have a fever
Bismarck classified
It was never marked Plaza
64 diesel Def
He says that the document talk about the biggest news in the world
Three.
3 9-40
It is
Hey there isn't the second
Document
Exactly
Yeah
Play Lady confirmation
Could you call Marriott again I was really starting to enjoy.
Little kids in there
Warren
We just took the floorboards up man it's there
What is this song
So I mean he's already there then they ever that's not a surprise
Dead kids
Is in his basement
Like the more he describes that
Closer and closer to him like
Making apps
Right
I don't disagree
I want to take
Stretch my shoulder
I feel pretty good about that research
Read a lot of documents could you be a little bit more pleased with yourself I can't
I can't I will I will be in a minute
Is
I would actually I would like to send this clip to Alanis Morissette
Because I think this clip is the definition
Can of irony
Oh yeah
When the book
Teepublic
Oh my God
Bicycling
Biopsy
Contractor
You're being fed psyops in lies as well your your future is being destroyed
Interesting
Alex
That's amazing
It's so crazy
Write that.
Pieczenik in their new life
2015 invest
Navigation we've seen as Steve pieczenik
Crazy calling on Alex
And like exactly what he saying there is what happened to him
Exactly what happened
Crazy
He's so gullible gorgeous of people who are immune to con men are always the ones who go
Hook Line & Sinker
Elizabeth
No Alex has one more b*******
I still think
He gave that Niger
Oh yeah
My friend
Yeah
Do you have evidence
The FEMA camp
So what do you think about that
I mean if that is
Your master plan
It seems like it'll be messy
They're like more fact
Voices are there cheaper
To do it I assume then
Organizing a mass war against
Internal
Mleota
Nle donut
Website
The truth if I can research it
Which I want
But I can
That means you must
OU
You should not have done
Google go to the website
What are things you find is a press release dated July 24th 2009
3 years before Alex's last episode we're listening to right now from the Homeland
Security website
Does for immediate release
Suppressor
The Department of Homeland Security will launch a national level exercise 2009
Nle 09
The first national level exercise to focus on terrorism prevent
In conjunction with federal state local tribal private sector and
International partners
Coordinating with our partners across the United States and around the world is critical to protecting the nation
Terrorist attack
XO secretary Janet Napolitano
The national level exercise allows us to test our capabilities in real time
Can find and strengthen our strategies
For preventing terrorist attack
This is something that has been going on
For a number of
It's a different name before that but this is just a joint
Exercise that's done
It doesn't always
Involved
Countries
International partner Nations will include Australia Canada Mexico and the United Kingdom
The Navajo Nation will also be
Okay
Training exercises
I understand if they come up with a scenario
Have them run through the scenario and how they would coordinate with each other and
Like like
In real life work
Supposed to us
It's like with the idea behind Jade helm
Yeah
You can't train
In Iraq
You know you can't do that today
Targeting civilians
Utrade on your own turf
To get better at doing things elsewhere
Or even to get better at doing things here cuz terrorist to do exist
So
This is bulshit
There are 15 Nations I can find no evidence
4 +
Which which would the other
Okay
Oron
New axis of Evil
Channel 9
Italy
Wait
Axis Powers actually actually yes those would absolutely be there
Spain
And why not Luxembourg they got a huge terrorism issue but a difference
60 years make
Absolutely so Alex loop on the third is stealing
Tomato pole working on that
Alex
He hasn't read this
Lupus
Alex has not read this fm3.
39.4
I know that
Because
It's very long
That was
That was all I needed
If hundreds of page
All I need
Absolutely
Lost in the Phantom can't even make it all the way through the Hobbit
The Hobbit
That's not even Lord of the Rings were talking about The Hobbit
He read the chapter titles
Yeah that's the headline of a novel
The headlight of the novel it was certainly true in Around the World in 80 Days with long-ass titles
I'm a big fan of that
Chapter titles from
Blood Meridian Cormac McCarthy
Which is just a short synopsis
You read the chapter titles to be like
I got it
In this clip Alex is the devil
Let's go send a text
Jim process is responsibility to psychological
Operations officer
Hoosier products
Call
Us--or IR Basilica
Cauliflower
Important
Thomas a coward tortures will sit back while troops are.
Yeah
39.4
Manual for operation
Internment
Inforum
A talks about
Host Nations
Repeatedly and
Conspiracy theorists
Such as Alex
Hundred
It's a bother
Websites that you can find
If you Google it
They misrepresent
Something that's very important
There are a couple packages
About
Operation
Little bit about that before
Okay just because it is
Did it is what part of the light about
It isn't this isn't like because it's Sunday
This is the aftermath
They talked about how to change operations from
What they would do in a foreign
Incase
Domestic
Including
The operations
They might use the dinner
Operation
Address consequence
Natural or man-made disasters
Terrorist attacks or incidents in the United States
Yeah it's something that you would need
Cuz otherwise you're going to have masks
Right and
What's a do da
Is
They conflate
The most
That guy book
Couple pass
Messages about
Domestic Opera
They don't
Realize that all of the stuff
About psyops
About
Finding Malcolm
Contempt
And all that stuff
Is despotism
Very very germane
24in
Force
Back there are tons
The generals who have gone on record and said
I wish
That we'd had this
When I was when I was in
When I was in the ship
Did the the
Basically all it is is
A reflection
Alexa
And learned from Vietnam and
Cambodia
Those times
We had we had
All of them but they tried to detain people you had
You had political dissenters in there and there's there is a better way to
To deal with them
Then
Violence
Absolutely
I don't understand why it is
They White
Why are we
Even
Trying whiskey
No I mean anytime they talk about bills or anything like that
The conspiracy
It doesn't matter
They're going to find a way
Only way to not deal with conspiracy theories
Is if you don't
Publishers
Information which you should but if you don't publish
That means the conspiracy theorists going to be like what are they hiding from or if it gets found then so you're trying to hide this from
What we need to accept is that
Conspiracy theorist on this level are just like Hoarders
People with Siri
Depression or something along those lines
That bright but in the same way that not all orders are
Are people with Siri
But
No it is actually I want to get let me get through this document then I want to get back to what you're talkin about.
Fortin point that we need
Foreign policy
The article
390. 69
2008 Serge there were few guidelines and regulations to help soldiers conducting
These massive detention
Operation
According to a former military officer
Who conducted detainee operations
Facilities in Iraq
Quote I would have loved to have this field manual 5 years ago
The vast majority of guidance
To the manuals intended for you
Using foreign theater
Noting that only a handful of paragraphs
Backpage Manuel address domestic
An army spokesman speaking on background said
The current state of online posting
I taken passages from the manual significantly out of
Conflating wartime operational guidance
Psychological operation
With peacetime operation
In which a limited number of the manual
Principles will be applied on us soil
In exceptional cases such as the relief efforts
After Hurricane
Now granted the hurricane
300,000 bungling
What have you here I think is the most sale
Lead us to what I wanted to get to
Yeah that is
Radicalization is driven in large part by victimization
Ameritas whether it's fear of Big Brother watching Big Bank looting big government
Season 1
For big global war on is
A document like FM 3-3 9.40
Is red is a
Confirming the worst fears of an unusually wide spectrum
Political dissenters radicals
And would be violent
Extremists from the right left
Gasoline
So
Radicalization
Immigration narrative
This is really the most
And that is what you experience
Everyday listen
Alex Jones
Now I want it I want here's the point that I wanted to bring
I don't think the quest
German government
Being skeptical is at all on how you were saying
Absolutely not
But I am getting
Elote
Like Alex says this frequently that
Conspiracy theory
Especially Rodger Stone and then bring this up because of JFK files are come
Coming out right like that
Although the ones that
It's important
Did not come out now which is like what a Cox
Is the American government
But
Alex make this point of Rodger stone make
And then I'll need supposedly
Jimmy Dore make this point on Twitter
The idea that
Conspiracy theorist
Does the term popularized by
The government
CIA after the JFK assassination
To Tar and feather all the people who a question
Send about it and make them look like crazy
Maybe you guys made yourselves look like
Possible but also if you look into it
If you do a deep dive on it
You will find
That
Be termed
Conspiracy theorist
Has had the exact same conversation that it has
Currently
Dating back
2D
Mid-to-late 80
There are instances of a being used in the exact same
Slightly pejorative or slightly dismissive way right
Over
150 years
It's not on
This idea.
The government was like a we're going to use the term it's going to catch on like wildfire anything more appropriate
Conspiracy theorist
Thinking that
Is a conspiracy
Bingo
Perpetuates victimization
Narratives which fueled
Experiencing in the world
But you know the one thing that
It is
What should be taken away from that is the things that word list
Are all
Things like I don't like the government isn't
But they are going to
Make you not be able to get an abortion
F****** cry
The things that they described radicalized
The people and their things
The government has
Has done
To us
Right and that is why we are radical
Spear of the Big Bang
They are absolutely maybe they should stop that and we wouldn't be afraid
You could conceivably
Now this is crazy dad
You could make that go foreign policy did not do the best job of coming up with
Examples
Entirely remiss
If I don't point out that like
A lot of the things that conspiracy theorist
Are conspiracy theories
Think about our things that
You know like
There's some history two people doing that like false flag narrative have a route in reality
Stuff that happened
6070 years ago like a lot of Tonkin
And stuff like that that's
A long time in the past
They have to scramble to
Turn current event into false flag
In order to be like they're still doing it
And when you do that when you have that mentality you end up saying things like say
Sandy Hook is fake
By the way Alex Jones the other day
Said Sandy Hook was
In 2017
He said Sandy Hook was fake
You got to give the man credit
For going back on it you know why cuz he probably heard Steve pieczenik say that someone scared him out of believing any like
F*** you
Right
Who's going to stop
Who gives
It's not like literally the only people who are like
You need to stop this guy or at least
Crye-Leike
Yeah.
Not like Kelly I'm not like taking off the air anyting
Arrested for arrest
Or the thing where you arrest him
Being an accessory to Larry Nichols
Blackmail are coming down
I don't want to do that I don't either
We recording this on Sunday and the so we don't know who the indictments
Therefore also recordings on Sunday so we don't know what Rodger
Just don't response is going to be to be kicked off Twitter
No actually did bring me Rodger Stone
Documentary someone tweeted at Salix to port or whatever that Rogers
Stone is tweeting from the he's moved over to his other account and he wrote back I've always been here slapstick
Which I love
Make me think
Jeff Jarrett
The wrestler Jeff Jerry's to call people slapnut
Trial of people with a guitar
Cocaine
Like El kabong
Yeah basically
How do we know what El kabong
So
Let's move
A pretty good job of debunking a lot of this
In the lightning round
You got 546
I was even like
I don't know
It looks like they could be real
You the one on the feud for sure but on the
$25,000 Pyramid
All of them are
Hot dog
So let's get it
In the next clip
We get a further
Extension
Of the mythology
Give Alex Jones
Does father
The CIA dentist
But that is not what
Everytime I look at my children other people's children out innocent
I realize that we just absolutely should be honored
The only fair you need to have is a
You're alive this one X people in this test
This is so real
Fake crying again
It is accelerated it's built to a fever Crescendo my father
Was approached by a patient of 10 years
The homeland security spy
Spy on his
Patience why
My dad
It was real
Call the card number Olive
Homeland Security
Okay
The average person gets approached by this and gets on a power trip if you're out there listening think you're special
Pretty sure
No wonder I wake up with Dennis 6 a.m.
Useful idiot moron
Okay
And the people
He said the only talked to her the same way
Yahoo.com
People are filthy
Military working for
Chicago
5 years later I can
Confirm Chicago still here
I don't either
A really good job
Preemptively contextualizing any whites
Supremacist militia attack
Globalist
Strength
It's
But
I can't
Can't hang with
This narrative about his dad
And here's why
Just one reason well I mean the one big one is
Come on
The more specific
Is the correct phrase
The first is why are they trying to get
Who's going who's
We don't know what is patient
That's true
But still
He said that they were trying to get a bunch of other dentists
What was one of his patient
Pretend
I assume they're FBI spies going to happen
Are they all spying on Alex's
So here's the other problem
If we are to believe the things that Alex says about
The globalist
Tried to get him when he was like 16
You rebuff very very
So then he grows up and he becomes a dentist
The globalist
Course knowing that they're fishing in a dry well
This guy is already slept moving up to your tennis Idol plan
Not only that
They're fishing in
The dentist
Right he's a dentist
No
This is this is the Jingle writer running guns
Apologizing
Nonsense
But it's fun
Fun
How would he
Spy on people
He's a dentist
Is he just going to
What is asking
Rarararararara you knock them out and look at their cell phone
I don't know it's dumb
Because you are knocked out you can use the thumbprint on the iPhone you can crack
Was easy
Is social engineering
That's the trash
I watch the movie hackers
Good movie
Sakamoto is a religious studies
To the extent
But Alex does his
Dentist father
I would have to say that my dad wrote the
Well what you think about what you don't know is that your dad was approached
I do
So that's
A little bit later Alex
Call
Alex thanks
Jesus-pie
What's your view on civilian inmate
The Army at concentration camps
Well I definitely think that
There are legitimate issues like ndaa that's legitimate policy I think that Presidential Directive 51
So I want to stop there.
Focus look
She said that there are legitimate issues
A lot of things that you referenced as a legitimate issue is ndaa
Remember that
With regard to this particular document
I would like you and or Paul Joseph Watson
Point guard
Specifically to wear
It mentions anything about Kona
Because I have found a document on an army website Army pubs
Got army.mil
This is not a top-secret document and I think
Alice
You're out there
California
U.s. citizen illegal
And you're calling up
Article in the Army times where they say they're going to start pulling
Trigger Zone Diet
I can't find
Score
Right it was their plan
You put it out open late
Psyop the people who were
Confirm that I don't
You could say that I've done everything sounds like a
Urban militia
Drill sound like
Sounds like
My dad
God though
We should help him
True
Amazon Fire you shouldn't be upset and you started out by saying ndaa
You didn't
He said that it's legit illegitimate bill
That was listed as one of the
Alex is intentionally twisting his words
Tire world
Of US citizens
Unbelievable
It was crafted for you
So Alex is at this point
Decided that he is a cop
Or something like that
Ryan is working with the global
Bright
No one said this is okay what I'm saying to you is this particular document is not what you're making it out to be and
You need to tell her specifically what mentioned the continental United States within this document
You are misleading your audience like you did before the 20 minutes with the president
So apparently
Apparently I previous to this episode
Clint Eastwood
That was a mock interview with a president
Computer glitch for a minute the same one on the bottom
But I'm trying to find something where is the article
This is a boring joke
From the document
Directions home
Fortunate
Five political activist
Call Mary
Nice lady customer service
None of this is in relation
Caller was asking is where does it say
In the United States
But if you get into the context of where it says those things
You have to really stretch
Instructions were necessary
Military police
Tell me
What I'm saying is this Alex I'm not
Almost
What I was about to
Are you sure
So
I have I recently a conversation
Friend of the shofar out
Nearest talking about the idea of interviewing out
And I told him
Though I've been studying him for almost 11 months
Incomplete dedication
I would never want to talk
Of course
And this clip
Damonte
Sturtevant why
Cuz you just yell at you there's no point
What's finish up this club
Talk about about a little boy
Okay
What is it true about this groundbreaking
In this document
Grouting is groundbreaking
Ground-breaking
Change the goalposts
Domestically as well in Tod support
Balboa paragraph
Page and paragraph in the PDF or we can find it in reference the United States of America
Call Lanier and have him tell us where it's at that he read it
He wrote about it
Operations
I called to ask you about the storm
You watch what happens in this country
You go ahead and do that
So
I would like to say at the end of this
His
You look what's going to happen to the country
You use psyop techniques on people
They look what's goin to happen
5 years later
Look what's happened
You use psyop techniques on your audio
And we know this because
One of your biggest influences
Is a psyop officer
Even if it's not
Call it Sia
Even then all psyops
Really artist
It's absolutely up on people to get them to like
American policy
Well
In the same way that Alex Jones says you should like Trump
The only difference is that these are enemy
Combatants where's Alex
Actually work
I'm not advocating for the death of Ali
George Jones
But if
If I were designing a perfect
World if I were designing a civilization
That I think
Function
Perfectly
Well the show Designing Women
1st and Taylor
Linda bloodworth-thomason
Delta Burke I would say that actively and consciously
Engaging and propaganda should be an executed
Because of the amount of disasters that you create
The amount of misinformation
The how many people you lead astray
Through
Attractive
But deceitful
News
Prevalence
Like it is a disaster
There's the possibility of us
Really ever coming
Together
And working
Towards common goal
Is completely knocked off track by people like Alex Jones
Absolute again
I'm not saying
You should even be arrested
That's not the world we live in
Put in a Utopia
We would really look at the idea that
Well were willingly misleading people
Like executing people might be counterproductive
Why do that's why we do the show the way we do it should have is f***
Classes in school
Here's how you recognized propagandist rhetoric the reason we can't have those classes
Is because religious people would go
Jaguar
To be like
Okay well we know religion isn't real Ouroboros kind of because also the reason that you can't
Get the schools to work
As well as they should it's because people like the last cuz it's propaganda stopped right
These people who can't run
Well when we have
Things like
Standardized testing No Child Left Behind
Commoncoresheets
And the funding is
Thank you just can't
Can teach kid with a need-to-know to grow up understanding logic and rhetoric
Those two things are
Critically important
You need to understand
Deconstruct in Ark
Number one
You cannot go
Get through life without or else you will be tricked by people like this ding dong right second you need to understand rhetoric
Bravo he's never going to make it out
For Eddie
Sweet sweet Addie you stupid bastard
Because you need to understand
Rhetorical tricks
People use like
What's shutting down
Every single time
This guy truck
To talk and then pretending that he's not answer
Question right that is a rhetorical technique in order to silence your opposition
You need to know these
These tricks cuz you need to know when people are using them and then you can pick the next step which is
Why are they
And we go back to your religious argument
People would shut down all of that discussion
Beno secretly
That their
Absolutely
School s*** all right I'm going to walk back the idea of killing property
But I think I'd like for your heart
I'll tell you why
This is becoming
Somebody to kill
Right as I walk that back I still think it would be a very serious
Deal to be a problem
Where is it
You making money
I forgot my thought
Good it's a good thought which is
I lean back more towards
Okay
The
What are the Three Kingdoms
Whenever you had legalism and taoism and Buddhism and all of those
Mainly because those all of those were
Built around the idea of how is it
That we getting
Ineffective government
Like if you read the
Mainly it's about
Not not like
How you should live and how you say
Three people but
If I were the king
Here's how not to be an ass
Exactly
Really boils down to
If
You are running a competition
Government
The rule of Leah Plaza
The rule of law
Applies equally to ever
Where people are
Where they feel safe where they have their base
They don't have to fret about this before Maslow even came up with his hierarchy
Exactly and you
Will wind up not have
Nothing to worry about these prop
Yeah that's a good point
Because because the root of all of this root of all of the the why we believe in the propaganda
So why we believe in religion believe in all of this is because life is miserable and nobody is doing anything
Victimization narrative
It comes down to that but you're miserable because you don't have your needs met you need to find someone to blame
Alex Jones
Simple
My fault that I got back
Well I don't know how I can relate to that but Alex doesn't believe
But do you think
Yeah and I know that
Because if he did
He would be calling for
Taking the street
Absolute
If you legitimately believe that this was
Government.
To incarcerate
Dissidents in America in FEMA camps
It's separate agitators like himself
He would call for an overthrow of the f****** government
Infowars
Well I mean
Easiest way to
Who are the people who really believed
That abortion is murdering babies
Like if you really believe that you are murdering a live thing
That isn't
So the people who are going out there and protesting and doing all that s***
At the very least
They believe what b*******
Salad I don't know if we want to look I don't want to say it's very least
I do I write I don't want to use that as like a feather in the cap
Prepare enough
Question the authenticity of their beliefs
Where is it
Clearly a con game
Vicky would be actor
Completely
Evan secondarily running his own militia
Absolutely
The problem with that is like we can sort of assess what Alex Jones really believes and what he does
But what's scary is to think about
The logic
Would be in a person's mind if they ask
Actually believe
Because if they actually believed him
They're the ones who are going to take
Take to the street there's a while let's take that out of it even though that definitely is a piece of
Let's just say
Old people
Or people who aren't going to storm places with guns
See now in my perfect
Society
It would be nice
Executable offense
Oh boy
I'm going to
So what I'm saying is if you actually believe in Alex Jones
The thing that you should do is give him literally Olive
Because if you believe it
He is the person
Who has the best
Chance of taking down these globalist
You keep staring you about
Then your money is useless if he loses
So the only
Logical rational thing to do
Would be
Pour everything you can into him
And do everything he tells you
And that's kind of scary
Well I mean your money would be worthless
Seawinds 2
No
Overthrow the government
No no no
No because if you listen to him you would have bought gold
That's true take care of that
Xbox
Stuff did I when I listen to this that's what really scares me
Is the idea of rationality in his listeners
Like a twisted rash
Irrational
Logic
But that's why so many people give to like
Your wealth glitterbug
Prosperity got in the history of the world
Jim Baker Supply we will do that for the future
August singer
Anti-semite
Running me down man
He was trying to get some work done the other night
Errands
I was watching like
Majority report videos
I do getting work done
Computer
And one of the things that was recommended to me because I have
Terrible YouTube
Kerry Cassidy is live
She was interviewing the guy live
Or this guy was interviewing her like I watched about 20 minutes of it
Not good
Well it was going live there's a chat room
On YouTube
For the livestream
They were in
It was wild
Also no updates about Jim 70s
A man just a couple clips
Journal we can wrap this up cuz this is a classic knowledge fight episode we're already at 2
This is back in the good old days
Next weekend
As we work toward this happy Monday to you and yours
On the previous caller who is completely rational
Start over
The decided was a cop
For no reason
Young man like this guy just called and he's either a fraud
Or total cool
I don't have a clue what's going on in his life
Military
He's like a deputy
Listen but you're nothing special they tried to recruit every dentist my dad works with
Okay
They're even going up for bringing foreign troops enforce it because I'll tell you on my whole family's military I have bias
Military been in the military
Afghanistan Iraq
And I'mma tell you right now these fine young people in the military are going to rebuild their knockout they're not going to go along with it
So they're going to have to bring in a lot of
Lots of United Nations Forces
Do it
Help
They're admitting it
Alright
So if you're saying
That the United States military is going to
The largest military
In the world
All the other ones
Combine
They're going to bring in some un troops
Is the US military rebelled against
Anybody world
Boy like that cont the countries that were listed in that DHHS press release are Australia they're not going to be able to
How much
Compared to us
Mexico
No
PennLive
Cartels they not a sucker
Might as well
The Navajo Nation that's when you got to worry about
Franklin
They may not have the people put god dammit if they don't have the motivation
Anybody wants to
It's been Ava Hotel
Your point is well taken
Nothing to fear unless
The military does Rebelle
Yeah which is increasingly becoming
Not likelihood with a possibility
Well I mean
Imagine
It's run by a military junta
Scary is the most military Hunters are horrifica in small-town
Countries where they can't do anything
Oh I want everybody back to my idea about killing prop
One of the reasons that I
Confidence
About that in a Utopia
Is when we look at things
Like what we talked about
What number of episodes back
About Edward Bernays
Leading to a three-year Civil War Guatemala
So many deaths that are attributable to propaganda
And it's not
It's not a game
Like the things that Alex Jones says
Is not it's not a game
He's making a ton of money on this s***
But people do lose their lives people are terrorized
Like I read an article recently about a couple that was at the Las Vegas
Country
Free concert
That was attack
And the guy
It got shot in the head
Running away
From the
The
Conflagration
It works
Just because it was off by about an inch
It wasn't that bad
It wasn't relevant
And so he and his girlfriend had an interview
And they were talking
Think about how
Immediately he was inundated
With tons and tons of messages about how someone needs to
The Killing
Someone needs to shoot him in the head for real
Because he is a f******
Can crisis actor and all this s*** isn't real
Now that's not Alex Jones is narrative this time but it's something
You perpetuate
It's something with the Sandy Hook stuff that he's
Perpetuated and fostered in
The idea crisis actors isn't it doesn't start with him
But God damn it if he isn't one of the biggest people who push that narrative
He has to share the blame in this
It's not that it's not no steak
It's not a situation where you and I are sitting here
And we're like
Hey Alex Jones sucks doesn't he
It's it's this damn it
Those people are being terrorized
The families of Sandy Hook victims
Terrorized
Is it for years now at this point
It's just
A byproduct
To the ship
Guy coming to Pizza Hut Pizza Hut
Comet Ping Pong with a gun
All that stuff is
Just
Very predictable outcome
Envista
This stuff about Ms
Fm3
In concert with all of his lies about Elohim City in Oklahoma City bombing
It combines
To create
A very dangerous
White
Militia
Organization
And again
He's not solely responsible
For creating that
But he's the most mainstream voice that is super in favor of it and popularized
Able to make effects in the world
Changes in the world
Talking nonsense
I don't understand why
We don't have millions of dollars
Quite frankly
Because
We are debunked propagate
We don't
Dole it out because there's no money on the Progressive side of things
There is like the myths about Soros are real
Whereas the myths about the Koch brothers in the Mercers
So that's really what
Soros was real like in the
Presents him we would have a lot of money we wouldn't be in my
F****** bedroom right now
Anyway
I know
I was talking about it I Utopia that is hypothetical
You made a good point
To talk me off the ledge about the Dow
And about how it would be necessary
If their needs were met
Retina Group
Okay
So now
Quahog
How would you kill
What are we talkin about are we bringing back or we bring it back guillotine
Cuz that was fun
Actually about the guillotine
In my ideal scenario what it would be
Is a protracted
Trial
We're in everything that they say like it'll be just every episode of our podcast
Add by the end they would have already killed himself point-by-point
This is what you said
This is the reality
And make them confess
To everything
No just be like look
What we really need to do is get them really drunk one night
Boredom in court demonstrate
Untruthfulness of all their claims
And that's a fact
Now
Next.
Seppuku after they're already honorable death
After they're already dead but also they don't deserve that honorable
After they're already dead
I propose we Oliver Cromwell
Diggum back
Put them back on trial and then B had them
Interesting
On that
Eclipse
The first one is
Alex misleading people about Hillary Clinton
Early
Hillary Kentucky voice real
She was running against Obama in 2008
I don't feel no Ways Tired
I started from nobody told me that the road would be easy
Bridgeton California
Cuz he was going
Got some family that I would like
Italian restaurants
Luigi
Condescending
I have another example
How about you go on the BBC and do a British accent while you talk over the other guests on the show
Condescending condescending
A little bit
So anyway
Really bad about EX
That was maybe the worst Tennessee an accident
Trying to
To be like hey
Look at this kind of bed I'm doing it
You guys know that I'm cool with you and it's just like a little thing
Know what she's doing is she's reciting the lyrics of a song by James Cleveland four-time Grammy Award
Winner for gospel album
The year
It's a song called I've gone too far to come back or
Are unfortunately written
Patois
Grades of the accidents not good
But the
She's forced into it a little bit by the
Even back then you can really see that her campaign handlers have no idea what they're doing
Yeah
The stiffest
Most
Knowledgeable person we can find
Yeah and try and get them to do B
Really making
You complain I think I would more
Complained
It's a little race
Yeah I know because the the
Cleveland song is from
Use born in nineteen
These are these are Old Time song
It's kind of like
Jim's dialogue is written
Now there is a little bit more like how the national anthem
Support
Right right
It it it's
And I would I would
Think that Alex can
Much easier attackpoint there then to say that she's doing hillbilly voice
Do that
Because she's stepping on his game of Bad Axe
What we saw
Exactly I was fair
Yeah so at the end
To somebody else
Alternators Gerald Celente
He has Gerald Celente
A bunch of bulshit
The Show by saying that the president
There's no real
He screamed about some guy of the saying stuff about the Army when
And he's never served
I don't know Gerald Celente is ever
Reserved himself I have no idea but
Is the age where he would have been in Vietnam
I have no idea I don't want to cast aspersions cuz I don't know his history
I don't know
You would think that he would bring it up while he's screaming at somebody about talking about the military
Be that as it may
I think based on the ramps but I've gone on about property
On this episode This Is A fitting way for us to
Episode
I know these are the German style culture
This isn't a third world Banana Republic
Rucdr beautiful buildings
From the late 1800s early 1900s
And then you see in between them all new-construction from post-world war
And it keeps going on everywhere you go
Behold bombed-out building
So it's been haunting me since I've returned
I said to myself
These are the German
How can I have lead
No little
Freak
Like Hitler
Destroy their entire country
Well
Victimization
Narratives
You 2016
Chop
President of the United States
Well I mean one of the big reason
Things that people line along
With
Hitler
Was because of desperation
The country because of things that actually the global Community was responsible for
Treaty of Versailles is
Proof of exactly what it is that I'm
Right
They will absolutely go for whatever.
Is going to give them that
Outlet for their.
Wichita
Anybody who expresses away out of your victims
Narrative
But Alex
Poses
Exploit
The job loss
In the Midwest
Coal mining
Territory
Exploit
The pain of people who have lost people
To opiate addiction
Exploit
The fear of immigrants
All he's doing is
Providing
Convenient scapegoat in
Talk about all the
Exactly the same way Hitler did
With the Jew Bang
General
Gerald I would say
Look in the mirror
That would be my recommendation
Its role to play in all of this
He brings up an Ana Republic
Oh yeah
Lot of that is propaganda
Capitalism
Right but
Yeah I mean that's just
Ultimately come down to propaganda is
Especially when it's used is
The tool from by the
It is
Is just one part
That's that you know
Unrestrained capitalism
Kleptocracy
They really you can have the
These people
Who are like if the Democrats
While at the same time they're voting for candidates
Who support the very policies that are putting them where they are
Like if you're going to if if Alex is going to b**** about the opioid crisis
The very guy that you wanted to take things over
Is doing nothing about it
He's talking
And being
These people
AR
Far-right
They're angry
And they are
Tricked
By the people they should be angry
That's what that's what propaganda is
Like North Korea
Why are you guys f****** starving
And yet at the same time you believe your leader is a God
Propaganda
Exactly
It's it's
You know it it's not a psyop
So much as it is
If you shout live loud enough a lot of people are going to believe
There's a thin line
Between marketing
And propaganda
Is very important
I'm at
He does Lincoln
There whatever
For some reason
In the movie The Lincoln Lawyer and he was also Abraham Lincoln
What's going on
So anyway
My my my
Calendar
For sending us down this
In history and also it was not really all that much about
Experience
Very important things in the mythology of Alex Jones travel episode we've ever done
You're like
Oh okay
He's going to do Y2K all over it
Nope
It's camps at the airport
No concentration camps
Austin Airport
Except for the one where Reagan got busted
That was Target
He wasn't necessarily but
He was definitely pay
Goodonya
Delivery life
So I mean we've gone through a bunch of bulshit
The currency being illegal
Narrative
The idea that
Madeleine Albright
Walter Cronkite
Came out publicly and said that Osama Bin Laden was killed before
All that stuff
All these things are really easily the monster
Probably not true the chicken man narrative yez is full of s***
American Hero
America
You know what I think he's not as cool as
San Diego
Goodnight who is Mike the Headless
Oh that's true
It also then we just have
Capture
Beware it really came together
Like to know also I listen to the day after this
Real talk about it very much ever you know why
Go get Charlie Daniels at a guess
Wow yep
Tootsie ask
How did you come up with the Devil
Charlie Daniels is on to talk about how evil Agenda 21
We got to get to the bottom of this Devil Went Down to Georgia
Charlie Daniels answer underwhelming
Story
He has no story about how he came up with
He stepped down
Wait
He was predict
Exit program
Be comfortable with the death indeed but it is
The time capsule
I appreciate that for what it is
Absolutely
Let me ask you a question
I got it
Have you ever been to a website
No okay well you can times that I ever have
You're not on Twitter
You should hire a social media manager
This podcast that is so great
Is that by Design
You have to do all the way
If I start doing any work
Demolishes the entire point
I don't think less of you for not doing the work
I'm fine
I started out with a healthy
Dose of insecurities about it
And then
Good that's how it it works
Now there's one guy I know
Please go to knowledge fight.com
The show button
If we can get that number up 35% more of our goal
We will do a full-length commentary
I'll put up a Twitter poll of like
Three options of Alex's documentaries
And I will
I promise you this
Spend as long as it takes
Going through and debunking every point in
And I will write
Jokes
I will do a commentary track over it that
Might end up being like 5 hours long
Webcams
Although we can't get the rights to the LOL
On YouTube
If you guys want to support that.
But I do want to do it so nice and also
We're waiting.
Yeah
I'm doing something
You know
When he's talking about the cas
CIA
Being a
Approached
You think about teeth
I think about I think about one guy I know was approached
Alright interesting Theory
Those approach
Sobriety the stalwart
Difference
CIA
Who puts
CIA psyop
Psyops
And let me tell you something
As
Tragic is that story you really would think that's biasi Optique
Would sound better in a mile
You really think
No
An appearance has no I mean
Sound aesthetic
I'm talking about
Do you want that marble
Gummy mouth
My buddy Ryan Beck has a great joke that he doesn't do anymore which pisses me off cuz
It's a great joke
Why do old people always look like they're chewing something
Good joke
Fuc yourself
You're an a******
Look
Anyways I'm saying go f*** yourself John Rappaport May the wolf choke on your flesh
Holding
Alex