Holding
Alexandra Thurston color
Alex Jones
There's a special twist today or not
Beverages
In honor of a area California
Now it's Fran
Also the Palisades are in
Another knot is Anita area of California
I don't know I think it is cuz I associate them
I associate them with the Saved by the Bell
For some reason
The Palisades
Julie had to keep building Palisades to keep the Huns out
Zack Zack Morris wedding 2
The door cat on the show yet
Also what is the podcast
That's family matters
We're going to make
You know a lot about Alex you don't know anything about him
Today we'll be going over the November 1st
2017 Ragnarok
Absolutely
2 days away from Thor
I want to get into really quick
Before we start the show that
Have nothing to do with the little bit of
Alex Jones
Doughboy
I got a couple people I want to put on blast
The first of them is Wilson
Will Smith fine
Somebody finally took him down before we start the show live
Year on Twitch
I like
To have a theme playlist
And today's was
Songs with cities or Bentley
Counting in the title as I realize like
Miami
Will Smith that's one of them
As I went back and listen to it
And I realize Will Smith's got a lot of album
I am so I was like
Why does he have a lot of album
That's that's embarrassing
I didn't work out for it hey man
If you are a polymath is a polymath no matter how you
Big Willie Style was a hit
And then willenium what was his second album
And I went I was like I was looking through
Workout
Get that
Mothers will enter either his will
So I was I was scrolling through it and I saw that Wild Wild West
Repeat song from wild wild what was on there
While I want to f****** listen to Wild Wild West
Because it's important
I want you to listen to this
Nobody has ever said that was an absolute support
It's not the same as the beginning
In the movie Wild Wild West
Godzilla versus Mothra
Velocity
Like listen to this it'll become clear why I'm putting them on blast
Took the headphone jack out there could have been so smooth
The terrible two the bus
He's blaming his son
For putting Wild Wild West
The olive album came out on the Wild Wild West soundtrack
What I do it again album
His baby son
I don't like how that's very Alex Jones interaction
Adorable
Put the song on there
I've got too many hot tracks put this on my kid
Yeah and then they are so he thought has been ruining our lives
Ever since the beginning I can never get enough of that song Those actually Jaden might have been right but be that as it may Will Smith
Still going on blast for blaming his kid for putting his eyes
Another person's got to go on blast
I don't know.
Smith for putting wild wild west on that album I don't know the name of this person
But a person's going on blast hard and it is the person
Who created the bus stop at
For the Ninja Turtles Adventure in New York City
Those of you who haven't seen these there's a bunch of them
Can you stand up this
There's one of them
The Turtles in Time Square
And they're all like doing posedown
Donatello's got like the Statue of Liberty
And what have you
Look at Michelangelo
Has food in his hand
What is it
It's not pizza it's a pretzel
What the f*** are they doing
Crossbow
In the video games it was
Boy games
It was the most important piece of
The video game
F******
Pretzel
Get out of here
Everybody
It's not like it like I can understand of his like he was holding the salad or something cuz right
Eat healthy right
Steve is a lot of salt house that ad gets through
The entire ad
Agency without that something like
Hold on now
Bulldog
That was like the last line of the
A line that is
You still to this day from the original Teenage Mutant
Ninja Turtles movie
Is divine
Was like
To err is human but Pizza is awesome
Glitter made of
Is weird
Movie was very strange because that is a
Teenage mutant
Ninja Turtles movie
Right it is actually a
Very interesting look at how
Raiders
The parasite movie
Sound effects for that at a later date
Maybe
First of all like to give a couple of policy walk shout out
Hi to new donors really appreciate
Shout out to Kevin
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you so much
Welcome aboard
Someone else is the globalist
With a
Incredibly generous
Appreciate very much
Amanat Ali Aprilia
Someone someone sodomites
Thank you very much you're officially a globalist
Bottoms.of might be a bucket of poop
Never not going to enjoy that never it's
The gift that keeps on giving from Reverend
David Banner
So are we going to get in today's episode
Out of context drop from this episode
Fire
Yep
Thank you I just don't think for clarifying that we will get to you in a minute
There's a lot of
So
Rodger Stone
Explaining light
Baby
Perhaps the best
That's like a con man
Teaching the FBI how to con
Right but still actively engaging in confidence game
Khan movie where
The conman Hat
Have to be playing the FBI as well
Painted now
Today's episode features a lot of people giving up the game
There's some big news
In the world of Alex
But didn't excite everybody
Beyond that there I have to put Media Matters on black
Will Smith
MPI property behind the Ninja Turtles in New York
I can't pay matters is doing and bring
Attention to stuff
But they made a critical error
But let's start off with
Some big news
And Alex Jones lamb
Al Gore
Behind the scenes
Quarterback
We have Soros
Al Gore
You seen podesta
Alex Jones
Shu know what
Your financial support
You know what t
Not know what it is
The name of like a
And a Sanders
Bsh you-know-what
This is going to come back to over and over again
Over and over and over again and it turns out that may or may not be suing Alex
From all the context clues that I have
I don't know if it's a butt
Someone is f******
Can sue and Alex Alex
Scared
He is shook
Cazares we know he is a halfway crook
Scared to look
He is an easy
Trouble something big is happening behind the scenes
And I think it might have something to do with this next clip
I think they can smash us all that'll do is invigorate us
Even more
Churchill said
Never Surrender
He said we should go on today and whatever the price Maybe
Is Churchill is getting better
What we've got
Really freaked out already
Billy Baxter
So
They figured out where stock
I don't trust Alex Jones to hire a competent private investigator based on everything
Everyone else has ever hired
Pictures of Al Gore's windows
Owen Shroyer putting on a
Manhattan glass
It might as well be
Sherlock Holmes it's absolute Insanity all likelihood
Do like he has been
Stocking
Certain people may be one of the podesta's
That seems to be implied a little bit later in the episode The
That was one of people who put the P eyes on
But one of the fun things about this episode is you'll notice
He just keeps saying like
I can't wait
I can't talk about
Lookout
Talking about how we can't talk about how Outdoors
One of these lawyers so bad his lawyer is f***
Rich because of a lot of billable hours
All the Guardians of Ga'Hoole
I mean naturally Alex Jones
Thanks Hogwarts is Brielle so they would have the best Thursday
They can call people
Yesterday.
I was yesterday
A little propaganda game that I would
He played it with a guest
Two goes by the name of Zach
Alex
Without investigating this guy at all pretends that he has high level
Intelligence information
And
I don't I don't I don't know
No but
You did that would be great
Pollard's
Did agree with Alex Jones as guess who said that they were helicopters
Involved in the Las Vegas shooting
Where people were shooting at the crowd from hell
So
Credible
Real credible
Helicopter
People shooting
From the crowd no shooting at the crowd
Alex has the caller Zach in the game that he played I apologize to everyone who listen to yesterday
Episode 4 the game was
He says
He knows all of the in
Information
About what happened but he can't talk about it
The Gasbuddy has Shepard ambellas
And just call her say a bunch
After the call Alex is like
Can you believe it that's all the secret information I
He plays that game a lot it's comfy
F****** it's complete nonsense
He said yesterday I want to get this
Conclusion of that
Two other agencies promoted
You said
Saudi Arabia
Attacks
Coming
Weave into the Manhattan
Truck attack
I could have him yesterday
I'm sorry we heard you were on
Infowars
Right
We just can't have
The friar anymore
We. Can't do it do not representing McDonald's very well
The order piling up this is your third one
More likely he got called into a meeting with his
His mom
Victor's no f****** way
That there was like
But you got called into the
The FBI director's office
Any raid was about to
Entirely possible
Me too came out people like that a lot I'm going to guess that the guy was either like I don't want to do this
B B B has gone far enough
Did Alex presented is like he's called in 4 years
Reckon tell you that I've been studying Alex for the last 11 months I've listened to the entirety of 2015
And a whole bunch episodes
Other than that
Not yet he doesn't call in
That's like Robert
DeLand
Are you saying
Zach a guy is a Reddit celebrity
Is that is that the case
I think we might be getting
Some Intel from the from the chat room
Pretend this person's an
Garbage day
Call Greg
Deep Space Nine in real life would be is just like
Are you there
Can you have a garbage
Garbage is not based Stickman
Man was also on display
Maybe this accuracy is a faker
He might be ready
It's Library
Stickman is like
I keep getting YouTube mixed up or no
It's either
Slenderman is the reason
Ideas
Slenderman
Slenderman I'm also scared of the Bab
Alright
Yeah that is a
My dude over here like the five best weed ever at first
Going on
Right
Is Alex Jones's found out about the truck
In Manhattan
That's not good
He pretends
Keep some pizza
The news a wafer
From having some pizza
Have pizza goddamnit Alex neither can you get a pretzel
So Alex
I don't know how else to set this up
Launches into it incredibly
Bigoted
Some of the stuff that
Media Matters recovery
One of the discussion about that
Episode explained
What they could have done
Isis
Look at that.
This stuff was not
In the immediate matters report
Look at that
Truly in red
Apologies
But Autumn you can better believe we're engaging in self-flagellation
Love this
Fellatio
Always
Believe their God
Seriously
Armies of inbred psycho killers
Call
Muslim Hillbillies
Missouri
You don't mess with those people there.
Appalachians in the world
Brad psychotic
Heather just literally
I just got this
Okay great
Thanks thanks for that
If you wanted to do tell people like it is you should actually get into the reality of inbreeding
Especially when it's like second cousin
Stuff like that
I'm really not bad bad
The only
We talked about this in great detail
You know we've talked about inbreeding
In the context of
It doesn't necessarily
Create
Diseases
It just gives you a higher likelihood if they're already there
Gene traits are going to explode your higher there's a higher chance of
Mutation
It's not like a guaranteed
Everybody is going to come out looking like The Hills Have Eyes because guess what a lot of times it just gives you a giant foot
Elephantitis
Or some sort of physical ailment
Doesn't make you crazy
Brighten Super Mario 3
Just drove around
Exactly kickball
Yep all the kids want to hang out with me
Here is this is more of what
Hellboy more of what Media Matters actually cover
Piece of garbage
You're you're drooling idiot
Watch this but with your hand
Come On song
All the slave trading all of it comes from me
What we're supposed to
Be culturally rich
Great
You have more in common with them
Yeah
Doesn't he have a lot more in common with them
Describe first
Himself he makes
Excuses for C
Seems to really be in
The other thing I don't want
In the past
Discuss what I want to talk about is very
Like the big thing the headline
Let me get mad or sad is he's talking about how linda sarsour looks like
The Sibling of the attacker
That was that was that was there with Joan says Linda sarsour look
Looks like I think he called the guy a retarded animal breeding forever
Yeah that's that's what they did
Dig Inn at all into other things
But he says
That are much
More troubling
The thing that I want to get to the
My finger on
Here is what he is saying
Vistaprint
Everything you saying
Is all Muslims are unipolar
There are only one sort of Muslim
And this is
Perspectives that we've encountered over and over again
Another thing I want to bring into Focus as
Is today while I was on the bus
Going to and from therapy
Rhinitis
I noticed on Twitter a lot of people complaining about Laura Loomer
Laura Loomer
And she said
Can someone start an Uber or Lyft doesn't use Muslim drivers I don't want to
I don't want to
Give money to a Muslim immigrant
Something along those lines
And everyone got surprised
I'm like guys
Yeah
We've we've been over this
Everyone's getting hundreds of retweets or being like Laura Loomer sucks like
We could have told you that 6-month
Citgo there are no rabbit there are no irrational Muslims
Is no moderate Muslims
What you want on the show and said that everyone's in denial about the idea that we're at war with that religion
We already f****** knew that she's come out inside way worse
Surprise
F****** garbage
Keep the up-to-speed you a******
Naughty people listening you're great but the rest of the world
To get up to speed this is
Problem
Scary Twitter Forever by
Discover
It's not wonderful
Apparently
Exploding with happiness
Also apparently has a little bit of a Twitter war
Between Loomer and Laura Southern
Lauren Southern
Is exciting
Why is it why disease
Exist now damn
Damn
Do ourselves because no one took care of Alex Jones 5 years
Because his mom died
Anyway
Pretty decent Authority that that doesn't sound anything
Sing like Alex's
From someone who has
Pizza
Hollywood a little bit
In a fairly Gross Way
He's talking about charges against one
Harvey Weinstein
Your world
Play black women young girls
Daystar
I think you just jiz
No
No no I mean
I'd like to strike that clip from the record and then his
Throat I don't know what to tell you about how f****** horrific that I don't know the Weinstein is involved
Call just bringing the Muslim terrorist
Send to the country or United Muslim
Steven all of it but also let's not forget that this is
Is exactly what got Alex food buy Chobani
Good Jerry
For that loss
Company good
That's possible
The person who's suing Alex currently doesn't learn from his past mistakes
Yeah that's that's obvious
What
What do you mean he doesn't learn from
He learned from his past
Put out a video and then your lifters are like
And your listeners are just like oh course he did that he doesn't want to deal with the hassle
He doesn't want to deal with
You've got a family
Are far ahead really suck
Tosses balls over the coals
We will have a very different Alex
Soon enough
Standing
Cynthia
We could we could get that Larry klayman
Which shout out to listen to giulio sent me a link to
Larry klayman is petitioning to be the lawyer investigating or trying Hillary
Grimes
Which would be an amazing Friday
You are exactly
Kangaroo court lawyer I want
Told to not appear as not allowed to appear in multiple People's Court today
So Alex talked about earlier you said the Jake Tapper is saying that like that terrorism is wonderful and all that
Because
He said that
The clip that Alex plays
I'm saying that
The driver said Allah Akbar
Usually that is a
Common usually a wonderful celebratory of
Positive contact
Sting
And so this is
Does it say about that
If you do what he does
As you said All Odds are she's with so beautiful
Beautiful
That's really sick
Virtue signaling
Bet
We got your back
Keep doing what you doing
Shot Powersports Felician others
Wolf Blitzer
Dim the screen in the background
So here's the fun thing
The guy who came on Wolf Blitzer show didn't
Scalise was a hero he said that he was it was a friend of
Instead it is a normal guy you just seems like he was burnt out on politics
It's fed up with a political state
Yeah I mean that's what you hear from serial killers friend
Neighbors are like you know Ted Bundy's neighbors that he was a normal guy
One of you so lying about what the guy said on Wolf Blitzer show
But either
Exposed himself
He's saying
Endorses terrorism much like
When is Steve scalise shooting
Wolf Blitzer didn't
Say anything to Rebecca
Alex
You had Mars base people on your show
You didn't robot them
You had David icon
On multiple times and you didn't push back about lizards yet
He'll two similar standards at all no but it's fun
Whenever I was
Listen to that
Are the Pats
Three Clips in
Secession
Alex
What is bigotry
Is
Barry
Very like
Whenever we whatever you played the BBC
C-clip and the guy
He was
Ingrained in that it's so horrific
It's not just that you do you say
He's turning muzzle
Into unipolar
Which
Is more to identifying
A race
It's not like
The faith or any
He's looking at a man's face
And saying
Almost phrenology Style
These are the parts of the face that may
Make a bad person
All of the stuff that
People from the Middle East
Look like horrible
Bigoted races
And if your issue if you know what you know what something about what
Somebody else walking look
Close to getting
Expressing what the issue is so people could take it seriously
At least this piece of
Millencolin
No cigar
I like doing that but
See that your heart agree I agree with you wholeheartedly and I
Tom Brokaw
Demon unalloyed racist
And Alex
The guy use a five-dollar words
And accurately representative
We got lots of
But
Back to your point
About the physical traits
But he's going off of it
Are bad
He's about to get into one
Did I take particular issue
Would you show me an image of the famous
Berg
Islamic friends have it as well
Another
The British aristocracy
Folks in a crocodile
F*** off Alex
What is that
Isaac has a cross-eyed gentleman
Go fuc yourself
Alex
Even
Get his idea of his
Street
England
And Alex has gone to Aristocrat Authority
Now there is a real version
At the cross I being assigned
Nobility
England is one of them
Like being overweight
In a lot of population
Like in Hawaii that was always a functional reason for that
The blood disease most of European nobility aristocracy had for a long time
Time because they were all inbred NASA
Like what they all believe what's the one where you believe really
Even beyond that what I'm saying is like
Resource
Poor areas
People who are overweight as are seen as higher class
Because they are able to
Sustain a higher caloric intake
You look at pictures of like old Rich Hawaiian
They're f******
Superhero
That's the reason that I heard
Speculated that like
Generally the builds are bigger
Hawaii because there was
Is overtime
And isolated population
And people
Selected towards that
So I'll be there stuff like that cross I you cannot explain that way
Just bring random cross-eyed people into your aristocratic Circle
Who doesn't do that
I do
Alex Jones fights himself
To assert
Isis is super into pedophilia
And then you'll see what he does for me
Encourages pedophilia
In the absence of women
Enjoy young boys
Forcing them into harem
Also I mean he's reciting
Infowars
What do you mean
We report we wrote this
Where are the bad ones evil people of
It's
I want to plow into all of this
Domino's spend a few minutes
CareFirst
Just encouraging lister's understand that
When you buy T-shirts
Other materials from Infowars store
That's not possible
It is
You are funding
Looks dirty pretty clear about it
The revolution that has one
Or is Winnick
We might be under attack
Turn turn turn
So you're saying that I wanted
Bring out at 1
Interesting kind of add pivot that Alex
Is doing on this show
On this November 1st
Tell you what
Missouri coming out
Did the kind of pivot he's doing are these really slow intense
Channel 18 there's a feeling of desperation in
Andis pivot
Before
This money generally be like
He is deported
I think he's getting sued based on
The nature of the pivot
Text Clues
So in this next
Clip alx50 in your Dino I know you were trying to start another clip
Respond
Refill Mike wine
No is it
Really is always
Something that hits
The idea of
How
We can just blow by the fact that
He called everybody a patty
Violin
Everything he doesn't like with
F****** chilled
We just go buy it because you don't have it
Commonplace to us now like
It's like if you if you
Genuinely believe that every Republican
Who said that
Being gay is equivalent to being a pedophile
Should be f******
Murder
But this is
Everything
If you're gay you're a pedophile
Porcupine
Nevermind
Or if you're not white
On yesterday's show you legitimately said that Auntie for the foundation of it all is f****** kid
Not everybody does
But that's what it's about
Ridiculous
The 27th
Post social media post
Availability of
People like I mean even we can just broadcast on the internet Alex Jones is able to broadcast up without censorship without
I could get sued and stuff like that
It's just the equivalent of
Highly ramped-up accelerated seitan
It's the same stuff that we saw with like the McMartin School cases
Or just seeing it again but it's
Much worse and it's much
Alex has no one toosii
Right except how do you like I could have
Someone
Goddamn
I think someone will
We're still big fan
So we talked about on our last episode we were on together how Alex is suspiciously not talking about George
Papadopoulos
His guilty plea
Ready-made
The Alex
About it and guess what
Is a complete setup
So that's about all yes
But
Out of the
The Trump
Papadopoulos when he was just a low-level
Coffee Warriors
Something like that
Doesn't matter
Is he
If he's
Not what if he did
He could just be a guy off the street it doesn't matter how far
TV violated eloped
That he talked with campaign officials about doing it
They lied about it
Then we have the proof is their problem isn't like
Alex
I don't give a s*** about that we don't have time to talk
Set up
I don't I don't
Connecticut little dirty
But at the same time
I don't give a s*** about
Doesn't talk about it much
Right for what he gets into
Because it jogs
His mind
Is a piece of his biography
Another Pizza
This one is f***** up
Shut up
Swamp operate
I was in 8th grade I was not a drug user but I smoked marijuana before
And
And in the Fieldhouse
Buy a joint for me in the morning
The joint
For me in the morning
Will the next follows me in the bathroom first.
Is it here please buy it
They still told me the office
Marijuana cigarette
You shut him up
Are you at the organized criminal your
Deinonychus black people that's what's going on
Is that they just wanted
Teach me a lesson
Hellboy
So interesting
Interesting piece of Alex Jones's false
I self told a biography
Okay
Bright
Do you know what's great about being
Being a drug dealer
You don't have to
Run people down to sell dry
Define
Drugs and people buy them
Totally don't people deliver when you get to be an adult
Fantastic
So what happened was
He was
He didn't have any money
He said he would have money in the morning to buy a joy
Probably in the bathroom
Gets caught
Vent cover story
Holding up
Now course the teachers are are the principal is like
What how did you learn to lie like this
F*****'-a
Insane person
That was our first time that Alex Jones
Is the psychopath
Will eighth grade
Avakin life like that 8th grade is 14
Look like what was there couple hundred girls before he was 16 so
Is big as your head
He's already sexually active at this point as a fourteen-year-old
I think you probably about a joint
Absolutely by remember
Myschools
You know the kids who were into drugs
Usually we're the ones were fighting
All kinds of troublemaking goes
Together
Kind of you know if there's a there's a umbrella thing
Especially at least before Alexa
I think if you're doing drugs
Protecting your great
Yeah but it 14 that's a little early
If you're 16
Like
Slow down
No we don't make it like a party route
Team
Enjoyed
That way you really enjoyed
As opposed to just make it another Choice like I got to buy milk
Got to buy the story Alex Jones is told in
Involved him
You had a
Conspiracy that the
Schools or the police
We're actually selling drugs through the kid
He doesn't bring up that stuff cure this
Completely
Different
Childhood getting
Jammed up for drugs
Story
Very easily be
Oh you got caught with drugs
Absolutely
You're just making up reasons
To pretend you weren't the bad guy everything he does
King of reasons
It look I'm not I don't like black people
They started the fight
Like
Do you absolutely certain
Look up somebody
Punches you after you call them
Edward
They started it
You started
That actually triggered something in my mind I want to say first.
Exit to focus when you receive the narratives that he pushes in modern-day of
The 40 something year old man
And you just relate them
Child brain
Process
It makes so much
Like all of it starts
To come into Folk
I wanted to talk about was
The release
All the names
We're not all of them but the first
Twitter
Screen names
Of the people who were
Russian Bots
Haha
I was looking through the list
Edit fuc
Crazy
It's so clear what they were up to
Okay
There's so many screen names that are like
Chicago News Daily News
Aries daily
City names with
Daily News
Record Ryan meme
And then there were like
Blm's Soldier
There were a bunch of like Bass
Screen name
Used to sew division March
For Trump was one of them
Like they're very clean.
I would say
Most of the ones are on the way
Are facsimile is a real people today
And then there's a bunch of
And the ones that aren't
Fall very easily into
Oggi's
This is exactly what Alex Jones
Yep
Trump positive
There's racial Division 1
So clear
Well and we already have only one batch
There was one that
I underscore a underscore a underscore
Fantastic
That's fine I'm fine
I don't like the idea of Scatman being a Russian bot
If that was all the Russian Bots did is just
A long list of different scatman's
Perfect
Paris gay but
Gay headlights
5/8
Forgot to write you guys
Is that is that a wrong it's clear that they have a
Exactly hundred percent better understanding of social media
Screen names, somewhere like
Someone
Would make as a joke
Look up one suckers book the intelligence
How to take down America years ago
Let's remember that was this
One of the Russian
What did Alexander Alexander Dugan had the one about creating racial division
Military school
And all of this stuff is
Very similar right in line with that
Has been a multiple-time Gaston Alex Jones Show and Alex
Has been on his show in Russia
Twitter
Perry underscore a Scatman
Twitter handles had a funny
Tweets Twitter handle that involve the n-word
Band
Can say it just because it's
The Twitter handle
I don't I don't know what's appropriate
That funny
Look like
Alright
Cummins been sitting on that
That's pretty that's wild
Russian Bots
Infiltrator black Twitter
Very strange
I don't know if they did or not but
But make it appear pretty pretty well report
Stories about how
Russian ads
Funded a lot of
Different black lives matter
Meetup Center
Yeah exactly
Keating Facebook events
Yeah
Groups of people were just showing up to fight each other we're all bugs
Sincerely think I'm not going to because I don't really care about social media and it doesn't really affect
Like me all that much in
Lord knows that I've even like listeners
If we didn't but I sincerely think that the crisis of our time
Beyond even a lot of this propaganda and
Is we all have to
Walk away from social media
There's a lot of fun
Fun things you can do with it
And what have you
But AAA I think it is
Something that is just ultimately not worth it
Call one
Once once I read up on
Analytica that was
The moment where I was like
Oh maybe
Maybe all of the
What's going to kill
Yeah yeah it'll get us to kill each other
Predictive programming
Rodger Stone comes on the show today
Beg for mercy
Willard's Crossing Orwell
Miller's Crossing
He comes on and Alex and
Them say it
Look into it
Even town in Austin to strategize
Is what Alex says
We'll get to that in the next but first how far away is
Exactly getting real close to the Border
So here is that what Rodger Stone has
To say
What do you make of this timing
The NFL Hollywood literally collapse
There's not
People are pulling the plug on cable in general and that's
Really hurting NFL rating
Conversation about this I didn't even realize
That they made a new rule in the NFL that every touchdown
Have to be reviewed
Yeah I didn't realize that and that completely destroys the game
Makes it almost on watchable I would have no enjoyment you can't celebrate with your team and what have you
It's their own fault they did this
Not standing for the national anthem
Value go to Hollywood
Has been an issue that's been broiling under the surface and people have been talking about for a while and
And it's coming forward to some people are brave enough to make it happen
Death
That's not
It's not a coincidence
Alex Banks
God
I just think America
Very interesting Lee that I came on and I laid out a scenario
So I want to auto parts right there before you get to the scenario cuz
Interesting thing that I've started to pick up on on Infowars that I don't think we do a good
Enough.
And that is Whenever two people or talk to each other
They're not having a conversation
One person says something and then the other person is like
Interesting thing you said I'm not going to talk about it
It's it's
Rotana
Oh by which the president
Demand that Jeff sessions appointed special counsel to look into uranium one
This would have the effect
I'll putting mister mister call me mr. McCabe the associate director of the FBI
And Rod Rosenstein the de facto Attorney General of the United States
Play Yesterday headline
A piece on rawstory the worst of the worst fake news
Plane is falling apart
You just told us what you fear you fear this move by Donald Trump
Rodger
Come on man
You just told us what you fear
No
Scared about this Russian investigation
Does he not realize that the things he's saying or like
Imperative is the most desperate slapped together
I'm clearly not worried about it
Here's my 20-part plan
Google
Ariel
So cancel
Can people get really pissed
Is get rid of them
No no
Amore Independence
Of course
Larry
And the only reason I know this is going to happen
Larry Nichols
The Pinnacles
Who's blackmailing the gbg
Mueller has released some indictments and no one is gone down Larry Nichols hasn't shown up on Alex Jones Show
By the way
I don't know this is unconfirmed
But if you Google Larry Nichols or if you
I don't want to put his phone number out of
Website that comes out
Phone number out there but it turns out
Google the phone number
What comes up is a scam report
There's a website that lists scams
I've ever someone who is listed Larry Nichols scam report claiming that he doesn't have cancer
And that he is defrauding people of money
Yeah
There is a day I don't know if it's true
If it's the matter of people sending me tons of money
That's possible
I know I know a bunch of things that I don't know. No no no
This is from this scam report
Those ladies people have been getting scammed off
And she called the number and talk to him
He gave the name of the hospital that he was getting treatment
She called the hospital
And there's no
Simpson goes there by the name of Larry
Now I don't know
I want to believe it
Can you pretend to be like a family members
I don't know
Maybe Larry Nichols money is also clever enough to
Scam Hospital into giving them private records Affair Place probably not real but I wanted to date
If you have lung cancer why are you smoking on video and then Alex Jones documentary
You're welcome if you got them I don't know anyway I just want to believe it
Find
Papabubble of your pumps
Conspiracy theory I don't know it is a conspiracy theory
And
Like Larry Nichols
But the other thing is that like it's it's Larry Nichols character
Your profile
Maybe
I don't suppose you were going started this
I said it
Maybe not real
It maybe not real but I want to believe it at somewhere
Yeah I know
Well let's call it a dog
Alex
Does not want to talk about the algor lawsuit
I'm not ready to tell folks about it
Law firm of Obama
I have
I mean
What about last night
What's the allegations
Before March
The empire
They thought
Stop
That also very clearly says
That was Buckley
Yeah that was Buckley turning it off I was like
You are actually getting sued Alex this is not this
This is very serious
And I don't think it's that I don't think that Obama sticked his second law firm against
Alex
I don't think of Rodger Stone
I don't think Al Gore is suing
Alex
Once you get the details out will be able to parse through and figure out what the reality of the situation
Obviously slandered someone again
I mean this is easily that
Just about anybody who wants
How to do everyone's at 7 months ago we went over the Chobani yogurt
Who's very guilty there
Yep I got out of the p
Pizzagate thing just in time
Although he still he talks about pizzagate on this episode
He seems to think that like
Those videos you deleted from the internet don't exist anymore
There's no consequence
I know we have all of his
He's committed at least
15 crimes in time that we've talked about what might be treason
Straight-up be treason
Or the very we
Please conspiracy
Stop
Symbiosis symbiotics non-zero-sum game
And so like somebody like
We want Frosty
That you got it energized
Global
Infowars
I didn't I just brought it back
Chick-fil-A
That's not a good sign
I don't know what this early
The last clause
Okay I don't I don't know if it's ready
Urges a random mix of...
By the way he perceives of his place in the world is
He's leading the populace charge all around the world
These are populist movements
That's what you are the mouthpiece of
Does
It might
You might be on the wrong side
Might
Might be furthermore might just be
You can't
Lead
A nationalist movement
Globally
Well they make the argument that it's like
No it is
Everyone wants to have their own Nation
Nationalism is super sexy
The word Coalition of all these nations that just want our own nationalism
Right I understand why that's
The maddening butt
The way they think is going to happen if they okay
God dammit
I know what you're going to say
You're going to say that okay so you guys have a bunch of globally there's a bunch of
Countries that are super nationalistic and after their own interests are going to end up fighting
Because they are nationalistic
Legal conclusion that most
People come to
Yeah but the reality is that that's probably not what
It's going to be like
Conglomerate
Chin of these
Nationalist
Six states that
That take resources
Ramen
More license slave
All the third world countries is probably all the brown place
Yeah yeah
I was going to say that okay I thought you were going to go dump version
Really really f****** went to town
Movies gone down the group
Before I know but I was talking
What I'm saying is what they
Clearly
Is that if they are Jordan I know I got you
Now you know how f****** I feel
Alright
We just had a we just had a public order fight of sorry Dan we love each other
Alex
No it's it's so stupid to imagine that okay
You're leading there's a centralized nationalist movement
The tree surgeon
And what is going to happen
If they do win
Those leaders are already leading to
Together they're going to cooperate
Yeah you're just creating a different United Nations nationalist Nations
Actress of power
Yep that is going to see I would happen
S46
What are Revolution November 4th
Hilltop
Talk show host
Right
Brother to priority
Cops
And talk show host
Well we got to solve the real problem actually I would argue that's priority
Rubio's
I'm putting Alex up top
Super clear about that last movie taken out of context
Right
Yeah we just want the Second Amendment people to political
Right I don't I don't
Anyway
Rodger Stone
He's not just there
They also have some gossip
But he wants to report at news
And Alex has one of the stupidest things overheard at the end of this clip
But last night I was with a very high-level Republican lobbyist
With very very close ties to the Bush family and to
Specifically
Had lunch with Jeb
Trump will be gone by December
Couple be gone by December what is that tell you the whole show of that
Start over
Right
Rodger
I was hit with a polonium Dart
Classic Bowl
And even if he did Bluff
He would be bluffing about this politically
Absolutely
F****** idiot
This is what happens when you end up like
Working and being partners with a manipulator
Like you don't do it for that reason
You think they'd like
You can team up with
Stop music
Right over time the person who is more powerful in manipulation
Going to be able to
I just run the roost
Rodger Stone
More or less
You can get out
You are your particular look you never blocked
Look is what happens with me and my cat get a better relationship
PowerBlock nationalistic
Hellboy
It was surprising a
This Mexico
Yeah I'm going to call this out I'm just going to go ahead and tell you ahead of time
I usually like you to be blindsided by the pivots to add
Threats but I need to tell you ahead of time so you can
Track how he does it
This is clunky is s***
Is this
2 mi in
Indicates massive desperation
Destiny indicates like a severe situation that Alex's face
This is not just
I want another boat
This is definitely like I'm a
In trouble
Christine
Is Ali Akbar
Islamic
Terrorism at its worst
Dippin Dots
Very very true
So we're going to listen to the rest of it
I bet he does cuz it's
F***** up
Another driver and then apropos of nothing
He just goes into
This like
Through it all
You buy products in for store.com
Resistance to the Mosasaurus
And for his billions
Millions can counter that but we need Millions
That
Either
People who are in marketing
Sometimes things are best-sellers events or not
Infowarsstore.com
And get one of those 60 70 t-shirts
Today
Restore.com
Are AAA 2533 139
Warfare
Wolf
Wow
Yeah
Florida's with money now
I mean as a sales pitch
It's blunt
People dancing around it this is the Bernie Sanders
Not really
Give me all your money
I will fight my fake enemies to the death
I mean look
The way this all shakes out I think
The most likely
Scenario is
A couple more indict
Come down and Trump
I think that's probably what's going to happen
You're going to realize
If I don't
The entire family businesses fuc
I probably
Penske probably pardon me and my family you know.
Work out some kind of backroom deal that's going to happen
The other problem with
Propaganda still Infowars is still going to be a problem
All that stuff because they're not going
Going to be like
Do you say will be a completely like he was forced by the globalist
Go back to the John Kelly at poison
Narrative probably at that point
There'll be some sort of thing but like
I don't know I don't know how I got off on that but I mean it's just this
Peak bulshit
It's amazing
You know what's really amazing
Rodger Stone describing it as
Islamic terrorism at at
It's worse right which is like
No
And two if it were
We just had white terrorism at its worst
Holy s*** there's about fifty times as many people
They're better at murdering random people
Because he believed it was a psyop with helicopters
The fun thing for me
Is obviously Rodger Stone knows that it
Course
It's
Like for real
Maybe the only real white supremacy is that white p
People are
Complete sociopaths willing to murder everybody and that's how we got where we are today
Willing to lie for each other
Willing to lie desperately for each other to protect white supremacy
Like consider
Most serial killers are white
True alright also most people who hurt children
Is it possible that that's a mutation of the regular white jean which is just
Taking over the world with cross eyes out of this
I am actually advocating for the move from a soft yes
Jesus that's not good I mean there's nowhere else to escalate this podcast is over
There's only one solution to our problems and that's
Backwards ethnic cleansing Jordan I've appreciated our time together
Did this is really just about to be radicalized
I think of you listen
If you showed enough
People enough Infowars eventually we'd all be like
It's not a bad I
Do you listen to our podcast and the dollop
It's game over for you there's no hope for lights out
I mean
Justin Bieber's super super clear get just because I'm so self-conscious
Just about like Alex listening
Take it out of context
We don't think white people are evil
The tradition has been
Really terrible
Write the history is really awful
There's nothing intrinsically evil about whites
Skin
You dumb f*** Alex
Hypothetically
Its skin color how do you not get that
Not you
Alex
We're still doing this
Apparently yeah anyway
Call Jones's karaoke moment of the day
Burning inside with a fire
Hazel Miller
Alex Jones
Ride Along
Along with that
He's right here and it's about him
Trump Twitter
Needs to be regulated like a utility
Companies a private company but they can't deny you a telephone
This is a First Amendment issue
So they could have
First Rogerstown is advocating for a regulation on a private business
Which is
Fun
Also it's not like a phone
At all because there are many platforms you can
Communicate with online
You can choose not to it's not it's not as essential to your life
Instaconnect
Yeah
Now isn't it
Strange that the guy that you want in there is
Rodger Stone
Have you ever heard of hip-hop
Paseo yes you have your a f****** classic bullshiter
Rates
He should be saying this about internet
As opposed to saying it about a private business internet didn't hurt him
Twitter
Absolutely
That's what all of these
These people like stone is smart enough to know that what you saying is dumb
And it's only going to hurt people other than him
The issue all of these people
Regulation in finally
When it finally touches them they're like
Regulation is always bad but not in this
Free Speech issue neo-Nazi
Befriend you old glamourpuss
I like calling him
Glamourpuss
Earlier I said that I took some issues with Media Matters
Issues was when we talked about that the
The beginning that they didn't really give the full context
The complaints
Complaints is very generous
2 saying about this guy attack
Manhattan
But
The thing that I think
Irresponsible
Derelict in their Duty
As media watchdog
Is it they didn't listen to the rest of the episode
Because the rest of the episode at the end
Alex Jones has an interview with a guy named Matt Bracken
Who is a guy who is very much
In favor of militaristic act
Action
Against
He's allegedly has a military background
Not entirely sure he probably does I don't know
Allegedly because I
No I don't I haven't done looking at
Broadcast
On Skype from his den
Pretty cool
I like his dad all of his pictures are hung up
I'll tell you that much about that
I'm out
But I also get garbage dicks
The throwing this out that's that I appreciate you reminding
He is a novelist
And he's written a bunch
Novels that purportedly
God revealed truths
About the world but it's all fiction
Islamophobic
Who would have garbage dick has labeled him as a right-wing wank fiction author and I think that's fair
Solid solid
F****** crazy
A lot of times and pictures book
Like a plug his books and what have you
The reason I bring up Matt Bracken
Read a book called
How to hide your
How to hack roblox.com
Where to find books
Yes
Everywhere else
No
Never gun safe
Media Matters if you talk
About Matt Bragg
Because he is the more important
Miss you and I know that it's not a sexy cuz most people don't know that who he is
Even done a better job talking about the all the stuff
That was around that clip
What they talked about about Linda sarsour
Being compared to a
Is that b
Linda sarsour looks like this guy's brother witch
Another
Freudian slip
I think he was legitimately
Can you call her
I was being more generous than I probably should have been
Clicks based on your dumb headlights but let us know
Then let us write the article
You fuking idiot
Pokemon go
There's never will in trouble
Look you can really monetized
Corporate left there not going to be October
Seems like also antifa socialist
So
Maybe a couple
Maybe a couple folks
Miss out
That it's real shame
Did aunt
Contact you or like how you tone down the white gentleman but don't be so obvious
November 4th
You know what to do indoors
Matt Bracken is what out they should be focusing on
Because he says a lot of stuff that is
Is much worse
Right
We were the people who people could rely on
To cover Alex Jones
We have an article about him
Maybe we will incorporate in the future onto knowledge site.com but
Your ears
Welcoming map bracket on the show
And Jackie
He's talking about Islam being bad
Actual translation of
Is great that's a big mistake
When they say Allah hoo and they put the
Greater
Is greater than your God Allah hoo Akbar is
Concord
Cancel
I know and also it's not true
It much like you says Raza Barraza means the race that means people
Best translating
Bracken is kind of right on some level but he is wrong in his
Interpretation according to Mainline Islamic scholars
I mean God is greater
But the understanding generally is a God is greater than you
Plumb-rite
God is greater than the things that are your it your issue
To put you in your place
In terms of the hierarchy of God and man Allah and man
Or even a God will never give you more than you can handle
God God is omnipotent
That that sort of there's like connotation
The other thing is the other translation of Allahu Akbar
If God is omnipotent
He is by definition greater than your guy
That's true
Neither God is omnipotent
One of them is in the other one isn't
Would have to be real
And then we'd really get the
Could one of the guys become big enough
Not that the other couldn't let you
Could become a big enough Mountain that the other
Could lift
Crazy
I'm also the other translation
Very common for amputation of Allahu Akbar is God is greatest
And that is not God is the greatest god
Because
All these religions are monotheistic
Islam
Christian right about the money buckets on the Family
Carbonized
Look this what happens when you're raised in the f****** sure it's up communion there we go
That didn't go over well with the chat room
I'm also garbage dick dropped in some of the
Matt Bracken
Book titles
Here we have
Enemies foreign and domestic
Domestic enemies
Foreign enemies and traitors
I also
He is a mess
Here is his next
His name is literally a sword of Allah
Nobody a very extreme wedding picked up on the fact that
His parents named
Anyone that he won the Isis Lottery
To come to America
And bring 28 more I just heard today bring 28 of this closest
Inbred family here
Which I'm sure on welfare
They're plotting more Jihad attacks
Because we're creative
Yikes
Because the least
Creative most inbred tax
Who did do the truck attack his name is very similar to would-be translator
Rated as
The sword of Allah
But that doesn't mean anything
You know what Ariel mean
Play Muriel
Lion of God
Largest animal
Okay
They are vicious killers in the name of God
Brandon memes
Mermaids
Sword
In Celtic
Okay
I don't know
Prepare everything
There's another I can't remember what it is but there is a very common Anglo.
I mean sort of God
Like it is a common name I don't remember what it is I thought it was David but that's gift of
Got
That are from Andy
Find Manti Te'o
Tradition of violence within name
You know what Daisy Mae
Cock-block
Crazy Little Flower cock-block
The other thing I mean
I'm getting more into the inbreeding
I guess I made this guy had been here since 2000
It is entirely possible that
This was around
Against
But anyway
Welfare being given
Within five years
Of becoming a
The citizen
I am so it is 7 years after possible that they were on assistance
So Bracken is just throwing around a lot of
Idea that the argument is
Tax dollars are going to pay for people
It's the Welfare Queen
It's a modern welfare
Great episode Coronavirus
But also the
Bracken
No
Did that little scat there
Guess what I was trying to
What I was trying to come out with was
The idea that
Matt Bracken is reinforcing also this idea that there is only one sort of
Air and it's
Predetermine today
Tommy Robinson has a great book
Muslims kill 44
You can't
It is The Ten Commandments are all kill kill kill
There's no way to take it out
Beautiful
Spring
We support you brother good job
Just make sure it's a church next time
I mean it's beyond
But
What's fascinating is
What happened
Dan if you break one of the ten
You go to hell
No you shall be put to death
Oh really
So you'd wait
Yeah
Is that right
Also I don't think there is as well as all the Lost
From Deuteronomy late night show has some
Conversion of the top 10 list
Because David Letterman did it ready so successful but I don't
Just because the Bible was so successful with it
Doesn't mean that that's in every religion there's no
You don't say
He's understanding of s*** is very is very wack and the idea that all the Commandments are to kill
And Islam we got over this over and over again the the analyses that have been done about violence
In the Bible and
The crime show that Bible is
Not a ton but little bit more violent
So
I don't know it's just a dumb conversation
Also if alter I can't like her to kill why don't you
Ableton Commandments where to kill you
You could have gotten
Point off with four
Commandment number one
Kill
Commandment number 2
Commandment number 3
Kill like you got it
Brevity is the soul of wit
But it is not the soul of religion
Bright also Tommy Robinson is a disastrous bigot
He is a British version of Alex Jones
To some degree
Think of Tommy Davis
A domes in England Davidson
Movies playing
Living Color right
Pizones
He did
Pizza Hut spokesman whenever pizones came out
Crazy
Anyway that bracket
Anyway
Yesterday we went over we
We apparently
We went over
The biggest
Big
Big story
Alright
So Mike cernovich
Was trying to give a speech
In New York
Columbia University
Why
Cuz he likes to rile people up
Publicity stunt
In order to keep himself relevant otherwise
You know you can exploit it pretty far
Mike cernovich is giving a speech there
Protest
And they had a sign
It said no
Soupremacy
No pedo bashing
No Mike Serna
I wonder which
Bay Focus
That was one sign for that that when you hear me tell you that
What what's your first thought about
You see a picture of that
What do you think
Plant
You
Archicad
Alright dumb libtard
Talk about it for about
Third of the show yesterday about how expensive are coming out of the woodwork
Of course there was a reporter from Gotham S2 was on site and he took a bunch of
Two pictures that show that that is just somebody came up
In a mass
Unfurled the protesters
And immediately when they saw what it was
Destroyed design
It was clearly an outright plant the guy in The Mask
They got a good picture though I mean not good picture but you got to make sure that's good enough and you know what would Owen Shroyer said the
The other day not the other Dave a couple weeks back
Optics
Become the story
Then that is exactly what's happened here
So today
Mr Porter
Feel really bad that I can
Can't remember his name
But he was reporting that
Of course the song got destroyed immediately
Antifa
People who were there were like
They didn't even
Print out art logo
The flag that was the wrong color in the logo like there's no way that we
Someone who's not involved with
And we went over there yesterday but just so you know
Advice didn investigation into NAMBLA
Sometimes they have November
Yeah it well used to existence
Something for these folks
To throw
As a boogie
Right so it was a complete
It was a complete nonsense publicity
Would not be surprised if Mike cernovich was keenly aware of it at least someone involved
Maybe Jack Boscobel
Check
Mike cernovich comes on the show today
November 1st
And here is
Them talking about it
Mike cernovich
What is the point of them
There's a full-page ad in New York about hey we're going to start a civil war
It's about
Protests about rallies
Yeah
As far as I know part of it
Amendments
Never heard
You're on Shaky Ground bring the Ten Commandments with you wherever you go
Does my butt did you notice
This is exactly like that.
Where Alex
Just one question I'd like son of a
It's just answers another
Who why do they say nothing's going to happen on the 4th and then this ad
What is going on
So weird and unhinged earn from
Wenatchee foot was tearing a pedophile sign and then they just handed it to us
You just going to carry around what everybody hands you
So that
That indicates two
To me that
This was sort of like
Polite
Right Mike cernovich
Expect out of people in order to like
Exploit
Do you know that
Can you hold this for me for a second
Like it if I
You probably wouldn't do that at
Airport Logan use examples like someone asked me to hold their bags
Could you hold this, clay cartoon
Big circle
Let's just be fun.
Well let's say I mean someone gave you
I don't even know how to make it an analogy because my my brain keeps going to like
A goblet covered in ship
Or something like that
And you hold it for them hold it for them not knowing
I was just being polite at all I don't understand
Crank no it's not a human being and and him knowing
The people would respond that way
I kind of think that
Vitamin B
Because because he has this line ready to go it's possible that he just came up with it since then
If possible to
Linda
The more suspicious that he
You might have been
No proof at all that like you said yesterday
First of all
No proof at all there were people on
Saw the entire thing
Pictures
Pedophile
Right
Now they're having to admit false Flags could exist
Because I need Alex's.
Being here this is at this isn't for
No proof at all that like you said yesterday
Albert Avenue admit false Flags could exist
Right which is a narrative
Either way
Whoops
Got to give up the game there a little bit
Alienvault
Reddit conspiracy propaganda world
Happened like
Helicopters shooting at people in Las Vegas
Oh wait hold on someone give someone a sign and someone took a picture of it I guess I know that it was fake
I guess Sandy Hook didn't happen all right
Not lying
I am lying to you
But what if I'm not
Even if I am
You might as well just be making noises
Clips up where they like
Larry Brown
And then the next one
Labrador
A better show would be like
Just Alex screaming at a monkey
Keep pissing in his own face
Viral
Every great episode
Alright looks April come on anymore we got Koko the gorilla coming in the face in a round face
There's there's
I meant the Coco Coco the gorilla with there's a lot of gorillas have cocoa
Sign language
Girl is a speak sign language
Also
Disney Pixar Coco coming out sometime
I sure there was a me though
That wasn't sign language to voice talk
Let's move on
I told you to hold on to your thoughts about that Lottery
Through this
That was dressed and I walked back into the break room to get a
Coffee
Blaming Trump for New York
This is the guy that got the bill passed with Obama's
He's the chief sponsor
Diversity Lottery
Enrichment
Makeup
No but you're lying
Married to you here in 1987 the US government under President Ronald Reagan decided
I found an official immigration Lottery
Call the diversity Visa Lottery
Through this program they wanted to make sure the diversity of Nations
In the United States of America will be preserved in the future
Because they regarded as a characteristic
The creature of The American Nation
The immigration
The immigration DV Green Card Lottery still exist today
The permission to become a legal permanent resident
Midstate
Alex
You don't know anything
Why is it why would
Anyone listen to
What is it what is going on cuz he
I just heard that pretty confidently
Alright that's
That's why we're f*****
Alright okay
Make you this promise ring
Greg
Reagan got that diversity pass
Yeah
That's my favorite
Infowars news we've ever covered in this next clip
Don Jr outing
That he did
It is Trump's fault
More less
There's a lot of Dynamics involved
Ultimately one of the just for safety's sake and accuracy
His hands or not
Absolutely that's what I would say
Terrorism
Whenever there are so many people
Who feel like there's
Nowhere else
When you're just
The system doesn't work
When you're poor when you have no money
When nobody get there's no social safety
Peanuts there's nothing
To deal with Larry is corollary of rioting is the voice of the unheard
Anne Winters
And when you got nothing left to lose
Yeah you can't be a suicide bomber
I'm stupid not to understand that historical
Oh you sure can we found that out
How did Donald Trump jr. is one of Mike cernovich is sources right
You didn't get really mad at me
He does realize that's life
And I was making it up
Did you bring that up
Like in the real world
That could get someone
Killed that got reality winner f****** tossed in prison
Exactly
That behavior
The outing of a stores
That Alex did you fart
That's life
Why is one of them
And most challenged
Situation
Copyright
Speech
And Beyond
Source being
Who killed possibly for giving the information that they're not supposed to give
That's your credibility out the window why would any Source ever talk to you again
And you know he doesn't need them cuz he don't have sources are not real
Just go to 4chan Pol today
That's the only sources
Alex pretends he doesn't his callers calling
You believe that's exactly what my secret information
The emperor has no clothes
No the kids
Cares
Beheaded
Don't you remember that
I would eat violate one of The Commandments
So difficult about Charlottesville
Text which is to kill Heat
Here's the Scoop about Charlotte's Beltsville being fake
We can have big Marques we can bring a lot of people out
Anime use fat fat and bags with these alright morons in Charlottesville
You know why Obama
Texas I mean
Hard enough
The false flag
Bright
Okay
Who committed the terrorist Act
Hard right
He was in all writer
Music
There's a there's a great comment in Manning is is an Oreo
By his own word
So was this f******
Whatever who cares what it's for
From where
Gamergate started there was
Some good analysis
What happened to apply to crnkovich back then
It's because they were convinced their opponents were using them again
The truth is
Who cares
Mike cernovich and Alex Jones all these people are so caught up in their white
They can't possibly believe that anything a white person does
Monstrous
Is real
So they create this whole narrative
04 swaggerty and stuff like that
Justifies it to them use it again
Deliberate
And it's
This is everything they say
Think we're doing
Is what they're due
It's more complicated than that
It's more complicated and more provable than
Like that's what he says
I don't ever want to use the exact rhetoric
Cowardly
AIDS
Utter ironic
That's what is going on
More life
Cuz this is what we're this is this
And I don't mean liberals I don't mean antifa faces what the world is
Are critical to our survival
I don't think we get Sunshine that everybody gets a
The sandwich
They stop this
The time
Dialing up millions of people to
To be duped by them
I mean what it serves
To do is make sure that no one get
Get the sandwich cuz we've got to babysit these f***
All the time
No one's paying attention
Right we are essentially babysitting
I'm cleaning up
The mess that the Alex Jones makes everyday it's just
I mean we should have thousands more listeners
Relatively intelligent person has done with the rest of the shity human race Ferrari
People doing a lot better job on other
Global issues and I think a lot of people are doing a better job about Trump
And what have you
It's too much on him
Very few people are doing good job about propaganda
Except as it relates to Russian stuff
Cuz that's
Yeah that's me
The right that's a hot check the hot talk
It's just a
Like please take care of that Folk
Absolutely
Please take care of that
But realize once it's over
We still got this mess
Yeah man we're just getting a head start on cleaning it up
Alex Jones is leading a real militia
I will be like
We've been saying this for five years
No one is listening
Bracken is leading the gorilla anti-muslim unit
I'm telling Dad
Posthumously
We are going to be thought of
Actually successful
We're going to get the ship kicked out of us by proud boys
Maybe being able to pay our rent
And getting beat up by the owl tonight
Great
I'm not
I refuse to
Proud boys
But also
Chicago
You're not too concerned about them but Alex is really concerned about being sued
I know I've been making a point over and over
I'm making that point over and over again cuz that is the story of this episode
Let me ask you about November 4th when I kick this thing off I actually my lawyers want me to get into it but I mean literally
Real Gore
Got his whole deal
March is on the Run
Again they cut him off by ramping up there like soundrop
Going to come out in the in the next few days probably
But also the idea T saying that Al Gore is told him to lay down by November 4th
F****** b*******
Just trying to bolster his narrative he's probably getting sued by
I wouldn't even be too surprised if it was hamdullah Kaya again
And that he is giving you a
You call to ask
An index
If you just said they're coming for me
That works
Like 22
Just kind of a long time. Your marketing it's not good marketing unless you know
Know when you need the money
Specifically
Is that might be the case
Leah Morales
Cut the world
Timing doesn't make a mix
I think I think it's a lot to run afoul of there
Their agreement
The Brittany
The whatever agreement they made in force
Observe
I'm lucky they got out of that
Also
Here's my ears one Theory I have
I don't think it's
But it's entirely pop
Because I don't
For the longest time as been saying you know in terms of Sandy Hook
We just had the bait
We played both sides
Will you play Devil's Advocate
Still denying
But a week ago
He did
Yeah he straight-up said it's fake as a $3 bill
I think there might be a chance that maybe some of the families are
I would be
Please still get death threats from his listeners
Reading the news now because it's just like everyday
Family members
Constantly feel like people like Jimmy Dore even making comments that are similar to Alice
Like you're supposed to be you're supposed to be
Progressive bro right don't fall for the same b*******
But he fell for that he was at least
Putting his dick in the water with the Seth rich
A man he was
Spouting a bunch of nonsense on
Oh my God
Larry Nichols his number
The other day he tweeted something about
Jimmy
Dammit dammit
I went when it all goes down
Logos
Radio show host
Watch
RadioShack
Maybe you were trying to sell them
Joint at school
I don't know
One more click here
This is very troubling
Incredibly trouble
Because we have been operating under an
That I think is a fair assumption
Reasonable
Thing to believe
In terms of
Propaganda
Look at it as
They are talking to their audio
Yeah I think we have been remiss
I think we've been looking at it wrong
Is there a habit
In this next clip Mike cernovich really gives up
The game about what they're at
Actually doing
I ever criticize Trump
Consumers doing
Send tracking Schumer's doing that
From someone directly
Orange over and hear a joke
City of Bushnell
Trump supporters
A day or two later
At that rally in Arizona Trump finally for the first
No professionals do our jobs we know what we're doing
Negotiation
You just not going to steamroll last
So
The the thing that we should take away from that I believe is that they aren't really interested I mean
Because he's got to sell his product
Same way that Steve
Russia
Well yeah
Yeah they're there a.m. and there is much as anybody else they only use public
Opinion as opposed to
The target of their their propaganda is Trump
To a greater
So f***** up
I don't even know why there's nothing else to say
Aborting a filled with bigot realized is the direct line to the president
Screaming in a video
When we went on the same show
Mike cernovich
Literally said I don't care if it's real or not we win either way about a
Propaganda photos
Stunt that got done at one of his events
That's not okay to me
Would be okay with me
Now that's f***** up
The dishes
The destruction
Of the the
Separation of Journalism
Manpower
This is the destruction of public discourses
Destruction of everything
It's coming from both sides and I don't mean
Right and left
I mean topping
Like these for rich people in Minnesota
Destroying it in their way which is to
Mckfacts obsolete
I'm in the top is destroying it in there
Making only the facts that they want known
Only the way they want those facts
Do in all of this
Everybody else gets f*****
They're the ones
Both sides make a s*** ton of money
Yep that's good game
Yep good
Yep that's what it is
If you look at the group
As
Which being represented by a person
It's f***** up
We're done man
I do remember the ad that Hillary Clinton
Who do you want
Answering the phone at 4 in the morning
I imagine
That is very different.
Do you want the president to get his news from Fox and Friends
Do you want him to still be up at 4 in the morning
The present
Skip this news
From Fox and Friends
The president
Is scared of what Alex Jones thinks of him
Is shook
By Mike cernovich
I'm not nowhere else
Nothing
More scary
Make me quiver in my boots
Influence
Poop
Goddamn and it's dark
You look good you look a little dream
Yeah I'm running around today and that right before the show I was real stressed out
Going to get all the clips
I feel like I didn't do a good
Enough job of research
A lot of stuff
I don't know
Uno
I just there's Bears elements of Alex that are fun and there's a limit
The rampant islamophobia isn't
Fun and especially when we have an instant
Of like
Alyssa
Listen to his show
I know what
He said
IC Media Matters
Who should be the one
Helping with
Us with this
I'm in the world
Right it is their charge
Hey rightwingwatch
Is there a charge
Watch the
These people
And be like hey this is what they're saying
And haven't watched it I know that they didn't
Yeah
Burlington more thorough job
What about like
Here's why this is right
It's just a transcript of the clip and the clip anger people you cannot reach people
But you can't help
And it's never going
Pierce the people who do believe
The propaganda
If all you're doing is like
Hey look at this isn't this f***** up
That is a good
But then again
It's complicated
Was that pronunciation name
You're not talking about Avril Lavigne on my list
Complicated
I also
I was like a blister on the back of my foot
Your to your
You're too happy
No I
And since then I've had a blister on the back of my
My foot and because it's on the back of the foot
F****** get rid of
You got to go to bed
I've been using a Band-Aid liquid bandage
Destroying
Great radio
Longest Ride
I'm stopping it up
Anyway I don't
I don't disagree with you
In that
They are they are part of the outrage machine in there propagating that and
In some ways
They're utilizing
The same tools that alley
In the way of
What's the best way to get people to engage
It's not make me feel better
It's not educate
It's not his country.
Absolute
Space Mo
Yeah so if you are still a business
If you're not a non-profit
And so I get it which
Is part of the problem
Repeat if you want to make
People outraged
About
What happened on Alex Jones Show
I don't think the way to do it now
Necessarily
Play
Linda sarsour looks like
This terrorist
Thrust of your article
I think it is much
More infuriating
Two people and much easier
Intro into
To like
Well this is very easily disprovable
Is the stuff with Matt Bracken
Especially
The clip where he's saying that all the tenants of Islam in the Quran or kill kill kill kill kill
Write that sort of stuff is much easier
And would make people much angrier I think you get more clips
But
What are every every
Every editor app
Every continent is going to be like
Celebrity gossip boom
Toss it up there as a celebrity
Maybe
World what else what else do you got
Are you have a random
Unabomber style author
Who is
Send Unabomber style authorship
So what are you doing
She probably was
Temperature in Celsius
No and even then I think we can move past
Islamophobia
Like that
That is too much of a subset
Now for Alex Jones wear
It has to be
White males who
He is not an islamophobe
Pictures not the program
Christian
Straight male to
It's wasping
As gospel
Easier attack
At 4
You know Media Matters to make it might not outrage
Many people but
Posting something about Mike cernovich
Days after the entire pedo sign is
Been debunked help itching it
Those admissions
Ardmore damning to them
I think
Because
Look what is those types of admissions they got rid of
Dish it up just like that's
The different era
No longer exists you can just make it all out there I would argue that there's probably a good
2%
These ding-dongs base
But isn't going to leave
20%
That you could get rid of
From supporting them
If you
Do you understand they are explaining on-air that they're calling you
Do you understand that that is what's going on
Or if
You played some of his ridiculous throws to
Explain this is a technique this is a rhetorical technique
It is what
It's how they train people at QVC
That's how you sell things
Yeah you try and create an emotional response
10 people and then lay the sales pitch
It's classic salesmanship
So if you did something like that you could I
I think makes
Some dent
In their their population nor their their fan bases
Never going anywhere
Yeah I would say that you can get
The other third
Split pretty well but
Between
Either not being
Actively engaged
Becoming
Pure ladylike
I don't believe them anymore and they're not going to come over to the
Don't think you are I'm just expressing that I don't care I'm not
Of the libs
This is so fun this is such a this is such a weird reversal here
Palisade wine
Why is it that I'm the one
BMX
Hey Dan your anger is out of
Arrow
Therapy starting to work
Finger touch with this goddamn
Map
The nail on the head there that's exactly
No but like
Look who came to the lot about
I don't give a s***
And you know that's what I'm saying
About
Swelling the ranks of antifa
The ranks of the Democrats or the last diva
I care about people not falling
If you don't believe Alex Jones
And know that he's a liar and recognize what he's doing
And you still
Believe in trickle-down economics
If you still believe in states rights
Cool
We can have a conversation about that
Right
I just agreed but that's fine
I don't think you can do that
I don't think it was
Alex
Alex's tricks are just a more obvious version of everybody
You said it right there
They're more obvious
Your teeth like he's a he's a practice level
You know like you're cutting
Teeth on this is a very obvious form of bigotry
Andkon
You know
And then you
Graduates of Fox News in your life
Oh they're doing the same thing
Flickr app
About it but I still think you can graduate through a bunch
Two levels and still have
Conservative ID
I don't think so
Whatever
Entirely
I think it is Isaac supplied
Most of my life the people who have been
Conservative politicians
Seem to be
But I am not
I look I don't know I don't
You're the f****** call me a Centrist no give a s***
Not
Bothell
I just don't care I don't I don't care about the the game but
Between parties
I don't care about the idea that like
Hey I believe that the world works better in xy&z way and I believe it works better in a b and c way
As long as you ditch the racist propaganda you aren't beholden to
These ideas right and function
Because we can have a polite disagreement about stuff and some places can Implement some plan some places
And we can see what work
That's the idea of
Forget the government
And stuff like that there is something to that
Now if you want to dismantle the entire federal government in the name of states right
You're stupid we can't do
But the idea of
Like the idea that people pitch in terms of states rights
About like
Let's see how things work
In Colorado and then baby if it works there
If we can expand it
That is kind of what happened with
Marijuana legalization
They had her right
To do that and we learned a f****** work
Super well
And two other states adopted
Yeah the kind of thing that I understand
Where that
Philosophy comes from
And I don't hate it
Now if you want to stay that all can
Conservative
Ideology is stupid and it's a con
I disagree with you cuz I think that's as bad as Alex
Calling all liberal stupid
But I don't
I don't
I don't think that you're dumb and I don't think that like
I don't think you have haven't thought out your opinion and I certainly think that most of the people we recognize as
Conservative politicians
Aren't necessarily
Just that
Right
B
This point I want to get you is
This is
There are instances of political disagreements that are acceptable
Fast forward that's more likely
And because we only have
Conservative and liberal as our sort of two Polar Opposites
Yeah we get to talk about that's the reason I use that as the
I I think that was just a misunderstanding
Modern conservatism
Is inference
Physically tied up with
Because that's the only way that you can
Kansel
F****** yourself over
Right like that's like if you look at what Kansas what happened in
The way that Sam Brownback
Implemented all of the
Conservative tenets
Destroy Kansas's in entire
Economy and infrastructure
And if we don't have all the other stuff
Piggybacking in the end
The Nan a giant backpack around it right and we would have seen
That stuff didn't work
And we would have been able to Discount those sorry already know that
Because it's been applied
So many
Times in American
History in the past
And it never will
Spray ever
Look I I I respect your
Like I totally get what you're saying
Coming
From the idea of
Polite disagreement is a valuable thing
I think the problem that we are having or at least in this
Discussion
Is a lot of
The polite disc
Disagreements that were talk
Talking about
Happened
Hundreds of years ago and
We're just still having those
Disagree
Cuz I don't agree with
A lot of
Different ways
I absolutely think that
That can go
We're not polygon
There is a rational approach to
But at the same time
Trickle down economics
Is Magic
It doesn't exist
Conservative
Disagreement
Is gone there is no further discussion
Up tax breaks for the rich
Leading to economic
We're done there
So that's not a
Disagreement
Well for you because you're making it rude
You're making it a little rude
Okay in this hypothetical conversation that you're having with a conservator
Pathetical conversation
You're not conversation
What that's like that's like arguing about whether or not climate change is real
Well that would be on my love
Jill Brightwell
That's not a polite disagreement
Disagreement in the same way
If there's an established
Fact
Dude
What you're not
I believe that what you're not taking into account
Okay is that let's take the
The climate change
As an example of what you're talk
If you take away
A lot of the
Conspiracy propaganda beliefs about climate
Change
There would be much less disagreement about
If people were relying on science
About it
They were relying on empirical evidence
There wouldn't be nearly as many people who were saying there are two
Two sides
Cuz a lot of people who
Whether they
Really
Consciously understand it or not
A lot of people who are against
Believe
Letter r did they
The UN is
Inspire and they're faking all this the one that I get for my phone
Family all the time
At the scientist
It look the scientist
How to say this
This in order to get Grandma
Brave
Disregarding the fact that they
Maybe get hundreds of
Listen to the dollars while the people who are causing climate
Get billions
But
If you take away all of those right
A lot of conversations that you're bringing up and I imagine
Trickle-down economics might be one of them that also goes away
Maybe was a bad thing for me to use it as an example
I respect that
I don't know where this
Started
I'm looking at the chat room
I think we lost a lot of
Garbage dick brought up a Libertarian philosophy
Puppies that are burgeoning right now and I love you totally clear I got no time for Libertarians
No matter how much I want to be inclusive of 0 time for Libertarians
Nope
I don't want him to have any more conversation
Curling up in a ball over here
Absolutely well
To donate
We really appreciate it already new block every Thursday
Want to be up tomorrow or today when you're listening
Twitter that's correct
Also pay
And then you can go to iTunes
Can you go to Stitcher
Stitcher the Libertarians of podcast distribution services
Is now
YouTube channel
You matter
Media Matters this podcast
From now on
Buena Park
Has been fun
I know it's been
Stressful and exciting
Attacked my therapist and then
Anyway
Alright
Does a good man he's anything like
This one dude
Guy
Doesn't
Billy beer
Does he hang up all his pictures
Alex Jones talking about cross eyes being a sign of nobility
And I am going to this guy they were talking about you'll be Noble
And I
England
The guy has a cross eye
Just like me
Anything Goes
Now you're the part where I would say May the wolf joke on its last but Jordan
Pointed out to me
And another that that's kind of a compliment
And no longer say it
That's why you
Alexandra Thurston color