Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work
We are back
For another episode here on the podcast
Episode
Which is basically against our entire eighth of
That as long as possible is the way to describe me like my job
So today we're going to do is
Maybe this will be a new thing
Infowars roulette
Who is selected
10 minute video
From infowars.com
One of us will.
Play Russian Roulette video
Straight up
Real talk
Root beer talk
Makes me
Scared
Is I don't know if this is an Alex
XVideos disa might be one of his subordinates
M32r this is great
We're going to get into this
No matter what
Jordan let me ask you this
Would you like me to
Play it straight through
Or would you like it
Pause in the middle
If I say play it straight through
I'm going to yell at you halfway through to pause in the middle
Fair enough
So let's
Let's play it by ear I'm going to turn it off and immediately
Alright let's fight this fight
Knowledge fight
This video is called tough talk leaked
Attack Trump
Love it already
That's the logo are
Now they cut off
What the heck
They drown
Town people in steel cages
Haven't seen this
I've been saying this
Nobody say
A many many years
All Nations have a moral
That sounds like the opening crawl
When I was in college there was that Daniel Pearl video
Don't like my friends
Watched
Already already going to be six and a half hours long
Please say no
Oh thank God
I did not either but I I listen to
To my friends watching it
Another room
Beheading video
Sleepyhead
Tacos
Yeah they have those videos now with Isis where they behead people but I'm saying
So when Trump is
Be up on stage
We haven't seen bad in
Since the Middle Ages
Have you seen
Like those old Faces of Death
Why would you why would you but I'm aware of
Just the existence of them I shouldn't watch
Grotesque
Unless I accidentally
That is
The eleventh commandment right eye
So Trump might have some more V
Geisha disp
Speak out against such vile
Call Neisha
Heavy duty to work
Work together to confront it and
Viciously
If we have to
Express clearly
Today
To the American people
I want Express clearly that he breathes like Alex
He breathes weird
Why isn't the two of them breathing weird I don't know I think it's cuz bulshit only goes one way
Alright
It only comes out
Administration
Sinful to everything
Power to defendant
Protect religious liberty
Villages
I must forever remain a
Tolerant Society where all
Call Cesar respect
And we're all
Everett Chevy
Can feel safe
And secure
Say fancy
I just want to let you know that I want to kill myself after
Listening to that and then
Being where we are in the world
Can we all just murder ourselves right now
All the lies that Trump has said
I'm the leader of that coloring
I want
I'm Traders like
I get it I get it you're not wrong you're not wrong bro
I'm not jumping on
Time in my life
I still might get there at some point but I have a holy war against Alex Jones When I got to carry out
I got a larger I got a larger
In recent days
We have begun
To take necessary
To achieve that goal
God I hate him so much I haven't right
That went well
I hate him so much I went well you touch a garbage piece of it how do you
Jamming
Was
Boss do you remember do you remember those pictures of whenever Osama was killed this episode 3 hours long
33 hours live
We're not even two-and-a-half seconds into the eclipse
Do you remember the the pictures of the of summary
Where they have
Obama they have Hillary they have at everybody
Staring intently at that video what's going to happen
All of the reports of the Yemen raid
Trump going
Big fan of intelligence briefings and then everything going to ship
What could he have done
That room really
At least pretended to be a
F****** know
Who's very convinced of his incompetence
He probably would have only screwed it up more
What what we put in
Into a
Tiny little bubble wrap room
Okay just
Perfectly like you know how happy you
You feel when you cry
Bubble wrap
Sure sure
Just full of bubble wrap
Whenever he comes out of it 6 years from now whatever
Bubble wrap
What corner or laptop
What corners
Salisbury someone
A laptop that has only pointing
Clicker games on it
Just
If somebody
Explain to him that we don't know where Carmen Sandiego is
His entire presidency would be about 5:30 sitio
Acapella
Rockapella
Where is, all right we're at we're on our
Not even gotten into Banda
It's going to be
Okay and he also
God dammit it's David night
I want to hear some David Knight
Let's finally get it
Before we go any further Uno David night so boring
David Knight is non-existent I've never heard David nights week before here's what it looks like I'm looking at David
And I hope
Yeah let's ride this out
Listeners if there was a guy quintessentially look like a guy you wanted to get hit by a
You all have phones just Google David
Your wife phone
Alright
Here-we-go David Knight David Knight
Tell you he said
Tough phone call
It's time
We got caught
And we're going to take care of this talks about that
He talks about
What you just heard in terms of the
Persecution
That we see the violence that we see that we have to confront he understands that isn't duty to protect us as Citizens
You're being really unfair with your friend I'm sorry I understand
Boring boring human being I've ever heard my life
How is it that Alex is on the same network as this the most boring human being has ever been
How many episodes will just be like a little
Glimpses into these other people
Wasn't he
Came up with dirty dossier
Give him a little bit
That is the duty of the American government and then he
Talks about shutting down
The suppression of
Free speech
Call speech and yet
What does the media Focus
The media folks
Chris is on his opening
Joke to the audience
Headlines Trump opens National Prayer Breakfast
We'll talk about TV ratings
Noted in this is the hell
Noted his tremendous success
Sistar reality shows Apprentice
How many views does a
Particular instance
This video has 4,000
2 views at press time
34,000 right now his
About when Alex Jones pulls his
Cult leader nonsense
Millions of videos
Well that Maybe not maybe hundreds of thousands
Is amazingly boring
But this is unconscionable
Wondering
Exist
At all and now this goes this is
How long
On the past episodes when I was so mad how long is he been talking for
It seems like a year this is the most boring human being ever
He is at his job
Merit
So he's boring
Alright
His drool
Is in stark contrast
To Alex's
Frenetic
Insane pace
Yeah but it's sort of Elders
We've all fallen in love with Alex Jones
Glacier David Knight
Is be like
Are you sure he's trying to I'm trying to find a corollary like the only thing I can think of is
Hey Alexa
Okay
Not a Jane Austen
Novel
I'm listening
But the reviewer of a Jane Austen novel
Who works at a like
Really low-level College
I really feel like at like
At like Eastern Illinois University who's like
I got a grinder pic with Jane Austen
Is Alex Davis metaphor
This is what I'm saying is boring as
Dave
David Knight
Not worth knowing is named it's not worth
Let's see how it looks
Willie say anything interesting
If he doesn't say dirty.com
Pissed off
Celebrity Apprentice as well
This is just
This this is now like these episodes
Are now our attic are excuse to just
Be filled with bile and raised
He's not random to me though he's my friend my friend
He's a member of your well I understand
Well
Isn't a****** though let's see
This is what he had to say said we know how that turned out
And I want
You just pray for Arnold
We can pray for those rate
Prayer breakfast
Big at Arnold Schwarzenegger because Arnold Schwarzenegger
He just throws us out there as a joke.
But that's the only thing
Out of this
Significant speech that he gave the only thing that the media
Want to talk about
Of course when he talked about
Choptalk don't worry about
Had a couple of
With all my God
This whole time to he is not made icon
Contact with camera is just looking down at papers of course not
If you looked into his eyes you would see the empty otamatone that exist
The in-between
You just need dirty.
If you'd like do you remember Men In Black do you remember watching that movie
I was sorry but then there was like this
Bright flashing
Play Robin Thicke
Remember how they were those aliens that like
Like they they cut the head open and then there's that little alien driving vedvik
Human person
That's what David Knight teams like to me
There's a tiny little alien inside of his head
Driving a David Knight
I don't think you're totally wrong
Search Don Twitter for like
Responses to
The
Trump prayer breakfast
Also I wish I had was Arnold
Schwarzenegger doing a video reply
Nope
Don't don't care what he thinks about his ratings also
It's not do we wake up every morning going like wait
Talktalk is
Kohl's with
Boren Leach
Like Australia's leader
Would be hung up
Alright
First off
We have a National Prayer Breakfast
Prestwich
I'm not cool
It's also not what it is
Breakfast and you just assumed
Reading Eggs
And baby
Behold
Yeah
Right
Yeah yeah all of our president
Like a member of Russia's
Like Putin
Party was there
No so we got this we got this precedents all of the presidents
Go to this dump breakfast have to
Where they pretend to give a s***
Do I
Do I think that Obama believes in religion the way that
Christians believe in
Is the weather conservative Christians believe in it
Now of course
Cuz
If you did
Your f****** elude
But you also believe that he is
George George W
No same thing he doesn't give a s*** about you
Keep on going back
However have still gone to that dumb
Yes all of them
Tended
At the very least
To give a s*** about.
Trump
I made fun
Schwarzenegger's ratings ratings are great
Those are bad
That is
Hilarious
I want a black was I one hundred percent support a president
If it weren't for the score for the rest of all the ship
What are the things that I'm having to wrestle with
More and more like
Bailey is
How
It might suck
Wenxuecity
Is petty
In the real world
How funny it is in constant diarrhea
Has other things
To it
So scary if we lived in the real world Obama is doing all of the other
Normal stuff that he does
And then just one day he just shows up that at the National Prayer Breakfast
That is just a
Dick
That's so f****** funny
But still funny
Trump like no regrets can be all lit on fire but also
In order for this
Analogy to make
Accent like let's say Obama put out a single
Before word for he was president
The junior high with put out a single
The-Dream
Right if so
Migos the prayer breakfast is like
Look
Wasn't I know the dreams got a great great song
It's better
Hilarious hilarious
But ya never exist in real world
This is the world we live in
Anyway here's more boring ass Days of Night
The bigger story
More so
Ban what came out of these quotes with a not there true now course the Mexican Government
Has denied
What was
Leaked to the
Associated Press
Mexican government
Slammed the claim as a downright
Troops to Max
The co if they don't take care of them
It's an affectation
Donald Trump might
Send troops to
Like who the f*** talks like that
That I'm not picking up
Mug
It sounds smart it's very small it sounds like such a it sounds like
It sounds like Madonna coming back from
Britain
What being married to Guy Ritchie whenever Alex
It's kind of weird attacks on his ear
Yeah there's that towel
Yeah that were David Knight
Lies
Is this
Speaks his smugness picks up a little bit money
He's one of these like
Brownie playlist bad video games
Like like Megaman
The early Mega Man games
Are you there
Mega Man 2
The pattern is super
Liquid-filled Bubble Man
The Robot Masters in into like
Dr. Wiley
Piece of s***
Super easy
But like
You see the pattern
Pretty quickly with the first man to probably not
No it was the hardest game. But once you got to make a man
And then you went back to Mega Man 2 you like
I get it
MB truck listening to David Knight
Or is
That David Knight is
First boss
In Megaman
He doesn't have the 11 Alex Alex keeps you on your toes
Zane keeps you entertained wacky bulshit listen to
Maybe
One minute 45 seconds
3 minutes including that
Developed a respect for Alex
I could ever have imagined David tonight
Are the world go
Dirty dossier
Is reported to have said what the AP reported that he said was you have a bunch of bad Hombres down there
You're doing a cobra
So I just might send them down to take care of it
Here
Kind of
MPR of Infowars
Your right is the crazy Wing bat
MPR
Yeah
He's there to Loop Inn
V like really old people who think Alex Yelp
I don't like it when Alex
But Davidson tonight I like I liked it when I hear the same insane
Very comforting tone that really makes me feel good
Dirty dossier
That was the allegation of the Madeleine
My wife had no comment on that
Australian prime minister
Malcolm Turnbull
Those
He received no what if your address
If you're if you're going on air
You really should know what the title of the person you're talk
This has become my favorite thing for us to do now because we have no
Like we've just been set free from the
Boring like we can do whatever the f*** we want now and then
What does Comics Unleashed yeah yeah just
Justice f****** The Lion the Witch and the Wardrobe
Kind of situation
Wasn't David Knight is the Turkish
Crystal Light Of Hope
Going to go.
Yeah there's so much more left
How
What is happening with
Dirty.
Make it sound very impressive
Political Pulp Fiction
How to try to
Also just a little note on the dirty dossier one of the guys who is suspected to be one
One of the leaks from Russia was found dead
In his car
Yep couple other people who respect
I've been arrested by Russia for treason
So
Maybe it's not bulshit perhaps
Shortly following the election
Population of Davao
Call
With the
The prime minister
Let's not be remiss in saying
How to call with Putin
Mysteriously wasn't recorded
You know what's crazy about that
That Cole wasn't recorded and then immediately following that
There were a lot of bombs dropped on Ukraine almost immediately immediately
To the point of
Noticeability
The day before
We're close.
Close enough to zero within the margin of error
But there was still conflict
We're not we're not
We're not embellishing anything
When we say the number is 911 was way less than
Yeah and then the next day the number was way more
N1000
I don't know if that has anything to do with each other
Themes
Unrelated
If I if I
Just put on my
I wonder if
I want David
Weather
I would actually buy that
Anyway
Tell us the truth David
Of course that's what they're trying to do
It's about
What was supposedly said
I'm between Trump and the Australian prime minister between Trump and the Mexican
Is not a fool
Show called Dirty.
Sissy
He was doing this leak
And he knew that was coming
Who's coming from
Intelligent
Community leaders that are they
Through the narrative
Infowars
Spinning really hard
Trump
He likes
Selective leafedout
Information books
Call Central
Who would lie
That's really good like a classic is like
You give
Each you give each agency some
False information in DC which comes back in your life
I know which one's leaking at
Smart move
They have that story
Not real
Trump is not smart enough to do that but that's the really smart move
Engine have
Stop is coming from
The fruit Folk
But we've been so concerned about
Withdraw
Surveillance of the American people
This is something that people have been
Rightfully concerned about
What's the Frank Church
And the congressman Pike
Hearing
Back in the 1970s where they realized
The CIA in the NSA
Doing
Unconstitutional
Illegal surveillance
Of American citizen
Here in America without search warrant
I got to stop that
They need to stop
Is the breathing in on Mike
I have
35 North I don't know what your
Talking about
It just seems like
It's time for us to
These Mikes cost about $100
So I have breath guards on them
And I like
I wasn't back to the
Before I post them I don't
Think there's any
But what
It's so I think I think it's just that there's no old
Your breath there just a little going on
In his brain
So
So this Desiree like you nailed it when you made the MPR
Like I I remember listening to
Napa
Of your
You're This American Life
Where is American Life
I did that
What
David Knight was on it
Now that does sound like that sounds right
For 45 minutes to remember that one
I really was
In-depth investigation about
People who can
By the way sponsors
We be a big ass
Real talk
George Soros
If you're out there
Give me some goddamn money no s*** right if you're the architect of what you purport to be
Or at least other people for
Us more than I think putting up
This amount of work for
For free
What I have a nine-to-five goddamn job
Stressed out
We get we get 25
$0.25 /
And $50,000 year retainer
Was bulshit
$50,000 a year
Work
More than
I work yet
I don't make
You and me both
Iran protests
No I wouldn't
I wouldn't do that if I didn't believe in what it was
Cuz I wouldn't even
Navigate work.
Hypothetical b*******
Responding hypothetically to hypothetical situation is never a good
How is it the David Knight has not made it through 10 words before I was falling asleep
Who f****** bored
Intelligence surveillance
Back to say
We don't want
What was searches
The Pfizer
Powers
The fisa court which is a single judge
And the government bureaucrat goes to that single judge in size I want a search warrant for mr. mrs. Verizon or whatever they want
And there is no publicity of that
That's one hundred percent right
I agree with him
100%
Okay
Fisa is a f******
Absolute rubber stamp
Court
That allows them to surveil all of us
All the time with no real surveillance
Sure with no real like
Check
It is
It is absolutely unconscionable
I agree with him
David Knight has nailed it
And I am about to fall asleep he is the most boring man in history of the world
I don't think surveillance is great
Google
Bay
Claim that with that fisa Court they are amending the Constitution
Real quick just to make
The the way we're going to make this interesting as one of us dies at the end of this, right
BET our lives on the end
Okay
Over-under on how many
More times is dirty.
Five you take over or under
5 / Runner
Okay
So that you're going to say one more time
We're not even allowed to know about that
How to close all the way back to the 1970s
You saw them talking about the assassination gun
People didn't talk about
What's the fact that
Congressman
Everybody try to exist
They all said
If I said I want to see
Your
Reorganization that's what was created we were created by an executive order by president
No we're not going to show that to you
I swear to God I feel like
I feel like
We're just going to fall asleep and this clip is going to end and that's going to be the end of the
This is the most boring thing I've ever heard in my entire life
Supposed to be about phone calls how is this possible
Don't know this man is so boring
This is what I'm worried I'm worried that
Going to keep saying I'm worried that we're going to become boring by pointing at like
Sent to this boring man
It's going to rub off
God
What what is it feel like
Okay
Imagine you're married to this
He's married actually I have no idea about it
Doesn't matter your hypothetical
Improv yellow
Alright I'm David Knight's wife
Alright I tried to turn my chair around it will not go out
Alright hey
Do you want to go out
For dinner later on this evening
Trick food into my mouth
All right what
What type of food do you like to take
I love you in Spanish
Alright sessoms Bates
Is nice how do you feel about
Food from
Asia
All right how do you spell medieval
Food from Australia
Well I don't like
Alex Jones I know I was married to you though
Galaxy Drive
No
Alright alright
You can't know what we're about
We don't report to you
What we see here
After Decades of this after every attempt has
Then turned around and used against us
People are coming after
A president
Who doesn't
Support
They're dark
Globalist
Agenda
And they're doing everything they can try to destroy him to try to embarrass him
That came out
It just made him look better
With the people who voted for him
Because what he's telling
Australian prime minister
Is a Goldman Sachs Banker
It just came out in the last week contributed I think it's like one and a half a million dollars maybe that's Australian money
The most money on the Phillies
Electrician as ever
Country has no idea what Australian
No idea what I was really
Australian kangaroo
Translate Australian kangaroo pouch for a 1.1 dollars today
No idea what
This also goes to the idea
Just a little bit earlier in this clip even like
The idea that he has no idea of Conte
He gets
On camera
And tell this story without any idea of what he's at
Actually saying
Like
Yep in their head about like
Do not use until
Proctor's right here we're just telling
Maybe you should
Maybe you should have some idea of what you're saying
This clip is the
Post to be about
Top talk
Like
Talon
World leaders what's up
So far
We don't know what Australia skirt
We don't know what the name of the leader is
We don't
When we know it's truly know it's
We don't know his title
We don't know exactly really what happened
We're pretending a call to Putin didn't happen
All the stuff
You're not
Gamer
He
Was a literate man
He would act
Actually believe that Turnbull was the villain of the
Iodine
Kind of get that
Let's get back.
You hiccup the a******
Otpp he still wants to keep the TPP going even though
Trump has shut that down with America
Climate change agenda
So he's there on all three of those issues this is a hardcore
Goldman Sachs
Text guy who is on with all three legs
Of the globalist agenda
What were they
Talking about what do they have the contentious conversation about what
They were talking about whether not refugees which Australia would not allow into their country but instead
For housing and Papa New Guinea
Dave said well we want you to take them off of our hands
I 1000% don't believe
I'm struggling
To follow along
Every every word he says makes me less interested in the word he said before it
He's insanely boring like the fight that they had was
Was about like
The Australian prime minister Turnbull being like
Dude
You got to take some of these refugees off our hands makes more sense to me than
Demi-leigh
Act like if the conversation that
What address
You should take
Some of these refugees
No do you ever mixed up
I'm supposed to be doing that to you
No but I mean
Take some refugees
I do be tremendous
I might I don't even know
David Knight has got both of us
So bored I that's what I'm trying to do I don't know we're losing
This is what happens when you listen to David Knight login us
Like their fight came up because
Really would like to take some over refugees and long enough without
Alex Jones anoculus unbelievable
Iris
2 believable is just a
Parcel of boring
The but yeah that's what I'm saying
It's not that it's believable
It's so unfair andalus
Yeah because he's not yelling at you eating the morning traffic report
You would believe any like
Eating like on 90/94 we have
A block there
I'm not block is called by
Caused by Muslim refugees who are
Dancing around
They are burning an effigy of
Trump right now
That is a block on a
Before you be like
Oh yeah that makes sense
But he's saying that
Australia in a spot because
Australia wanted us
If Alex was saying
Re-reading that news he would be screaming
About the history
Of Australia being a penal colony
And how they're a bunch of dicks
Right right
England tip walk
Player
Panache
Some f****** panache
Yeah
David nights just boring the f*** I swear to God every moment
Murder David Knight
There's only like another minute left of his self in a minute left open listening to David
Flight 46 years hopefully
The seconds of it is
The envelope when I when I was a young man David Knight started talking in this club
Why are you going to die while you're still talking
PJ's but they want us
To take them all
He's wearing Dental right
Lodi
That's a dangerous man
Prime minister was doing a Donald Trump says a disagreement with Obama
I'm not interested in doing that
About 25 minutes
Panda. 22 Donald Trump
Hung up on him
Rightfully so
With ease
Leeks
That
Kind of making him look better
But the key thing here that is really dangerous
It's a fact that we have
Surveillance
Open late
Attacking
Elected president
Unprecedented way
National real estate is a problem that was the end of the clip I totally agree
I f****** god boo into the the envelope
Nationals
But it has nothing to do with what he was talking about
Let's be clear let's be clear
Never
My president
Hang up on a 4in lift never want that
Lakeland Weekend at Bernie's
Like a dead person
Cuz otherwise have gone forever
So Trump
Heroic president
Fake Hitler in another country
They start talking
Yeah
I still don't want
Fake Trump
Hanging up on fake Hitler
I still don't want that to happen
I still would rather him
Trying to make negotiation
In the same wave it like
At my job
I got to deal with some assholes
Sometimes the phone
Yeah I never hang up on them
I'm always
Crying
Excuse me mr. Trump
Ending z life's of JuJu's
Play some not I'm not into it
I'm not a fan
How are you doing
You're not interested in
My day is well
I have ended the life of
20 Jews today
How many how many Jews
Do you know but I'm I'm coming back I'm coming back
Smoking is a terrible addiction
I apologize
My point
Stan's I don't
Birds
I don't
Think that it's good
For us too
Shutdown
Communication
I do think that that
It is it is the most damage
If I heard that Obama hung up on some
Foreign leader
I would think that was f***** up is because all
All the time that we're listen to this
We find ourselves constantly
Not concert
I would say occasionally
Or frequently enough
Agreeing with their endgame
Write their final Point like
Yes
The national security system
Is out of
Comes to observing
American citizens
And we're against that because they can be used against citizens
Because imaginal beings are following us you know like
Like that
That's the area where we disconnected it happens when you don't have a team like
Is you and I don't have a
Team
Like when you come to the Democrat vs Republican thing
Like
Thank God we need one building
Right now at least at least women are doing a way better job than
We are
Spider-Man
F*** yeah because I'm a giant pile of garbage
So so but that's that's what happened
Is if you don't have it
Team to constantly defend
Like when Obama was President
S*** tons of
Extradition
Killings that he had withdrawn bombings and all that
Where you like
No
Know you murdered
An innocent
Family
I just an innocent guy
Anderson
Family
You killed it
That's on you
Obama yeah we're mad at
But if you have a team you're like oh well
It's Obama doing it so he believes it's right
Murder that f******
Can kid you with a shity thing and you're on that team so you're like
Oh no you just opened up a really interesting thing that I
I think we need to
Address for how many
What hour of this podcast are we on
Jesus Christ
There is a
Perspective
From
The Infowars side that
They keep saying
Felt like when Obama did these things
Yeah
Care
And that's
Illusory that's not yet
Obama
Did drone kill people
People speaking out against
Literally pissed off about it
That's
That's a complete
Absolutely not true
Well it's not a complete Straub no cuz some people work
It's not a complete set because there is there is an element of work hairdos
Right
But if you're playing the game as a
Team sport which it seems to be that
Versus d
And it really does seem to be the overwhelming reality of what we live in now is that
Anyway
Ladies and gentlemen
I believe this has been our first
I think this is our first Short episode regarding David night hopefully
Episode regarding David Knight I Hope
Or it never one this is this should be the end
The other guys
Like unpleasant
Manipulate
The voices
Paul Joseph Watson we could do an episode about him
You would hate him just as much forever.
Like these guys the rest of his cohorts
Are terrible about Alex
We're going to find each of these guys
Still them
To their essence
Switch and David nights case
Is
I f******
From The Lord of the Rings
The Rings
But user-friendly
David Knight
Now he's a bad
Racist ass
Anyway guys
Thanks for joining us you can follow us on Twitter at knowledge
Underscore fight
The podcast you can reach us
For that please
Also review review
If if
I'll say this
I'm going to make a new thing
If you give us a 5-star review
And email me
Acknowledge
Cam
I will tweet something really ugly it out
I will say something
Alex Jones that I wouldn't say to my mother will you reveal our individual like
@jake
I don't want anyone knowing my business
I am at and then cross.
If you feel like isolating the audio from each of us you may find out which one I am
Them to figure out who we are
I don't want just in case someone randomly finds it I have no
Doc the s*** out of me I don't even know who I am and how dare you
Jordans
Vince Vaughn
Goodnight
If we were drama coaches
Let's give him a little bit of outro advice
Pick it up
Right
Be a little more dangerous
Projector
21 the only thing
He's doing fine
Disagree he seems like he's talking into his chest
That's the entire
He is in love
Make it seem like you care
Make it seem like you can
Act
Yeah like
Like
Did no matter what bulshit he says
He might care Alex believes 20% of a of what he says and
Believes that he believes
Hundred percent of everything
Ever said
Believes 100% of what he says
Hebron
That poor bastard
What a butt a dingo
Anyway sounds like
He's only ever had missionary position
They were so mean to you but I don't
And you're a
Part of it really bad system
I hope someday you're bankrupt
You suck
You're terrible at your job and talk to you about this last 15 minutes of the
You and your family anyway guys
Open funnel catch
Goodnight goodnight
Alexandra Thurston color