Alexandra Thurston color
We're here really quick just to drop
Spiritual correction
Episode
About
Campaign
Hillary Clinton
And we were not inaccurate
But I found information later that episode
I feel like I would be remiss if I didn't point out
And call myself out on
One of those things that's most important is
That Renaissance Technologies
Bee Company that is owned by Robert Mercer
Gave 15 million dollars
In the campaign
But he also gave Hillary 40
Million-dollar
So
So he's hedging his bets
Literally every billionaire.
Like everybody at Goldman Sachs
Gave Hillary a s*** ton of money and
Also
Actually
Directions actually that's
Kind of interesting
The other direction that I needed about the Goldman Sachs stuff with Trump
Okay
The reality is the Goldman Sachs band all their partners for making donations
Interested
And Pence interests
Is
That they'd made a policy change
About
Support running for state or local offices
I as well as giving money to people who are sitting state or local officials
Running for federal
Quotes from a memo
It was distributed to Goldman Sachs
Supplies
This policy change is meant to prevent inadvertently violating paid
Two-player rules
Particularly the look-back for
When Partners transition
Trolls covered by these rules
The policy change is also meant to minimize
Potential reputational damage caused by
False perception
Play Ruel
Particular
Partners seniority and visibility
So basically what it comes company with all of it
F****** former members
The goddamn
Right right
Here is the issue it has to do with state and local representative
Right because those make rules that more directly
Stuck with
Yeah
The situation is
The banks
Compliance team pointed to
Did the Trump Pence campaign logo
Because Pam has the governor of Indiana giving him influence over state pension
Right so that was a situation where they couldn't
Give him because he was a state official
Meanwhile the new rules Goldman Sachs
Text don't restrict
Democratic
Candidate Hillary Clinton
Because she currently doesn't hold office
Her vice president
Is u.s. Senator
So would be subject to the rules either
Because he's not a state or local if
The Goldman Sachs employees were
Unallowed
To give money to the
But it wasn't because Trump
It was because of state and local
So this particular thing this particular rule that they implemented
Somehow
Wound up happy
To the Trump campaign
It was
Not
Purposeful it was just
Kind of
Coincidence
The governor
It's fine that they gave
Hillary Clinton money and they would have given Trump money
And the other thing is I just calling myself out
There were people who gave
Tens of millions of dollars to Hillary to
And I feel like when I listened back to what I was misrepresenting thing
Bye
Do you have these million-dollar to million-dollar donation
I meant we said Mercer gave 15 million to Trump
Right. She didn't have
Large-scale donor
It was unintentional
But
But even then the larger point is billionaires
Don't give a fuk
And they're just going to give Millions to
Because if they become president
We already gave you million but also the other
Is that a lot of
Hyatt donations on Hillary's from Union
And stuff like that
No wonder though one of the larger like in the
Pantheon
There's billionaires and then there's Union
Not
Equivalent but
They still give a s***
Please enjoy longer episode today but I just wanted to do this because
Being above board and I felt like
When I listened back to that episode was
Slightly unfair
Alex
Jones has never done
Probably not
I will talk to you real soon but until then
Rapoport
You still live
Holding
Alex