I'm a policy wonk
Welcome back for you
A little bit of a scheduling difficulty I had to go get my stitches taken out
From my minor surgery that I had recently
And so you know what with work schedules whenever you have time to get together
But I wanted to get something out for you here on this Wednesday to enjoy
It seems to me like perhaps a great opportunity to make a little bit of it
About business
Have donated to the show and I really appreciate it all y'all
What's out there
And I want to try and sweeten the pot a little bit in terms of what you get if you donate
Not great at making buttons or
Bumper stickers or as we apparently
Knowledge fight podcast
That which may be in the works
I'm not great at that stuff
But I do like creating content for you and making shows
Answer what are the things that we're going to be doing now is if you are a policy walk if you donate to the show
Over $2 a month
You will be granted access to a password protected
Page
On.com
Contain all sorts of goodies
I invited so I mean it will be the exclusive
Place where you can find
New episodes of me and Marty DeRosa show
That's what they want
Hey conspiracy theory exploration show
I guess would be the best way to put that I don't know it's kind of dumb
A lot of fun people seem to enjoy that
Also I will be doing a paranormal investigation
I'm sure that I
Start it up and then abandoned about a year-and-a-half ago or so I put out one episode about it
I'm just stop cuz it was too much work
But I'm going to pick that up and it will be behind a wall
So if you guys would like
Dude
Be at granted access to that stuff
Actual page on the website
Right now
And will give everyone an update when there will actually be new episodes
I am new contents up on there a lot of people who work
Coming around around back when that's what they want
You to think existed
So I felt
Maybe
We should take this opportunity for you to get a little taste of what the heck show is
Because
It's a little different than just listening to Alex Bunch certainly different than that
Also here I would like to present to you
I do enjoy a little teaser a little while
This is an episode of that's what they want you to think that me and Marty DeRosa recorded
Perhaps
Maybe two years ago year-and-a-half ago
This is an episode that we did about
The Salem witch trials
I don't remember anything about it but I
But I guess we got to the bottom of it I I predict that we didn't get
Sidetracked talking about sucking at all anyway I hope you all enjoyed
And like I said if you'd like to donate please do so go to knowledge fight.com
Click D support the show button
And like I said I will send out password
For the
Page on knowledge vype.com in the near future
Thank you all and regular knowledge fight episode
Very shortly
I'm a policy wonk
Hey everybody hello I'd like a reason but I've been freezing alongside me
My man my man man
My conspiracy theory bro
My
Minister of Truth
IMDb man with the
Faricy Theory plan
I am
WhatsApp
Yeah probably Professor Griff Professor Griff
Sister Souljah
If if I was going to have our truth
Pro wrestler archers officiate my wedding minister.
That would be great
In Ring of Honor
Wish Copacabana famous
One of the
He'll facts
Martini
Who is the
You got to get him on the show
Done
Bugatti
Jim
Anyway
Really hot out my bus driver
This guy that I've known for
Yelling at black bus driver door issues not a race issue
Truth martini
Is his faction is called the house of
Truth and he has a book called The Book of
Anytime you use
Truth becomes like
You're lying
Do you know any it automatically
Dokdo
I'm still getting Facebook messages
And tweets
About what
Photo of a text message
Well because of you and f****** damn
You made me feel normal thing we did RJ
And a park you guys
For all of the you like podcast
320 izzar so episode
Nothing is really wrong
People's Bell
You and me talking about weird ship
It's like I always say with you
If your
You're sitting behind the desk at work right now or something like that maybe this isn't another
The wrestling pop over to Marty and Sarah love wrestling
Picture picture
Maybe like music
Cannot make yourself a ham sandwich
Sure all these are options
For your day
With this one
This is when that sun needs
To be down
You're maybe a little high
You're in bed maybe
I don't recommend
Here's what I what I say
Had a long day at work
Doing as a job
Okay
She's at a long day but dealing with the issues
She works 3 on 4 off she just had her third day
She is exhausted
Oh my God
She is home but she has four days off for days off
That's a long haul
She's with the candle in the bathroom
Call Jay
Burnet herb
Backpacks
Chicago
I'm just asking
Yeah salt
Amor bubble
Scenario
She's got
Bath bomb
Choice
She got
Suction cups
What a dildo
Vets in her drawer
But
She's got all the accoutrement
That makes me drink
Kimkaps
Master
So she turns off the lights candles going
Cheap
He's get past the same thing to stop sticking around
They don't want you to use
I know what the truth is if you don't know what we're talking about this week
Maybe Dan put it in the description
But it's something that's always been on my mind thinking how the f*** did that happened was Isis
You ready to come bolt at such an early age in this country's life five women are afraid
Where man can't handle York
I got to say we met
I had a hole about
Periods and I just can't imagine
Speaking of the producer I had to cut you off there
Some of the things I've wondered about sure
These questions we talked about it in the elevator laptop
Why specifically a
Pet
Your multiple
This is what I hope everybody listen to all
Call sandwich
Where is famously posed nude
Eating your Starbucks bathrobe Woodyard
Cooking robot
What do you think
Actually should be out today
And you want to hear Marty on Jam
I might say a few things one of the Bands a microphone
Yes yes we could stop a band
Limp Bizkit came up
I think I might go with
Evanescence
Yeah I like having a
Iraq
Today on Facebook
Yeah yeah yeah
Call Me When You're Sober
Before you
Yoga wake me up the volume
He was very attractive though
I love doing wake me up at karaoke karaoke jams I like also how you
Famously said
Of yours
That you hate when guys do what song is karaoke
I f****** hate post
Snarky things about like
Think the joke is your unattractive like posed
Like Big Pimpin
Gayish it in my kitchen shirt off being funny
We think that there's comedy value today
Chick song I don't really think
There's much
It does not
Super interesting about
And
That's My Bae
Meredith Brooks
I'm doing b**** you know they don't like I don't like when when women
Especially color
Oh boy
Staying
Pretty Fly for a White Guy
Not a fan
Take that
To take that ship somewhere else
I don't like you don't like to be playful sing original prankster
Other bad offspring
How do I people who are into combining separated
Okay
Movin On that was for you
I don't like people
To discuss always been on your mind
That's interesting
Anything
Is of the kind of Supernatural
Real I'm on board
Times that universes
Are you guys thinking
Like one of the one of the real
Weird hidden gems
These Rising
Hitler loves
Here's one of the things that I think about
Rising falling
Is there
There's sweet
Tooth Fairy occult
Yeah and there's so many layers
In that world you're never taught
School
If I was sitting in class
N100
Teachers was like
So yeah you know that they put the Jews in the car
Tration camp
They tried to take over Europe
Also they believe
That there was a
A fountain of youth
Just thought there was all these like
Treasures out there they were actually working on it
Figured out
Remember
I don't know I don't know who he sent out but they want
Hugh
And what kind
No
Parodies like
Native people
And they were so fast
Plaster casts
Their faces
We're like okay
It was so bizarre they like okay
They just be game what they forgot to put like us
Straw or some type of breathing apparatus.
Ocean
Nazis but
Respond
Your point with all that though is that real
Stuff that happened in our history where I'm just like
Who thought this was okay
DIY pretty crazy
That that mentality does also inform our our modern lives
Send it like
It'd be stupid for us to think that whatever culture is
Is today
F*** is that alright
Short attic is it good gay people how was your day
And women are trans
That's a very much bleeds into our topic
I wonder what like even like
Like when a woman got her. They must have
Like I know from a lot of
Religious text
You are unclean yeah you must go to the shack
Hurry up.
I have to assume
Even in caveman times there was like
Alright you go to that part of the case no one can touch her
Yeah that's everything I wore their real
You think those cavemen were popping the cork
Jesus
Can we strike that from the record
Why did I say that
Anyway
Another another
It's kind of crazy how there's such an cuz I think I was watching MSNBC
And they were talking about
51% of women
So crazy how
More like so equal a dump
That's true
That's weird
Why is that weird
Why isn't there like 30% men 70% women
I think because of how you know how genetic coin toss
Yeah basically with coin tosses
If you have a million coin tosses that'll be a proxy
500000 heads
Approximately 500
Seven billion people on the planet
Don't know number 7
Yeah it's you have that of course it's going to be about 50
The coin flip
Call everytime you
I never switched around
No
Interesting
How many how many position changes you think you're there Kenworth
Partners looking at Marti right now
I think I'm good for like
Tops
Metaphors about your average
For without it getting really weird
Those are like you're going
I saw that I want to try this
Talking about
From your ex
I call that Mommy style now anyway
WhatsApp setup
But we're 60 minutes and we haven't said
What's the schedule
Play times over
Holy s*** they happen they were real you can go there it's an amusement
Part kind of thing now
Starks
Memorial Park
Teacup ride
This is this is
Yeah
Lock you in a room
You're sad date
Call man
I think that's a date thing where it's like for stayed for something like that
Just For Real
Yeah like reality
Watch
It's a book called a buckeye
Bookshelf
Was watching like a mystery that you know the
Watch it like a pro
All that's right
Basically it is, new Unsolved Mysteries
Yeah
The Denise feeling
Dateline Rhapsody
Boyfriend
The conclusion
Salem witch trials
Interesting life because it's
It's something that I learned about in school days
And I didn't care that much
I will say that my research of it for preparation of the podcast
About it
Anderson wife
Researching
Here's why I love it
I feel like I wasn't paying attention
In school which is
Impossibility
Americado a pro wrestling Illustrated
Folded up in my notebook and
I was reading it
Taking notes
Dreaming of one day being the next
Meltzer
The card that I was going to have
Wrestlers
I got home
I could definitely see you being a fanfiction
Felt maybe even still today I love
Witches
Dark arts
Perfect knuckle tattoos
And I I
I also love
I am passing by the idea of a society
Freaking out
Yeah over some words like
What's even Within
The context of a
Trial that went on
Yeah yeah
Everybody basically accepted that magic in the Supernatural s*** was real
Part of it
He's almost like the force in some ways from Star Wars
That there's some of that
Little bit of context
Situation
From February 16th to May 6th
That's ovary
Year it was going on
What does Delaware
It was in Salem Village
Large
Okay
Man
Village
Cuz there was Salem Village
There were two different entities
The time
But we're very closely involved with each other
Robust
Tile town
For they were Industries
1500 dime
Was a far more agricultural rooted
Area
So
You know what I didn't hear it
You know what that was that was not where I had a problem with Shyamalan
Love the idea
The Purge great idea
The Purge
Has my boys
I love Ethan Hawke I love the Hawkeye read the hottest summer his book
Much as I do
Heard it was
Too long congratulatory / 12
That is super impressive
They're going to call it 12 years old
Good
Executed
Over the course of this
Year
They were familiars
And s*** like that or just
Actually accused of being male
20 people who were executed
Free was killed by putting rocks on top of him
Well the reason
Not guilty
If he said not guilty and was found guilty he would have to give up rights to his estate
Giving a please
He protected his estate
So
In situations where they don't give a
You still going to torture a little bit in order to get them to please
So they put a board on top of it and just started pressing rocks on top
Giving rocks
I think it I think it said it took two days
Of him to be impressed by bored
The other one
5 people died in prison
Because of
Conditions
Incarceration
Again
Is my eye
Oftentimes to be misinformed when we're talking
Nope sound
YouTube
Think about
Mistrial
Was that like
Thankfully they do like a witch
We're going to like light you on fire
You are a witch
To survive it if you're not well
We were wrong from the English
Oh okay
To do it
Instances in New England of them being again
You won't drown
To do more with that
English variety
Like
Such like flawed logic
Sending out these sentences know that
Because it's a thing works like what the problem solved itself
Either we're right or we were on but she's
It's a lot of
Individual people who
So much of it makes me think of Socrates
Cuz
Greece
He was killed by
The past on
And
The reason
For his execution was
Because he
Didn't want to
Say that there were
The story that were told
But if you actually look at the history
They killed him cuz he was being a dick
Annoyed
He was a schizophrenic who would run around town
I like Pat agresti real life
Theatrics
The dramas
Basically that is annoying
The Socratic method is just like
Constantly asking questions
People who don't like pro wrestling sound
You know it's fake
But the reason that he
Comes to mind is that like people
So you will either kill you or you can
Leave town
We're going to give you a death sentence
Come and smuggle you away if you want to go
But the reason
Either way it takes care of the problem people out
So many of these people are just like
You know
Weather which or not
It'll solve our
I want what I need you to do and I'm sure you'll do it
People were
Trouble
What I want to do is lay out
Play a little bit of a context
For the world that we're living in
So we have
Where are all these things
Take place
Know how far we have to go back but
Dead people who came over from
We're looking for Religious Freedom and choir shirt
They were kind of assholes
Are religion
Jeffrey Lee
And also forcing a lot of people
Yeah not let anyone else do any other
So in the 1600s
People their version of religion was
Very f*****-up
In terms of the devil was a real thing
Penny Wears Prada
Cheap
These ideas about ghosts
And it goes down to Michigan
Are Georgia Michigan version
Devil went down to Mission
The one up to Michigan
Yeah you're right
When was Easter
Instead of the Fiddler's to turntable
Maybe gold
Mittal Steel
All the wheels
Pretty good
I want to save the KMC kru
Keep right at the end
I'm going to look it up yeah it's so good
Devil went up to Michigan
More people having
Done their own version of The Devil Went Down to Georgia
Avery's play right now cuz I
Spotify
So
Q60 93 is when the proper Salem Witch Trials were going on in that Hysteria
However
50 years before that or so
There was
A bunch of other
Witchcraft
Related
Situations
Recognize generally is the first woman who was put to death
For being a witch
In the Massachusetts Bay Colony
For the lady named Alice
Young
47 years old
In Springfield
To hang for being a witch
Historically
Generally people
See it as a
Inheritance
Cuz already late husband
The very largest
She had no sun
Hotel
Like one of these like lookie here what are we got here a couple witches
Is she has no son
There's no one to inherit
Estate
Damn to further make that claim
I heard
Who could have inherited
Stop if she got married
Tyrus
With probably acoustic also
Matter fact
Emojis
So after that in 1648
48 to 1660
C3 there's a Proto witch-hunt
It goes on
This sort of thing
80 people are accused of being a witch 15 or killed two of them are men
Or killed
Some of the stuff
Is
Hilarious
What constitutes an being witches
Everything sounds like I'm so glad we live
Europe
Events guys like
Dammit
Witchfinder General
Cedric the Entertainer were just ask which Hunter
I'm sure
Emmanuel
In order to help people find witches
Course and I'm sure this is going to be real fact-based
Absolutely
This first technique that he used was
A technique called
Watching
Okay
Daylight with people watching and if they are actually
Within 24 hours
An imp will appear
What's an amp
What lake is familiarly I got like a
And they would show up within 24 hours because they depend on the witch
Graffiti
So if it's
That that was ever successful
How many times have you come across that being the case
So many.
We would step number one this was used
The case of Margaret
Her kid was like
Mom
I'm starving I want breakfast
Margaret Jones was the
Person who was
60/40 whatever
And she was found guilty and fees are the reasons that were given
Recorded
The evidence
It was against her
She had a malignant
The people that treat touch would end up getting sick
Phil Collins song
You came in contact with her.
Okay we can
Very easily arduous
Communicable diseases
Is she was a practicing
Medicine
Like enemies
Yeah I guess hey drink this
Poop water it'll make you feel better
Let you know
Mother worst discipline
She could tell the future
I don't believe is the truth
Something
Came to pass
That you should have no knowledge of
She had upon search and apparent
As fresh as hell
Forced search it was withered
Began on the opposite side of her
I don't know
She had titties
Chad weird titties
I don't know
Okay
Watching Park
Comes into play
In the prison in clear daylight
There was more arms
She's sitting on the floor and her clothes up a little child which ran from her into another room
And the officer following it
Was Vanna
The like childish
Two other places
And one made this our Chelsea
Upon it and was cured by the said Margaret
Who used means to be employed
Her behavior is very and temperamental
In the like distemper she died
Disappeared
And then was cute by Margaret
Was mean in court
I mean
Maybe a lot of
Yeah there's a lot of
There's a lot of stuff like that
We are
I think I've gotten to the bottom of water
Before we get to the actual Seance there's a couple of other case study that are to me
That we are not dealing with witchcraft pretty much ever
First case
We have basically
Heritance
Protecting inheritance
Gibbons
5 she was killed in
AM 640
Tri suit
Scooter overcharged
Overcharged Earth
So they called the church to investigate
Basically
Refuse to apologize
For the Carpenters who committed a crime against her
And crawl are
I got it
She just throw it back
And
Also Adam Carolla
Because she would apologize who excommunicated
The church accuses her of usurping her husband's Authority
Because of her behavior it because of suing these contractors
Once her husband is dead
She's tried for being a witch
So basically she was trying for
Basically
She was not conforming to social role becoming a
Is the chi was more socially connected the most
Of the other people who'd ever been accused okay
I feel like it's real easy to Railroad like a loner origin
You know
Make her way in the world
Yes
In the Endocrinology be like third
Linda's produce
Rode me like
I bet she was tough
I like to think she
Tell you about her is that her second husband
He had a
First wife before hurt
Esther behling
That's the s***
So I
Was her deceased husband's first wife
Hester's Brother Richard Bellingham
Was the assistant governor of Massachusetts
And was instrumental in am given
Conviction of being a witch
Well okay
Your sister
And her husband married another lady
Kind of like a cooze and public and they got there but that's my family
To his nephew essentially otherwise
To be a team that is
Is developing a little better
You were talking about
In 1648
She's accusing fast and whipped
S*** out of her
Everybody seems like pumpkins in the story more like
Australia
The bad rap
It was a prison
Like
Call a present
But the worst of the worst from England went over there
Whatever
For here
Are just like
The biggest weirdo
Super weird
End of religion and Catholicism
If this is all were so religious and weird
Do the whole separate
I think that came later
That was a good 80 years after all this is going on
What will find
When this dive down
Pretty quickly after that it becomes embarrassing
Yeah because I hope they back on their face
The distinction between Salem Village in Salem
And a lot of the other is
More intellectual centers in like she aware of what's going on for a bit
Oh I love it blew my mind
5 was
It took eight
Ears
For its renewal
To get from England
To America
So for eight years
There wasn't a constitutionally bound Authority
Okay X gear and then x + 8
Alright in the meantime
Governing bodies that everybody
Question their authenticity Lord of the Flies
A little bit his is a little more structured but yet
From the authority to the
Call Anita
Could take months
To get from the news
The Philadelphia
They're killing people with
Rocks
This matching some guy is gay
You're not going to believe what
F*** now
They're blaming women for being witches
Disney collector
Mary Johnson
She was into the devil
She killed a child
Sushi Chicago
She ever killed child
Most likely by Nathaniel rusko who's the guy
Image of like
They're not really taking a lot of power
The jail
Cowabunga f**** lady prisoners
This is the sort of witch-hunt stuff that have been going on before
So there is a context where and they believe in the devil but at the same time
It's very rarely like a this evil person needs
Replenished
There's there's an agenda
Alfred
Can do a little investigative work like
If we were their defense
We were there
Be like
I think we got a case
Yeah we were a country
Joseph Granville religious
Are the types
Who believed in this like watching kind of test
And these are things that they believe that they can prove he exists
Sense of the Supernatural cast Glenn Beck Rush Limbaugh 100% yes yes
Alex Jones
He's very religious
Malibu
Glenn Beck still feels more right
Supposed crying.
Over there
This brings us to the proper beginning in 14
February
Were the Salem witch trial proper kicks
About to try
I just feel like these women were railroad and there was no right answer and it was either like
Admit you're a witch okay you're a witch
We still think you're wet
Started
A Scarlet Letter
Actually
Inspiration
I don't
Nathaniel Hawthorne
Scarlet Letter
Alright so
This is so much
Information
69th Terrace
Because the
An ordained minister had a mature ministers
Kind of liked it
Controversial
This Reverend Eli Capistrano open mic comedy club coming sound effect
Be perfect
About it
Yeah I mean I know that we have no chance of growth
Yeah we're having a better time
I think history would dictate that
Comedy Club coming to town was a bad idea
Metaphorically speaking in Salem
Okay so Samuel Perez Comes To Town
And down in the middle of what
You could almost look at as a Hatfields and McCoys
Type battle between two families
Bensalem
The Putnams and the porter
Okay
Well you know the Hatfields and The McCoys
Never heard of
I so can come by her generosity,
He comes to town
And he's like it in the lay-of-the-land what was going on and he's kind of pinion
If you look at the record that
No matter what happens
The trials kicked off he was quoted as saying
Yeah it's almost
Phuc yea
Display
Keep it is best sort of think
I don't know it's hard to judge a person in hindsight but it seems like
Avoid
The town split
But he's very
So
His daughter Betty
Abigail Williams
In February of 62 start to act really weird
They start to have seizures
They start to have tourettes
Start yelling at inappropriate times interrupting church sermons and stuff like that
And started
Flailing their arms and like
Bucked up
Bad news
Nice I like that
Start acting all f***** up
Pretty quickly a bunch of kids in town start acting really f***** up in similar ways
Which as we know from being kids
Annoying kid
A lot of that could just be copycat
If you see someone you'll b******* in church b******* in church
Yeah it's so fun
You realize that like
I can get away with doing the things that are
Or
There's just that power
People start being like well we got to figure out what's going on
That is
Is very mad
He believes that there's a conspiracy involving the devil
Especially because he's also a preacher in the idea of sermons getting interrupted is very that's
Hostetter
Dealing with hecklers I try to avoid
YouTube John Putnam crushes girl yelling outfit in church
Did you just get a video.
Call man so people start
You get the idea like I we got to figure out what
Not the fun way
But also their 9 and 12
Get that out of your head
Probably trust kids to
Weird
So the three of them accused three women
The three women who were first accused Sarah good
She is a homeless beggar
Because
Choosing is rejecting fear and ideas of self-control
Didn't help lead kids on a path to Salvation
What your kin goes back to the Socrates
So she wasn't funny
Homeless and a beggar
Didn't help kids
Okay
There's no like there's no corrupting influences like
You're saying bulshit
The ornithologist
The righteous path
Meanwhile As We Know
Whoever was murdered was the coolest
Hero
Osborne
Sarah
Yeah
Sedona
Shining
Socially was the cheated married
Error husband Paterson but marrying the indentured servant
Jeopardize
The Inheritance
Again
People really don't like that
Also
You can really do
To make sure the government eminent domain
To make matters worse
The Sun
Who could theoretically
Get cut out of the inheritance by this marriage
The nephew of John Putnam scene
One of the members of the
Cool
Demand the third woman who is Accused with
Associated with African roots
Some of India
But she would tell Abigail and Betty
He's fascinating stories that bordered on Vudu
Convicted of inflaming their imaginations
So she's guilty
Yeah it's probably have a little drink or smoke
You've got the homeless beggar
It's probably pretty cool
Social conventions in married an indentured servant which is awesome
Lose your mind
Yes
Middle name
He don't yet I have no idea that Raven
School Stories
I could just imagine
So
One of the other reasons
I think I might just hit my hand
All right one of the other accusers besides Abigail Williams
Was a junior
Early on
Was fingering the
People
That
Some of them
I'm fine I know I'm an adult
You been on a lineup
Singers
Viewing Freddy
Call are very like a lot of them seem to have weird
Like the people who are being
Sarah Osborne
It had been sued by
John Putnam
I'm senior in the past
Overland
Pop had been sued in the past
Or it had
Beefs
With the Putnam family
All I want to do this comes up and it's very suspicious
Abigail Williams
Third person
Who's making accusations
Is
A member of the Putnam family
A twelve-year-old child in the Putnam family
Go back in time
Now I'm just a comedian
I don't know about your small-town agricultural Justice
I feel like the other money
Also what I would do
Come at me bro styles
Come at me bro
CT impression
Mycourtcase
Get accused then
Get out of here
Like the three of them kind of getting accused well alright
More the next person is Accused is Martha Corey
And She's accused
Because she publicly expressed skepticism about the girls accusation
Okay president
You're going down
Rebecca nurse
Are both upstanding citizen
Cool then become accused of being witches
They aren't homeless
Start
To fuel this idea that it can be anybody anybody can be a witch
Not just
Porsche people anybody can be at so we all have to accuse each other
Yeah it's like
How do I know you're not
That there was a joke
Type character during the time making lots of which jokes
Killed so fast which one of you ladies wants to go out
The next person who's this is where
In the resurgent this is where my mind broke
Okay
Is Dorothy good
Who is the daughter Sarah good the homeless beggar lady years old
Now she's not
Convicted of being a witch
But then also it might be thing word
I don't know a whole lot about her history
From tragedy in
Was recently almost lost her Lander
Maybe the Putnam took her lantai noise
So
She wasn't convicted but she was interrogated
And the answer is yes
Judges
Was used to implicate her mother
Which is nuts
Questions
You are interrogating
Shake
I'm picturing you as Matlock
Now I am I
It's an old table
Yes I do
We are leave
Tachypnea
This point
No there's no specifics but her testimony
Is f***** up is a four-year-old has no idea what you say
We are really killing it right now
You have to understand how bad
Convicted
Ended up being killed
Another person who's involved
Pursued
Control
Sarah cloyce another Sarah
Also happens to be Rebecca's sister
Elizabeth
Elizabeth Proctor's husband is like hey you guys got to cut this out
Husband
The guy's got pressed
Eventually gets arrested
Abigail Hobbs her stepmom delivery
Mary Warren
Who was Elizabeth Proctor's servant someone who made accusations of witchcraft
Ulcer
And the three of them split
They confessed to being witches
And start pointing fingers at everybody
They do just start
Pointing finger strategically at a lot of people
Yeah
Also headlamp
That sort of thing
William Hobbs
Is Deliverance
Hobbs is husband
Who is another lady who is
Who is Derek and Rebecca nurses other sister
McCoy
You're basically there's a lot of people who get mixed up in it
But a lot of it is just like our side into prison
Wow
Interesting Lee enough
Father
No.
The look of belief on your Facebook
There's no doubt
So
At this point
The accusations become too numerous to list
And things just spiral out of control again
It's like
And it has got to be knobs.
I'd like to think
They were staying
I think the most of the same people laugh
Jermaine
I think Reverend Burroughs
Spell differently
But
He was involved like being Jewish around these
If you think they're doing
24-hour
Hornswoggle
You dangle a bar of gold
At the beginning you had a bunch of people who were super related to the Putnam Porter
The family
Everything loses control
And a bunch of people who aren't involved at all get accused
And I think appearances here
So we have to pretend but the things that we were doing before we're real
Arthur J
40 people
I wonder why
Yeah
I'm sleep a lot of them are killed
They can do that
Chirp
I don't
Imprisoned
I'm going back to the Jedi
What are authorized in German
So they were just hang up
Shallow Grave
And then generally what would happen is the families would come
And bring them back to their home
That's usually
Was caught up in the end it believe they're witches
The shallow grave
Is really f***** up stuff
Type of this
If you take the human tragedy out of it and I'll just like sadness
People dying
Brooks movie here somewhere
Is a comedy of dumbass
Okay
Because in court they're legitimately arguing
Where did Manhattan lawyer
Whether or not a person has to give the devil permission
To use their face
Do torment
Because
These kids
Are saying
That like
Sarah Goode
It was a shade of you it was an apparition
The devil was using your form
Lawyers are arguing
Permission
At one point
It's so like that is very bizarre
How funny
Remember from my previous study
Someone wants to
Fidelis to ask
The devil tried to overthrow God
But your permission
What the f*** religion worship
Religious my favorite
Do they do there's one of those things that using Court where is like if
Having seizures and stuff like that
Crutches the person and they are healed
That proves their witch
Because
They believe that whatever illness I caused you I can
Secure
Because
Venomous evil comes out of my eyes
And when I talked to truly flows back into my body would almost think that at that point
They would almost
I'll try to
Weaponized
Or use them as
Healers
Well they can only heal that which they cause
Okay just in case
I totally understand
Especially
They hate these Native Americans so much instead of blankets giving these women
I'm very curious to see
First of all I have no doubt
Like Wally World
I would assume there was some of that
But outside
I'm going to give her a king-size
Like I'm going to have sex with her
If it might be stretched
She's a witch
It does seem like
Stop is as bad as that but not that
Formalized into
Apple stuff
Yes I would almost
Guarantee
One awful
Not really all that awful B really f****** stupid
Is the thing called The Witch
Which cake are you aware of the witch cave
No but it sounds delicious
It's not
Ate something that they used in court as a method
To like trying
Define delicious piece of cake in front of
Newegg
But you wish that was what they did
So what they did was make a cake out of
And
The urine of the children that were Bewitched
So these kids with p and make a cake
Campus
Repeat it to a dog
Now their belief was
The one the dog eats potato
It will hurt
So you would hear the screams of the witch when the cake is being eaten
Because some sort of the evil is carried through the children's urine or something like that it's super
I was rid of time machine
And we brought one of the guys back and
But hear me out
Explained
First of all weird to be here in your seat
Future
Second of all
What do you know about
Michelle I want witch cakes
If you follow my thoughts
It's it's
Stay
If you look at all the scholarly sources tonight
Full of books about
Urine of the child
Conduit
Make sense
So they
Do you have to think that the possibility
I can't imagine this ever gave concrete evidence
To like
Dumped by my cavity brain also
If you want to go
Imagine the test that didn't get approved
My forklift
Afterwards if she's not a witch then get a proper
Well realizer in
Influence is gone
Or you say
Evil spirits
Got to her
Tricked out concerto
Play learn
So about 2
The end of the relevant information
Which sucks because I was so much fun
Information who is the president
There wasn't
Oh I'm sorry I'm sorry for the revolution
I'm sorry
Who's the president information getting from England
The Colony took eight years or so
Get their King has no idea about what's going on here
I know imagine this is over and like 7 years later
What the f*** were they doing over there America's at the big game of grab ass
If you think about it the revolution
Start
60 years after that there now
There might be an element of it
Kingwood
Maybe we can fly to the revolution because it's like the yeah we got to keep up a little bit of appearance
Justin likes
Is it worth it
The taxes were bringing in really
These jerks
Maybe America is
The dumbest of the dumb
Pretty conceivable
Guess what
Hey witch catcher
Forgot your pit cakes
The f*** out of here
Yeah
20 people X
Executed
5 died in prison
Two of them little babies
Singing prison
You also have to wonder
Property
Yep power
Money that still is pulled
Old now we're talkin
Money
Free land land up
For grabbing
Everything's moving so fast
Power such an ability
So there's a lot of theories into in terms of like what was going on
One of the ones that's really popular among people as those other got poisoning
In the Rye
In the city
Claviceps
Do the precursor for LSD
So a lot of people believe that the
Going to town was infected
The falls
But that doesn't explain why a lot of freaking out
Not entirely sure
Sleep paralysis is another explanation
Infer why kids that have terrifying visions of
The people
Maybe you're a kid and you run into a homeless beggar
That can be scary just in the affected like
Sure an adult
Shouldn't they be not
Yeah
You see that person
In your head
I'd say what growing up
Indiana
The Greeks
Kali merah
But
The
They had like
The grandmother live
Course
Kalispera
We didn't like her
Oh no no malaka
Carrizo
Oh yeah
Malakas
The bad person
Okay
I don't think I had a work for f*****.
Evil
Call Ed Perth
We are
We doing the backyard freaking out like that
Sleep paralysis at work
Sure my speaker
There's a huge phenomenon of people seeing an old hag
Call old hags
Syndrome
Sleep paralysis and when they come to the hallucinate
Old woman sitting on their chest
This is just something that is
Super bizarre but it does happen
That's pretty good
Explanation
I don't know which way they're boner
There's another instant
Leave the round the time there was an outbreak of
Bird born encephalitis
Which is a bird carry disease that causes paralysis catatonia
Nocturnal
Not emission emission nope
Just nocturnality baseball your sleep schedule
Do you have delayed responses to physical and mental stimulus
My girlfriend's I think would have been considered
I can't sleep
So at the end of it
I am hundred percent convinced
That the beginning of it had to do with the porter Putnam
The two families
Yeah when you look into them
The reason
Loggerhead
Was
That
The Putnam family wanted
To stay into the app
Cultural part of the city
That's what they were more invested in
Thomas from salemtowne
The Porter Family saw more promising
In progress and the future
Salemtowne
Involved in
And they wanted to be absorbed into salemtowne
The two families had f******
It's not like
You don't like it
Someone
Nowadays near the feud with them
Back then
People who weren't part of their family
Would be out drinking
Uba uba
We're sitting here having a beer everything is fine
Then
All of a sudden we're fighting
Psych player Hogan fans
Craigslist
Unrelated parties get involved in the feud
Two families philosophy
It's kind of like bricks
A little bit in terms of like there's actually leaves Allentown
Or so to be absorbed into Salem
Really hot feeling
About it
So
The Reverend Parris becomes Town can't figure out how to solve
Is more involved
And the pot
Numb side
The autonomy side
4 Salem
In addition to that
Well
Here's why it's such b*******
He's involved with the Putnam side of the philosophy
His daughter and niece are the first two people
Who make accusations
Along with an Putnam Junior
Three people to start making accusations on the Putnam side
Or people that the
Land disputes with
The Putnams
You just do people constantly being involved
What are you do
If you come to town
Specifically
The land.
Churches on
Savannah's pretty good amount
You got to fix this
What are you doing
Absolutely
Which is siding with these manipulative
I don't know I mean if you truly believe the Salem should be autonomous from the other Salem
I don't know what to do
Big crew
Big strong
Big stromboli
Yeah
We're just saying
Number f****** around
You get Braun strowman on your side I'm bringing the f******
Family
You think these guys are witches what are you going to do about it
Will f****** throw boards in rocks all over everybody
Man this just drives me crazy
It really drives me f******
Just to give you a couple of platinum family members
Senior also to use a bunch of people
Edward Putnam
He was
Yeah them people work
Nb-1
Seems like
Adventurist
Hannah Putnam
Made a bunch of accusations at blame
For being a witch and killing her eight-year-old child
Probably sit also backpack
Kids at table.
Is the biggest dick in the world
He's the one who sued bunch of people who all
To be on the outside
That Reverend Burroughs that I mentioned earlier
Reverend Burroughs gets out of town
Cuz he didn't like the way things were going
Seniors
Yeah
Everything alright I'll come back
But the two of them.
Them still don't get along the 15 years later you like
Talking to the witch
Saint Ambrose
The ends up being
Yeah
This dispute it becomes
Beyond that you do have to wrestle with the fact that it's so against women
Kylee Russell
Welcome.
Sorry
Button
That's not an irrelevant piece of
Yeah I think
For the little too
Baldi for the
That time
Survey
Claiming her own land
Church
Standing up again
Putnam John Putnam Senior as well
Threatening
I got a lot a lot of it
Instead of the Salem witch trials
These might have been called the tailor
The Salem witch trials
We have to wonder to how many like I wouldn't be super surprises
Were people who rejected men
I would not be at all if some of that was the real reason
I mean
Is there anything you read that were like
How real is that
They're also
Holistic healing
Now there were those three ladies
I can't remember I'm trying to come up with
The salt pepper and Spinderella
Britches
Microsoft
I do today are you
Shoot I saw them live their terrible they were terrible
Are there were those three whose names are
Really they probably just admitted it
Either because I
Hey where we real cool if we admit it
We can blame anybody
Which is
I think a piece of it too is that like some of these people were on the lower end of society
I maybe like to drink at night
Accrue
The pleasure
And my Rhymes are a good shop
Oh really
Did you welcome people to it
To bring you in here
Van Halen
Are there is
Steven is they wanted to be
Marty what's your what's your feeling on all this
It away
It does kind of make
Acme
I love hate really
Our government
Tyranitar
It does
Make me
Think like you know
We kind of do need
Somebody in charge
To be like what the
F*** are you gay
All of us don't do it someone,
Now
At the other hand it's like
Yep this is what we do
There are
The Salem Witch Trials nowadays
But there are
11 weeks
Now with
Eastern Arizona
That's kind of fueling a lot of the
The reason for that
Very easy
Easy also
Is one thing
To push another
Nazis did it to
Best of
Charge will take
But
Power
Like real cool dude
Take care of a problem but create
Absolutely Bush Administration
Sure
Another 9/11
Someone was
Yeah I mean it's just one of those things where it's like
You look back in history
Time ago
Black Widow video
Listen to the things like that
Situation where guy came up to her and was like
You should have my babies
And she was like No I don't want
Absolutely there is an entitlement there is a like I deserve
I think a hundred years from now hopefully will be back on that if you like
I can't believe
This is Heidi didn't rise up as a whole and erratic
Quicker
Mental illness is still a thing
We don't fight
Understand
Comprehend
Madeline says
I had some mental illness
Factors
And just by going to the woman on the train saying have my babies
Probably
What's the mental illness
Absolutely crazy but
People are crazy
Ignore or diminish
The anti-women acid rain
Evil in this Witch Trials map of like
Either fear of women or hatred
And that
Bed of amplifier
There's no power here
And absolute power and no oversight being ignored
Three some sort of like track
I agree I think all that is true and then also I think
Absolutely
John Putnam Senior
Maybe one of the biggest dicks
I think he's responsible for 90% of this welcome to the club
Prescott Bush
Adolf Hitler
The book controversial
People to throw in there
Bubba Bubba
Pottsboro
Warhol
I'm an ass-whole
I'm going to go and throw h.h. Holmes
Sure sure actual serial killer
And I'm Night Shyamalan because of the village
I think we found some truth here I think we have I like the first time
You could argue that
Women had to die
For this episode common thread
But it also
Sheds another
China Delights OdoBan
White magic
Just sometimes women are not true
And hopefully
Like it just to me as though if there would have been like
Warlock
Trials or something
Men wear
I mean
It's a
It's one of those things
Yeah well I mean
Slavery
It's like one of those like
Where can I get soup
With WTF WTF podcast
Witch trials
You want people to pee in a cakewalk
If there are any
Salem witch trial apology
Probably
I'm
5th generation
I would also like that person on the vodka
Let me explain my point of view
Yeah
Repeat that
Spectral evidence
Trials
Intel outside later
Bastard
Justice doesn't exist evidence
If if the
The Civil War
Or let's just say like
You know kind of
What's going on
If all these
Entries are
Able
Be kind of wire
Indiana
Boa constrictor
Damien Damien
The earthquake killed Damien
Come on
Adele
Play the original first
Are you ready
You probably have a great Charlie Daniels
I'll take that bet you'll
The song where
You'll be
Show you one
Mobile
Just sit at a bar by your this reminds me of re store
Sounds like just a bunch of dudes
By themselves
Smoking watch
Like
Something sports report
And then some
Like that
If you're going to play in Texas you better have a fiddle in the band
Any day of the week
Really
Guitar is hot but not for a Louisiana man
Alright
If you're going to play in Texas
You better have excited right now
Velcro
Kru
All cat of course
So this is the KMC kru and is there answer
Down
Georgia
Detroit Michigan
Michigan
Oh really
Play Anarbor got a raid adhere
The new
View
Also this video is awesome
The devil
Netflix
At this point the devil knows he's.
I hope he calls the devil the son of a b**** the end
What's a thug
Play Hot Fire
Like I'm not done with you I only hate that he doesn't tell the devil of son-of-a-b**** of the air
Harley-Davidson
Are looking this up I found another song
I've never heard but it might be important
Number of devil came to blank
I'm fine
Get your get your erections erect
This is the devil went to Jamaica
This part of the song
Omad
Play the theme song so far I hope it gets like real reggae please
Chez paree on the 1st off
Walking the Bible version
No it's
I think he has to my walk
That n-word devil
YouTube
Who was likewise
The kids said boy let me tell you why
So your wife net worth
This is not David Allan Coe
I'll bet a million in cash
You think mine's better and you were accountant
There's another one devil came up to Boston
I wish was the Bosstones
The Jabba
I will Irish she the Adam Ezra group
Talk off
Quincy where we grind out of wasp
Talking Tom
Do like Boston blackface
Tell you what
It was Derek f****** Jada
I'm in a lot of got in a pack of Mamba
Do you like
There's an opportunity
For anybody who wants to make
Ifucking devil song
Hello Chicago
Danny kallis
Chicago
For some Italian
No the premise always have to be
Delaware
Chicago
Griselda Steel
Jimmy was behind the counter making italian-based that's pretty good
2B music
What's the quintessential
Now we okay
Blues Brothers we get the Blues Brothers 2016
They were so here's the story
Keloland
All the sudden he said
My brother
You put out
He seems legit
Not
Chubby Checker walked in I said shut up
I like that idea of
Makes me mad
Listen to me.
Morning Zoo crew 101
You get a binder
From there to here to happen
Audubon Zoo Cruise especially the day
There was Comedy Circus with pre-internet
Services
Comedian
The song
And they probably get like a binder
And it's like
Hey do a double
Down 24 whatever your local
That's morning radio Zoo crew 101
Bedeviled
Googling it is David Allan Coe
Crazy
How
I love David Allan Coe songs
Fair enough I got somebody on my phone here
I can't play in front of certain
France
Spiraled quite a ways from our conspiracy theory
Senior is a bad dude
Cheers Cheers Cheers
Here
Jeers to talks
Masculine
Mediabox
LSD
Wonderful
Podcast
ITune surf mlw
Rite Aid
Conan
More podcast Conan Conan whatever
It's that salt. Bro
That you're on fire
Sarah with an H
Also still like means you should know. Calm every Wednesday night
If you if you want
Still there
It's all there
Reaching out on Twitter
It's great I love I love
Whatever donations
Cuz
Takes a lot of time and
How to pay for hosting and
Appreciate listening
But until then
Please
Misaligned
Battle
Tell them I've been
Solving mr.
My chair
Dang that's what they want you to beg that's what
Illuminati
Elevator body 10 words which
A kilogram name for being which is an all kinds of weird stuff
Lesbian the bread and don't forget the property that's what they were