Alex
Color
Hey everybody hello
Drink novelty Beverages and talk a little bit but Alex Jones
Is there like a reason so like is there a twist
So like
Is it like
2 years ago
You tweeted all the time
About Alex Jones
And then
Now you're sweet o
The exact
Opposite
Of what it is you
You criticized Alex
14 in the past
I'm just referencing Trump's dumbass
Okay
It's for a long time especially over this last weekend
NFL b*******
Wild thyme Flourtown country
What are we doing
It's 90°
Chicago at the end of September Puerto Rico
Destroyed and the Trump is pissed off
Colin Kaepernick
Great great
Burn It Down
It's almost like racist parody
Like it I know I know
Kind of letting things off the hook a little bit
But it's
It does at times
I know that this is Becky
But there have been times in my life where I've been
Convince the like
Ann Coulter is
The performance art
He's just doing this stuff
I can't believe
The people are so I can believe in God I believe this entire episode
Ann Coulter and
What's it
Jesse Jackson
Have you brought this up before and I don't know anything about Alex
We got a little mini episode
For the people
And the reason they were doing this is October is almost upon us
Yeah cheapest
95 degrees
October
Is because
Today
We will be going
Through
Alex version of his Halloween 2015
So everyone
When we hit
At the beginning of November.
2015 investigate
Talking about Alex Jones becoming a full-on for Russia
So we didn't have time to go over the Halloween story
Glass from The Listener
I got a couple of messages
Multiple people demand
Some more.
Basically always Tire episode. Paul's blog
And you know what they're right there right
We made dacious claim that Alex Jones tells multiple versions
Halloween story
With slight variation
To the point where I believe that most of it is alive
And we are drinking at prescription energy herbal tonic
Anyways
Personally don't like Halloween all that much as an adult I don't like dressing up much
I tend to go to
Bar with it
Like one year I was a monk
And I shaved my head
Like with the ring on top
You went too far
I went around with a bottle of Carlo Rossi
Jaguar
Whenever someone like committed a party fowl and made them
Some say Hail Marys and our fathers
When I was in high school
My parents mistakenly thought it was
And kept me from celebrating it in anyway because it was
Who is Eva
Pagan ritual
Considering the fact that I was
Seven that's code for devilshit though
How do I
Severe mythology was based
Pagan ritual
Indeed here is what we know
These are the only real facts
That I can
Confirm
That I believe
Okay
Alex Jones Halloween does exist
I can confirm that
Alex Jones went to a party
Also true that was for his
Cousin Buckley
It's his birthday party
All 18 of amethyst point
Eyewear escalated that number wages
So it was Buckley's birthday
And it was around Halloween and Alex Jones went to a fancy dress ball
Of sorts
Vitality
Your cousin
Old-time expression
A costume ball
Fancy dress ball
They would call it
I only I only know this cuz
Okay you been calling her
They called them fancy-dress balls I really like a
Theater
That's where
I'm off
I'm off my game
First version of the story this one comes to us from November 2nd
Isn't the first time that Alex
Steve's pit to tell the story of Buckley's Halloween birthday party you know that for sure
What do you mean I mean has this story been just November
15 or is he been telling
Oh no I have no idea
From your prior I could not tell you that
But I know in 2015
The first occasion
The Department of Transportation
Arkansas
He does
That is a good party
Ain't nobody like you.
Birthday party
I went to my cousin's birthday party
By the way
Real good occasion to
To skip a break
Like I got to tell the story about Buckley's birthday party
That's fun
Captain's hat
Austin
Do magic people music
So first of all I want
Keep track of the various
Details
Each and every go to the costume party on a boat
At this point
Kitty costume
He's not participate
Vine
I'm going to give it to him
Cuz I want I'm also
This is when I was in college
I dressed up like Michael McDonald from
The series Yacht Rock
I realized I looked
Just enough like JD Risner
That I could dress up like the character Michael McDonald
Aviat Rock people go back and take clips from your Halloween stores and they're like
None of these are consistent picture of Jada
I went to the I went to the f****** Barber I had them cut like a receding hairline
You're insane
Party
That was going around checking the Malibu rum
I love you
Who was Christopher Cross
Alright
Pretty fun anyway
Keep an eye on the details
Flat bar to a bunch of places
Come up
On the balcony
So hold on
There's three people a white guy a white girl and a
Suspiciously Arabic guy
He had a good night.
Buckley has rented a condo with another party
And then there is a restaurant that has a balcony
Most likely at the we're on the boat
We go to the condo
Then we go to the restaurant then we're back
I would argue that the restaurant might be Boat restaurant condo
Cuz you know you're not going to the party condo to shower up for the restaurant or change your clothes or any
Anything like that
You're going straight through
You're going you're getting drunk on the boat and then you're eating to refuel
I am and you're going to
To the condo Park
Absolutely
Also
The balcony is where the
For this confrontation which was supposed to mean is it a private condo
White guy
White girl
Suspiciously Arab
We don't know which one of these people is in play
What are you
Very clearly
What what if it is blackface
What can I draw
I'm running into our
The trademark too many details
Is $2 in dollars
Too much
Having dialogue
Usually means but Eli
Those two things together generally mean
You're probably make
Do right right
You want to show off and police women right here with your cultural superiority
And this whole cultural Jihad it's getting
So I'm guessing based on that uses language this is the era
But it's not the white guy who is
Confronted him on
Balcony under a beautiful night sky where he's watching a drone
Right I don't I'm not 100% sure though cuz
Fast and loose
These here detail
Except for the ones that are clearly not true you saying are you showing off
For the girl right next
So could be the white guy in the white girl
Girls going to come into play in a minute
The white girl is not yet
I don't think
Also $4
Congratulations
The one right corner
Alright I'm just imagining one of those as well
You cap it it's white
Sitting around
Great
What it's about
There was a blond college girl
So this is probably the white girl that he
He was referencing
Another person ever
Cuz he said that there were three people who accosted him about his car and they were walking
Maybe but if they were in the party than they would have to be friends of Buckley
Like
You rented out
A f****** condo
Is friends with all blonde
When you rent out a condo
I do I do he gets around
It's not a public space anymore it's not like you posting Flyers
Like its PCU or some s***
Everybody gets laid tonight at the pit
You know
Yeah I was just
Cruiser back
I like that movie
OverWatch 2
15 years
I remember it well from the early days of Comedy Central when they
Have anything else they are
Zack and Jason
You love that
Movies
Stockholm Syndrome
Before any program
Anyway back to the story
Blonde college girl
What's going around saying I just didn't want to wear any costume because of my
I don't want to offend anybody
There are people going around all over the place
But they're going I'm so guilty of what I'm wearing
At the restaurant
Is wearing a Nazi hat
You might have
That the two of them were both at the restaurant bar
But separately
Asking him I don't know
What
The I mean
Guest if it's a high-end Austin bar it's
Your blood has a balcony
Or whatever
If possible
Just be on the ground Florida
But at the same time is now in the course of his
Two-minute clip
We've been going over
They've gone from
322 people
The number of people who have complained about his costume
Is already trained
Completely manufactured a college
My suspicion is
The characters that he introduced
Beginning he is now peppering in
And throughout the store
She is now repurposed as a character who has too much white guilt
So it could be just a case of him trying to over inflate the numbers of people
Who will have
Confronted him about the costume
Actually I think there is
It is like
Over the course of this we're going to see a bit
Be flushed out so I can open my
Mike because he tells the story
A bunch
It's an unproductive open miking
I went oh no this isn't happening again
It look like
Really it's a classic police
So
Your theory that he accidentally bought a Nazi
Sweetheart
Is possible
Especially
30s
There is a possibility that accidentally bought enough we had that I am I'm allowing as a possibility he'll wonder it was so
The entire the other possibility
That I am
Going to enter
Is that these people knew who Alex was and they came up to him and be like
You are a f****** fascist and he thought they were complaining about his hat
That is entirely right again this goes back to the unreliable narrator aspect of Alex Jones
His life
The story a week later on November 9th
He revisits the story
And he also skip a break
To tell this neither confirm nor deny the break
Every time he needs to skip break
You should goes right into the
Every time
I would love it if his advertising budget
You just fell apart because
I'm Jewish
Oh boy
So he is already from the Middle East
Yeah there's
There's a new live in the Middle East Alex there's a large percentage of
Jewish people who are Arabic
That's silly of Alec
Beyond that
Soldiers people are from
Originally
Faribault
Are berries European
European not areas
You're not wrong but at the same time
Africa
Yeah that's possible too
I don't want to get into that cuz
I think it's time to get into that
Let's get this break about the right genetic
This is a week later from the first time he tells a story and already we have new things being introduced
Do it the are you a Nazi as opposed to is that a Nazi hadn't offended by that I'm Jewish
But it looks like an arrow through that means
It's
You bet he's already threatened he's flushed out these characters more in order to
To serve his purposes
Of the story
The context
We should know
So now you're the
This might be the white guy
And then I was going on everywhere
Another party
Asterisk
So now we have a fourth location
So now we have the boat
We have the restaurant bar
We have Buckley's rented Oconto
No we don't
And we don't have an assembly the condo floor of a bar
Renting out a condo
So either
Misrepresenting
One of these is not a cure
Or both
None of this is real
It's poor Buckley
Buckley Bay not exist the other thing that I'm allowing is a possibility
Is that all of this is
True but not the stuff with other
Like that Buckley not only rented a condo also rented out the top floor of a bar
Hey there are you going
Get f***** on crazy
Yeah that's
Possible
And Buckley likes
Party
Because why
Run through wives so quickly
Abogado Alex has a lecherous man
Ford love Lauren Buckley
See that's my other favorite
Remember how I'm supposed to
Respond to that
Watch it
I don't think that's right
And they're just people walking around
We've met on the show before personal trainer
No Pat Riley the personal trainer who went to Europe and probably cheated on his wife
Remember him from the
Horrible a dirt bikes
Outside
As well
The Buckley
Invited 400 people at the top floor of a bar
The Apparently maybe a rooftop bar but it's also open to the public
Cuz Alex said that earlier in this
Okay good I don't know what that means
I have no idea what that's me when you rent out a place
It's a private affair
It doesn't it's not a thing where you can
Everyone
Can get out also and there's no way Buckley knows 400
Of different ethnicities
That's where my incredulity get straps
But also
Important to stop at hearing
And point out the Buckley
Spin the wheel
Steel
Afrika Bambaataa stuff you know some old school s***
You can see backing up there putting on like
Shook Ones Part 2 onyx
Just that one song from
The song from my gusset
The American anthem for shady random size pants
Back to the back to the November 9th
In walkover
And then try to make you uncomfortable and have you submit to them
Power
So
I don't believe any of
Okay so
Now we have
Top of a roof
All Races
Creed's and backgrounds witch
Bleed red blood is not just
Arab look
Player
Then there's another guy and a girl walking around who won't go to Costco
No no
There is
Another white guy at some point stuff is the Arab guy
In the original version there was one sad white college girl
In this conversion everyone's running around there's enough of them
Everyone's weirded out by a are making people uncomfortable
Just my socially walking up to them and say
I can't wear a costume
I have too much white
First of all business but if it was this
Parties
Yeah I would beat a hasty Retreat from this party
I had I had to have it in in college me and my buddy Nikki gift we were going crash parties
Charismatic
We just go find a party
Insinuate ourselves
Almost invariably something would go wrong and I
We got to get the
F*** out here right now
That's what I would do and I was at Rooftop Bar party
Where am I
I'm here behind Austin bar where there's
DJ's on the roof
S*** like that
I need a refund
Alex Jones being a dick in there
What rights are we are walking around
Not wearing costumes
Filled with white guilt
Stop
In people because they want them
To submit
Does Alex Jones Theory that's the premise
Also you said it was the day before Halo
It was on the 30th
Yeah actually I'm looking back on another calendar from October 25th
The 30th is a Friday
Buckley's birthday
I was just trying to like
So get it in my head if it would make sense that people would dress up on the 30th weekend
Oh yeah
I thought that might be a possibility where is like a Thursday
Yusuf on the Friday
Or whatever
So far
We have two things that check out
And it was Friday the 30th people probably dressed
And
The other thing
I'm thinking
Is
Alex is not sober
Absolutely
I don't
You got to take everything
Sort of
Not at face value
And you think he's telling a story where he was probably f*****-up
And someone came up to him
What's up what's up with your paranoid
And then the next morning when he's hungover he's trying to re context relies on tourism being a dick to a stranger
Later on
Vaguely remember
Casting hammersley
Yeah my God
My audience is going to love that
So totally
Might as well throw them a little Halloween
The first person to story November 2nd
Yes second version November 9th
I got a whole week
Actually written down to maybe edited
It sort of
Speeds up
Okay
The rapidity of which story
Cuz now we go to November 11th
And yet again
Learning
To equate everything was how you been racially sliding
Mental patient
Neurotic
Does he not realize that he
He is talking entirely about him being racially slighted
Wearing his like
These people are a cult
Everything is about
Which is why I'm mad that I got Rachel which is why 80% of my show is about white genocide
You got to figure some s*** out the same time I would like
Tip mine on Nazi hat to him
Bye
It's because you shave the middle of your head prior to
Complement
Because he said drooling without following it up with
Mulin
Which is something that he does almost all the time
I don't like that at all to the story
Driven
And again
Cultural revolution
The restaurant bar
So now we're
Now it's not a rented out
Now we're out in public
At the restaurant.
The most
Alex Jones
Apologist E-Type people out there might be saying
Hey
You know what that bar that he rented out with the PJs
Stop the restaurant bar
And it could be the restaurant absolutely.
The club right into a restaurant bar / Club
And the way he's been
I'm talking about these individual places have been very different
So now
Take place
The top of the bar
Place restaurant
I mean
I don't know what point
So now the other person
The aggressor
Pics of change
He does not
Specify jewishness
He doesn't have any of those
The story
About this in the Conte
White guilt
Not really
Talking about
Liberal brainwashing
Story or at least
He's trying to get out of it
Now becomes him being Macho
You'll see
See here tells the version of
People
Heather was obviously
I'm just sick of these bullies I'm sick of their garbage
So
The contact that he's telling you
Here is some guy cosplay came up jumpers
Yeah and now it is the point is
But if someone with his liberal
Cultural revolution garbage comes up to flex on them and they fall apart
15 people
The Gang
They need to back up their gang mentality
Still beat them up
So the whole premise
Insanity
We just had one more
The story on November 12th
He was running thin
Okay on things
Used to talk about was the day that that
General stubblebine
Get the dumbass name right
That was the day where they're having like elaborate
White
Narrative
$30 for a car
So here is
He's at on the 12
Birthday party
I work half and Chad and I had a white person and an arrow
And I was nice of it first but then I turned it on and I got in their face and I should watch it man
All right now that's very different
Yeah that's a very different sort of reminiscent of one of the version
That would be
That response how does he not know that the bad idea
But that response is not germane to the other version
More
That's totally fine
I'm pretty sure everybody is in the right thing
Why are you dressed up like
Even Alex kind of knows he's the bad guy in the story right
I think he has to kind of have that suspicion
Cuz he's preemptively defending himself
True to anybody complaining about him dressing up
In case there was a picture that
That might be that might actually be accurate
And also clubs are dark
Officer hat
Similar
That's true like it's not like 12:30 policeman
Kind of we're not
There are
But like it's not like a Klan Hood
Or something like that that's really distinct
Rarest Breyer hat
White Cami dress up like 30 clan members
Why can't I dress up like the Reconstruction I'm just saying
But like
You know what I'm saying it's not like the Nazis had a distinctive hat like many other groups has had over the over the years
Great hats
Medallions yeah but beyond that there wasn't like
You get what I'm saying of the Hat
It's not like a sombrero it's not like
A beanie
Anything like that
So what if he was wearing
That's just
You know I'm not an option you know that's not the captain's hat
You don't have some moral High Ground by getting in my face
I suggest you turn around and walk away
Run
So
The implication is that the guy ran away
Yeah
And now he's in
Insisting that they think they have some sort of moral High Ground
All right that's the part of the cultural revolution
Evolve at
So now I am one hundred percent convinced he was wearing enough
Surprised
Lightning bolts right here like he was not just wearing a hat
I mean it's possible the only assessment I can
Especially in the context of now
When we know he supports
Look
My assessment is
We can establish that
For sure I think Alex
She's probably a******
In the situation
And in order to make a
The point about political correctness or something or other
He's
He's got the colonel of the story and because it's not true
Keeps changing
Slightly
Over the period of November
Second to the
And because he thinks
It's so illustrative
How brainwashed and stupid the Liberals are
He has
Going back to the well
Not realizing that every time he goes back to it
He's reviewing more and more that it's
Not real
So congratulations on the first 48
You would watch the first 48 and he's
Multiple times cuz he's also the guy who's like
Totally convicted at the end of my lawyer is named
So anyway let's let's wrap this up
Halloween stories
From 2015
Wherein we discover that Alex dress
Most
I don't understand why these guys are so obsessed with thinking
They're the victim
Even as he's
Like f******
Insisting that he could beat the s*** out of
These people I mean it's just
Piece of his worldview like it is this we are the victims of all of these
Mastiff
Possible conspiracy
But you know also everyone else should shut the f****** about being
Right it's just it's pathetic
It's conservatives I'm almost to a T
Intrinsically trampoline over other people
It's the argument of being a
Intolerant about intolerance
It's just stupid
And that is where Alex Jones live
Yeah hayirli
You hear it if you if you listen to his show
As much as I did and all the stuff
We don't end up talking about on the episode
So much of it is just that boring Vic
Narrative
You know I would love to
Even
It's not even
Pieocracy
It's
Kennedy
Like it's just that they're not
That is true or not capable of reconciling reality
So they create this
This false
Like eight
The best way to put
Yeah
Kind of like
They think
That they're white
Population
Listen Subway
Supreme
I don't get it
It's almost as if they think that there's relative values
Queen
White supremacy
White nationalism
Soupremacy
He's wearing
It's like it's like they build
It like the thing that is amazing
Every single like they
Have to keep
Building all of this s*** on
Because if they admit
That one little thing doesn't
Legacy just B like
You know what I think
Chuchero guy is right
The entirety of this world you come from
Like every little thing I'm not sure every little
It's just
You take away one little part of it and the entire Foundation
Conceivably
Coming up with more and more elaborate ways to describe
Themselves
Because
I want to I want to play you a clip
Okay
Because I am
This is a
This is a clip
From the September 9th
Episode of this year 27
Physically pipe old for the episode that I did
With injuries
Unfortunately supper
Amex technical difficulties
Clips from that episode
Oh by the way I caused all of those I was jealous that I
Israelites that I put my energy into it
Doesn't make any sense
So in this in this clip the reason I want to play this is because I think that it's really illustrative Ava Baseline believe
White
And I think it is something that is
Valuable and important for us to
Just got even if we can't go through all of these
Spoiler alert
Montgomery on that episode
Yeah great bringing that s*** back up
Balls on the
These kids
But this clip starts with a
I'm talking about how Hillary Clinton is going around saying
Kids funding
For her organization
The Russia
Propaganda
Against Russia
That's Trump and his son
RNC funds to pay for their legal defense
Against
Then lying
About being
It's a hot mess
It starts
To just
Dealsea
All the new Shoemaker tomatoes
Memory
Man I should not care about the bombshell folks
We were right about the
We were right about the whole thing
Nope
Massive censorship identify mean the war is on
Tony Lyon
Nobody's being spot-on we got everything
Give three more examples
Drooping Trophy Hunter
Genesis race
We're done
I know where you are
Farewell
No
Beca Pitch Perfect
Love doing that s*** I didn't edit that you love those clips
If you could this entire show would be like check out this
It might be a might as well be I mean nothing
Because you're
So f****** dumb
Like
It's so crass and fake
Is not fake on his part
Slipped
He didn't mean to compare the relative value
On-air of blacks and whites
What you don't just want black people who are virtuous
How dare you pretend otherwise I called an audible and play this clip
At the end of this episode is because you don't need a high
You are a f******.
Knights
That's very good so anyway
And I water filters are on sale
So mad about Alex Jones
Also we have new buttons you can buy them at the store
Become a we have not figured out how to go to
Really no idea how anyone is going to get these buttons idea
Was that Ivan idea
Maybe
Still going to work for everybody
Okay it'll be non-monetary
I have an ID
We'll talk
Okay look for that
Teasing this
Talk about it I don't want to f****** do it with like a
Show me a figure this s*** out right now because everybody knows this is going to be the most
Interesting
Website.com
I'm just completely rejected whatever you can follow us
Go to iTunes
Riverview
And then
Other things that you
You can do absolutely you know
There's one guy who doesn't make that turn
Who just can't do it doesn't have the skill
He scares the kids to come to his door
He's probably the guy who gives you an ass
I bet he's the guy who takes out his teeth
Every time you walk or has a bowl of spaghetti and guts or something
Eyeballs
Nazi that what would you want to say to her
I would say
Gutentag
You b****
I don't know anymore I don't know anyone like that
Android
Alex