Alexandra Thurston color
Indeed we are Dan
What's your favorite pepper
My favorite pepper is I mean right now
Habanero is strong in the pepper Camp I also have a Thai pepper plant that I
Gather the other day and
I bought it from a guy
I thought you were wandering around Chicago
Subscribers most likely
Hotter than habanero peppers but
I would like to
Ghost Pepper or you know like a scorpion
Grocery store
Do you need to order them from the places that make them where they need to be special
Hookah shop in Chicago like I don't think there's a good Pepper or
A good hot sauce store like there was tears of joy
But there's nothing like that here as best I can tell but if there is
So for now it's a habanero
It's great sprute
It's
Not spicy enough but
What do you why do you ask
This show
And this show
Has you
Knowing a lot about Alex
I know a lot about you tell me about Alex
And peppers
I am not
That sucks that I brought over on the 4th of July
I brought over a ghost pepper sauce
That is much too hot for a lot of people
Thank you put it straight up on your hot dog absolutely crazy
Crazy like crazy
Not your best transition not your best
Took it up to the next level
You so much
Kyle you are now a technocrat
I'm a policy wonk don't get mad and tell your brother someone sodomites
I don't want
Jesus Christ appreciate it very much if you would like
Refrigerator
Now I did call myself out about something
First of all this is the second time we tried to record the show
But that's why this is going to be saying this over again while Jordans
Already heard me say that
I'm terrible at internet
I'm bad at it
.
I'm good at doing this show but that's about it
End up
F****** up I f****** and
Better
Which is my way of saying that I am sorry to people who have written emails and have not got back
Somewhere it got infected
The late
I recognize that there are some people who
I just lost their emails and I have not remember to get ahold of you and if you send another email
And chastise me for it
I will own up to that and I will write you back
It will be a far better way for dance
Caucus first
And then say nice stuff
Will be
Great at it but if you just feel s*** talking
Oh my God someone said something negative
Remarkable things I've
I got your almost like
Urine
And 7 months of doing this show like
The very limited negative
Crazy
But
Clear no one is like making me feel this way no one has been like
Hey you're a dick
You need to write back to people or anything like that this is just
My insecurities and buy recognition that I know I dropped the ball
I want to do better and better in the future because you all
Our listeners you deserve it
And you mean a lot to us and absolutely apologize that my own psychological impeachment
Get in the way of
Keeping up with that end of this
When we started this I have the same perception that I had of other podcast I've done in the past which is almost no one will listen
There'll be a few people reach out to me but it won't be that many
That were flooded with emails or anything like that
But it's more people sending messages that I've ever experienced messages of substance
It's not something where I can just sit there and be like haha good one
It's it's growing pains
And I know that I should have done this
Before this
Right considering we're this far into the show
But I'm going to try and do better and thank you for putting up with us
We never we never thought that more than fifteen or so people would ever actually listen to
Extension of us drinking at a bar yelling at each other
We didn't realize that aspect and we also didn't realize the aspect of like
I don't know what your feelings were entirely but like
I didn't realize that we would
Hit as much as we did like not terms of being
Actually interesting things that I didn't expect to find
We were just going to talk about a crazy person
I mean I was always hoping
But I didn't expect that the show would be anything more than entertainment
And then we go along when I call my God this means very weird
A level of circumstantial evidence
Never have considered existed
What a little bit would be the ones to find yourself crazy for assuming that at the beginning
Beginning everybody would have been like
Also I'm going to call myself out
If you have not received a button
I'm sure this is a part of my part to Austin
I am
Very good at sending those buttons
I am not good at making sure those button
Get to where they need to go to USPS no it's not it's it's that I am
Unlike some sort of
Virginia
One of those other podcast hazardous.
Don't say their names
If you have reached out about getting a button and you have not gotten it
Whether or not
That's
You know whether or not that Postal Service
Or all our fault
Please get in touch with doesn't know what's right at gmail.com
We're going to make everything right
Where do better
I don't know why but man I feel bad about it
I don't know
General insecurity only compounds
Subway
Jordan today
On the first attempt at doing an episode I already explained my process has been
Terms of like
I got sidetracked on a bunch of weird
Sort of dead ends
In terms of that investigation
I have some stuff from 2009 that we're going to get to
I ran out of
Time today
In terms of presenting an episode
Until I forced it
Mayday
Bunch of bad clips
About Tucker Carlson
But then we continue going and we were both like to nail that five probably is
In 2012 Tucker Carlson was very clear that he hated Alex Jones
Alex's Show in 2014
And now in present-day Alex Jones says this
100percentpure Veritas hole-in-one
I've never done
Do you have this transformation over time and it did it follows the path of Tucker's career in
The fact that in 2012
Obama I had not one relaxed again in 2014
He was president
They had two more years to deal with it that I quite might as well make
Might as well but as we went through the episode became clear that like all the stuff you saying really isn't all that
Nothing it's just us being able to be like haha look hippocrate wait wait wait
About Obama's has being negative and now that Trump is doing it there like
Like it's over and over and over
These people have
No bottom
The first time I've ever done this in the middle of the episode
F*** this
Yeah I don't think
We've met did something after
3 minutes like we stopped
Because Dad
The vibe was off
But I've never
Control level is that I'd like to have that conversation
Skills
Worst 17 episode
I agree in a way that is not
Decorative swords
Messages from people
Bit like something that we did on our I would say 3rd
4th episode
And we were saying we were going to keep doing it
Call
Oh no
This game is I don't know what we're going to listen to
You don't know what we're going to listen to
Video from The Alex Jones Channel
See what we feel about it if it Sparks anything like as if this was a goddamn ask
This clip is doing the monologue
The first time we ended up accidentally getting a David Knight
California fires
For all of you who have ever wanted us to do in roulette again
The only thing I see
The reason that I was scanning through the top my eyes
Is because it says socialist in the title and I know that that probably means I was going to scream bunch
Capm socialist
Well I don't have the whole Title Here
Because it cuts off of I'm playing this from my phone
ABBA Dancing Queen
And there's a picture
Alexandria
So I
And probably going to make Jordan very mad
Let's enjoy
Is the silent majority has a voice
So they have a new graphic that plays at the front
Just give a little contacts
Full title now that I've video is socialist beauty queen channels Miss South Carolina
Which if you were called Miss South Carolina
I thought it was it going to be before you said it was about a Alexandria
I was like I remember there being a like
Some pageant like Miss America where finally someone was like
F*** the patriarchy
Miss South Carolina was the one who stepped
Simard on stage was like
I believe education should
Wherewithal
Used random words in a sentence
Dodge the pageant winner
But the thoughts didn't connect clearly like
The coaching
I don't understand what I'm talking about but
I think this is going to make me sound
It was it was
I can tell already
Regardless of whose answer is here
They're going to
To try and connect her
Alligator attack
BoRics
You just said her name in the most boring he just said her name boring next clip
Next clip
Eclipse
Just the very next one
Infowars
Hershey's call Froggy
Location of airports
Ice office
Of the Border
We need to occupy every airport every
Border weenie dog
Dubai every ice officer
Goddamnit you're making
Border
You know what
Is a weird rationality put also a lot of a lot of folks on the last laugh
I do
Say
We don't want borders
I think I'm literally called for that in the path
I need a lot of people are much more comfortable saying it
Demilitarized zone
That implies violence
Take your time
Borders when the American Military was invading Mexico
It was a really good idea for them to make sure that there was a clear
So we didn't like
If we like we took Texas and they were like okay
Get out of here
And now we all regret that
We would prefer to give Tech
Just because that would be hilarious for all the texts
Citizen
Ben Alexander be Mexican propaganda
Do you think you turn nationalist for them definition
Navigate to Louisiana
Jordan
When would I go to work to do real quick
Jordan 24
My only platform is working
Back to Max
Billing of Texas
People say that I owned the 6th
I don't want to
You want
YouTube
I don't want it
You want
I Remember the Alamo as a colonial is b*******
For the Legacy that Alex Jones
So good
Let's get back
In order
To get
Regardless
The very dangerous
Saved
Call Londa
Patrol in America
Okay this is so boring
Open Safari
Terrifyingly boring
Unlike to stations in the country
A real
Like even though how many viewers
Thousand
Great
Not great for your Infowars Empire that's got hundreds of millions of listeners
Facebook ad we could probably get to 9000 Cheese's okay so I'm going to switch up I'll write down
Any more of that cuz it's like the start of a
Maybe Define
It's not David
I hope
Alex has a manic energy deposit in your life
Know that this was going to happen
Buy something scrolled through and I I'll give you two off
What is a complete mystery I don't know who's hosting
Why is Robert Mueller targeting Rodger Stone
Why is Mueller Target
Or
Bearded Alex
Sitting in the makeshift secondary Studio
He's probably drunk
22 titles
Grab bag
Why is he targeting Rochester
What the f*** Congress
That's the title
Or 3
This is also Alex
Alex Jones epic reaction I've no idea what the reaction is to
I can't tell unless I click on the video
I don't like that that's
Mystery box
And if there's anything I know from watching game shows on Nick at night when I was five
You don't choose the Arab Electric
Never choose mystery boxes even further with
Says or at least whoever is doing it says it's an epic reaction
Which only sets us up for disappointment
Alright
Now we know
Yeah but we don't need
Not really
So now we've got what the f*** what the f*** Congress
With Alex
Or
Mystery host
Why is Mueller Target
Rogers Towne Cinema
I delayed
In Rodger Stone
Just his
But he's flare his eventual fall
Probably smart enough to steer clear of Rodger Stone defending clips
Alright then we got to go with what the f*** Congress
Alex Jones obviously the one that conspiracy theories
Theorist
Whose brand is bullying
Alex Jones is going to hear this is going to say
Why is CNN out to get made after the shooting
Alex Jones YouTube channel posted a video
That was seen by 2.3 million subscribers
Alleging that these
Merely
Actors and not Parkland
Who had experience
Horrific thing anyone could possibly imagine what happened with Infowars
Because they've made
Cottage industry out of this what they do is they deny
That these events
Why are they still on face
Do you recently decided
Not to ban Infowars
I don't like this already agree with Alex
Yeah
And I'm fine with that but I don't I don't like being in this clip
9 minutes
Okay
Scroll ahead 24 and a half
Let's just
Really
I want to start in the middle and then we're just going to try and reverse-engineer it
Buses from 4 minutes
22nd
S'mores.
Dot-com
He's able
It does not matter when you would have breastplate we would have immediately her to plug
Immediately
She knows
To use condoms
She said
Restraint
I just opened themselves up to
No
Later
You know who I am your speciality
Channel videos
That violates our harassment policy
Which is not an act of aggression at all
That's like
Getting an email that says
You have violated the terms and conditions of working on book or whatever
The Parkland shooting
I mean granted we didn't want to talk about the immediate aftermath
Way to Rob
Even in the bad bike
David Hogg clearly wasn't at the school
Intentionally misrepresenting the timeline look like
The argument
Absolutely
No no
Meatballs
Cuz cuz they're there
Their rights
Cuz I'm the guy that won't sell out
Oh that's white
Scared
Control box
So you just the same me again
Read defense
No idea
And you know that
I'm talking to
Put a video up
You will not show it
Moschino four-wheelers
She goes Alex Jones
Posted this
I don't want to make a note
Crap on them
He's got four
On his own server
He's got his own
We aren't going to be able to take him down today
Stop it
People recorded
From Project
Their lawyers
Came to them with a
Legal
But instead
Dude
He's got 14 million people
You don't want to go up and
He claims
Which he usually does
Billions
Instead
This time he said
The accurate number
Which is at best
14 million
I'm already and when I said I agree with him
I should clarify that
I don't think you should be I think we've already gone over this a little tight on Facebook
Do the kicked off Facebook part
What is beginning of a clip from Facebook
Isn't this one title
What the f*** Congress
Yeah but it turns out when you expand the flip it says
What the f*** Congress trying to get Infowars kicked off Facebook
Stop
That's a rough one is Hayden in the capabilities of my cell phone
What's the roulette into AAA in like a
We don't have a through line
Epic react
No I don't hate it but I do want to know what
Luzon every game
Optimistic
Infowars hoax or Alex Jones
Claimed it was going to happen he claims her there was going to be a new Civil War
On July 4th
AAA example of an Infowars
A story that was
And Design
Deceive people
But the end of this I'll show you a bunch of articles for USA Today
Says we're in a civil war
USA Today
Northern southern fighting
I said they're calling the Civil War
Asymmetrical Warfare intimidation the physical attack
Overthrow the president
I know you are but what am I
It would all be over July 4th
Begin July 4th
And I've been proven right continue
These are the people that on record the Democrats hate America
Bill Maher said they want to kill the economy
Ellen misrepresent you will also raise our hands
Overthrow Trump
Civil War
Let's eat
Imma stop right now
Start up plastic Alex Jones
Anything of substance sources
Never
Interrupted
That's amazing cuz I took the over under for how long he makes it before the 1st Plaza
Distracted him
Comedy
What's the name of the show reliable sources with Brian stelter
It's not like he's surprised by that he's like all I got a B for this
I got a B
Play Kabhi going to trucking
Set up for a bit
Call reliable source
Talk about Vegas odds
It was sparked by yes
Oh yeah you are
2 seconds
You know the big enchilada
The eyes Pocono
Who is Becca
Never
He never shows me
English Civil War
He doesn't show a video
He doesn't
Bluebird bluebird
Edwardsport Indiana
Do you and our article show you every time we make as a link
But notice
The Civil War would kill everybody
Shooting War
Demarcation line of them
Accelerate
This is such b******* because we're doing Jade Helm already over again
Like his his Elmwood going to be a takeover of saints
Always
Stirred up
The fear
That is
Parallel to and
A natural takeover
You can't pin me on saying that that's what this is what's going to happen
Heavily implied
Didn't say very much that said about the Civil War, and then
Videos
Play the Clippers
He did
Yeah he almost certainly did
What kind of idiot with a joke called reliable sources
Wouldn't
But what is it like we have unlimited time
In terms of our show
We can take a quick and we can listen to XM and talk about it for 10 minutes
Squishy to
Sponsors have commercials that got to go to they've got
Just do you have to have to if you can't do your whole show on Alex
So if they do a little segment on him obviously they're not going to play all the clips
Okay
We do have unlimited
Remember
Remember the Megyn Kelly interview when Alex was so terrified
What if
Is there a way for us
To do that can we find it
What network is that on Megyn Kelly
Who's on NBC I don't know I don't think anybody
Anybody anybody
But also I think it'll probably be like real Sirius Disclosure laws
In place like I think that
Wait I think you'll probably be a crime for the material disposal at least to write for SNL there on a PC
What is more high-profile
Some random rider for SNL walk
Recording for like 6 hours I get
One of those rare moments
That's where Alex like really showed ass
And that's why it would be interesting to know exactly what I want the whole thing
Show me the back to me I think we should for a minute let's be happy
So they went oh my God he's on.
Full page ads
Civil War
Rob Reiner
What a leader of the last forever.
Are people referred Carl Reiner Bankhead
Uber driver throw people out all the rest
Director that you can argue
Stop Infowars
Abstract
You know these companies say they're working hard everyday
Stop the spread
Unreliable
One day this week I was at a press event
YouTube All About That
And the next day
Was it a Facebook event
Yeah simp
How can Facebook
Serious about fighting missing
Information
I'm still at Infowars have a page with
Nearly 1 million followers
Okay posit
Okay that's a problem
Million followers
Speak now your argument is moot
Alright
Maybe we don't want Facebook to take off
Being forward page
On Facebook to take off 14 Infowars page
I still think I still think that it's the
I think it's the responsibility of the viewer I still think that
Because I think it's going to be impossible whatever guidelines
Could help with this whatever rules could help
Are going to
Be stymied by just implementation logistic
Like it's almost impossible the most narrowest and
Is what you're saying
Directly parallel to
It's so simple
It's really really simple I feel like I again
The cops
Institution
Except there should have been no no
They weren't around when it was written but also that I think that the problem was that
With your rule
It sounds
Good
It comes down to interpretation
Does any way too much like how do you actually enforce that sort of rule
Might not sound like Nazis to all grab a ton of girdles
Opaganda remove
Proper noun
If you're fitting in different proper nouns you just eternally same adjectives
You're crazy you're crazy
You're out
Look
On principle I agree with you I would love it that happen
Abused in a negative way I get it but I'm even think abused I think just the just the structural inability to deal with
The millions of posts that happen
Across
15 Channel
Who knows how many pages other outlets have like how many pages Breitbart has
You're going to run into trouble it's not going to work
It's not going to work but on the other hand
Your argument for people should be responsible for their own media consumption clearly failed
Because people are not responsible for it and they don't do a good job about it
Human beings are shity
Or at least an exploit
Pacific City Parts in order to further their own cause
I would say an almost unsolvable problem unless we walk away
Walkaway
Madlib girdles social media
And I could
Exploit
Various
Bruno Hot Topic
Pics of the day
And maybe
Retweets
Some stuff like that
But I don't want to be
I don't want to be a part of
I don't want to possibly get there
Social media
It's so dangerous
To me it's so weird
That like I restrain myself from out of
The fear that I might be
Someone somewhere
We should all walk away
She becomes how does anything exist without social media nowadays
Consider this
Get rid of tags
Interesting
Back to Mexico
From here on out that's my that I got two solutions
No no
Madlib madlib media blackout in Texas
Epic reaction
Was the
Start it over
That might have been what they were teasing
Whatever you end up doing
Just another weird hateful screed about Brian shelter
Hey just because
I went to the one that Trio of options that I wanted to go to now huh the service let's listen to a little bit of this
About Rodger Stone
Bulshit is Rodger
Yes
Loading slow but
God dammit
The freezer
Of an epoch
Clash ladies and gentlemen
Red
The indictment laid out
By Mister Rosen Stein
To be remind
As I was
Was forced to remind
Chris Cuomo
The other night
On CNN
Isn't
Proven
Accusation by the government
An Undisputed fact
I have purchased are already
This is him
Vikram the traffic
This is
This is why you don't buy the mystery box I can't believe it the title of the clip is why Robert Mueller is tar
Marketing Rodger Stone and stone in a gray white
Infowars green screen
You can say
Guccifer 2.0 is a Russia
Should I say
How to say it
That does not make it a fact
Certified in a court know but there are a lot of other things but do make it affect
Infowars graphic
Rudy Giuliani Rodger Stone on Infowars
What
I would believe
I feel like I got to go back
Yeah you're right you're right
And there you have former mayor Rudy
Giuliani
I don't think there's any way that Rodger Stone would sit there with a
Straight face and say this is
Most effective lawyers
She would laugh about it and be like look at Rudy saying good things about me my friend
The pantheon
Hook brings about the end times
I don't know my Norwegian
Religious
Okay well I will tell you the red-faced kickoff.
Here's a better question
To respond to that with
White
Wouldn't he though he's Rogers
This is a man
Who f****** balls to the walls
Because I think that
He would look like a Rube if he was pretending it was actually Rudy Giuliani when it wasn't
You would look like a Rube for believing that he actually believes
I'm so confused
I'm so confused it's f****** good at what he does I'm so confused about this for a number of reasons the first
But I'm willing to entertainment
The second thing is that like
Did Giuliani for years because of his 911
Even in like in 2009
They play a commercial on every episode
Multiple times
9-11 documentary bermas might have made or sorry
With the clip of Rudy Giuliani saying
If you're not with us
You're with the terrorist commercial
Doctor documentary commercial now
I'm so confused but we haven't we haven't watch the show
Maybe he's explicated this in the past
Like maybe this is something that is your jokes from way back
I kind of think it's Frank
Frank Caliendo
Gavin McInnes trained Yoda suppression Act
Rich Little does 1001 voices
What are those
I can't. I just can't believe that Rudy Giuliani recorded a voice-over where he says
I'm the former mayor
The greatest mayor of New York
I believe that
100%
You're listening to Rodger Stone on Infowars
It would be easy enough
Get though you could just get that through a voice message
It's not like he has to come into studio and be like
Alright
Sibilance
Zero effort
That f****** like
Let's juice this
It was actually Rodger
Just don't doing the boyfriend
What if it turns out he's a good impressionist
Is a brilliant
All of these voices
Alex Jones
No he
Makeup can do that
I think I think it's possible he's Eddie Murphy in the club
I would believe that
Possibly Owen Shroyer
Alex no absolutely not
I don't know whatever
This is probably the least important
If there's anything that we can take from this clip
Is that right
Notify
And he's
Really trying to do cuz he's not doing damage control for his real life
He's doing damage control for his Infowars
Like he's going through all this he knows what he's saying is
He knows that when he was in that
Batman
Because again
That indictment
Fantasy
Those those people are in Aldo Nova
Never coming to Justice
If there is
There's no chance of them actually facing the consequences
Further action bright the point of that
Is
To make sure everybody knows
There was an American
Who acted as an intermediary with Lee Stranahan to came up
About Rodger Stone
Just because Rodger Stone foolishly leaked
His own messages
MMA word to word the message
Just that were in that indictments
I do think that I do think that is
A message
On some on some leather
Indian
You're right you're right every there is no there's no way this is ever going to actually go to court unless they try them in a
Absentia
Going to happen
But at the same time Rogersville thing about like they can just say whatever they wanted don't prove it
A lot of facts very specific information
Like if you
Now
Since you're a journalist
Apparently on Infowars
Now it is your job
To take the information in that indictment the address
Is the server
One point
Employee relationship
That are laid out
All that
You can find
And a Fulton
Then
You get to critique
The information given
Let's find out if you find the fault
The president
Defense and
An offense
And calling out
The criminality
Of James
Call me
Robert Mueller and the other
Deep state
Who operate without any kind of
Whatsoever
Answering only to the Twitter
Rosenstein
Mr. Rosenstein
Mine is the man
Intentional
That was
To spy on the Trump campaign
Alright
I'm wondering
Right now
If he is address
Any of the real real accusations against him right so far no he's only said
The only thing that he's actually said Trump in Helsinki talking about the server the only thing the only thing he said is that
Guccifer 2.0
You can't prove is a Russian
Agent
That absolutely been proved it
Like
Scientifically
Using
Shirt not in the court of law but the preponderance of evidence is certainly public now
Wasn't even it wasn't even a preponderance of
Evans it was actually really really well hidden until the guy who is running
Didn't log into the VPN
And all the sudden now we have a direct
121 connect
And that incontrovertible
Right
Servers
No I give
And I would never fun
Like
This is a surprising thing for me to say
I think Rodger Stone
Oh
You don't say
That
Mister Rosen
Who's dying
Be prosecuted
This is just about
Beginning
Also just
They weren't spying
Outer indictment
Supposed is he stupid
Yeah but he's he's read the writing on the wall
Still smells to me like Saving Face
Seem like someone who's scared
And I think the reason again
That I keep saying
I think
Cut it.
Let's see if he's
Auburn Epic
Clash
Ladies and gentlemen
But anyway
The indict
Laid out
Last week by mr. Rose
Remind
Did as I was forced to remind
Chris Cuomo
The other night
On CNN
And indict
Isn't
By the government
It is not
An Undisputed fact
Generally it requires
To bring the indictment the first Warren
We already heard that a second ago cuz it's from the sizzle reel that they put before
Rudy Giuliani real or fake dropping in
You can say
Guccifer 2.0 is a Russian asset
As many as you want to say it
Certified in a port
Questions
I feel like that's not a denial.
As a witness
The former
Counterintelligence ITF
To prove definitively
Guccifer 2.0
Is indisputable a Russian
Exactly
It is amazing.
Screamin Mimi's the Box
Sis.
Daily Beast
And the other
Garbage media such as
That you can't cuz I'm playing answer my phone you don't see the video
Single close
Speaking directly to a wrestling promo
Slightly more details unless I'm going to kick your ass at the Coliseum
I don't think we're going to get much out of this
Here's the thing
What has never hosted his own show
Rodger Stone pick this up
Radio if the stones
What is yoke of the stone Zone
Refuse
No I'm no I know
Used to believe I know a guy who is kind of like a co-host
Of his show
I don't want to ask him about it but I'm worried because he was his co-host I don't
Edit music
This comedian named Travis Irvine
And who came to Chicago couple times I did some shows
Really cool dude
It was really fun to hang out with you run for like a libertarian
The office
In the past
So I'm thinking I did
Too crazy about that
Didn't suss out any
You might be friends with
Rodger Stone
We hang out
But then like when I was looking through Rogers like
Shows that he's Donna like
What the
Wait time is it on again what the f***
Do you Donuts on Rogers
It might be a little late
I want to give out information now I would like to pretend this didn't happen and go back to my
Ninja Turtles Ninja Turtles
But it's super weird like that that sort of
I think that's the closest
I have to Alex other than like
You know a couple of people who contacted me with like I know him or he has met him
But like the someone
Someone who has done
Multiple radio shows
With Rodger Stone
Who I have hung out drinking with and like
I have his number for knowledge
This is what you were always meant to do
Okay
Most alt right
Call Travis
Most all right
But and right
Male pundits
I guarantee at least
I will posit you
That Rodger Stone
Has at least done a few Open my
Oh yeah
They're all veiled chameleon
They just they're just all comedy and they realize that the right-wing doesn't understand,
So they try
Whether or not
Rodger has done open
I want
To say that I don't
Travis
The failed
Comedia very good at I'm not talking about you
Please dude in the world
Like they're all terrible stand-up who have pivoted into something else
We're like we don't have any talent to pull myself out I mean failed stand-up
Bye
Stand-up I reached the point where I felt
This is about as good as I can do and then I also didn't enjoy it anymore.
I reach that point three years ago and I'm still just trying to make get good mob work though
I watched you out at the Zanies
He's when I came out
You hosting
I saw frustration
In your face I saw
Almost I don't want that I saw a touch of I don't want to do this
It was still you do your job and being funny you're being funny and keeping the show
Running along and all that
And I couldn't do that
I couldn't do that anymore
There's no there's no
Even in my greatest days I don't think I could have done
United
I'm a driver man I'm going to get it done
I'm not a good host I have a I have a responsibility
As a paper fessional
I respect that
I think you do a great job
Let's go to this next question I don't know what it is
So this is what I scroll down a little bit the only thing I know is that
On my phone it says proud boy Rufio
Also
Did you know that
The guy who played Rufio
Was also The Voice
The Last Airbender
He's the voice of Zuko that's the same guy did you know that that was awesome also
Also in Legend of Korra
The trivia I was going to go with
Who is the grandson of General iroh
Do you know idea The Last Airbender
Is it the guy who played Rufio
But he was also in a Christian extreme
Sports movie called
Extreme days
What is it
Terrible but me and my buddy saw it in the theaters yet we thought it
You're like no boarding and what have you know but it was
Who is Derek's
Stream days
Extreme love of God
Parable
But me and my buddies
Nikki gift I believe was there
My my old Columbia Missouri buddies worth
And we all lost our
F****** s***
There was crazy and the movies terrible one of our friends through and in
Tire large Mountain Dew with the screen like we were out of control but
Weird Christian undertone to it
I freaked out because they had a
Car that they called their Joy Yoda
Is a Toyota but it was still full of God's joy
I actually love
Pam to the back bumper and I had made it a joy odense Toyota put that on a
It was like
Yeah alright you guys
Someone in set design did half-an-hour at work
I realize that now but it's times like crazy
I've never
Never
Consider that portmanteau
Emgeneral
Two things one
Toyotas don't bring people
I am not a very creative person
5-minute talk about various things that the guy who played Rufio did
Everybody's leaving who have not seen avatar The Last Airbender
Get on it
Completely skipped over the other part of it that he's a proud boy
Rufio is the proud boy
Somebody's been on that name I'm sitting
I'm taking from we're not saying that there is a family
That was born in the 90s
Born in the early 80s
And then decided when we have a kid
What else can we call it but Rufio
It's not his given name
I'm certain I'd let's find out
Anyway probably suck let's see what have
Cowboys
I've been hit with
Clubs and stuff on my hands and so
You know
Going full power obviously in defense is sometimes
Makes you vulnerable but
You know I did the best I could and
The governor
It's just awesome
So neither of these guys have ever been
So
Rufio Rufio
Damn man which I assume
Stickman
Bluefin was it blinking and start of Damon Wayans not David Alan Grier
Debatable
David Alan Grier
Supporting actor
Why he didn't get a Best Supporting Actor nominee I will never understand
That's what I say
So
Flights
Sidebar
Have you ever seen cheap seats
The brothers mst3k
So they did one episode
With the host
Competition
Because you're so much energy
Who do not have been there at
One of my favorite things
Early Loveline
I would hate to revisit a lot of it
So listening to those episodes when David Alan Grier would come in
Like
It was revolutionary
This person is crazy
Add just ripping his ass off
But like
Somehow
Underrated
If you actually listen to it
Layover Ray
It's bananas
That is a
Set an alarm for
Don't know
He's been with Delta Burke underrated
April left also
It's banana
Feel like I might just get some rest and love him
With the reason that I pause this
As
Either we got off on a tag thing
As you do
We have
Describe here and Alex Jones
Trying to relay like a governor
Search is Over
Swoll 20 something year old dude
Didn't like he's
Dislike
Like casual as f*** like at a bar like he's got his arm on Alex's table if I get
Posture of like I don't give a f*** the s*** I know this is what you want me to
You have Alex looking over at him
Like almost an admiration
Exactly how I feel like
Only in the sizzle reel here
Again before we get to but I hope it's another Rudy Giuliani drop
Oh yeah
Yeah yeah you know everything happen naturally inorganic be there
Going to hit you
Yep there you go
The sunglasses
The stuff
Hold on
I just watched that video
That he played it was
Rufio panman
Punching a dude
Followed through there was another woman
Maybe four feet from the person he just punched
And he doesn't punch her
I don't I don't know how
You don't also punch her
Inertia
I'm going to go with a lot of different reasons
First and foremost
The biggest problem here
Is Alex
Delighted
Buy the idea that
He should have hit her
Wants to hit a woman
You get rid of socialism in women
You smack him down
That's just
History Bell it's only watch the first
3 minutes of
Smack My b**** Up Video is that correct
Didn't get to the reveal nailed it
Country meats
Trying to get
The female you know and she wasn't wearing a mask so that was
Instantly my
My thought was the case she's not an immediate threat
Gentleman if she decides to be aggressive with me
And then my folks became on grabbing that baton that went to the ground and in complicating that weapon
Infowars logo
So
His
His basic point
He was doing
A situational analysis
Wilt in the middle of a punch
But he was like he was
Junior in Sherlock you know what time slow down bullet time when you're out there fighting
I am going to
Program confiscate button
Action
To the knee
His Livery swollen crab
Watch out there's a lady
So stupid
Wow
Problem
I don't think either of them
Really
Unhappy with the
Idea of punching
There is
Slightly different like let's say she was wearing mask
How many women has Alex
I know that
Made a bunch of abortions
They didn't want
I don't know if that's the equivalent of hitting but I know it's not great maybe
I don't know
I don't like how he said my baby right there
The proud boys
If you just joined us going out in
Forgot
Walking these guys out so maybe during the break and tell the crew to find those I've seen him
38 you just replay the exact same video of him
They're in and out it doesn't appear it it's not it's not Africa
Like this is not it does not appear to be a crowded melee it's just he's punching
Here is I don't know the circumstances of it so I can't comment on that
Pain
Alright
First thought
That we hear from the the best of clipper the sizzle reel is him
Dang
I don't know how you didn't
Cuz I would have given that woman
That makes me sick as hell
Next.
We saw them hitting women and children
That's an interesting
Yeah that stuff
That's tough.
I would say I would even go so far as to
To say
That means he likes hitting women it's it's
Only because we know that his narratives aren't true
Rolex is doing
Is doing
Isn't isn't real
Computer that justifies
Is the behavior like Rufio
Just like so many gun people
He he he
Fantasy about Justified
You're a good man with a pan
To shoot somebody or hit them with a pan but he needs to do it
Self-defense
So it's just a
So you say you want to hear more about bayspan man or do you want to move on
We got you don't want you know what this week
Linda crying
The idea of hitting with
That's all you're really going to get out of it
Jesus
Spin the wheel
Infowars graphic
Around around
The first sin Co-op
Baby 9 and we have on the
Align with us
Do I get him on again in light
Of the
Skip ahead
David Davis so boring
Fit BMX
Well we have that my Monday on the phone
Call David
But okay
Be so good to did this title is amazing
Ammon Bundy colon
Take Scholars and tells hope. Denies just
They're taking callers Ammon Bundy
His buddy
What do you mean the doj denies dresses
Well I don't think
The Bundys
They said
Shut up
Publix
Good for
People like the hammer
Boring
Increasingly is that
Ignore
The most
Like what
They keep people in
Several
That's true
About
Hold on so many people on Rikers Island
You can talk to
People on Rikers Island no no
Which is I guess I know probably slang that mean
No that means
Greg Weidman
Things they wouldn't allowed you on here
Alright alright
It's giving me like 30 more 30 seconds
Situation
How they came after
Is marijuana
Activist
Cool in jail
Without fail
Saying that was part
Of the New Jersey
His bail
Yeah
I'm fine with that he's not going to make that argument
They always
But every time we agree with them
They always make an argument
That they don't realize they're making
Veirs f******
It's like that it's like there's there so hard right that go to the other side
Truth in that
That's early Act
A lot of people
I believe that the further you go right the closer you get
The farthest end of the last
Interesting I don't know if that's true but I do know that
Based on the way the propaganda works
Even if you are a spiritual
With people on the hard life when you're on the hard right
You're still going to be like no I'm not
Are you still going to like
Kind towards
Something closer yet
I thought
Now that was never going to happen
Very excited
Everyone dies
Everyone dies it's the worst thing in the world
Okay alright
I'm very
To deceive this clip
I don't know what this is going to be about about Sacha Baron Cohen
Who is now really recent that
A couple days
I can scroll through that far back on my phone
You search Alex Jones you get the Great
I'm only looking in his actual Channel
Searching you're just going to the channel and then slide okay
No I only published
Okay
He doesn't know in the last week or so Sacha Baron Cohen
Put out his new documentary
Which we are America who is America a commercial for it came out
Everyone who got stuck
I'm parked by it came out in droves being like hey
I got IO they trick me into saying things I didn't mean to say
Bernie Sanders and interviews with him
Watch that I watched
The clips that
Is it soon as I can
Check this order thing is very hilarious
I don't I don't
Bernie Sanders got tricked by
Someone who was dumb
Evan Bernie was very polite
I tried to talk to him
Marysville
With people like our friend
#trash dick shout out to people like Trent Lott
People like
Alex Jones's dear friend Larry Pratt right citizens for gun
Why didn't Sacha Baron Cohen
Sacha Baron Cohen
I think Larry Nichols
That would have been the one not on their radar.
You guys don't even know
I don't even take in the analysis
Progressive media
People like Sam's
Cedar yeah
YouTube channels that have gone over it
How important
Larry Pratt
In terms of that
He's gone organization
Was one of the big major
Your forces bit pushed
The NRA so hard right like they were very instrumental
I'm pushing them
To be less than 2
Absolutely
In 2009 when we
Check in with Alex Jones
He hates the NRA
Because they are too wishy-washy
Possibly okay with you
They hadn't even
Metaphorically
So like
I love all this
See what Alex Jones at
Stupid
Sacha Baron Cohen
Goodbye
Bad news baby
The Onion
King of fake news
Oh no
What the title of this video is better than I could have possibly
So when I clicked on it all I saw was mus
Sacha Baron Cohen
I like Alex Jones
The whole title
Musty
Sacha Baron Cohen stocks Alex Jones
We're going to have to wear this
Late night comedy shows
Like Homeland
Notre Dame
Sacha Baron yeah yeah yeah
Infowars
Think about it
They put it out like this
Call for
Sizzle
Bad now that was a good
Make Ready line. Troops beyond their energy field
Strike Back
Cool
Are you taking the Republic back
Well
I suspected this six months ago but now we've
Baron Cohen
Emails right now
Infowars and wanting in the building
No s*** policy where I basically don't talk to me Street Media anymore
Divided America
They targeted him with the wrong character
Yeah
For sure cuz in least from what I've seen
From Israel
Lures people with
The
Disabled
Not disabled veteran guy
Who
Yeah
You go in
To Alex
With
I think that means that they went with the
The veteran
Probably
If they went with the Israel guy I think he probably would have been like are you kidding me hello
Contrarian
I'm just saying
You know what with the show
I'm going to pass
Approached
Here's my prediction I don't know if this is
I would predict
They even did reach out to him
He's not just trying to have Stolen Valor of
Please excuse possibility conversation
But if not
With that Patriot
Heartless
I don't give a
If they had
Approached him with
Something that stroked his vanity
Like the character who is like
You're getting a reward
We're getting an award for friends of his.
It was friends of Israel that would have given him so much leave
Skeptical
But he would have gotten over that pretty quick
Yeah he would have done a little bit of digging
Not been able to figure it out
Flash
Gmail
I said don't call her
Sacha Baron Cohen
SPC
You know
Like Homeland
From the opposition movement is not a common
They put it out like the things they're saying
And then today
Call Ford
Boarding pass more into Sacha Baron Cohen
Here is the problem structurally with
As opposed
The other clubs
So far
Literally two minutes into this clip
GDP
30 seconds of the sizzle reel
Seconds of the first
Minute
From a production
You can't just be like
I need to know more about his feelings
How long is Bigfoot
The clip of rattling
No I'm just asking
Skip ahead 2 minutes
7 ish 7 ish minutes
Right here we are coming in
What's 53
Homeland
Do you have
Storyline
Great article from 2015
Because
Weird
Watch this
Scrap
Republican voters also watch
Muse band
Not boring snack joke
This is the key
Myself
Bobby's Facebook
Bale
Want to know more about his feelings
About
Borat
That's all I want
That's all I wanted out of that clip
Yeah I like disappointing
I bet he didn't say much in that 26 minutes
He probably said some stuff about like you know what I was the big fish
Islip Cinemas
Bale
It's me that these guys just
Don't understand what the
Differences
Lego
Like if you get tricked
If nothing
How can you compare it to all of these Republicans
Going on the show and being like
Phuc yea let's arm children I don't give a s***
There there
Blue pit Joy is enough to indict them
Because I haven't watched
The entire shall I can only judge
The contacts
Clues I glean from that
Very clearly
Were these people were reading teleprompter
Conservative Ding Dongs we're reading a teleprompter
It's very clear they're doing a cold read
No s*** yes
I haven't I haven't seen any of it I'm just again
I'm out the trailer of it is a script
You can you can tell
It's a song
Did like
These people like Dana rohrabacher walls
Cold reading
Off of like
Well the
Kinderguardians program allows children to be able to protect themselves
Okay they're doing like a commercial
Okay it's clear that they are not seeing their own word right
I
Take issue with little league bomber
Tricked ya no no
It's worse than just getting tricked
Because if you are
Person
And you're reading a teleprompter
What is this I don't think
You're crazy
Here's what I'm about to say
These are stupid vapid people who will read whatever is put in front of them
So long as it like if you if you put in front of them like
I think we should
Give Healthcare to people they would like anything less than that
They're dumb
It just seems like there
Really dumb
The really that alright
Let's do one more
I know I know
Find trying to find one but
The issue for me now comes down
How did the fact that like
Titles are
Good
I can only see a few words of
The title
And I got to find
Alright
We got a we got a dismount on this
What are we got
The sound mix
Because Owen is much lower than the video that they're playing
Oh yeah
Based on
Audio
The video of it
Speeches
Is weird
The flipping
Zombie horde of ants
Trump protesters roasted
Great movie title
He's recording in like a kitchen
With no like
There is no video of him the video is over
I think he's
Just doing this like a maybe
Bathroom alright
Good question
Rigged
Ghetto
Good on
Attempted to
Good save
Reminder said correctly his defensive Russia
Well because
Scott realized how
That he's dumb because that's like that's what
Concretely provable is work done
B r o
Forensically
Approval in terms of
Intelligence
Is available
Art that they were successful
So
Did him being like Oh I'm going to roast you but
You should just say
No
Always giving them your info
No category clean up
I just like
It's this sound is so terrible
Mitigare
Maybe
After
A big night watching this clip
Commentary for it
That was 30 seconds old is Johnny hordes of anti Trump protesters wrote
I don't hear any roasting
Alright
And it's not like
There is not the precedent set
Just going to butt in with stuff he's going to butter with jelly
Really really really left-wing guy is jealous
Why would you
Why in God's name would you be like the FBI
Has been garbage for 1000
80s
Amazing
How weird it is for the left now to like rely on
High-top black male Martin Luther King
Junior as though it's some sort of bulwark against
Authoritarianism
BFDI is on the side of authoritarianism
I would say
Mike my defense today
I think
Is that I also do not
But I
And I hope
Live no reason
Believer
My romantic idealism coming out
Zoe's
Chapters in our history
You're talkin about
60 years ago
Years ago
During the Iraq War whenever Bob Mohler him
Self
Katie
And convincing people that good idea
Let's see what
Okay also
It's amazing to me
That Owen Shroyer hasn't figured out Alex's
District of
Don't let the full clip play or started again terrible idea
All of those things are legitimately reasonable
We're not going to listen to this whole thing but I
I'm f****** putting the clock on when Owens
So there you go
Terrible
Until he just
Listen to
Is there sounding horn
We will live
George Soros zombie horde
Alive ask George Soros
Peaches letting this play
Great great
We are 2 minutes and 40 seconds into this
This is a man asleep at the wheel
This is a drunk
Pilot who is Nat
What are what
I would love it I would love it
Owen Shroyer
And he was like
We just going along with this
If you were espousing
Yeah
I realize you're probably right
Right around 30 year old young
Young Buck
Like why don't you show your Bona fides get in there
You know instead of like
We're 2 minutes and 45 seconds
A minute
Silence
The rest of it has been
Nothing
When he comes in here
And I should be
Hydraclear
40 minutes
Honestly we're done with this ruler
Read to me
I understand the idea of letting
Sing someone
Speak their piece
Before you
Call Manon
Call VSCO Broadcasting
It's also just being courteous
Intellectually honest
Sitting there waiting for somebody
But you still interrupting
Like earlier with dumb b*******
Just don't have any
That's the thing that I
I wonder about
Is when people are listening to Orange
Which state
Net
3000 battery
If I had if I had all the data
Legacies
Turned it off after 40 seconds
His situation here though
He's letting the full clip
Play no
He's letting
Enough of the clip play
A reasonable
And then he's just
Denying reality
Like Drew
No that guy is
Put together
Like even if you disagree
Yeah that's your business but
So he's just he's just
Creating this alternate reality
Alex does that
Doesn't
Let the whole clip
Play doesn't let people make
That is coach
I'm going to let you come
Complete your thoughts
And then I'm going to live
Alex abuses
The Source material
He's much more of a believer
Yeah I think this is him
Phoniness
Jaden Hardy
Man I'll tell you what I own
I knows it
I've made a Cottage Inn
History out of hate
Infowars
Yeah it's kind of my thing
Yeah
Disappointed
We've listened to a lot of like bad video
But this one to me is like you guys weren't Eve
He's more of a bully
I don't know why you
Forever in
Not talking over
Yeah I don't
First and I don't
By Alex
It would allow this
To go out on
Reviews or whatever and I'm sure there's a super male vitality
The end of it
But like
Also I should tell you this
Alex
Marcon
Super male vitality
Atlantic in 2015
Kudzu Alex
Also super female vitality
Holyshit
Pay some money probably for
I don't know you maybe have to get
Trademark lawyer
Product I don't know
I just thought it was funny I was going through trademarks
Like most of his
Trademarks
Cares about that one
There's one
So I found this new trademark
From fries
I don't know what the
This is going to be okay I can't
Find it
But it was
Was just filed
A month-and-a-half
Firepower radio
Okay he filed a trademark
Look for Firepower radio
Weird
I don't know what that's going to be
But
You look over it and see
Just like
I saw that
Boilerplate
Yeah
What's Firepower
Also
That sort of thing
Is so crazy to
Because it reduces the idea of like you're able to like
Preemptive
Movie trademark
Yeah doing
Yeah why
You not at all
Take care of
425 Supply
Oh well okay
Well that's what a lot of witches
Infowars survival which is also not
It's like the patent trolls try to do try to take down pod
Cast
People registering domains that they think
Might be
Like I imagine you should be able to
Not should be
Be able to
I imagine if you were smart
Wood trademark
A lot of s*** nearby nobody
You
Did not
Trademark
Super male Vitality I'm looking up let me tell you something
Go to fill your hand, because it's about to go wild
I looked up all of the
Free Speech Systems LLC all of their trademarks
They have Infowars that
Current prison
Planet prison
Planet.com
Prison Planet
Broadcast
The Alex Jones Show
The real red pill
Heykorean
One of his new
Supplements for life
Tragic
Stupid
There's a number of these that are
AR
Call current
And then there's one
That are like
Zelda fan
Super male Vitality lap
No cuz I need to go
He probably just
Think anybody would pay attention doesn't want to waste his money on it
Here's the last thing I want to bring up
Before we close the show
Alex also
Got a trademark
For something called honor roll
I don't know what that means at all
I don't either
Kid honor roll
Kid maybe I don't leave the word
Words that we are going to look out for in the
Honor roll
Firepower radio
Those two things
AR
We're going to keep our eyes on that
And they are real thing okay
What would happen
If we did get the trademark for a Superman visor
Just something we can do
I don't think so
I think it would be like
Exposed
Grandfathered
Existing product or whatever
What is it would be in the paper being abusive
I feel I feel like it
First of all
Besties
But event
Superman
It's open
Nothing
So Jordan we've come to the end of this
Infowars roulette
I think
Better than we could have
I think when we started
We thought it would be
Well we're going to listen
I'm something boring for
And I would say that the more fun things
Is you and I being able to organically respond
Similarly
I love this
Intermittently in the
But I think
Who you want to submit
What we learned
Yeah
I Come Away with only one thing
What basketball
Well if you say first of all that means you didn't come away with only $0.01
Did Rudy Giuliani
To do that bumper
He did not going to plague me it is nightmare
More Rodger Stone episodes in order to make sure that call Rudy
Second thing I come
Is
I own before this
I don't know a lot of
The proud boys
I'd only known about bass
Stickman
Yeah I'm so
Hearing about Rufio panman
Fantastic
So excited
About the idea
You just have
8 word ends in a noun and two-man whatever you whatever you have hit
You are just Blankman
When it was only
Basic man and
Rufio
Once we got to New Jersey
Kauai
That's three that's a pattern
Coincidence
Batman
Francois's is a French name by doing
What do you what are you doing here baguette man that's how I should say
What do you think about
Should have been short pants
EBay even when he wears capris they go far too long legs are too short to box with God
Alrighty then if you wanted
Not updated that website
The longtime
Can busy
Like either my thoughts are
Yeah exactly
Like I'm either not putting forth an argument that you can't read somewhere else blood blood blood
Argument that people would look at
Nothing
A lot of my rating
Built up in
Long-term
Effort
There's no payoff
For that right now but everyone so much
Yahoo still
Enjoy the show Absolutely
Roulette but
I brought you
Well if you want
Download Lottery
People that we still exist in advertising
Anyways
I think we all know everybody
Who is listening to the show
Knows that there's
Only one
Who could make this garbage
Go f*** yourself David Knight
Actually
Need to worry about you
I know that that was one of the worst
Chapters
Because I want to say this
For the first time ever
Go fuc yourself
Go fuc yourself Owen Shroyer ship in a bottle man
Alex