Policy wonk
Everybody didn't hear
Hi I'm Jordan
Hey how's it going buddy
Just wanted to
To give you a little bit of taking this Friday
Off from an episode but we will be back on Monday so much again handled and terms
The move
Yeah I mean a lot of it I was able to take care of
And gradually do but there is
Blindsided by
Various things are so much
Somebody
Counts to move over like I know stuff
It so it's it's a lot so I'm I'm just going to take a 1-1 off me day here
Absolutely I think that's a great idea
You should definitely take the day off and
Clean off your sound
For god sakes get the compressed air for what
Tell me what to do with my soundboard
Cuz if you do
Dammit don't
Tell me what to do
Anyone in the movie
Pavement
I wish I had that we could do
Stupid episode but
I'll be back on Monday and everything and I think it everybody who's been so supportive and kind about
Telling me to take a week off
And just people being like that excited for the new
New place in
The new patch
New animal friend
Which I think I've made a decision on which will be forthcoming now you're teasing
I'm not fully made this decision but I'm bleeding very heavily in One Direction
Actually shocked the world
The world
Yes
Anyway for the shelter website has been updated
My food reviews
Shuffle let's do a little bit of what you got
I tried this last week or so
Well
I don't know baby
I expect you both to be terrible
Pop-Tarts
Pop-Tarts which kind
Froot Loops
Get the f*** out of get the f*** out of single pack at the corner store
I agree
I don't like
I don't like Pop-Tarts to begin with
I think the trash
I hate them I think I have food
Delivered to your house
I think most of them are
Glorified candy or whatever
Looking hot fudge sundae
Although I will eat those
For dessert maybe them in brown sugar is the only way to go as a breakfast maybe it's more
Fruit punch
Super crazy
Is beyond
So I grabbed them
Expected to be terrible
And then I did what I always do with Pop Tarts just cut off the edges cuz it's too much
The pastry distress
I didn't know about you
What they cut the edges of the doctor
No
Naughty
Really good
Really good I hate this is really good. Really good I don't want for breakfast
It was shockingly close to fruit
Flavor of the inside the filling was gooey
Yeah but it tasted like
And then because of the
Frosting on top
That recreated
Did the sort of sugary Vibe of the hyperloop
I thought it was very accurate to a fruit and I felt really ashamed
Afterwards
I guess now that you said that
I got to give it up to the Somali pirates
Accurate
I don't like
Transforming text
I don't like the same taste turning into a different text
I need the
Texture to match up
If I taste a fruit loop
Play better be crunchy
I don't disagree with you as a whole
But
I went in expecting garbage
And it wasn't that bad so I applaud
New oreo on the scene
But I found
Tiramisu Oreo 10 are these people crazy
So you're the happen
I got that got home
I grabbed one of these Oreos out
As I was eating it I realize I don't think I've ever had tiramisu
Not that I can remember
Did it taste like that's the question I can't answer
Not great taste
Great
Nobody's nobody's ever been like
My God I need a Tiramisu right
Been awhile
God I need a therapist or am I just got out of the bar
Cannoli
Yeah it was really interesting experience for me
To have that realization
Mid Oreos it like
He hasn't had with this is pretending to be free
Could be dead-on could be
It could be a lot I could give the middle finger to the Swedish Fish Oreo
Swedish Fish
Oreo
On our way back
Yeah what was the other one
India
Pop Rocks
You like that pop rocks
I don't like pop rocks
Alone
Incorporate something like an Oreo
It's pretty excited
Just a Sprinkle that pisses me off
Okay it's an aggressive sprinkle sprinkle
Fruit Loop Pop-Tarts
I need a Raley's I would say what it is is it
Seated my expectations and pleasantly surprised me giving advice to people who are trying
If you're interested in that give it
Does not disappoint
If you really like tiramisu
Maybe it's later this I couldn't tell you
You don't like tiramisu
The regular Oreos
Maybe I don't know
This is been my novelty Food review and George
The joy that
We got to get out of
Thanks for your patience everyone out there we really appreciate it and once we're all settled
Everything will be so spectacular and there'll be a new pad
I will talk to you
Right
Yes we will