Knowledge party.com
I have great respect for its knowledge B I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
We are the bad guys
Need need money
Everybody welcome back
A little
Intercontinental
Sneaky
Sneaky Snake
Evolved perhaps I forgot how to say snake in French
Has bit Rusty Xavier picked up a bit
Snake
Every time
That's my favorite part of being here every time because of my partner
She grew up in Canada and learn French through
Announcer
Every time she's tried to even come close to saying the French word
They just immediately go like
English
They don't even be cut you off before you even come close to being like
Bonjour there like 9 and suck you
My language named for her people who try to speak French which I think
The opposite of
Like what I've heard of in in Canada where there's everyone saved
Just saying if you don't
Give it a shot
Yeah
Jordan
We're recording this over Zoom I'm in Chicago you are in
Paris France
I am in the nicest bathroom in Paris France that I could buy the lighting looks
Terrible that I will say
Set a timer to 6 here so
30 ft away somebody is asleep
Fair enough
I don't want to get to it I think this is going to sound incredibly depressing but it's like
About midnight on Christmas for me
The day after Christmas at 6
M4u
And here we are here we are
Like totally normal people
God dammit
Yeah it's super good at it left and then everything happened
It was like she's going to be weak Jordan will be back and have no big deal
Alex Guzman
Yeah he turns on Trump
Besides
We have to deal with Trump saying that he got the booster and it's great
It's kind of amazing
It is kind of amazing that we have sex
At 2 months in the presence in almost holding pattern
Very much
Colvin Colvin
And then the moment I'm gone
Yeah it's
It's a whenever whenever if possible to
Cover the present
It sucks and then as soon as it's not possible
This a b
I'm listening to some of it you know I'm getting it ready for 14 we can record again at it
F****** sweet some of his real father
There's a real schadenfreude
That's actually kind of brings up why we're doing this little Zoom thing
Because
Who knows when you're going to be back honestly
Given the state of the world and international travel
We'd hope that Wednesday will you be back in time for us to have an episode for Wednesday
Probably isn't going to be the case
Doubtful
Very doubtful
We're looking
Probably a Friday
You can't leave people with a hole
A week till Friday we got to come in with a little
Something
Crazy to leave people with only what
One episode when we promised them 0
Right it's just not our style
Zero you're getting to up
So I guess before we get into something that I have prepared
For fun
A bright spot
I do have a break spot it is being aggressive
Bluespot just Soleil
Fantastic everybody everybody
Is paris's crazy incredible
I love it here
Have you gotten out to the countryside at all
No you literally
Do that
You cannot leave Paris and re-enter it
Without coordinating for like 10 days
Made me feel safer than otherwise sure
Gorgeous but maybe not that gorgeous not worth it that bad
Alside I'm an indoor kid anyways I like City man this is a good
Danny
City I've been to outside
San Francisco
Felt like a a city
Paris feels like a city
Yeah yeah
Are you taking in any like outdoor cafes
Oh yeah
Check it out that seem
Every Outdoor Cafe you can't avoid
Yeah he's not believe there would be this much
Depends
They're famous for
God damn all of these breads
Are there
Walking down the street
Do you want to shop allowed opan
So good
Trip when you get back we'll be able to decompress and everything
I have a actual bright spot in that is some presents that folks have sent
But I want to wait until
I want to wait until you're here to actually like
Shout out to them but just
Thank you to those folks and well
Rosie of the mailbag whenever you're back
But my other bright spot is that with you out of town a little bit of a lighter workload and so I took the time to
To finally do something I've been meaning to for a while
The night is I went and I got an eye exam
And I got some glasses,
So I'm very excited about that
Yep
I've been putting it off about scissor readers
What's up
All the time glasses
Yeah yeah all the time glasses
Gotcha I think a lot of the time
You know I don't know
I'm just going to wear the glasses looking forward to it a little bit of Adam
Fishing in my eyesight
Over the last like couple years and I-80
It's better to be proactive on that then not and I'm excited for the like to really work
Work on this professor look
I would like
Is going to cut starting to come together a little bit
So I know I'm telling you
When we do all we do you know how we do all of our lives
Sure all those live appearances we do
If you are free
Joe Jordan
Here's here's the deal
In your absence I've been trying to get a bit of stuff done
Until like I've been hitting some bases like
Reset Wars obviously I've been going through the reefs at worse.
But also I've been digging into some of the old
Files
But I've found
Various
RealPlayer
Things on websites that are long gone
X-Files
Applying for the little audio files
So today what I've got for you
Is a couple of cliff
From Alex's show on June 30th 1998
That
AR
So funny
So at this point
Alex's show is called exposing corruption
Andrea Lee
Yes
He also is part of another show in Austin called the freedom report
But that's not everyday
Of the week
I think this is just a weekly show at this point but
Anyway he takes calls
Sometimes
2 today we're going to listen to a guy who's calling in and wanting to talk to Alex about like
Hey man what are you doing
Are you serious
I thought this is where we will start
With this collar
Very passive person I'd I watch you practically every week Alex year
I got you admit a lot of you as entertainment as far as
The reason why I watching
Good things to
And I'm one of those people that go
Okay settle down everything's going to be cool I think everything you know
Really what I think there's what are you going to do
Neighborhood
From my grandparents. The ones that
Not my father's parents but my mother's parents
Humble Home
Niceville backyard
And I worked hard their lives and they're not rich
Rihanna
Wheeless
78 years old war veteran
Lives in South Austin in a humble home
I have to stop here
Does humble home means something like
Is that is that something really specific or is it just like it's not that big of a home
I think
The idea behind Humble Home is
The person who lives in it
Is not embarrassed
But also not going to tell people all about it it's not like ostentatious
It's not that
Okay so Alex's Grandpa
Yeah
I'm just picturing the moment
Young Alex says the IRS tribe
Bastille my parents home
Jackbooted
Thugs
Breaking in the middle of the night and trying to put like little
Suspenders underneath
The house to lift it up
Put it on the truck and get it out of that you know I am seeing people coming from black helicopters repelling down
Attaching the house to the helicopter
Yeah I think it's probably just as they didn't pay their taxes.
So anyway Alex's grandparents have befallen this fate and also some other guy but Alex
Nose
Had a stroke
Bureaucrats Target oil p
Do you sit here
Because they can't stand up
Because
Another World War 2 veteran
Not there
On
West 37th
$2,000 a fine
43-inch grass I showed you the
I'm standing up for the people dammit
Oh I understand
I did not call you
I got a problem
Grow stronger someday I may do what it takes
Defending this country
The mass psychology
If you want to
I love this so much for the quick Alex's monologuing and his nonsense
Book stuff works so much better when he has a cough button and he could just not like people
Great
I'm okay
Alex Alex you're screaming too much
You're an alarm
What are you talkin about
Yes unfortunately the file that I have doesn't have like
Everything surrounding this but
From all the contacts you can get he's Galaxy's talking about the IRS
Trying to steal people's
Palms
And this guy is saying that maybe he's being a little bit
Over-the-top about it
Alex
I get it I'm with you
But screaming about it isn't going to do too much good is it
Okay I'm starting to see that this might be an issue for her
Further conversation
There's something so awesome about just the juxtaposition
Into that like
Makes Alex is yelling so much funnier
Having a straight man to his
Exactly what you kind of need to
The pierce the the real like these the reality of it
The board would more calling
The straight man in
The funnier it is to see Alex loses but mine
For sure
So
This caller brings up
Alex
Doesn't really
Use a whole lot of sources
In his reporting that this is where the conversation veers off towards
And this this kind of makes Alex angry a little bit you might say
You rely on a source when it tells you something do you want to know
Otherwise our sources crap
Saving play for a rainy day
Cheaper Age receive May save thousands of children
DNA transfer going to help children
Okay
Children
Call goddess.
Yeah answer the question
You are a child
Child beans
Babies
We are the children dumbass
Phone calls
Yeah but Alex stormed off his own show
We have gone back
23 years only to discover that he's not mad at the crew
But he just can't do this for a while I'm going to go to rebroadcast
This color
I got to play a video and get the f*** out of here cuz this guy is a child
I like that
Hey Alex
Do you realize that everything you do is built entirely upon confirmation bias
What the f*** are you doing
Donut Tire
I like this that you know that the sign of an artist
I think he's somebody who will do the same thing when they're rich
And when they're struggling
And Tony Alex
Breaking out and storming off his own show when he's a millionaire
Pretty awesome
Hiding the real Hallmark of a of an artist is to never involved in any significant way
Evolution
You made a point that in the present-day Alex
You know he's not mad at the crew
And here's what happened right after this video that I was played in 1998
LOL
Hope you're enjoying
Michelle tonight
We're making a new rule
Nobody goes with
We have no reason
When do the show
Because every time
Five or six people come up
And hang out in the control room this happen
I don't understand why
This is all volunteer but I mean
We got to bring the public
Important
And I'm not mad at y'all
You still do the job what you do
We just got to keep
The crew
Exist outside of time is he right about one thing
No matter what
But it's not like
It's not
The same thing in terms of the
The content that he's putting out it's not the same thing in terms of
Even like a lot of the beliefs that he has
Petulant
Child
Yeah
This is what
Visit cautionary tale about people who are very suspicious about
Mental Health
Explanation
All of this
It's like when you get down to it
Alex
His parents didn't help him
He's not experienced any consequences
How do you get
I imagine it was years and years of him yelling at his parents and then coming back me like I'm not mad at the
Only conclusion that years ago
33 years ago when he was 12 or whatever
Scream with the teachers and then with storm out of the room and come back after talking to the counselor and be like look I'm not mad at Caesars
I'm sorry
Everytime I try to do math
We wind up doing this
But we got a sex man
Yeah I found that and I thought like well we cannot bring this to the world now I can't not
I can't sit on
I want night when I hear
1998 I'm not mad at the crew
Broadcast
And then rebroadcast
Whenever you get real Angry so Jordan I hope the rest of your trip goes well and you have a safe
Return
Thanks for
Thanks for making time in the bathroom
To do that
Of course
Disable this is maybe one of my favorite it's not my favorite
Sit in the bathroom and talk to Dan
I feel honored
And I will talk to you soon man
Be safe
Multi-man will see
Y'all on Friday probably
Alex
I love your work