Important
I have great respect for knowledge B I'm sick of them posing as if through the good guy
Knowledge vype.com
Everybody sit around and talk a little bit about Alex
What's up
Is
Chocolate graham crackers chocolate graham crackers very underrated
Are you talking the layer of chocolate on top of the graham crackers that are chocolate
They're not like actual milk chocolate chocolate
Grandpa
Underrated
Underrated straight up chocolate yes absolutely
To Suites on Geib and they're not I don't know I just asked
Got some recently and I thought they were really good and I'd forgotten how good they were. Remember the last time I had
Honestly you know you used to pour like
I used to pour like that
You get that handful of Teddy Grahams or whatever and drop it in that thing of milk and just practically drink it like cereal
Kind of like that except for the
Goodbye
My God
Teddy Grahams
Brickform
Alright that's what I'm going to do the new album
Play Isaiah Rashad first album in 5 years and it's fantastic
The sun's tirade
Was one of my favorite albums of 2016 it had
A absolute
Destruction of averse by Kendrick and
It was just fantastic and then his new album is really really great to I am very happy with it nice Tennessee
Represent sounds like the chocolate graham crackers over album
To Jordan today we have a re-release of an episode which is somehow we've done ever
Up to that point
I think sometimes we said hey go to check back out this episode or whatever I passed but
What I thought
Here's the deal Wednesday we discussed how we were going to check in with Alex as he
He goes to Sioux Falls with
This dumb cyber conference and obviously we're going to have to follow that story at under Marshall
Because Marshall I was going to Beyonce litter on on the 11th of Wednesday
What up happening
That's true
Tomorrow
Alex didn't go.
Course I was going to be a disaster he's been in studio this whole week and so like
That didn't happen we don't even like mentioned Mike Lindell and and all that stuff we may be a little bit
But like not not not enough to pique my fancy
And so like
Hello
That's a disappointment
I was looking forward to another Alex on the road
Situation where I was looking forward to him going to Mike lindell's
Big guy Comic-Con because
I spend a good bit of time
Watching his stream
Prepare myself to give myself the contacts that I needed to discuss and every Bowl
It was such a waste of time unbelievably bad
Improve his case and obviously the Supreme Court
Will be voting 900 today
Headlight
I don't know man the problem that I had was that
You know I seen a couple of funny clips on Twitter I was excited for whatever trainer
Direct was going to happen and it there's nothing it was just a long stretches
Just saying numbers
I got nothing to arriving to watch out for a PowerPoint presentation
Weird guy with an American flag bow tie
Whatever
I would rather
The guy from the 92 found a way to get free grant money from the government more this suit and did those commercials
I would do a 72-hour how to get free grant money from him I wonder about that guy I wonder if his free
Not not that far I wonder if like he actually help people
Anyway let's not do push-ups while I'm there
You know it was a bummer
Alex's Alex's not done anything really worthwhile
And the time that I would have spent just like being like a let's do a past episode 2 our who spent watching Mike lindell's stupid.
And
Okay well let's find some of this good audio from
MyPillow stop that if you wanted to search on on Twitter and socks you can find other people
Posted
Yeah that's the stuff that's fun and I don't think we need to Pirate their content or anyting
So what are the things that they did see come up
Is that
It's being discussed
That the source of the information behind Mike lindell's
Conspiracies
PayPal
Diem
Dennis Dennis Dennis
So turns out that not only is Dennis Montgomery The Source apparently of this
Information to Mike Lindell has
He also
Is the guy who claims that he created hammer and scorecard guess the things that are behind like Sydney
Powell's let her conspiracies billion-dollar loss
Syracuse
That did not get thrown out this week another important news
Until what are the things that I thought when I when I heard that is is like he's done it again
Is Dennis Montgomery guy
He is low-key one of the most destructive
The horses and Mike conspiracy theory
He's a whack-a-mole to it's like you think he's down and then all the sudden he pops back up behind Mike
Bloomdale 72-hour Symposium supposed to do with this ass he's a name but most people don't know
No but he's f***** up so much
It's not even like he's a behind-the-scenes guy
It's almost like you just
Find a way to get into the right situation give the wrong information to the right people and then we're all f*****
Yeah yeah yeah so the episode today that we're going to release is our 25th episode from
Yeah it's a ways back
And this is
I was thinking about is like well as Montgomery's coming back up we can talk about this again or
We already did
And I don't think a lot of people episodes
Probably haven't heard this
It's done it's done as Montgomery if anybody had listened to this ahead of time
Maybe you Michelangelo or Sydney Powell if they'd listened to
How many people would not be getting sued if they just listen to our share saved you 1.6 billion dollars
You just know no oh no
I do believe that in the episode I say if I saw Dennis Montgomery I would run the other direction
That would have been good advice for all you dumbasses
It's so funny
You know I think
I think what you have is
Overtime
People have become
So gullible I guess that somebody like Dennis Montgomery could get
Like well way back
You could get somebody like Joe Arpaio to go along with him because Joe Arpaio was trying to beat a
A case with a conspiracy that I could use
It doesn't work you know doesn't work then everyone's like dance like this noise
Everybody is like the world is so weird now
And Mike Lindell has so much money to throw around at nothing now they
All of this
Good bike
So much of the quote-unquote
Proof
And the lingering of the election conspiracies
Comes back to
This guy who should just be discounted out of ham
Yeah
What are you do when the going gets weird weird refused to die and continue to pop up wherever it is
Is that they can like f****** zombies trying to kill the rest of us all it's wild yeah
Just listening back to this episode
And just because I felt like
I want to check back in I think there's a couple things I want to say before we we had to playing
But one is that
This was the first time that I really tried on our show to
Get into a topic
And I can tell like a list of listening back to it as I did not have a lot of practice in
Doing that I don't think that
Response to it but
The definitely shows that I have not done a whole lot of that good
Five years later you should be better than you do
That seem kind of idea
I think that there's a little bit of language that we wouldn't use today
That is thrown around slightly different
And I was considering going back in like cutting out stuff
What have you but I I I don't I feel like that would be slightly dishonest
No we were who we were
Is coming from a far more ignorant place you know back
Back in 2017 we hadn't even really started the show episodes in but
Charizard listener base there was
Just
You know the few
The few people who lived in Chicago really that were that were around so
Now that now that I'm not in such an isolated place you know only being around comics only being
Being around all of those people and have
Hi there I think some of it it was like gear
To hear the time it does represent show some
Modicum of growth
And I I think that
Is something can I have to just take on the channel little bit
And then the other thing too
More fun backpack
I think it before the world
Became what it is now
Is a bit easier to have fun talking about the subject
It's it's it's really it was really remarkable to go back at 8 and
Seether the like
I don't know goofiness
Interrupt so much more and I was so much more into it because
We weren't living through a year-and-a-half two years on pandemic we could have mostly been averted
Yeah it was weird it's funny that back then I predicted that Trump would try and overthrow the government and
And become a dictator and then when it happened
I was surprised
Is very strange I was and I wasn't that surprised
Bile
It's
Different now though I'd be like me predicting wild ends Montgomery's going to be trouble in the future I'd still be surprised
Seriously again here we are
Holyshit
What up what a bummer
Something so easy to avoid Dennis Montgomery
You know it's weird when somebody is put together a decades-long body of work that
Proves beyond a shadow of a doubt
This is someone you should not trust yeah and then five years later people are still like
I'm going to give this Shifty weirdo shot you know every every group needs to have a loose cannon
I mean I would say that even like taking leaving aside whatever we did or this
Like that
I think there was plenty of public information not to take this guy seriously
Butts
People are addicted to it they're addicted to fake whistleblowers they're addicted to
Tales of intrigue and and like
Jason Bourne types it's kind of amazing that tell me what I want to hear will often override
Any and all information
3 bomber
Yes it is so we're going to get to that and that's that episode will be coming up with there's one other thing
I wanted to discuss little news item that I think is important
I don't know if you saw the Rand Paul news
Would you like to debate him on these stocks
To debate Rand Paul it is day
285 inside of officially demanded a debate with Rand Paul do you like to do
Rand Paul about the ethics of his wife owning stock in the company to make the red desert VR
Wow he goes on an anti-vaccination Crusade
That isn't a lock should last one sentence
Unethical Edward
Unethical
Daisy Marc dicey clay that's what we're dealing with
Pillar of Integrity Rand Paul immediately thought of you and thought of how much fun
That would be babe I want to debate him
God that would be hilarious
Please enjoy
This episode from The Archives
Man I don't know look at this maybe
Maybe on Thursday or Friday Alex will go to Sioux Falls
For the aftermath of our human stay away from this thing
Ground Zero 9/11 survey the damage
Will check in on Monday but I hope you all have a good weekend and we will
Catch you on the other side
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work
I'm Jordan we are back for yet another episode
Drink a little bit of wine
And discuss
So what's going on in the wacky wacky world
Chubby Checker
Featuring The Fat Boys
Level twist
Alright
Five Guys
Is that I watched
Nordstrom's in particular
Not at all not at Iota except
I did just turkey what you watching
You tried to get me to watch some
And then David
F****** demon
From beneath the the boring
Level of hell
Like the world
Most boring hobo coming on TV
He's got quite a bit of a sudden realize that
Yellow tongue
We recording this on
We wanted to check because Alex
To promote it online
He's about to drop a
Pizzagate
If we wanted to check in on what that was
Watching
So far
No bombshell
So we will monitor
Keep you up-to-date
Nope not at all
I'm still standing by my former theory that I espoused of last podcast
If you got threatened with a lawsuit
Yeah
I'm not sure that anything that he
He says today
Go to shake Bible
No he was definitely he's definitely serve some sort of papers
Maybe
Subpoenaed
Sure
He what yeah
But anyway
Loft
He was way more sugar
I'm going to go over
Going to be a special Xposed
Episode
Generally what we do is I take a day in the life of Alex
And I play the
The clipse
Disgust
Incredibly wrong
About every
His break
The entirety of last week
This is unprecedented
Busted ass but Alex
Cuz promoting
And the result
Of my
N2y Alex Jones
I feel like
Gastineau
That he's just being
Alright hamster no
I have
About 30 text review over this past
About how in
Cancer research
Just wonder I wonder
Court documents
What is wrong with you
Hey
This is
Now this is a venture
Play just going to turn into me
Wishing well
Thrilled I know
That's one of the problems I had an amazingly great time reading up on all this stuff
I found
Is like legitimately horrifying
There's individuals that we're going to do
Disgust
You probably wear of maybe one or two of them
Jesus sure he's going to come in the mix
Infowars
Franklin delanor Roosevelt
I think it's an accident but I'm not
Etiwanda
There's a guy at least one who's going to come up
Will know who he is
Before but the amount of research that I did
Really highlighted how much worse
From here
That was not fun
Reading some of the stories
Why are you taping
Because
I want it now all I can think about is who it might be
For some reason I don't think that's right
No we watched
Documentary we know how bad
I got you
But I know I'm doing too much teasing
But we have to start out or episodes of
With an
Text drop it at nothing
Call
Has fallen from 56
37th and National
No
Yep
A lot of people over 50%
Yeah
Alright
Here we go
Let's get to it
Get down to business
Alright cuz this is going to be
Alright I don't want to sing let's get down to business
From the Mulan
This Is How We Do It
Blora
The parties Uptown the Westside
You know what
Eventually I will make them
Just because I love cake
In-N-Out
I don't know that one
Pink Lana Del Rey Carly Rae Jepsen
Mount Rushmore
F*** you
Okay okay that's fine
He's pitching this entire game case
APK spaces
Song by song
I like the Orinoco Flow
Or that song
Sweet November only time
Alex on Mondays show sort of giving an inch
Introduction to
Pieces
What we're going to be talked about
You're listening to The Alex Jones Show
Dragon
Cam
You can see the headline right in the middle column it's been there since yesterday
Afternoon
Documents prove surveillance of trump
And his family bombshell discovery shows
Project
Now we got Bass
Inside Sheriff Joe Arpaio
Call Casey
Kohl's last year
Infowars.com
Because the feds
Well there's a new sheriff in town
Obama's concern date
Years
Obama
Website the world.
This morning
Document
Project
When he's a complete
No because when he's saying more that's that click here for more he's reading the link
Eminem
Hammond project dragon is a second link
He just didn't he doesn't even know what he's reading on the page
His rhythm of that is
Trump's more
Christopher Walken
Live his life
The preparation he doesn't know what he is
Actually
About to talk about it all
It's infuriating it drives me incredibly insane
But
So we have the this clip is done
There's more
What we have already as the introduction
Universe theme
It's that there is an essay CIA whistleblower who is come out
Who has a ton of documents
Donald Trump
Is being surveilled
Inez
Will learn
That not only is Donald Trump
Being
Surveilled and have been for years
Bethany was just
A business
Right not only that
Alex Jones
Michael Savage
Other people's families
The news
Just other people say hi
No
Although Snowden
Get clocked out a little bit in this episode minor compared to what this whistleblower
Is bringing out every single element
I will
If in the next
Two-and-a-half
23 hours
If we don't end up with everyone who hears this
Realizing that this is nothing
I will
Commit Harry Caray
Live at the purple couch
Look it up
The only way to go about things honorably
At least come out and say it wasn't true kind of like we got the microphone
Police and a Federal Marshals another copy from different division
And for a week the media
I also called the phone numbers on there
Right now
Again again that to him reading
I'm not figuring out outside
Works on the garage
Remember
Yes where we go
What's the movie with The Rock in
And Steve Carell is that right I don't know
Yeah with
The old one
They made a new one
Steve Carell
I don't think the rock was
Employment
So on Sunday of last week
Infowars published
What they
Believe claiming
A database
Phone numbers and address
Right and Alex
Who said this these were my old phone numbers this is correct
These are the phone numbers that I have for Donald Trump
These are real phone number
But as We Know
He doesn't know Donald Trump's phone number
Look for the prize he keeps
He's claimed that he has multiple phone numbers
It falls flat
Thompson different area code
He has he has these things that he published
With some redacted
Parts you know like you don't want to
Sacred on it even if you do
You've got you don't want to
The docks
The people
Phone number
They claimed it was a part of a massive index people who were being spied on
And this is from this whistleblowers
Now
The problem that we have with that
Is that it
Completely unproven
All of this information could have been gotten by someone who has
The minimum amount of hacking
Scales
Hated willing to
Who falsified
Keep that in mind as we go further
Posted
Does not have
Newcomb
He's posted on the website
Does not have to come
From
Like an NSA source for CIA
It's all very easily accessible information
Like a lot of the information is the address of Mara Lago
I could Google
I need print out like a part of the phone book did I think someone else
Did and sent it to him as evidence of a leak
Okay so it's
It's not the white papers
It's the white page
That's what we're talking about
Nailed it
Yeah you think I can sell my baby all day
So
This is basically the construction of
What is going on
Building
Eli's
If using whatever information that he got as evidence
The Trump has been being
Spied on
He's using it was right all along
Right
So on Monday he has an interview with
A guy
Named Mike zullo
Okay so is a former Detective
A for what
Yes so he come back for one last job
Is he
Two or three days away from retirement please give me something
Okay he's currently used car dealer as far as I can tell that's what I found in my flight
Research
I don't care too much about Mike zullo
Alright care about more is that he is
An employee
Informer
Former employee
Because he's not out of
Anymore
Sheriff Joe Arpaio
He was a member of his
Posse
And now I think it is time that we start to deal a tiny bit with Joe Arpaio
Racist
Garbage
Pile of
Human f***
Earlier when I said when you look at him he's way worse than even went huge
Just said I did not know
Everything I know about it
So we're going to get to it and
Lilo is going
To make the argument
Can get much worse
But you think the devil can't go lower but there we go the devil also
You know cheats of cards come on
So you always shoot
Get to
Zulos point
Which is basically
That when
Joe Arpaio was being
Tried
Court
For now
Making the necessary changes
Vetta judge
Insisted that he make
Based on findings that they had of racial discrimination
In the Maricopa
County police force
Default
Him to follow the law
X 2080
2010's
This is a severe problem
He was held in
Contempt of court
Arrested
What should have happened right in this court case
I don't like
So I don't want to remove it
Yeah exactly the argument
That he was being
Because being
Surveilled upon and wiretap
During
That investigation and we'll deal with that in the moment
I want to deal with first
Cuz I want to give an accurate picture of
Sheriff Joe Arpaio
Let's get down to it
I have
Pages
Subway
Where any one of these
Is disqualifying
So get ready
Does he say grandpa
No
Maricopa County in Arizona
Joe Arpaio set up a tent city
The houses inmates have not believed that they deserve to be inside
Great Arpaio literally describe the tent city as a
I like his willingness to embrace
Does monstrosity like
Didn't even bother to call it
The different he's like if I could burn you
I would I would totally do that
Speaking of burning these inmates please don't say anymore after
On July 2011 temperatures in Phoenix
18 degrees Fahrenheit
Arpaio measured the temperature inside
As 145 degrees
Some inmates complained that their fans near their beds were not working
From the Heat
During the summer of 2003 when outside temperatures exceeded 110 degrees Fahrenheit
Arpaio
Complaining inmate
Hit 120° in Iraq
The soldiers are living in tents
And they didn't commit any crime
So shut your mouth
Which is
Horrible
How do you not have any f
Empathy for another
The human being in 1997 Amnesty International said arpaio's Tent City Jail is not a quote
Humane alternative to housing
Inmates in suitable jail facility
People get mad when you leave a dog in a f****** car and this dude is little
Really burning people alive in
In the desert
Tent city is criticized
Is contending with their RV
The human and constitutional rights
Implicit in it
Formation
Yep you at
Do that
His argument is that they're criminals
Who cares
Committed crimes really bad argument
One of our public relations actions was a requirement that inmates wear pink underwear
In order to prevent it's fact by the released inmates
Which of the stupid rationale
He claimed the most harmless thing I've ever heard anybody
He claims that he has saved the county $70,000 in the first year this rule was in effect
King County
Subsequently started to sell customized with a Maricopa County Sheriff's logo
Joe on them
As a fundraiser for Sheriff's posse Association
What's the spike Arpaio declined to provide
For the money
He basically use it as a promotional tool
So so it's so
With his financial
We're not even
Close
M2010 Arpaio put together an arms illegal immigration policy to help enforce immigration laws
Posse Posse
You do it gets worse
This Posse included
Steven Seagal and Lou Ferrigno
No that's better
I know that
That Posse
Is
Immune to ninja
That's the first thing we know about that party
Building
And then if
Anybody gets
Really out of
Control
He's a big green guy
You would not like me if yours
Especially not if you're a God
Zebra
Close to the tip of the iceberg
Routinely abused detainees at Maricopa County Jail
Fruit leather
Contaminated food
Is to endanger their health
Denying them care for
For serious Medical
Mental health needs
And keeping The Pact
Sardines in holding cells for days
Now that's before they've been middle Medieval ages what is funky
Happening before they were charged
That's before they were charged for the f****** Christ
Pretrial detainees
That is probably true
People
No you should treat you awake
Human and constitutional rights
Yeah
That should have taken like toy
20 seconds
Under Arpaio the Maricopa County Jail multiple times
In September 2008 the National Committee on Correctional Healthcare
Terminated the accreditation of Maricopa County Sheriff's Office
Does jail for failure to maintain compliance with national standards
Information about such compliance
What does that mean
They lied
Accreditation does that mean people aren't allowed to be supported by these Medical Association
They're in charge of sort of
Keeping track of making sure that jails
They just
I think
That's bad I love though I love their life-saving
Enforcement capabilities but they do have
Like
Waving the finger
Can get a f*** face to go to a Goddamn pizza restaurant human being
Other human beings
Liberals are
Maricopa County
Are unconstitutional
And safety of prison
But these are different
OK Google
Arpaio
Is places of punishment
The inhabitants are Criminal
Although most inmates have not been convicted of a crime and are awaiting trial
F***
Q
What the f***
It gets worse
Where is Egypt worth
Ted Bundy was honest
About his
Monstrosity
Like I would much rather
Like he's a sociopath
But still allowed to roam the streets like you just
Figure it out
How to parking
Turn it into a money you like
Turn
Ted Bundy into a job
That's what he did was re-elected like four times
Arizona's a f****** garbage
That's fair
Here here here's another one
Under Arpaio the Maricopa County Sheriff's Office
May have been properly cleared
Or reported it solved as many as 75% of
Without a rest or proper investigation
How's that grab you
During a three-year period ending in 2007 more than 400 sex crimes reported to arpaio's office
No while providing police services for El Mirage Arizona
The Maricopa County Sheriff's Office at least 32 reported child molestation
Jesus f*** why
Menu
Many of the children at home
We're illegal
I don't care how do you
Not
Care about that
Hey 1999 undercover Maricopa County Sheriff's Office deputies arrested
Then 18 years old
And charged him with plotting to kill Arpaio with a pipe bomb
A local television station
I've been tipped off to the arrest by the Maricopa County Sheriff's Office
A broadcast
The Maricopa County Sheriff's Office
And everything else
It's not going to bother me
After spending four years in jail awaiting trial for years awaiting trial
He was about to sign a plea deal that would have sent to prison for 20 years
Although you maintain
He was initially unwilling to
Take a chance on being
To even longer
If you were convicted
However
The former head of undercover investigations for the Maricopa County Sheriff's Office
Based on his review of the case
He felt that
Although entrapment is all but impossible to prove in most jurisdictions
Civil attorneys eventually discovered that
The Maricopa County Sheriff's Office
Detective
Bought the bomparts themselves what
Then convince the vale to build it
Even though he was not predisposed to commit such a crime
On July 9th
Maricopa County superior court
Finding that the bomb plot was an elaborate publicity stunt
The Boost arpaio's re-election bid
Siri
In 2004 Seville argued Arpaio and the Maricopa County
Maricopa County
Seeking 10 billion dollars in Damages
Joe Arpaio
In 2008 the suit was settled with Maricopa County paying
Six billion dollar
Little bit less
You should have gotten but dollars
Yeah
I am
I like this
I am against the death penalty
But your pale should be f****** killed
He's only there's only one reason for the
Cheats for f****** monsters like him he's abused the public trust to such an
F******
Like there's no other
Hey Jordan.
No
He's already dead
This is the producer
Justice department
Unconstitutional
Tino's for detention and arrest
And retaliate retaliating against critics
In a report to justice department concluded that Arpaio oversaw quote the worst
Profiling in US history
It 2016
That's f****** hard to do
After after all Arjun
If you get labeled with that
In 2015 Arpaio was charged with
Contempt of court for failing to implement a court
Required changes
I to his police force regarding ramp
Social profile
He was also found to have destroyed evidence
Course he did
But he's also publicly promoted the Obama birther
Repeat
Up to December last year 2016
He was quote
Investigate the birth certificate
And he erroneously claimed
Points of forgery Obama's birthday
So
A2000
Slitting my f******
In 2008 win Phoenix mayor Phil Gordon called the federal investigation into a federal investigation
Immigration
My tactic
Arpaio's office respond
By demanding the mayor's emails and phone logs
Arpaio also had his critic Maricopa County Supervisor John
Republican arrested
Suspicion of failing
To properly discuss
This was business
Stapley agreed to a 3.5 million settlement
Is a lawsuit against Arpaio
Thomas
Beaver Falls
Multiple times
A suit for it and lost
He's cost
Tri-County
So many millions of dollars
Because of these illegal tactic
He's undergone
And he was re-elected
4 * has like a runoff election twice
It failed both.
Really yeah
How could this country have elected Trump
Deeply entrenched
I like
Illegal
Operation
This pile of s***
Yeah so
Awful but it's not in jail
Cuz he argues that he gets results
How is he
Wow you committed all the crimes
He might be soon
He should be dead
He already
His argument is that he is
Gruff but he gets results but that's not an argument in a case of law
In 1998
You're under arrest for terrorism
Excuse me
I believe I get results
The commission to study by Arizona State University criminal justice professor
Examine recidivism
Spaced on conditions of
Confinement so basically like
Beforehand
Comeback
It's supposed to be before him
After him
Recidivism rates under Arpaio to those of his predecessor
The study found
There's no significant difference observed between those offenders released in 1989 to 9
Released in 1994 to 1995
A criminal
A monster
And it's offensive I get results
F******
How can you help
Could you not
Prosecute
Like there's no
That you could not
Put him in jail forever and ever and ever
All the lives by rhino
In reincarnation or ghost
So that guy
Can be tortured every moment
For the rest of
F****** attorney
I'm giving you all of this information and they're still even more but the reason is because the interview that Alex does
Is with this guy's clothes
Associate degree in Waterford
2 hour
Transitive property of you're a f******
King monster
Determined
We're talking to a f***
He's an evil man
Here's the situation
There's a lot of really sucked up stuff
So you can find out about the history of
Joe Arpaio
Maricopa County
Sheriff's Association
F****** bullet point list of
Absolute
Upon reflection man Jordan talked it over and we've decided that a lot of the stuff is not
For us
Broadcast
I think
I think you should
On your own
In a comfortable place
Because I'm listening to it
In a row
Is
Overwhelming
So
Place to start you can find about
Want to go you can find out more about
The depth
Of the truly irresponsible
Evil
Police work that
Joe Arpaio presided over
Everyone
Convicted in the Nuremberg
I genuinely
I genuinely believe that
Is the sort of
Will be here
Are we going to give a moment of silence
Let's get it
We will wait
4 second
Right back at you like tapping my foot waiting
Here we go we get into now this interview with Mike zullo
One of the higher-ups
To the Maricopa County
Former higher-ups
Does it work
Alex does a lot of vamping
Accomplice to every single thing
Image of iPad
Implicitly sign
And off by supporting him
Supporting him to this day
Also Alex does a lot of sort of
Opening present
Temptation before
He gets to the interview
Some play couple quotes
The documents the surveillance arpaio's house is office all of us fight on
Serving
Decorated Sheriff Patriot
Monsters
Racist
Yours truly
Isn't that just special
Not particularly
Nope
Shipping about the paper
So the argument that make
That the black
Tommy's
So the argument that he's making there is that Arpaio was
Spy.
His trial
This is
Absolute Auto nonsense
The secondary argument that he's making is this
To come out with all of these
All these people
One of them
It's permission in Paw
And get the Blacklist RJ will get a little bit
Further down the line
Make sure
In a second but let's get through his his introduction
This is where he
Connect
What's going on
The Arpaio spying
Situation
To what we're going to be talking about later
The bigger case
That involves Trump
Involves Alex
It's the guy named Dennis Montgomery who is that nsa's CIA
Who is much bigger than Snowden
I swear to God I have you seen the movies
Yeah have you seen any movie where somebody has a giant pinboard
Filled with string connecting one thing to another
Because it's on your goddamn wall
This one's real simple though it's not out
I assure you this is not that hard
Line of string
That's all we needed for this basic
They ignored it
Even harder because he had the Whistleblower that had all this information
So
Connect everything there this whistleblower and question is this guy named Dennis monkey
Janet Montgomery
Would you like backstory on him now or later
Let's go with half an hour
Okay here's a fun one
Janice Montgomery was a guy who he sounded a video compression noise filtering business called
Etrepid Technologies
A video
Compression noise filter
Like in 1998
Oh okay
Business started out as
Tool for the cassette
Do you know industry but eventually they sought out government
In 2014
Montgomery was revealed to be working as a confidential in
Informant for Sheriff Joe Arpaio
He claimed
When he was Contracting
For the CIA through the
Etrepid Technologies
The government contract
Cuz he was doing
Your pain
Approved
Conspiracy against Arpaio
Basically that the
Department of justice under Eric Holder
Was working
With the judge
McKay's
Unopposed
Racial profiling case
Together
I had the doctor
Isn't that just called
Get like doing
Doing the law in this case it's conspiracy
Well I mean
Conspiracy
Is it just like
But I guess I mean
You can't man
They were otherwise
Conspiracy
Wiretap
That which the judge
I also don't
All my cards on the table
I don't think it was also
We know how bad do Joe Arpaio is
Publicity stunt in this 2004 claim that Montgomery made
As the result of Montgomery's investigation is quote
Junk
So even our pale things
Yep
Come on Alex Jones
Is a shadowy figure
Alright so he's a vampire
Mark Mike zullo
Who is arpaio's
Who's arpaia
Now cartel
Is
We're leaving up
Such an elaborate
And super-long
At least on Scream
The whole introduction I'm looking awkwardly
Jerome corsi
Looking uncomfortable
Jerome corsi is hanging out
Pacing back and forth
Things up
Between zullo at Alex
Do an interview
He is there as like a third wheel
Okay
This point Alex drop the information that shows
He doesn't have
About the situation that he's going to be
They're the ones that got the documents
Ohio
Interview
He doesn't know what to talk about unless this information is sitting right in front of them
Cuz he doesn't know the situation
Of course
He only knows if he's reading Awesome piece paper wet meanwhile he yells bodies teleprompter free
You don't know the story
He only knows
Staff
Is feeding him information
Key Alex
I had published
List of people's phone numbers and addresses
This Montgomery
Because Dennis Montgomery
I just did
Oh well let's recap what happened yesterday
+ 6
Being spied on
The group of documents
That Dennis Montgomery has revealed
But he hasn't
The nude
Going on
And Trump is being f****** railroaded
It's good
This
I wish you was on a railroad
Twisting their Pencil Thin Mustache
What
Once again I want to use this next clip
Just established
That Alex is
Specifically
Talkin about
And Arpaio
As being the exact same thing
What about
In the mix
I think
Second part of the series
Publix.com
Bombshell discovery shows Target
Project
Here's a Larry klayman article
Masturbate
With the 47 hard drives over 60
Ma
Talking about Snowden
Necessary
Also known as hard drives
Three-by-five floppies he's got a mountain of a
They claim it's actually 600 million documents
Aleksandra.
The issue is that no one really knows what's onto them or if they're even real
Could you
Impossible
Even a couple years lead-time couldn't process 600 million.
McDonald's
Can sell 99 billion
Alex is proof
But all this is real
Yeah it is that his phone number and his old phone number is
Along with
Donald Trump
Phone numbers which again we have
Suspicions whether he actually knows or not
Here's a clip of him providing literally the only evidence
At any point
This stuff
Is true
Super stoked bleached show Obama
Right on Trump
Alex Jones
Sheriff Arpaio
The second-biggest website in the world.
Showtime
Nothing on this
Respond
These phone numbers
Are the phone numbers to private
Apartment at Mar-A-Lago
These are the numbers
Miles cell phone number nobody had that's real wild private office
Numbers
Real
Around saying
This phone numbers that nobody could know
Chew it like
It's dumb why would you even have an office phone
To know your office phone number
Hit the nail right on the head a lot of the stuff is
Conceivably public information
But even Alex Jones cell phone number again
See I could find it I guarantee that if I had a tiny bit of hacking ability
I could find his phone number you can find anybody's private information
Really easily. All of the places that you would have dropped it
If you ever went to college all that information is really easily accessible
Like a bunch of your your addresses
Community College
Wichita
Two cell phones
But I mean a lot of a lot of the Community College
I don't think real
I don't think cell phones are around
Be that as it may
Sing is a lot of these things you end up filing information places
A lot of your private
Information is much more accessible than people think
The news reports about this
We're just
Mid-level basic
Hacking
Individual
What's
Not even the most evolved hackers are able to find tons and tons of private information about people
It is not illegal
Courtesy call
On your cell phone
Yeah they're just telling your number
Like if you ever gotten a call on your cell phone
Holding you that's because somebody told you
You can easily yeah all that information is
Super easy to find
What is proof of an essay
CIA database
Is is cockamamie
It's ludicrous
AT&T
Yeah absolutely and I mean
If we really want to get down to the wood like the bottom of it
I'm against that
I don't like the idea people are selling information
But that's
Contact that's not what I was
I was talking about
Anyway
It's not illegal to sell all of your information
So here we go here we go Alex is again reinforcing his own
Sort of narrative
But doing it in
I've got to get this is what she says
In terms of like
We have the proof
Headlines
You can show us headlines all day long with Ant-Man edited in so right before he says that
We have all the proof and then he says we have all the headlines
You look like a f******
To the actual zullo interview now
Going to lay out a story
That unfortunately
As he tells the story
You start to get the pictures
He actually doesn't
It's really unfortunate
The title that I gave this
They don't know what
To do with the information
We really don't know what is going on
We know that we made
Every endeavor
To bring
Mister Montgomery to Federal authorities
Like I said earlier
We contacted Larry klayman for his assistance
And under the direction of Sheriff Arpaio we brought Mr Montgomery to
Judge Royce Lamberth
We used to be the head of the fisa Courts
And then we got in there
The Dilemma was
Is where do we go
Mister Montgomery
During his tenure as a contractor
Weather in Michigan
Executed a search warrant on his phone
Fabricated affidavits to a judge
And that was all their doubt in trial
I can find no evidence.
A problem for us
Because the only other place we could have gone to it that time would have been the Department of Justice and I believe at that time it was still Eric Holder
That was a problem
So here's why it's a
The problem for the
Because
Not
Nothing no
Allegedly all of this 600 million documents
Is confidential information
They can't just go to a lawyer
He stole all this allegedly from the NSA
It is it is a problem
Get to the
YouTube Justice when holder is
Willing to press
But also
This guy Mike zullo and the next minute we're going to be dealing with this guy who keeps coming up Larry klayman
The two of them
Can't know anything about what's on those dock
And if they do they've committed a crime
Admit that they know anything on it
Their Evonne are
Committed
Is a pickle
That's really tough
Have to believe that I don't
Nesterly think that there
They're lying
They haven't looked at any of it
All know I think all they're going on
Is what
Has told them
They are telling Alex
What Dennis Montgomery has told them they say
Sandra playing a big game of telephone
That's the Alex had on the other day
Like third hand knowledge of
That where Michelle Obama says
Really wish that were true
And Report
Third hand
And arrow
That's
That's the problem for the
Cuz they
Can't make an Argy
All they can do is speculate about what possibly is in this information
Based on what
Does Montgomery has told them
So they're doing everything Alex Jones love
His investigation to try and help Joe Arpaio
I was called
By Joe Arpaio himself
So
That's one piece
Can't wait to f***
Nitrite doing it now we need we need to let it fails
So at this point zullo is going to explain what happened
Are they took
The information to the FBI I'll let him spell it
Larry klayman was successful in persuading mr. Montgomery
To talk to the FBI
Which he did
With
Larry
Is Mr Montgomery brought in
A sampling of some documentation
Dayton what is known as production immunity
Again
This is based on Larry excuse me
Montgomery
They wouldn't have done that though
If he is
Sonos
Vista 47 hard drives and 600 million documents
Goodbye
What's your name
Check out
They let him and then he just has been living his life
I also want to make this clear
Does Montgomery
At this point
In 2017
Is like 65 years old
He's an old dude he's not
Edward Snowden
He's young and like
It's a fun whistleblower image
Nobody's a write-in citizen 60
No not at all
It's like you get in your head this idea cuz
Snowden keeps coming up that he's like
Some able-bodied
YouTube
Usually aren't a seven-year-old dude that he actually
Maybe we can talk all the s*** we want but I do believe this guy actually does have some hacking ability
That's only because
Occam's razor tells me he
In order to fraudulent
Lee create the documents
That have been sent
Infowars
Alright I'll spell that out a little bit later as we go along
Bulshit
Let's talk a little bit more
And he brought in I believe it was like six hundred million records
He provided them that information some time goes by
And they called him back and they gave him testimonial immunity
47 hard drive
Pictures of information
Not necessarily
Again
Comes back to you like a lot of that stuff is
Fairly easy to find
Google
Some of it could be Googled someone I could just be
Sixty-five-year-old a lot of people
No you can't bring
Only Google ads
Everybody knows this
At this point to another part
Like it might have some play
Did she ever going to be the most boring person to live
No cuz they're on course he's still around midnight
So he's going to get into this and it sounds scary but don't worry about it I'll be right back on the other side of the 620
Let us find out where
Personal information on a lot of the 150,000 people is absolutely
Identify
That were alleged to be there
Because those bank accounts
It is suspected that they are actually fraudulent transactions
Had accounting it with I spect you too real estate gas and oil
Stock plays
Alex Azar
Derivative
Speculative
Thing thing
What is he
Those are
Sugar
Futures
I don't know
Actually really unfortunate that they use those specific
Because I can
Trace back exactly what their talk
FanDuel
But Dan
Find a little bit of an article from the news
Association in
Phoenix that was covering the trial
Some evidence
Suggesting that the informant Montgomery was investigating snow
Who was the lawyer
Who is
The judge
Joe Arpaio
Discrimination
Okay
That Montgomery Tesla was being employed by Joe Arpaio to invest
Navigate to Judd
Which would be very early
Really illegal
That
That fits with
Who is actively try
Billions of dollars of lawsuits.
Be filed because
Of his dictator is behavior
In any movie from
The South or the movies
Arpaio insisted he hadn't encouraged Montgomery
Investigate the judge
Instead Arpaio insisted the informant was investigating bank fraud
And the judge was one of 150,000
Alleged victims
In Maricopa County
Now that 150
Because that's
From the number
That this guy just reference
As the NSA CIA database
Allegedly included Donald Trump
And Alex Jones
Do they live in Maricopa County
So it seems like it's
Possibility
That that
Their information
Two different bullshittin
Right
Wow that's well
We should resign
I think that's it very important
Climate changes
Coming
Keep on throwing your old bulshit
Exactly
So Arpaio
Arpaio in Montgomery had this bank fraud thing
That was cover
For him invest
Navigating this job
There was trying to
Racial profiling
What is not actually invested in
Striking him down
He's hearing the case
The prosecutors are more the issue
But he's investigating
He's investigating
Can I get leverage over
What have you
That that fits with the kind of paranoid personality that we're dealing with because
He doesn't believe that it is never
He always believed this one guy
All of the Power because he is a guy with all of this dump
Actually tear him down
In the same way that
Trump is a dictator who can't
Stand that
He can't understand that laws are
So that this part gets a little bit fun
Judge snow order that the Sheriff's Office
Turn over documents relating to Montgomery
Montgomery's investigation
These documents
Include flowcharts conversations inclusion
Between judge snow the doj
And the law firm of Covington & Burling
Which represents
The plaintiff
An Factory
On Friday plaintiff's lawyer Stanley young questioned Arpaio repeatedly about Montgomery
Montgomery was looking into judge snow
And was personally interested in that Pro
Both are intensified
In this route
They didn't ask Montgomery to make those
Sheridan testified earlier in the hearing
He told the detective and Sergeant working with Montgomery
Not to pursue the investigation.
Judge smell
Article goes on to explain
That I want to find exact part 2
It's f****** hilarious
Young
Who was employed by Covington and Burlington
This lawyer Young
Who's employed by Covington Burlington showed Arpaio I had received a fax from Montgomery
In November 2013
With an early version of a timeline showing event
In the Department of Justice is racial profiling
Have a racial profiling case in judge Snow's Court
As well as information about alleged wiretap again
On the back of the FAQ
Arpaio used a typewriter to make some
Note
Girls are we
2013 uses a typewriter on are we traveling through time right now
Handwritten notes about possible connections
And hand wrote on the same
F****** backup
Do you hand write notes about
About possible connections
Between judge snow in the law firm Covington in Burlington
Tiaras Berwyn
Turkey
These notes mentioned that former Arizona Senator John works with the law firm Covington & Burling
There's no mention
There's also mention
Judge Snow's wife work there as well
Which is not true
The notes read
Snow's snow confirmed by US Senate
Keilon Judiciary Committee on June 26th 2008 Obama takes office January 2009
Judge born 1959
It's all crazy nonsense
Handwritten
Scrawled on the back of this
Making up X
Together
All of it is
Desperately grasping at straws and
And clearly Montgomery was not working on a bank fraud
He was that was cover
Did he use
Note also noted quote
Wilcox husband Envy 150,000
That's the people
That were allegedly being
Being targeted as well as the number of Jehovah's Witness
Wilcox refer to for Maricopa County Supervisor Mary Rose Wilcox husband Earl
Arpaio said it was a reference to him
Can we just talk about how those of the whitest names in a row you just
Earl and Mary Rose Wilcox
Arpaio said it was a reference to him being among the 150,000 victims of bank fraud
That note quote totally floored Earl Wilcox
Who is seated in the courtroom and saw his own name in the doctor
On a monitor in the gallery
The wilcox's are vocal opponent
The Sheriff's Office had
To criminally indict Mary Rose Wilcox
And she won a civil suit against
The county for the
Baseless charges
So you get a sense of what's going on here
Arpeggio is
Acting illegally all the time
Super all the time
And
Montgomery
Was
Confidential informant
In quotes
Who is actually doing
Pretty illegal investigation
On his behalf
Yeah
That's the flavor we've got right now
Promise
This is going to develop
It's going to be a rose
Blossom
I would prefer
A Bloomin Onion
TGI Friday
If you want to do a roast battle
At this point the alleged 151000
People who include Donald Trump Alex Jones
Alex Jones is old
And what have you
His old cell phone number
His mom's birthday
Suns
Bar mitzvah
His great-grandmother's
She's a slave I don't know
Was used
Years ago in this court case
As alleged
Information
Of all people who live in Maricopa County
For being
Victims of bank fraud
In order to cover for an investigation
Into a federal judge
So that's what's going on
Alex
Kemp
It's possible he doesn't know that he did not know any of that
All of those words you just said are more words than Alex Jones can understand
Right you should have boiled baby Alex Jones
Headline
You just okay
Here's what you did
Alrighty you built
Gathered
Research
Natalie
You put a lot of work
Time and
Effort into
All of that point
To only one
Possible conclusion
You can then
Establish is reality
Even further
Where do you think in that line
Alex Jones Woodstock
He wouldn't eat just part where you said
Here's what we're going to do
Do you know where he would stop as soon as any like indication that he's not totally right
It's Mike zullo a game of getting into how they don't actually know anything
I'm going to come down right now on the side of Alex
Being duped
Because he's an idiot
I think that it's possible
I think there's pretty strong and
Later,
How many profit later he's going to talk about how great he talks to him and stuff like that
I believe there is a vested interest
Alex
Defending him
I don't know if
If he's super willing to be
Established
So many times the Alex Jones is always super willing to
Tell that's true
Truly horrific
Nightmarish pile of garbage human being
To suck up to
In the same way that he wants to suck up to
To the f****** dudes
Alleged Nazi Jesse James
As well as alleged
Since you got a lot of pain.
We got a lot of ground to cover so I'm going to skip this next clip.
Again we talked about it earlier
Azula repeating
In different language that they don't really actually know what's
They don't know what the
80-in
Next clip explaining
Some of Dennis Montgomery
Pedigree
And where it comes from which is actually evidence of my
That he is able
To discover
People private information
Through techno
He's able to employ on his own
As opposed to Batman who just kind of
Hangs out in the bush
Well I I don't want to go into too much of what he said
Actually mr. Montgomery in this is public
Was a contractor who developed the
Hacking software
That could penetrate firewalls
A computer's breach them
Take over as the administrator and remain undetected for about an hour and a half
And download whatever they are
Timeframe from the movie
Jack location
We can mask him for an hour and a half
Real something that only lasts
For an hour-and-a-half because it's a lie
I think it might be alive
But I do believe that he has some hacking
I have done some research
And figured out exactly
What
Dennis Montgomery was doing when he had government
Contrast subtitle of this episode is
So
I told you about Dennis Montgomery
He founded a company called etrepid technology
Andy Montgomery Burns
Thank you
We're going to burn him
So like I said it started out as like a
The casino tool
Eventually I started targeting Sino industry they started to branch of government
In 2003 or thereabouts right around
Dennis claimed that he had developed software that would analyze barcodes that appeared on Al Jazeera
Any used these Dakota
Information gleaned
To predict impending terrorist
This is what he develop
He's a study student of the Kabbalah is that what you're saying
Barcode barcode
He's just
So here's hoping they're planning
The terrorist attack
Through the barcode
On YouTube
Yeah
Terrorist attacks
Needlessly,
Make sense
No. No no
Sup
At that point
The gentleman named Tom Ridge was Homeland Security director
He was convinced
I'm about this software and that it was legit
Information
Raise the terror alert multiple times
He went so far as
To evacuate public building
A call for flights to be grounded
Based on interpretation
Of barcodes on Al Jazeera
Through Dennis Montgomery's software
It is don't tell me that's real
Very real living a dumb enough to believe that
It's so real
Legit like you know is it in the Kabbalah where it's like they they put
Certain letters of
Weird Bible Code stuff
It's the same sort of logic
Spanish
Just because I don't want to ruin where this is going to go
I don't want to ruin
The entire end of the story yet
The CIA agent who was involved in like
The implementation of
This technology and it being brought in
Requested anonymity but he was quoted later
Talking about the meeting where they
Learned about this
This information is being
This is so embarrassing
Yeah there was no use
It was dimple
What's the status
I'll just spell out the rest of the story now because why not
Theory
There's no way they could have killed JFK
These people bikes
You f****** stupid
Such incompetence considered
Play f****** amorous
When you have a conclusion that you want to arrive at and someone gives you
You like
Confirmation possible version of of your conclusion
Inside Job
So
This guy
His software
That does Montgomery his software is implemented and it's used
To make Terror prediction
Is it what is it what is it even look like
This is 2003 level software
Don't
TuneIn and this is back when you had to use
3 by 5 floppy
No it.
My heart. Where you would have I mean
We're using or using
Let's call it Windows 2000
You've noticed
Windows
Well whatever
It's Montgomery let's call it Windows 95 I don't know if it's like MLB The Show
Bass windows
Our first
GUI
And this guy puts
Cinema City
That analyzes
What's on Al Jazeera
So that means
What
You got screenshots of Al Jazeera it takes him 5 minutes
To download picture of Al Jazeera
Can you pull up a command prompt and it looks at it like
Does one of those like this software had to have been the exact same level of Technology
Where in the world is
Without rockapella
There's no
Possible way that was even
Real software
Fascinating number generator
Well here's what
Alright a little bit down the line
And they realize that Dennis Montgomery was just making s*** up
And I know about the
Not only that
These barcodes on Al Jazeera
Where would you put dance he just made even that part
So the FBI didn't is a conman of ridiculous
Csbi did a counter investigate
History of fraud
Etihad
He had extensive gambling problem with G step
A CIA agent like I said was quoted as saying that the whole thing was very embarrassing
His former lawyer
Representative
Which is weird cuz that's my son's name
It's not the same guy as far as I can tell
What's up
I think we can rule out Michael j.fox was basically the characters
The Secret of My Success
That's right
Former lawyer describe Dennis Montgomery is a con artist
Anclote a habitual liar
Engaged in fraud
Defended him
So that's
The guy that's the guy
Somehow
Lake
The conman then I just get like catch me if
You can memories in my head lyrics
Continue to call me if I'm not there too many movies
Where are Secret Service in our cia's in our intelligence
Community
Competent
When there's so many more stories were there
Right right
CIA
Stupid that deserves our public enter
Trista we want we like to
Create
Feel alot better if I knew they were stupid
Jordan Montgomery
No
51 really great
Yes you do
So in 2006
Does gubernatorial race
Visit Nevada
He claimed
His own business
Casino chips
And $100,000 in cash in exchange for favor
Said that
Committed
That was his that was his like
York I committed a crime
It's not great for immunity beforehand or did you just call a press conference on clear
So he claimed he claimed that they gave him all of this money in exchange for favor
Sprite soda Montgomery
Claimed that he had emails from Gibbons
Private email
That proved that
He was he was not lying
Gibbons said that the emails were fake
A computer expert testified
Must challenge the authenticity of the email
The court case was thrown out
And 18 months
FBI investigation concluded the Gibbons did nothing wrong
They cleared him of all charge
18 months
A US intelligence community
A US House Ethics Committee investigating
The charges as well
And found no wrongdoing
Now why is this case super important
Montgomery is a liar
An idiot
To falsify documents
Super Why
There is an indication
That was
Borne out in court
He has
Fraudulently created
And so now we're citing his.
I meant on the Alex Jones
Be a hoax
Give
Investigation
All the shows
He has no credibility
Has been shown to create.
Do you commit a crime with you if you accuse that dude
Committing a crime
Then say
Happened so
Heat Montgomery's off the hook for bribe
Cuz he didn't do just driving buddy
Or making false statements
There was actually
The trial he would have had to testify that
And testified that then that would be perjury
He would have perjured himself under oath
When he went to trial
Said he'd
Do any of these claims
Initiated
And then he never said any
If you have anyone committed a crime
So this is the guy who's the route
Of these
Navigation
Fake
Database that I was Jones exciting as evidence
Himself and Trump
Being spider
It's
Clear at this point
So that is not true
Absolutely not
Morass
On that story than anyone has ever
I promise
That's an expose
That you just did that no one will really ever hit and nose hairs
Do you know what the reason that they're complaining about how the FBI is making no moves on this stuff
And there's a media blackout
But they were talking about now is why there's a media blackout
The guy has no credibility
What was the
Yeah you just
You just kicked it you just kick the ass you kept all the answer the story
It's not done
We still have to get to Larry klayman
Seriously
This is amazing
This next
So we're still in Missoula interview
And Jerome corsi who is
Been silently a part of this the whole time
But then
To try and
Ouch
For the situation that's going on
And I want to play this clip
Little another side argument I want to make right
I want to see 4
Bikes
Actually
Couple of weeks
Used car dealer
Speaks the truth
Carefully
Put together
Here's why play that clip
He's desperately trying to provide credibility for Mike zullo
Right
But
He doesn't realize that if you look at the history of Jerome corsi
That's a liar vouching for your credibility
Which actually hurts
Jerome corsi
Laid out in the past has written
A book about Obama's birth certificate
He was also a member of the Swift
Swift boat lettering
Yeah so he is that so when he comes in and says this guy is honest as the day is long
That means
Oh we just both have the same propaganda goal
That's all he said
Anyway I'm looking and being like dude I love this guy's lies
We have one more clip
It one more clip with Mike zullo again
Spelling out very clearly and
And very overtly
But he doesn't know anything
There's no information that he has
And in this clip he even let slip
The he can't even confirm that anybody was ever wiretap
Which is kind of unfortunate for the
Just claims he's trying to
Well if I'm Sheriff arpaio's account is
The timeline and I'm going by memory
I understand
This alleged wiretapping
Got orange seeds
Is when they were pursuing Sheriff Arpaio under a criminal charge
Was dropped
And at the same time
Individuals that were
Case moved over to a private Law Firm
The Clearblue a civil
Proceeding ensued
Hey this is talking about Covington & Burling
Again this is
Basically what we covered earlier but
Let's be clear
Alex is trying to say that like you don't have DNA testing can't prove it's a duck
The expression is if it walks like a duck and talks like a duck
It's a duck
Going the other direction with a duck
Metaphor
I love it I love it
Starting in the middle of Forrest Fenn like
Hold on one second we're going to need a blood
A son f****** prove
Yeah
Prove that's a duck
Uist son-of-a-b****
You and also it shows that Alex Jones has a higher standard of proof about like what is a duck
Anything else we talked about on his show of evidence
Is is glaring
So we're going to leave Mike zullo now that is been
Who
Time in the Sun
As it were
I don't necessarily have a ton against Mike zullo except that I found
In an article
He's part of the Joe Arpaio thing I hope it gets hit by a
That's enough
Done and done from the Phoenix
From the Phoenix New Times I did find an article about the
The case against Arpaio and it's interesting that Mike's
I was called to testify
Invoke the 5th
What a shocker
He pleaded the fifth against self-incrimination in court which means
I mean
You're not always guilty when you plead the Fifth
But in this case
It does seem to imply if he wants to go out there publicly and talk about how there's a railroad in case being done its
If you're in if you're in court you'd want to
Provide the evidence than Ingo
Afraid of what might come out
Anyone who is under 18
Do not say a goddamn word
Whether or not he's guilty
And whether or not you should be in jail
Those things
But I do think
Do not say a goddamn thing to the cops
Ladies and gentlemen
So now at this point one thing I can tell you
Sodus Point
We transition our investigation are we go to how Alex
End of the week
This gentleman who's come up a couple times
Larry klayman
On the Friday
Episode of the show
Meanwhile throughout the week
He was yelling about this evidence and how it proved
Everything that is
He's been saying is correct
They have a database
Esme
Baba baba
Savannah's Larry klayman as a guest
Here is the introduction of how he brings him into
Show
World
Larry
The clay man
Exposing 4 is fine going on against the president against Congress has been in the news for years
Here in just a moment Larry klayman legendary Larry klayman
Little bird
But here's where we getting to where this is
Exeter Murphy
Convince
When will iOS
Devin Nunez
Presented this new evidence
No he didn't
He got it from Larry klayman
Larry klayman
That's what Alex just said
And in this interview
Larry klayman
Says as much
Do we have any evidence that Larry klayman would have talked to him
Only based on Larry's word
Speculation
Episode
In some ways because
The history does bear out there is
Look I can't I can't prove it
These Liars are always lying
But
If only
But based on Larry klayman telling of it he had been trying to get this information to Devin Nunez for quite a while
And succeeded
So
All of this stuff with Trump feels like anime
I wrote it on the back of
I threw a paper airplane in the directions
I have been doing everything I can to get the
Information iduna
Again that's Montgomery not
Claim
But
Establish those are the only Farm
The communication that Alex
Velcro
One thing that's important to lay out here is that Larry klayman is Dennis Montgomery's lawyer now
The former lawyer called him a con artist
Habitually engaged in fraud
Now
Larry klayman is
The two of them met
Through Joe Arpaio
When
Being represented by Larry klayman
Dennis Montgomery
The confidential
So we're having
A wonderful romantic comedy
We're taking slaves to do a love triangle we take a slight break from all of this information
We've been laying out
Introduction Alex Jones realizes that you got to pay the bill
Reclaiming on Injustice
Case against the interstate going on years ago
Supporting
If you don't mind products
First off you're crazy we have the best
Can organic soil silver and
National surgeon
Batman fractured the biggest manufacturer in the country
Tell you who's our private labeling but this is an iodine. Her attitude
I think you might have just breached his contract
That's not that's not fair
To Tom's of Maine
The contract says you can't say who made it
Tom's of Maine
Whoops whoops I f***** up
The time I've not reviewed their contract so I
So here we go
Alex Jones
Full on Bayou
Of Larry klayman
I'll be back
Bayou
It would take too long
He knows who Larry klayman is
No one knows who Larry klayman is
No one knows who Larry klayman is his bio
So I will
Would you like to know
Would you like to know some fun facts about Larry klayman
Following claimants behavior in a 1992 trial in California Federal Court
Judge William Lehman from his courtroom for life
Hold on
Five years later in a separate case in New York clayman's Behavior led men
Chin
To issue a lifetime ban on the attorney practice
Single all before him
Well then eaten sounds like he's in the mafia
Have barred him from Pratt
In front of him
4life
Claiming his written about his dealings with do that
Yeah
If you're judging
Nope it's essential
It's essentially an extreme version of holding someone
Absolutely
Get to say he's out of order for
Flaming has written about his dealings
So Cal and was quote obviously drunk
At the bench
I don't believe you but I don't believe
In 2017
Received a $25,000 retainer from a woman facing criminal charge
And she accused him of not providing legal services in return
The Florida Bar Association
Can I claim it agreed
To pay off a small portion
He was reprimanded by the Association
Hey
Dude
He's filed at least you don't have to pay
He has filed at least 18 lawsuits against the Clinton
Raven from accusations of racketeering
To a bunch of s*** about Benghazi
In the wake of the 26
Shooting of Dallas police officer
Claimant filed a lawsuit against Obama
Former US Attorney General Eric Holder the Nation of Islam leader Louis Farrakhan
Al Sharpton
Founders of black lives matter movement
That led to the shooting
Claiming amended the complaint to include Dallas police officer
And Hillary Clinton and George Soros as defense I mean this is super weird but I'm reading off your
Ice cream former San Antonio Spurs star Tim Duncan
I don't know how he got in there
But he is part of the conspiracy
That case
It was just a poet was
And all of them
Definitely like nobody's going to take a lot to get disbarred
What even is being a lawyer if you can just
Is anybody
Also James Carville Cajun
Call Tim luggage
Claiming his mother for $50,000
Did he win
Seeking reimbursement for medical care provided to his maternal grandmother
After claiming brother told Newsweek magazine
It was your brother
Got to stretch
It was on
So he's just
Into October 2014 play the Obama Administration
Secretly allowed Ebola virus
Caucasian race and Jewish Christian religion
Can't imagine any other possible
Ground Zero mosque
He was involved in that
Love those lies
2015 Clement
Dennis Montgomery
Do during the day
I think he's
Media horror
Well yeah
Lawyer I know but like what is he too is probably a sleazy lawyer who I don't know
Who knows
Settlement
Listen
Open a cast
Probably I wouldn't be surprised if it's Better Call Saul type of guy
Super good at that has a little bit with Dennis Montgomery
Defamation lawsuit on behalf of
Against James
The author of a book called pay any price
Greed power in the endless war
The lawsuit alleged
Describe Montgomery is the Maestro behind
Former US officials
Believe was the most elaborate
And dangerous hoaxes in American history
This is that software we discussed earlier
So
That's such a solid
How do you get to be good of a con man
That you can just make
Make that s*** up
Just like
It couldn't have even looked
Like like that's the thing about computer I don't think I don't think you would understand
Show the Doppler effect
Hero to take software thing but because
People don't have that key
Computer savvy they're willing to
Like they're just like
This is why we can't have old people in
Power anymore
They don't even know
It's like we can't do it
Weekends like
They don't even live in the world we live in
DMC hacking
Was not some sort of
Clicked on a f******
Like that's all it was
Like there's no real hacking going on like what people
Sophisticated
Complicated
It's really good stuff but
All of this
People that we have
Out-of-touch
Let me get through I Larry klayman spy
Cuz Alex refuses to get the bundle
Well you know what
Alex was right in
And saying that he
You did not have
We do
Clayman
On behalf of Dennis Montgomery file this lawsuit
In 2016 in federal court dismissed lawsuit
Repealed
Appeal was
I believe is Marine Le Pen
Prime ministerial candidate
Kim and will call her affection
Brothers at the great lawsuit
Is legally fashion
But then the other side of it is just finding was that
You can't
Considerate defamation when you're in
Political
Describing someone
Political beliefs
Isn't defamation
If there is
Credibility to
Larry klayman filed at least
Free lawsuits claiming that Obama was not eligible to be president cuz his birth certificate was fake
Okay he tried to defend Cliven Bundy as his lawyer
Good as we all know Cliven Bundy is a crazy person
As is Larry klayman as is
Clayman
History of discipline
Escorts and he had no clearance or standing to assign himself
As someone else's lawyer
Cliven Bundy
Did not
His help at all
I would ask
The direction where the judge
You said you were
More than you
Claiming
Century Bike Tour
20 judges
I'm a victim
Yeah
Claimant declare to the conservative rally in Washington DC that quote
This President is not a president of We the People
He's a president of his people
Whoops
That's probably rarely recharge
He urged the crowd to begin a quote
Second American nonviolent Revolution
And demanded that President Obama quotes
Put the Quorum down and figuratively come out with his hands up
Weeks Later
Put the Quran down
Claimant sponsored reclaim America rally
In Lafayette Square across from the white
Calling for the president's removal
Claim and stated that if Obama did
The first America
Can on violin
I can't think of one
I think I think we had a lot more of the of the
Violent revolution
Did not resign conservative activists would meet
Whoops bad use of terms
Considering that now all they talk about is how there's a shadow government
Anyway
Clayman
Billions to occupy Washington DC
He was between 130 and 200 people
Also
They're going to talk about
Announce already referenced
He won a court case
About
So we're talking about his
We're not talking about as many and varied and magnificently
Yeah we're going to talk about it
Klayman vs. Obama
Where he was
Two contestants
A phone and internet Metairie
Good
That's a good
We can agree that
Like a lot of that stuff is
Pretty
It's pretty f*****-up horrifying and a police state
So he brought this case in front of a judge
If you're a judge
And you Google this
It's f****** guy win
Like no Get It Go
The judge will
Would have a brew
Out of the Court
The Apollo
What you should do
2013 and US federal judge Richard J Leon
He ruled
Book collection of America
Telephone metadata
He had insanely
Legitimate
Concern
About
Call
This program could violate people's Fourth Amendment
Against unreasonable searches
Publicly
And then actually
Comes into the ruling
Cuz that it wasn't before
He ruled in favor
Of
Clayman
The guy whose last name is strange
Alright
Defendant
Or plaintiff
The original trial was held
So they brought the state and the judge agreed with the arguments
That metadata collection violates the Fourth Amendment
In his ruling was to say I suspend my
Rent for 6-month
To allow
The government
To appeal
That he
Conjunction
That any
Metadata collection regarding strange or Clayman
Might have to stop
Every
Bit of information that had
Had to be destroyed
Ruling for 6-month
Allowing for appeal
During that
6 months
They can
Still collect their meditate
No
Have to change for the next 6 months
And
Basically
The appeals court found that
Because the program had been ended they didn't have a responsibility to rule on the legality
Of the Fourth Amendment
Secondarily they found
That
There's no evidence
The could be provided
They claiming
Or strain
Actually worse B on it
Or had their metadata collected
And therefore they had no standing in
Import
To bring the sky
Even though the government did collect bulk metadata because they couldn't prove their meditate
It was collected
And they can't represent
Tyranny of the
Part of their argument was the bear Verizon
That the government is collected Verizon
Yeah but the thing is
Hold on
The government admitted that they collected business
Through Verizon
Like Verizon business
Individual
You and I
Cell phone owner
They collected things through a different
Part of Verizon's business
This is dubious
I don't like that I don't
I do think
That based on the law
And based on
I'm telling you
I read these Court decision
Yeah I know cuz your loot
And I don't think
That they did
The decisions were Rock
I think the appeals court was right
He didn't have the standing
But at the same time the conclusion is correct
The metadata collection
Is a nun
Reasonable certainty
He was right and they probably stopped it
I think I think it has
In a lot of way
I just don't want all the information we can find it has stopped
Based on
What were afraid is actually the truth
Larry klayman is right on that count
He's wrong about everything else
His claims that he beat the NSA in a court case is wrong
He had a case where they agreed with him or they were
Inclined to agree with him
Suspended judgment
Anyway
I'm spent most work
I think any human being has ever done
Here is where
Larry klayman
This clip
Do a little bit of a dance or he has to be sure that he has not
Seen any of the information
We on Sunday
Via
Mother fobs other work Weathers
Publishing things have been out there in federal court
Showing the Trump was being surveilled
What's a boilermaker
Montgomery system for a long time to do this together that is wanting
Shepherd
Smash.com
I apologize that was Alex
Trying not to implicate himself and
So
You're right I am
Yeah
Larry
Breaking down
What he sees as
Montgomery
Declassified Chaser involve dinner
So much
About a bunch of bulshit
And also
Also on this episode
Nickname is Esperanto
Benghazi attack
Tonto
Spiranto is the hero of Benghazi
He came off his is fairly reasonable but also pretty aggressive
At the end of the interview you said like
People are afraid like they wanna arrest George Soros and they're afraid
I'll do it
I'll go in I'll do it
So Alex later uses that as like
Hey Tanto paronto was George Soros
Afraid we should arrest him
I'll go in and do it I'm a Marine
No
It's like he's like
You think Sunday should be arrested
He's ready to go do it himself
They just being held back a real Marine
Benghazi
Do we know that
There's a movie
Monkeys are real too
Oh he's a real dude I can't risk going on Alex Jones
Disrespected
Weather
I'm against it seemed like a pretty decent dude
But they also reflect
Lowe's
He is probably been kicked out of only one
Court and never allowed to be there
In this day
Richard
Cannabis first name now is the NSA
Stop
And then now he has Larry klayman on
We had a lot of guests
He has to man
You still scrambling
You scrambling
The fire
Sing a little bit
I don't know maybe next week I will be different you know this this week
You started with the at the end of the Ring right now
IOU did his big
Pizzagate apology
That could reinvigorate him a little bit we'll see
600 million pages of information
Again went the only
Evidence we can find of him being
A contractor at all is
Creating that software that analyzes Al Jazeera
Questionable weather in that capacity he would have access at all
47 hard drives or 600 million
Documents
If he if he did that have all those things
That's pretty crazy and you must have been going way outside of his way in order to get those things which
Is massively illegal
All is all the
It's all about
Much like Mike zullo
And a
Really trying hard to make sure that people don't think
Classified
And we need to put it in the right hands
Chicken committed a crime
And what he told me was on there
United States
156 judges
President Trump when he was a businessman
Oprah
D'amato's
Take a step back
The only time that he could have possibly had access to nfac
Is around. Of 2003
He was involved and was massively discredited
He was thrown out with
The FBI's investigation on him and found to be a fraud
There's no way you'd ever be able to get any sort of clearance after that
I'm listening
That al-jazeera
Did work
A trojan horse
And have you considered this
Right so
Like
I'm listening
Which is the other one the acronym
It from the very beginning
Like from the very beginning
Because the al-jazeera software was on there
Montgomery
Point a Curative
Every level of government
Because
He is
Actually
The guy who
Occam's razor
I don't like this
Simplest explanation
Possibly have
Information
Stolen
The early 2010
He's working with Joe Arpaio
And he has this database of Maricopa County
Victims of bank fraud
Which is now being repurposed
As people who are being spied on
Including Trump Alex Jones all this s***
600 million sound so f******
Made up
Where do you get 600 million documents
Genuinely
What
What area of the government other than maybe that bulk
Metadata collection
System
Close to 600 million
Everything
And even if it was about meditate
Documents
Point-by-point
GPS location
So where would you get
600 million.
And it would be like I said
From
14 years
Is it is there even that much information in the f****** Library of Congress
In The Archives of all the stuff
Is a made-up game
Jillian.
Point is that Larry klayman is coming out as a lawyer
Being on Alex Jones
To discuss this stuff
Wyoming
He is coming on
But he only has secondary knowledge of he has no idea what's actually in these documents
Exact
How old is much like Rodger Stone on his doctor's appointment they can't repeat that
Regal Theater on July 5th
Yeah
If these same games that are so it
It's propaganda even though
Right
You got
600 million
I don't know I just
You got to get a taste of the coke to make sure that it's real I'd be so scared
You don't
I probably run away that's why you don't buy my drugs
Freeman run the other direction
I like I don't want anything
As everybody knows
You take your Coke pinky nail
You put it into
You make sure the
The kokusai quote
So if it's next one
Is Clayman
Confirming
He did
In fact disgusting
Things with
Devin Nunes
Come forward with information
And that's what we've done and we
Coming forward and then some
Either all of this is
Just a fantasy world lies there's a possibility
And that's where he shot and that's where he got a lot of this information that has led to this is very confusing.
History
Nunez is acting up and not certainly not acting as
The house
Intelligence committee chairman
And if he is acting impact on this information that has its roots
And someone who has
Complete conman engaged
In habitual fraud
Said the document showed no indication of
I think all of this
I think it's like a zigzag
Nunez being shook
Because there was
Came out the other day about
The inner of the meetings that he had with the Turkish ambassador
About
Extraditing
Gulen guy
Turkey
52b
Erdogan believes that this
Cleric was responsible for
The fake poop
I'm pretty sure it was
Totally
He wants this guy extradited
United States
Does not believe
The appropriate
I have Flynn was being paid
To help extradite
That came out
The meeting
Between Flynn
And the Turkish ambassador
Was also attended by Devin Nunes
He was also there
Really
So now we sit with the information
Because now we have information that may
Yeah at this point on Steven Weber recording this
Donut
Connecticut to come out
There's indications and sources
Anonymous sources are indicating that he might have cut a deal
Anonymous sources are Anonymous sources are the grain of salt
This is a possibility
Possible it's not proven it's not.
Part the only part
That's hard to swallow
If you look at all of this
Everybody would go down
Yeah
Genuinely
The entire government
Get taken down
From top to bottom
Not everyone everyone but like
Big a deal as we
It's hard to say I think the truth is probably somewhere in between
But the reality is that like
All that stuff that isn't
We can't prove
We can prove that Nunez was in that meeting with flan and the Turkish Ambassador attacked doesn't look good
New nurses in the f****** balls of
And
Newness has given
Handy's
With a little bit of prostate
Imitation of him disappearing the night before he went to the White House
Apparently meeting with somebody
Like there's a lot of stuff that's
Real f*****-up
Yeah so
The shutdown for
My thought nobody should be allowed to do any
My thought is that I don't think he was meeting with Larry klayman that night
But some of that stuff does relate
To this
We meeting with Larry
It's possible
I don't know
He's one of those guys who I don't care if he's alive today so I have no idea
Great
Is essentially that a lot of his stuff
Nunez's Behavior
Singularly
Motivated at 5 is Montgomery in
Information which weave
Pretty clearly I think on this episode
Idle take
Much clearer that is
Part of
His behavior was
Is influenced by
Clayman and Montgomery Inn
Also the conspiracy theory Community is
Is a flame
There's a lot of like on the blog
Another message board
Why are people investigating Montgomery
I just did
Yeah suck it this is even more this is kind of even more
Interesting is that
Conspiracy theory blogs
And yet the same
It's hard not to
To look at reality and go
Some kind of conspiracy
Spira see is happening
Been stuck
Pump fluid
Of idiot
Happening all the same time
Weird coincidence
Almost as likely as anything else
I think you just as likely
Like with the Montgomery thing right
Those idiots believe
It's just as likely what's going on right now is that everybody
Conspiracy
Bushfire
I think that I've been wanting to bring up for a while and I'll
Deal with
Go to slightly
Liar Alex Jones
Stuff is b*******
I don't want
Paint with a broad brush
All people who believe in conspiracy theories
People who are very smart and real good research
Video
The entire conspiracy community
By attacking Alex Jones
Is unfair
And I think that is easy to
Make that assumption if we're not clear about
There's a lot of people who also believe Alex Jones is full of s***
Believing
Conspiracies
There goes there are
Chemtrails got a cam
Sure there are not stupid crazy people in that world
There is a lot of stupid
And we fall somewhere
Absolutely
So this next clip
Is Larry klayman explaining why this is a matter of
Immediate
Importance
Do something that has to be dealt with Now or Never
Exactly like how we need to finally get to the bottom of it
Certificate Lord never will file three court cases about it
He's risked his life
Please come forward
You know how a brain aneurysm works right like
Just died from a brain
Aneurysm
Yeah
Any moment he needs to be interview right now
But again it's just right
Create a sense of immediacy about it it's also trying to create sort of a tragic hero story around this
Obvious liar
What possible
I'd like to interview
That's a good point
Colorado podcast
I meant be him on all of our
Carnival
Who's next
Your perfect Sunday
First date
Bistro or movie
What is a bistro
No idea
You don't have it I legitimately think I flashback to like French class
I think my brain just like snack before midnight
Richard linklater
Two of Us movie
Anyway it's Richard linklater is out there
Exhausting
This next clip claimant gets into talking a little bit more about
Montgomery himself in a situation
Montgomery from
Alex
It's so easy
Unsuccessfully. It's so easy to destroy his credibility
All it took was like
A couple Google searches
Again Google
Injustice
Couple
Couple article
Like it's not that hard you find this guy is a massive
Snake oil fill
Self-abuse
And if he wasn't
Being used
For propaganda
Purposes I agree with
He would be
It would be fun
Is he going to make it there's a there's a there's a there's always a part of me that's going to be on this side of the guy trying to f***
I think that there also is an archetype
Of that like down and out
Two-time loser gambling loser
Kind of guy who just like try to pull one last for
We're all in Grain to pull for that
Like we all want to see the little guy
Strike out against the system and it's unfortunate
That this little guy striking out against the system is being used
Propagandistic lie to support the system
Yeah it's
It's like we all want a Robinhood and they all wind up
Robin Hood Robin Hood is working for the Sheriff of Nottingham
Turns out
Yeah that's that's
Monstera Sheriff of not
You know what we got to get back
The most
That f****** nonsense the sheriff's movement all that stuff that's for another day
Inaccurate
That's the guy who wrote the book about
Involved
And again
Larry klayman
As lawyer for Dennis Montgomery
Sue this writer
Was unsuccessful
The case was thrown out
Of course so now you coming
You failed
Obama's immigration
That didn't happen
Which is why we're proceeding on a separate track
And he's a great man.
But I was just talked to him he's staying out of
He's staying out of
If you say Arpaio is a great man
I automatically with
You lose all The Sopranos
You do not belong in the
You one-hundred-percent or you're not at least you're not in touch
With your own Humana
But then Alex being like
I'll talk to Arpaio you staying out of this
Our personal reason Arpaio said
That
Montgomery's
Investigation was
Junk
That's a good reason
Stay out of it so now I want to bring this back
To this
Phoenix
News article that I was talking about earlier
Right
I wanted I wanted
Play the song again Robert Young
Is the lawyer
Let's try encase
According to reports
Presented in court in November 2014 to outside experts with
Experience of the nsa's
For the Sheriff's Office
And concluded that Montgomery was quote
A complete and total fraud
Young brought this up in court to Arpaio
Quote
At least by November 2014
You knew Dennis Montgomery was a fraud
The question
That was putting it lightly
Arpaio said
That was putting it lightly Arpaio said noted they have been working
They've been working Montgomery for a year at that point
So we decided to
To stop paying
Young went on to present email records showing members of arpaio's team we're still in touch with
After that into 2015
Would a law enforcement officer have to be incredibly stupid to continue working with someone known to be a
Total fraud
Young ass
Arpaio's Attorney John Masterson objective
The question
Which judge snow system
How can you say that
Okay technically that is
I'm going to go with you
The answer is as humans is a
The fair question in court
Probably
Masterson accused young of insulting
Younger
Reminded are piled
The judge snow had asked him in April weather Montgomery
And never brought up the
Blinds
Begin where the faxes
With the weird type writing on the back
Or other documents Montgomery had made
That included judge snow
Quote I never saw the timeline when he asked me the question
Arpaio said
Do you regret not
Telling him those things that April young a
Quote in retrospect
Maybe I should have brought it up but it never came to my mind at that time
Arpaio set
So f*** you
Is really not
Really relevant
He's admitted in court
That this guy is a complete and total fraud
Admitted
She kept working with him or his Department
After an essay
Investigators evaluated his hard drives as a fraud
This is again this is like Marie Le Pen fascist
Situation
You should be allowed to prove
I think
It is a legal imperative
The only reason I disagree is.
It's irrelevant
Like that
If you were to bring a court case
Specifically designed to prove that he's an idiot
That it's relevant
But because it's a
Contempt of court case
Haha it's
It's irrelevant to the matter at hand
Are you an idiot
Which I still love that the Apollo in the eventual death penalty
Should be under
You
Probably should
Unless you're in text
At this point play Michigan
You should exit
I don't
I think he doesn't deserve it
I'd like to see a court trial though
I don't want any violence to happen
Come to him except for sanction
Because of his ass
Don't believe in the death penalty believe that
I want to be clear that me and Jordan know a ton more than is on this podcast
And please look into Joe arpaio's history
Based on what we wanted our
Not even close we had to edit some stuff out
Nearly
We had to pause I had to
Go outside and walk around just based on how bad
So please look into that again or files a monster
We have to get back to the matter at hand which is
This interview with Larry klayman
Where he insist
Incredible and then beyond
He goes to lay the blame
The Trump spying
And all this s***
On people who are no longer
The current predicament
Is the Fault
A people who have not been
Involved
For quite a while
Conference
I don't know what's going on I don't know why that hasn't happened
Are we clear
Generally agreeable a lot of times
The grain of salt
They're sharing
Not
Sometimes it's manipulative sometimes it is people protecting their
It goes both ways sometimes it is legit sometimes
Dino Dan
There's a very
The message
I think that is most important is that intelligence communities dualite
It's people a lot of the time
But sometimes you should look for evidence
You should look for truth
As opposed to
Disbelieving
But things are said to be
Take things as
They come to
Look for fat
Having knowledge
I've realized
Legitimately
That was this
Smoothest you've ever been
Legitimately I'm getting to the point where I'm realizing that if I ever want this to take off I'm going to have to start mimicking some of Alex Jones's behaviors
So I'm going to start with look for dumbfucks
Meanwhile our listeners
Are really awesome
And they're really cool
Yeah I don't think that you guys are
Maybe a couple
Assuming we have like
Statistically
But I got to assume there's something
Guys guys we've had a we had a rough Park
I have just learned more about Joe Arpaio deal understand where we're coming from
Blame the wine for me being smooth and for me lashing out hypothetical listener
The Android record on Wednesdays Wednesdays is Dan therapy day
Anyway here we go back back to this where he blames like
Clapper
I think I've done it
Punch
The Director of National Intelligence
To get rid of all these dudes who are no longer in office
Flapper is not
Got to get rid of them
John
I think the example that Alex keep going back to is that
Clapper
John Brennan
Who I was
God
In between him
Sworn you said that you should watch his mouth
He should be careful about things he said
Motherfuking watch your mouth I mean talks kind of message
I get I get where Alex's interpretation of it being like people I watch am out
I know that Floyd has racial connotations
Play I get where Alex takes
Some umbrage at that but I also would understand how anybody was in
Community
Noises mistake
Of the president running his mouth
Are you can piss off foreign powers
Accidentally
Well you didn't even f****** shake merkel's hands like a
Put these things to insult foreign powers that are our allies
Who have deep
Jeep
Blood-filled
Alliances
And he can insult them
And you should watch your mouth
You should be really careful what you say
Diplomacy
Now there's a reason we have
A department
Hayirli devoted to
Diplomacy
And there's a reason
Filled
With people
Or diplomat
Instead
Who actually has been quoted
Sing he didn't want the job
And his wife
Do it
And then they have not stuff that
Department
Everybody
It confused
And now it started
Bomb North Korea
Rr4 but you know
Like it
It's strange
To be so obsessed
With domestic policy
The shed out of Syria killing more civilians than we've killed
So long
Repeat very
Non
Like it's not even
Defensible the variability
Retarget offended so many of our allies
When we
Threatened
So many countries
This is why
This is Larry klayman saying that everything in the world
Essentially is Obama
Excellent
I'm certain
Again he's talking about all this information
That Montgomery
But he hasn't looked
From before Obama's
So again he's sure that it's all about
Probably
Great I'll take your word for it lady claiming guy who is
Clearly I'm credit
Sure they always
It was a bubble bomb originally
About Obama
Obama open
Other countries
That'll super unfortunate
And if it's Dominic zample like
Brazil recently had a coup you know
The ones where they hold their leaders responsible
Benjamin Netanyahu has never been held responsible for any of the
Literally not allowed to run for
Is legally bar
Currently home
Doorly illegal
So he uses these two countries as an example to make a point
Long is no longer the president
Needs to be held responsible for b*******
Why's that
It's incredibly
It is insane like you could
It's the FBI buying software based on Al jazeera's barcode
Yeah it's right up
Italia
Cuisine
That's the last clip that I have for Larry clayman's interview
If you want to know more about him and you want him to speak
Checkers
He probably has written books
I didn't look into that
If you want to
He or his
Entire argument laid out
I will link it
On the website
He has an article that he wrote
Newsmax
That just lays out his entire argument
About Montgomery
It's all lies
But at least
If you go there
It's basically all the stuff
My cut out from the
Cuz it's just boring and a lot of it
It was covered by Mike zullo
A lot of it is just repetitious
Here is a
The Funplex
Play man doesn't say anything
Because Alex Jones
Just trying to
Really desperately make you believe
The people he has on his show
Are real
Manchester
Not
Sesame Street puppets
Sometimes you know
Fake Pizza Gastrology
Hey Jude
Yeah so I mean like your death to 99% accurate
Don't know how you would
Quantify what
Percent your guests are accurate but I know that if there was a system
99%
Ambitious
People news site 99%
Seems ambitious right I think the most
Spectabile new sources that I trust
Have maybe 80
Yeah 75% is amazing
Sing to me
Like I said I told you on the last episode of and reading foreign policy
And a lot of 0
Imma walk
A lot of stuff that I've been reading in the area it seems incredibly probably looked into things that are cited
But I still think they get things wrong from time to time
It's every Citizen's
Responsibility to take in
Media and news
Evaluate
That's your responsibility
It's not the media's responsibility to your right every time
When they're wrong
It is the responsibility
To own up to it
Exactly correction
To make sure that everybody knows that
Which place is like the New York Times Washington Post
These sorts of
Bushman
Do
On a regular
They do they perhaps.
Do as loudly as baby
Should
Yeah
It's unfortunate because this weekend again Alex Jones came out with his
Apology about pizza
Nope
He never does
And this piece of apology is not evidence that he doesn't
Cuz even packaged with entomology
Throwing other news organizations logo
But hey they said it we're reporting on it what do you want to do
Sing other people it wasn't
Do not doing our due diligence
Yeah and if they had done any due-diligence they never would have reported any of this
The news Outlet
And I did my due diligence about pizza
YouTube
Not about
Clips that are just kind of fun
This one
Jerome corsi
Has been he wasn't on the phone during the Playman interview
Unicorn singing
Zip-a-Dee-Doo-Dah
Slightly racist Disney song
This one is
I don't know why that came to my head
It's a good song though
If you take the race
Depart out of it what a wonderful day
What's fun
Anyway
Econo-pak
Bar baby in El Reno
Drunk horse he was in the background essentially for the entire Mike zullo interview and then once Mike zullo gets off the phone
Alex Jones
Jerome corsi has asked for a little while
This clip
And it's one way of looking at
And when I explained
Better way of looking at it
I'm also powerful
Either from high-level leaks or house
What shows
You are really On Target my friend
Cuc
What his listen everything we write
Everybody looks
Everything you write
Nobody look
Nail that's how I'm Target
Hey
Right everything Paul Joseph Watson does everyone loves
That yeah
Ignores your like a conspiracy theorist
Even if
Wonky community
Like not function
I realize that
Seeing that Paul Ryan's walk
Penis is wonky
Absolutely
Function
Too Playa
The Parting Shot
Generally I like to try it
Come up with something
I really stopped
Thumbs up
Listen to two-and-a-half hours of us talk
The last 5 minutes
Where you will have a good cook
Before we get to this clip lights of Jaws
Give us light
Information of every
Everything we've got
Monsters
Liars
Everybody involved with the Alex Jones Show is all of those
That's pretty much what
I think you did a good real brief summation imma try for a little more
The meat on their bones
Is Joe Arpaio is a complete monster he is
Guilty
Racial profiling
So much work
He is absolutely he was not being wiretapped by any information
Has publicly of a
Deserve the death
He had a confidential informant named Dennis Montgomery who is a proven liar front of History
Fraud
History of
Trying to set up people
What's fake documents
And
Clearly
His lawyer Larry klayman is a
Complete islamophobic
Bigot
Has Pride
Multiple times
Frivolous lawsuits against
Liberals kicked out of course forever
4life
Not allowed to be Cliven Bundy
These are the characters that we're dealing with
Alex Jones takes this
And information about an alleged
Wiretapping
That's been going on.
Billy has his phone numbers
Which again
Montgomery could easily get that information
From very mild hacking which he is shown
Through
People
About him
And history has shown that he is capable of those things so
Can write basic software
Turn 2002
Yeah
So what we have here is Alex Jones either willingly or unwillingly being
Tricked
Bye
To Joe Arpaio
Crimes against
And probably deserve
But
Probably could get you a good deal on a hunt
Amazing
Probably
So Alex Jones
Alex Jones
What do you need to write down
I've done no Research into any of these things
Oroville
He is
Truly
100%
Trying to lie in a way that we may only be in the way that we have always had that kind of
Spectrum going back and forth
If
Alex Jones has done
Any research
We're 100
That he is lying and
I'm pedaling a false Niro
If he is not
Which to me see
The more likely
Situation
Because again
All of the work
You've done all of the research
You've done
So far beyond anything Alex Jones is
Capable of
It hasn't taken me that long
Exactly Rihanna's even more
To be honest
We're not getting paid
To the show
I have a nine-to-five job generally at 8 to 6
Job
I'm at work
A lot of my life and I can't be
Spending time researching
I have not been tearing my hair out researching this
Exactly
It's been pretty easy to find most
Information
It fits within the Alex Jones and what we know of
That he would not have
Even the most cursory
If someone comes to Jerome corsi
And says I have evidence
The Trump is being
Spied on
Jerome corsi is going to write up an article
And Alex Jones is going to Justin
Implicitly believe it no matter what he's not going to do any research
Figure out is this worth me posting on my site
Do any of that work
And because
And because Jerome corsi
Is
Someone credit
Someone ethical
He just brings this b******* into the house
So
Tumi I fall on the side
Alex Jones
Not
Mafia.
In this particular
That's interesting
You willfully misleading people in the way that he would be
If he had done any research
Now see here's where I disagree with you just on it
White technicality
Yes I think he willfully does
Do the research
The part of him know that if
He would invalidate his own beliefs
Your objection
Is this
So
Realistically
What week what we ended this
Is
Trump was not being spied on in the West
Because that's the narrative
Who's pitching the entire week
The idea that his phone number in Trump's phone number and all that was part of this database
Is absolutely
Retrieve
I think firmly
And it took
There's a web of things it's built upon it
Do you have multiple interviews
With people
Propping up this why it's complete bulshit
Nunez
Has confirmed
Nunez is Italy stink
Credulous
Crick in some way
His behavior was altered by some of this information Nunez I would act
Is on the evil side is on the evil Spectrum
Lie
Especially
Protect Trump but
In the same way
She is wagging to what
He thinks Walt
Torn down
Going to
Like just 50/50 horse race
What's blank
Who do you think you would rather hit your horse to right now
Paul Ryan
Donald Trump
Sophie's Choice
Both of my children
No that's that's a no winds
Situation I don't want
To either of them but if I had to choose I probably go truck
You probably go Trump yet
Still going to go with
I would go Trump
But real
Just because I don't want anything to do with Paul Ryan
Outback trunk
Once every
Isaac
I think
I think Trump is a
Trader
Yeah but somehow I think Paul Ryan
Absolutely
So I would go I would go with Trump
But
I wouldn't worry about it
Stop talking about who's the
Murmansk
Then you go Ryan
Right
Play I think Ryan is going
I mean
Wolfie and then
The healthcare
I would
Before the whole Healthcare
I would have said that
Ryan
Capable of
Because the health
Maybe
The most
Ever introduced into Congress
And he
Still put all of his ex
Miri
Just maybe
Alright
Idiot
He is definitely not like historical smart
Gone it's also interesting though because I don't I don't know really
Research into it but I did read an article
How
Trump making a hard sell on the health-care bill ended up losing them
10 votes
Negotiate
With folks
Paul Ryan maybe could have pulled it off without
Blustery
Either way we have one more clip
Is Alex Jones talking
This is just
Alright let's all just play
Let's get some dessert on the
This is absolutely just
This world being so unstable
Richard Ramirez
Alex Jones showing his true colors God that felt so good
Sources I have wanted for month
Now they're going to kill Trump
Let me ask
Let me answer question form
Where would you find us
If you were looking for
Well I would say that
You can find us as knowledge
Support the show we do take donations at patreon there's a link
Knowledge feit.com we are welcome to do that
You don't have to
Market
Also
Play Weird Al review
Do you know that
Is our rankings up or something and a half
Thank you to a friend
Thank you Brian
What's up baby
You left us a nice review on
Like it really it really does
Part of
Rivershire
By the way
Remember when I was complaining about someone leaving the four star review
Yeah I went back
Can checks I think they changed it to a 5
I'm sorry that I believe you
I'm so sorry
You get overly defensive I get
Way over lacing
Ciara Like sir
It is it is true
Definitely feel too but I have a
Don't even sod
Hard
Hard because
Feeling like part of the resist
Or whatever it is
It seems very few.
Where resistance
2 something
Try it really is
Like looking at
Protest in Russia
You see those people who are
That's real bravery
Far more Brave than anything I can
Imagine because
Ever just going there
Possibility of killing
It truly does
Warm
Police
Making lines in order to
Shuttle all the protesters into a building
They are
Like f****** RoboCop
Like it's
So just
Feel like
I am at the
Very least
Smallest amount of what I
Because I'm soaked
Confused about how to
All we do is
All we can do is
Encourage people to
Call your representative
Do everything
That's a small thing
It's very easy to do
To the ACLU absolutely any other cause that you support
That's what
We want to encourage people
And then beyond that also and I'm guilty of not doing a
With all the time
Frank
But like
It does go a long way
Just be nice to me
That is a really important thing
Further
Into daily
Importantly beanie
Try
Try to see the humanity in your fellowship
People dad I will tell you this right now is
Place to leave a great review of mouth
I'm glad you got that cuz that was that was my point anyways
The Twitter knowledge
The score fight you can email us at knowledge email.com
Also
Think we mention this in the last episode but thank you to the AV club giving us a nice shout-out
Block
Super awesome thank you very much anybody else who wants to write anything about of please do we need help
And if you do want to write anything about us
You should definitely meant
At the end of the article that we
Are a couple of
Just
You know I don't know
He wants is that right
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color