Knowledge party.com
I have a great respect for Tenaya Lodge B B I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Alex Jones Jordan
Go first I have a I got a double bright spot
I got a rare double Brightside precedent it
By my partner
Summer
School is out my friend
Summer vacation
School's out for summer forever
Absolutely
And then at the same time
We just discovered a new show
But that's old For All Mankind
It's alternate history what if Russia won the Space Race To The Moon sort of like a man in the High Castle
Absolutely
Who's f****** grade
I want to be an astronaut so bad
No it is they told me my eyes were too bad probably too late
They haven't gotten better in the interview I feel like you're just going to need to wait
Until it's really normal to go to space
And then you could be a space cowboy type of guy
Just going up there a Ruffian and that'll be pretty cool
For sure
I'm going to have to I'm going to have to learn Jeet Kune Do that'll take about Mandalorian right
Spike Spiegel my man bouquet
Okay that's the way to do it all right
I don't have a ride for
I'm not cool enough
Because I can be jet though I can cook
I'm tall
Those are my qualities
Attempt
I guess
I wish you the best.
Thank you very much actually is
Itrip
2 St Louis
Planned in the near future I get to go my
Mutual friends what do you do for my stand-up days is getting married
And
Destination wedding
He must be back in Missouri Maya my buddy Nick
The gift was there so absolutely
Good time
Weather
I was going to see this as a bright spot but I'm going to put it in as a sort of an addendum
Dreamy creamy summer is going on as we all know of course
And I have been
Some creams some of them have been dreamy
Some of them have been
Dreamy creamy
I have to say
Jeni's Ice Cream is being treated by everybody as like
This is such great ice
It's a tie level everyone loves it and I've got to say the price tag
What do you do to believe
I got Boston cream
Green pie Jennings flavor
I look
No shade on Jenny
She's great
I'm sure she is
I got to say
Fudge
Is really hyped up on the package
We got this great fudge
It's true
Is
F****** Hershey's syrup
The Taste exactly like Hershey syrup
Now that's something you getting a bottle and you pour into your mouth when you're high
Here's my problem with all ice cream
No one person
Can make that many flavors
Alright you can't do it though it's not just
I understand it's not just an entity a hive-mind if you will
Only create so many flavors Baskin-Robbins did not have
126 flavors
The correct amount
Maximum that can be made one for each of the most days of the month I have to say if if I can be frank I would say that
I don't think Boston cream pie is like
Number one an Innovative flavor nor do I think it's that difficult to emulate
It's got custard you know what channel 8
Chocolate somehow
That price I am looking for a little more than Hershey's syrup Jenny
You realize
It was actually not too bad I just felt like a little bit
Change nothing fun about things
Okay
Could have been better
Nobody could have
It wasn't f****** Hershey syrup
So Jordan today we have episode in front of us minisode I suppose
I will see what
Entailing
But Didi situation I wanted to just give a little bit of
Does a
Context and maybe a little bit of an apology
Feedback about this
People
Are reaching out then
More people may have
Felt this way
I
They want to just say hey sorry that we did not give more of
The point to
Mike Tyson's history of abuse and rape conviction
On our last episode
I know that
It's not your responsibility Jordan to bring things up responding person
Falls more on me and the reason that I didn't include
More of it as a point to bring up in
Really thought that we talked about it before in the past
I'm pretty sure we had more.
Detail
That might be a misconception on my part or or whatever but I
I I felt like it would be sort of redundant
Rite Aid
Bye
Do you know Microsoft
Options maybe off on that
I am 22 weeks and felt like we were just given short shrift to that I I apologize I don't that
I want that to be the perception that
It's not you know who this is
Awful history isn't a big deal
I suppose it's the best
But it sure
Today the situation we have in front of us is
Trouble
Trouble yes
Alex
Has been
Studio C
June 6th pure
Sure he has been on vacation or a work
Location share
And you know there's a lot of stuff that's been going on
I think
I think bears
His response
But I'm interested
Where he's at about these things
From the proud boys being indicted for sedition
Conspiracy
And the fact that
Barry's video of
Enrique tarrio the leader of the proud boys meeting in the basement of a parking garage with
Stewart Road who are being charged with sedition
Conspiracy meeting in a Clint that they would pay they work together
Conspiratorially
Curious buddies take on
Some of that his absence might be a little glaring even
CNN apparently Ramsey documentary about Alex that you know curious
What his thoughts are on that
Joe Biggs
Apparently hired nor pattice
Curious what Alex thinks about to have to stay there
I was thinking about this
If I were Alex I would have fired Norm immediately
If you was going
Represent
It needs seditious
Conspiracy trial because
It provides to close of a link
How could you be like well of course we share the same lawyer but I've never met this guy before in my work for
Diagnose
Come on man
I would be like no you cannot represent
Yeah it really must being that the
Cool is that shallow
The pool has to be that shallow which is almost reassuring
If you
Afford to fire Norm baddest
That means there aren't that many options
Or
Conversely Alex
Got Joe Biggs
A lawyer
Because otherwise Joe might say something
I don't know but it's it's
It has the appearance of the lake
Rank shadiness
Norfolk
Do you think that would be like if in the wire you don't have the cartel and they had that
Huge lawyer Maurice Levy
If they had literally Foghorn Leghorn has the cartels
Don't worry
You're going to do 5 but we got a good lawyer for a I'll show you the proud boys did nothing wrong now you're here
Exactly why are you hiring also like
You know it would probably look even worse if
Thank God this
Isn't the case
If Alex
Didn't publicly join the proud boys
That would be a problem
Oh there was a McGinnis
Initiated him alive on the show that's not good
She was he hasn't been in studio so we don't have any episodes where he goes
Listen to talk about these things
Time since he's been on
He's called in
Ameriben
Some
Little Snippets
And we're going to go over a little bit of that
It doesn't Merit a full episode and also when I was on the phone or doing this
Pre-record
It's not really that interesting
No cuz
He's going to just hit kind of standard he knows like what I got to do about that
The tight time here not like when he has to fill three hours and there's like plenty of time for him to expound on
Dumb Fox to be able to have
Freewheeling
Explosions of improv he can't be held into a small
Container
Noticed as a performer
He needs to be able to explore the space absolutely
And yes it's kind of a bummer
On the 7th
There's no call
No, he doesn't call in on the 7th
Xavier
Comes along and Alex
Calls into agitate about of a migrant Caravan
There's migrant Caravan
Where is he that he's catching migrant Caravan
It's mostly just an excuse to be like
And then the economy will collapse that's why you go by my survival
Nothing happens until the 10th
And
Is the day after the first January 6th committee
And so
And here is him introducing a little phone
Conversation without
Just being in this historic moment seeing where the Democrats are going
There's never been such an evil force in this country I don't know if the country's ever experienced
The government weaponize against the people like we're seeing right now
How do we harness this energy for good how do we
How do we take these trying times
And turn them into a positive for America to unite the people to bring people together back with love
Desire for freedom and prosperity
Cuz I know it's there Alex
I know it's there
That's exactly
Starting a civil war there
Organizations
The New World Order
Really f***** up
Bears
Do the show as long as we have
You know that
Periodically colors
We'll ask Alex
When is it time to start shooting
When you see this at you know various qna
Big directly asked out
They were always in a Cold War what we went when does it turn hot Alex
Well apparently it's hot now yeah
Yep
Definition
This is something good Alex just says as a throwaway doesn't mean
Anything to him
But it's
To the right
Year of his listeners
This has the potential for them to be like this is Alex giving massage
Go ahead
Do it like that
It's got to be dramatic
I mean it listen
You would not get
You would not believe Alex
Calling for it from a phone
Yeah you would know
Because you would think maybe
He's in a bunker
Oh yeah that's a good point
Yeah what you doing
Hiding from war
Figurehead of the Patriots
Yes it is
Call Alex has an underground armored riddle
Where you can broadcast
Brian get the message out to the page
Even if the whole grid goes down
Alex Jones Infowars pirate underground post-apocalyptic radio beat
The f****** worse
Yeah
Liam saligo grow longer
I'm not there we know that your eyes aren't good I'm not good at seeing
I could get ambushed really easy in the dark you just have to offer them the food you cooked
Exactly
360 mini comes up and here's your some valances.
I want to go back to last
Dot-com
They are framing
The Americans
People terrorists
Position as terrorists
Decided not to surveillance
We're just two weeks ago the
Two random people
In the middle of the street
Colorado
Okay
People
Cialix is hanging his hat on that bring it up as a sort of a counter
Example or whatever
The situation where they were
Car that was not slowing down before running out of the way
The guy ended up accidentally hitting two people
Shooting them
And they both
Ask for restored
Justice opposed
Analogous
At all and it's not worth using as a example for like
Oh yeah
What about that one guy from that one time way back over there in a small town as opposed to the capital of
Knighted goddamn state
Yeah
Square
It appears
That
Some representatives were complicit in some stuff and she knowingly or not
Perhaps and there were multiple groups of real f*****-up weirdo ride
With plans guns
Alex's friends
Long-time gas
Like for instance
They played a video of Stewart Road
Alex is like
So I never heard Stewart Roads
People talk about
Information
We were all concerned
Security for some of the events we have
Before
Everybody knows that
Hey look we got a million
Joe Biden
Campfield
Jeep dealership
Maybe one of the reasons that Trump could draw these big crowds and Biden was unable to his cuz Trump's fanbase thought that ignoring public
Health advice was a central tenet of their political ideology
Big part of it
To do with it
Owen Shroyer was burning a black lives
A matter of like outside his hotel the night before cuz he was afraid of Antigua if you burn a black lives matter
Butterfly gets like it's at you no like me
Mosquitoes can't
Get to the Zumba the smoke it said that's what he was thinking you know right I guess I don't know
Now just seems like bulshit 100% lies that they made up that they were not absolutely afraid of it all
Alex saying like I've never heard Stewart
Talk about going into the capitol
Astor was talking about going as a capitalized in Eldritch
I wonder if you heard Matt Bracken
Talk about it on Infowars
A 31st remember when we played that on the are your buddy
Guy who
This is not anymore
I hope he's okay
6 anymore
If this looks a little bit longer because
Speed the direction it goes
Is
Not good
American people
Preposterous
16 days
Baldy
The real issue
Because
Daily contacts
Constantly
For two years
You got
Hollywood star
His hometown
The police live
40 + X Change
18 *
For now
State Police or the
Was this on January 6th
We know we're being lied to
All of this right on
On time
For the midterms
Didn't happen
What I'm saying is
This thing is
Well I can't
All I'm saying is
Is the season and the timing
McConaughey's town
President
Later
This is
Massive massive
If you were going on everybody
Like
I don't know how else
You can really interpret interpret it as
Keep living 20-24 that right all right all right
Ends in the White House
Right we had the Michelle Obama Hillary
That is a stupid
Amazingly stupid yeah
Good road to go down Alex
Two words from your brain you would have to spend a lot of money to go
Get Sandy Hook removed from his brain and safe
Billion dollars right
I mean if your damn yeah
Like Eternal Sunshine that's not just bring up Sandy Hook
You know he number of anomalies Within
Sandy Hook
I know from being in a deposition room with him
Talking about this stuff
He doesn't know any anomalies about Sandy Hook
Well then he is making it a completely accurate state
Will 10:00
Exactly but yeah this is
Yeah they're not not good
Not good
Now is the time
To be like
Listen
There were a lot of anomalies at Sandy Hook why am I talking
What is happening
12 because you need to do something with the like the January 6th comedian talking about that a hearing is probably not for
You're the best
So you got to put it in the context of this is all part of
Demonizing Us in order to win the midterm
Bill's big part of that is also this
Buffalo shooting in the Uvalde
The shooter
And it's all this
Season the
Planning
Is just
I'm saying it was staged
Maybe not actors and no people died maybe wasn't totally fake
But yeah this is
This is bad
I think this this
This Blake form of this info is got a
Run its course
Actually write like it all sounds exactly the same though the Russian to send photo the
Whenever MBS
Khashoggi like the all the denials are so similar in just like this
Absolutely didn't happen and if it did happen it wasn't that big a deal but it didn't happen in there lying about it
They're lying because they don't want you to talk about that thing that they did right there and I definitely didn't kill khashoggi
100% okay well I did it but
You can't do s*** about it like that
It's the same way ever yell Benghazi and throw a smoke bomb
Yes it matter where it's coming from
Tell me a fact
Right
Certainly not so long or legs
X's and O's snap bracelet
Good because I think it appeals to people's emotional w
They walked
Denial
To give it to them they'll accept it
They just really yeah
Well it's easier than admitting that you have
Participated in a horrific violence against
Text everybody
I think the Alex I still don't know
There's strong evidence
Alex
Knew anything about what people might have
Been doing
Haunted
And if that evidence has come out
Thrilled to see it
But
If Alex were to take seriously the things that are known
And have come out
The weather be from these indictments
Or the testimony
And be things that we've heard from the commission
Alex would really have to do a little bit of soul-searching about why it is
He promoted
The Oath Keepers and Stewart Road
For as long as he did
Doesn't instantly as he did Even though Stewart Road was constantly talking
About wanting to shoot people
And wanting her to be
A situation where Trump would
Deputize him as the sheriff of the United States
Basically
You'd have to wrestle with y
He helped promote the proud boys
Gavin McInnes on
In the earlier times and supported
Rufio panman based Stickman
And all of these people
Like
He'd have to wrestle with the fact that there were these group
That we're actively involved in planning
To do what happen
He is a part of that
Constellation weather he was knowingly
Involved in any of that planning or do anything about it
Or if
He was just
Be louder
Cheerleader and facilitator for these groups
For the last
Decade
Yeah you know it
Well I mean
The thing that he's got going
That dumb is
Not just that
But
The time that he was like this and I'm not going to tell you
Anyways my sources Donald Trump
What's you know that that's going to happen you just don't
Tell Alex that s***
You don't tell Alex anything that he's going to say on air
So that became a known quantity I think among that group so
I doubt he has anything that is I doubt they gave him any information
That he could repay
Well I think I said this before
I think I feel like that
Still feel this way until
Someone could provide any like real evidence but like
I think that Alex would have behaved the exact same way he
He did on the six
Whether or not
He knew any
You don't need to tell him of any plans
Nokia's just a guy who's going to try and incite a crowd and yellow 1776
All the time so
If you just plant him somewhere he's going to do whatever he did
Telling him the plan only gives him something to rage again
Right you know he would be a chaotic agent against your plan
Where is if he doesn't know the plan he can be the 8th chaotic age
Agent that you want him
I think
I feel like
Strategically that would be
And you're best if it makes sense
Now I have these people acted in their best interest 100% of the time no
No matter also kind of dumb
Yeah
Be at the other thing I wanted after wrestle with
It was is the fact that Joe Biggs
Used to work at Infowars
For quite a while
And was
Involved in the
Conversation
With proud boys
In a planning a
Senior leadership in
The moment you ask
Ask yourself the question why are all of my friend
Nazis
There's really only two ants
Add you can say yes or no to what
You know
Yep is it cuz I'm a Nazi
Yes or no
And I bad news raps
The
The next day's a little quiet
And we get to the 14th
And this is where we hear a little bit more formality
Infowars has been inundated the last week
Viewers asking where is Alex Jones if I
I've been on a business / vacation trip
On the West Coast
I have had a lot of people
And the answer is
I never take time off
We also have a lot of
Sponsor opportunities of the things
Edward needs a personal touch that I've been involved in
I am taking off
OurTime
At least for the rest of this week
In studio
Crazy world
Alex needs to disclose
You gave him that money because
He got eight million dollars in Bitcoin and then took a week off on a
Very uncharacteristically long
Work vacation
It kind of
Lead someone to think that maybe that mystery donor
Looks like you got to come
I visit there you got it we got to talk about
Plans or something
I gave you a million dollars guess what you're going to give
I don't know if that's the case but that's the reason that Alex needs to be a little bit more transparent
Because it does create the impression it's a possible conclusion people could come to
Absolutely
Like I think the
That's what
Start to get suspicious of like
Hey what's going on
You doing
Yeah you know
At the end of this I'm so worried that we're going to find out that his listeners are like there's just a
The total of 1000
Some people but there's
Two of them who by
A trillion dollars worth of product everyday
Unlikely done like
But come on
This is so absurd how can you
Still be trapped in his
Brady
Well I think that one of the reasons is because no one looks
This is critically and no one
No one who's not sort of in a conspiratorial mindset really
Pays attention
Google look I'm saying
I'm saying
That Alex is vacation
Could be entirely about sponsors that he's going to visit it could be something where he needs
The new supplement line
But
The lack of transparency does
Weird one
To think
Maybe these things are connected
Conspiracy theorist listening to a conspiracy theory show and a guy conspiratorially got a billion dollars and then
And ran away for awhile I think maybe there's a
Conspiracy
But none of that is jumping to that conclusion that is just a logistical things like
A + B could
Sequel see this is weird right you should clear this up so people don't
If this isn't
The case you would think
Realistically this is more what is Audie
Where is
Conspiracy here
Doing all right now January 6th
Thinking maybe that I was going to repetitive the hills or something it again
That is not
This has been planned for a long time
Separately
If I try to respond Olivia January 6th lies or just CNN lies
Let it be fair last Sunday
Important
Yeah sure
His audiences more like Alex's disappear
If you run away in the bunker
Did they give him is he in the gulag
Yeah
Remind of The Listener is far more creative
They come up with more abstract and a toriel explanation
For why Alex is gone as opposed to like
Probably some sort of shady business
Yeah I can't possibly
Just be that somebody
Gave him $8000000
Weird why would you suddenly take a trip for $8000000 that's practically
More than seven million dollars
A little higher
We have one more clip here from the 14th
And
Good news
Course
Are going to
We are real
We are legitimate
And the people
I am travel to multiple States
On the West Coast
Last week
All four of them
Mob
Grocery stores
Bob
Mom at hotels I mean
25 people
Chapping pictures asking for autographs
What are we doing
We know you're right
We know you told the truth hero Legend
The point is
A couple of things
First
Celebrity ding dong
Think about me
Give me I'm with this a******
Take a picture you show your friend and I think people would want to know that your kind of violent
So maybe don't want to fight you in about maybe
Also yeah sure
It's the same strfkr either that he treats other people with
He's being treated by
By the labors
Second thing
I know that we've heard
Alex
Disgusting sort of
Perceptual distortions
Yeah like when people in the grocery store turn into demons and go back
I think he might have some
A+ versions of Suspicion baby
This is his inability to gauge reality
I will say
But that sounds suspiciously like
Every movie scene where the guy is looking in the mirror after having a huge crisis
Confidence and then builds himself back up Psychopathic lie with that
Do you know what
You are right
Everybody loves you every time you see somebody on the street they come down and they say
You know what your Greek god
That's exactly what that was
Yeah
But it's good news is good news great news
Great news tell me better news is in the
Bibleman
The author of lies that has children
And they want to tell you that Infowars is no good
They are the writers assistance of Lies
So stupid
So I honestly think like there isn't
Much that's interested like a lot of the stuff their response you'd have
To the January 6th and I even the CNN thing is kind of
Same thing after talking points
Boilerplate nonsense
So like I don't even
Listening over this I don't even feel like
Most of it was
Worth
The time but
I think honestly
Clip where he's
Talking about
Uvalde in the Buffalo shooting his outrageous
It shows end illegal mentality
Will be back on Monday with the Fuller episode
To be a little bit too nebulous territory cuz Alex did say he's going to be gone
Until
Next week
Sprite and so by Monday or Sunday when we record there won't be
Any content
Two golfers a lot that
Figure something out right we will ya
We will and I'll tell you what
It based on his going rate we
We cannot afford to
To get Alex back in studio
No we do not have that kind of scratch neither doesn't for Bitcoin her otherwise
Another thing to ingest real quick
I
I wanted to give this
Qualifier about next episode
We were making a big joke out of like how Tyson needs
To lick the toad
And like how
It's cowardly.
Very much
Safe responsible service message
I do think that we did
Make a point that there is some research into
Chemical
Could have psychological benefits
But maybe we didn't
Maybe we were a little bit more derisive of the whole thing then
Maybe we should have been takeaway that's not
It was not our point it's worth it
Licking toads is very funny
Nothing else
I don't know if the benefits
It are the certain thing where you would
Do it 60 times I don't know I don't know
That's not but I'm not I'm not a shaman
Yeah I don't know either
Jordans.com
5 - 8 Jordan
Will be back also some people have asked
Duet with Fire Emblem
Which school I chose the Black Eagle
Right you couldn't be the same so I chose
In the blue lions
Hope you all have a dreamy creamy summer
And now here comes
What the sex robe
Alex
Birthstone colors